In the OR, time loses meaning.
In the midst of sutures
and saving lives,
the clock ceases to matter.
Fifteen minutes, 15 hours.
Inside the OR, the best
surgeons make time fly.
Outside the OR, however,
time takes pleasure
in kicking our asses.
♪ Never knew the
best was yet to come ♪
For even the strongest of
us, it seems to play tricks.
Slowing down...
hovering...
♪ Life began when
I saw your face ♪
until it freezes...
leaving us stuck in a moment,
unable to move in one
direction or the other.
Izzie. Izzie. Come on.
OK. She's been in there all
night. We have to do something.
- Yeah.
- Why are you all looking at me?
This is familiar
territory for you.
There is nothing
familiar about this.
Unfamiliar. Denny died.
The man she loves died.
Yeah, but you're all
dark and twisty inside.
- Dark and twisty?
- The mother with
the Alzheimer's,
the father you don't talk to.
Tequila thing. The
inappropriate men thing.
You are dark and twisty and
now Izzie is dark and twisty.
So I'm the president of
People With Crappy Lives?
Seriously, we have
to do something.
Someone has to go in there.
The seven years you
spend as a surgical resident
will be the best and
worst of your life.
Look around you.
Say hello to your competition.
- Hi. Izzie Stevens. Washington.
- Alex Karev. Iowa.
This is nice. They throw a
mixer for the new interns.
It's just an excuse to get us all
happy and drunk before they torture us.
- What program are you in?
- Surgery.
- Seriously?
- Seriously.
What?
I'd picked you for Gynie
or Peds or something.
You don't think I can be a
surgeon? I can be a surgeon.
- Surgery's hardcore.
- I'm hardcore.
You won't last the first year.
- Hey, Izzie...
- What?
Maybe you should...
change your clothes.
- Maybe something
more comfortable.
- Stop it.
- Izzie.
- Stop it, I mean it.
Stop talking.
There is nothing to talk
about, do you understand me?
There is nothing to discuss.
I'm so sorry.
Yeah. Yeah, me too.
- You're a surgeon?
- Yes.
Usually don't send surgeons.
What do we need to... How
do I do this? What do we...?
Just ID the body before I
take him to the funeral home.
- So I don't take the wrong guy.
- That happens?
You wouldn't believe
how many times.
That's him. That's
Denny Duquette.
Great. Load him up.
And... sign.
- When's the funeral?
- No funeral.
The family asked to have
the body sent to Memphis.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Why are we making sandwiches?
That's what you do when
someone dies. You cook.
I know what to do
when someone dies.
I am a Jew. I know
food and death.
- It's shiva.
- Is it shiva
even if she's Catholic?
Well, shiva's what I know
how to do, so yeah, it's shiva.
If we're sitting shiva for
Denny, then we should order in.
Making sandwiches is
not the same as cooking.
Sandwiches are comfort food.
What's wrong with you?
Everything is fine. It's
Izzie we're worried about.
Oh, what did you do?
Denny died, Burke got shot.
Let's just have some perspective,
and remember what I did
- is a tiny, slightly small...
- Whatever. Spit it out.
I lost my panties last night.
- Back already?
- I never left.
I did a craniotomy on a
ruptured saccular aneurism.
I've been here all night, too.
I wanted to see the
autopsy on Duquette.
Yeah. You seen Meredith?
Dr. Grey. Have
you seen Dr. Grey?
Why? What's going on with you?
Can you get somebody to cover
my rounds so I can take care of stuff?
Are you free? Dr. Shepherd,
there's an incoming head trauma,
and the pit's overcrowded
with early flu season.
Giselle Toussant,
42-year-old woman.
Unrestrained driver of
a car that hit a railing.
She was... We were coming
to the ER. We were both sick.
We couldn't shake
this flu thing, so...
- She was better,
so I let her drive.
- Sir?
- Omar?
- Giselle?
- Honey?
- Where are we?
- Are we... Are we dancing?
- We had an accident.
She's leaking spinal fluid.
Let's get an OR ready, OK?
- The dancing's so beautiful.
- You're beautiful.
He's burning up.
Get him a bed. Let's get
her to the OR right away.
- What's going on?
- Premature newborn
found in a trash can. The
umbilical cord's still attached.
You didn't start an
IV? He's dehydrated.
- Couldn't find a vein.
- I need to get an IV access.
Get me an IO needle and I
need a neonatal intubation kit.
Olivia. Go, move. Now!
They pulled me from the floor.
I'm just down here
helping with the flu overflow.
Alex, how old is that baby?
Wait, wait. What are you doing?
Think I'm gonna leave this
sick, premature infant in the ER?
He has to be admitted.
Can't take him.
Just page Addison Shepherd.
- Karev?
- Premature newborn
with petechia.
- What's his platelet count?
- 17,000.
17,000? Did you
transfuse platelets?
- Yes, but it didn't help.
- Where's the mother?
I don't know.
I'm not asking you where
the mother is for my health,
I expect you to use your
brain. Where's the mother?
I don't know. The baby was found
in a trash can at a high school.
They left him in a trash can.
He's got some inner
abdominal bleeding on CT.
You wanna run some more tests?
Dr. Shepherd?
I need a stat ultrasound
and for you to infuse
two grams of IVIG,
if there is no cranial bleeding.
Then find out
where the mother is.
I need to test for maternal
platelet antibodies.
Can't you do surgery
to fix the bleeding?
If I wanted to kill him, I
could do that. Damn it.
- Who does this?
- Dr. Montgomery-Shepherd?
There are some people
here, about the baby.
- Busy morning.
- Getting busier.
You have a new
appointment on the books.
I have back-to-back surgeries...
You'll want to
take this meeting.
She made an appointment.
The clot's been evacuated.
Are we ready to close?
Just want to make sure
there's no bone fragments.
- How's Izzie?
- As well as can be expected.
Never gets easier, you
know, losing a patient.
It's a little less
shocking, I guess,
but it never gets any easier.
Izzie was in love with him.
Denny wasn't just a
patient. They were in love.
You had sex with Derek in
an exam room at the prom?
- Yes.
- Last night?
- You and Shepherd did it.
- Yes.
You and McDreamy
did the nasty-nasty?
- Cristina!
- Not judging,
just trying to wrap
my mind around it.
You're with Finn and
he's with Addison.
- He's married to Addison.
- Yeah.
Well, what did Derek say?
He said, "Meredith,
what does this mean?"
OK. He has sex with you and
he's standing there all McGuilty,
and all he has to say for himself
is, "What does this mean?"
- What does this mean?
- I don't know.
Well, are you gonna
go back to Finn?
Is Shepherd leaving his wife?
- I just...
- - Hold on with both hands!
Meredith!
- Mommy!
- Richard, you were
to tell Adele...
- I can't do that.
- That's what we agreed.
- Richard!
- I can't.
♪ On paper my future will lay ♪
- Please. Please.
- Ellis, no.
Richard, you can't leave me!
♪ I'll fold every
failure into a crane ♪
Please. Richard!
Richard!
♪ Trust is quicksand ♪
You didn't need an
appointment. I'm your husband.
It seemed to be the best way
to get your undivided attention
- because here you are.
- Adele, listen...
- Sit down. Sit down!
- Adele.
- We have an appointment.
- Chief...
Excuse... The IDC is here.
We had a couple come in.
Derek finished a
craniotomy on the wife,
but her husband's
got severe flu.
Swollen lymph nodes, buboes.
Turns out they
came in contact with...
The plague? Look, I'm sorry,
Adele. I need to deal with this.
Is a straight-A student.
Mine gets a B, she's
birthing babies in toilets?
I'm Dr. Montgomery-Shepherd,
treating the newborn.
He has a blood condition.
I need to know whose
baby it is I'm dealing with.
Yeah. We'd all like to
know that. Sara, talk.
I don't know anything
about any baby.
- None of us do.
- One of you must, otherwise,
you and your parents
wouldn't be here.
Our girls... The principal said
that they were the last people
in the bathroom before
that baby was found.
We thought before
the police show...
One of you knows.
And you better confess.
Don't want Lisa in this.
Police'll be here soon. Can't
you just do some DNA test
- so the rest of us can get out?
- DNA results take days.
I'm not concerned with getting
the rest of you out of here.
If this baby isn't
treated, he's going to die.
Now I can do vaginal
exams on each of the girls.
My daughter is 14,
she's not sexually active.
I won't have you violating her.
You won't have it 'cause you
know it's yours. Tell you what.
You have my consent to do what
it takes to prove Lisa's innocent.
You are a sick
bastard, you know that?
A child's life is
in jeopardy here.
And it's not your
consent that I need.
We didn't do anything wrong.
It doesn't mean it's our baby.
Do we look like girls
who get pregnant
and throw their
kids in the trash?
Nice work today, O'Malley.
Did Meredith go home with Izzie?
Yeah, Cristina too.
I'm headed there now.
- Yeah, me too.
- Oh, great. It's just...
I don't know if Izzie's
up for a lot of people.
I'm gonna go see Meredith.
- All right.
- OK.
- Dr. Shepherd?
- Yes.
- Dr. O'Malley.
- Yeah?
I'm with the IDC. Is
anyone else in this room?
- No.
- Perform the surgery
on Mrs. Toussant?
- Yes.
- She was in close contact
with a victim of the plague.
- She may have been exposed.
- So we may have been.
- Yeah.
- I can't do this.
We're waiting on the
diagnosis of Mr. Toussant.
This room's sealed until we
know the threat's contained
- and you're safe.
- You're not saying...
You cannot leave. You
two are quarantined.
IDC has everything
under control?
They work fast. Anyone that
was in contact is quarantined.
Shepherd and
O'Malley are not happy.
Everything's under control if
you need to get back to your wife.
Oh, no. I should check
in with the IDC rep.
Gonna have to stay
on top of my hospital.
Keep me posted.
Hello. Hello!
I need help. Somebody. Please.
I know you can hear me.
I see you standing in
your giant, white spacesuit.
- Sir?
- Yes!
No unauthorized
personnel beyond this point.
IDC regulations.
I know he's under quarantine,
but he's also a patient,
and I will not ignore a patient.
Hello out there. Thank God.
Thank God you can hear me.
- How is my wife?
- My name is Dr. Bailey. Miranda Bailey.
Your wife is out of surgery.
She's quarantined in
recovery, but she's fine.
You were asking for help?
Know how many
day's I've been here?
- It's only been a few hours.
- Really?
I'm losing... I'm
losing track of time.
OK, sir, you're sweating.
I need you to sit down.
Get back in the bed.
What about my wife, Giselle?
Can you find out about Giselle?
Like I said, sir, she came
out of surgery just fine,
but I can check
on her status again.
You just stay calm
until I get back.
No! No, wait, wait.
Don't go. Please.
Just... Just stay a minute.
- Please.
- OK, um...
I'm staying.
Omar. Call me Omar.
OK, Omar. I'm... I'm right here.
I brought food.
George isn't here.
No, I know. He's in a
quarantine because of a thing.
I was off duty and worried
about him and going crazy
and thought about
Izzie so I brought food.
- For the shiva.
- Are you gonna let me in?
Yeah.
Relax. I'm not
gonna bring it up.
You and McDreamy and the sex.
- I'm not that person.
- Good.
- OK.
Shiva? Is it shiva
if Izzie's Catholic?
Did you say quarantine?
This thing that you're
doing, it's not healthy.
You gotta take off that dress.
Get off the floor, take off
that dress, and take a shower.
Tell me about shiva.
It's something you do
when someone dies.
- We did it for my grandmother.
- How does it work?
People bring over
food, family comes over.
It's supposed to help with
the grieving. It honors the dead.
- Sounds nice.
- Yeah. There's a lot of rules.
Seven days of no leather
shoes, no work, no sex.
No sitting on things higher
than a foot. No shaving, no...
What?
No clean clothes.
Izzie, this doesn't
have to be shiva.
You know they
took his body away.
I'll never see him again.
How would you feel if you
never saw Burke again?
So we're sitting
shiva for Denny.
- You want to see him?
- See who?
- The baby. Your baby.
- It's not our baby.
I've given you permission to
do this, now what's the hang-up?
The hang-up, sir, is
that if your daughter
doesn't want to do
it, I can't force her.
They're 14. They're
minors. We still have a say.
No, you don't. If someone doesn't
want to submit to a vaginal exam,
they don't have
to. It's the law.
All right, that' it. I'm
taking Lisa home.
You do that, sir, and I
will have you arrested
before you hit the parking lot.
The law isn't the
only thing in play here.
If I do the exam
and the girl's a virgin,
there could be
bleeding, undue trauma,
not to mention emotional stress.
If I had to guess
as to whose kid
doesn't have to
worry about that...
- What's that mean?
- It'd be nice if
Karen had a curfew.
At least she's not a shoplifter.
Shannon stole one lipstick
when she was nine. Get over it.
I know Lisa is a virgin.
Really? How do you know that?
Because she's only 14 years old!
Listen to me.
Derek, you can't do this.
We have to talk about this.
- No, we don't.
- Give me a chance to explain.
Wait. What are you
doing with my clothes?
It was one time! I know
that's what people say.
I know that's what gets said.
I don't know how it happened.
Don't know what I was
thinking. He was here.
You screw my best friend
and all you can say is,
- "He was here?" Get out.
- No.
- Get out.
- No. No, I'm not going.
- Get out of my house now!
- We have to talk about this.
I'm holding my ground.
I'm holding my
ground. We don't quit!
- We have to work...
- Get out.
What are you
doing? Derek, no, no!
Please. Derek.
Please.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
You have to give me a chance...
You have to give me a chance
to show you how sorry I am.
I'm sorry, OK?
- OK?
- OK.
I'm gonna go. You stay. I'll
get my clothes in the morning.
No, no, no. We can survive
this. Derek, we can survive this.
We're... We're
Addison and Derek.
I can't look at you.
I look at you and I
feel nauseous. I just...
♪ My love for you is ready ♪
We're not Derek and
Addison anymore.
If you go now... If you go now,
we're not going
to get through this.
If you go now... we
don't have a chance.
We don't have a chance!
If you go now... If you go...
Hi, you're... Are
you Preston Burke?
- Yes.
- The Preston Burke.
Dr. Burke, I am such a huge fan.
Stentless valve replacement for
infectious endocarditis you performed.
And your use of
transmyocardio revascularization.
I'm Cristina Yang.
If I could just get the chance
to study under you, I'd be...
- You are so amazing!
- Yes. Well, thank you.
♪ It's gone daddy gone
The love is gone away ♪
I mean, one of my
choices was San Diego.
I could've gone to San
Diego, but Seattle's home, so...
- So you're new to Seattle?
- Oh, no, I kind of live here.
My mother lived here... lives
here, and I live in her house.
That's great 'cause
housing's a nightmare.
I'm living with my parents
at home, which, well... sucks.
Oh, it's nice meeting you.
- We've been exposed to plague.
- They don't know it's plague.
So the men in the white suits,
what, making a
fashion statement?
No, it's a precaution.
When the blood work
comes back we'll be out.
What if the results come
back and she has the plague?
Well, then we get the
plague. Then we die in here?
With the crappy benches and the dirty
scrubs and the lockers full of old food?
There's food in the lockers?
Those are people's
personal... That's Alex's apple.
That's just rude.
We're dead men.
No time to be polite.
Safe haven laws.
All those girls would've had
to do was drop that baby off
at a fire station or a hospital.
Now... it's a mess.
What are our options here?
Blood-typing. We take a
sample from each of the girls.
The baby's blood
type is double O.
If the girls are A or B it
means the baby's not theirs.
Do it.
Everyone thinks I'll
know what to say to her.
I don't know what to say to her.
Dark and twisty Meredith.
I'm not dark and twisty.
And if I am, it's
because I live my life
under a banner of avoidance.
I avoid. I'm an avoider.
Hello?
- Hey.
So can we...
Izzie. I gotta go
check on Izzie.
Don't take it personally.
- It's the doctor thing.
- What?
Four years of high school,
four years of college,
four years of med school.
By the time we graduate
we're in our late 20s
and we've never done anything except
go to school and think about science.
Time stops. We're
socially retarded.
I mean, look at me.
I'm in love with a guy who
won't say he loves me back,
and here I am, in his kitchen, hoping
he comes home and notices me.
I'm a total freak.
I'm that girl in the back of
the class who eats her hair.
And Meredith...
she's 17 years old.
We're all 17. This is high
school with scalpels, Finn.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
- How are we doing?
- We're not taking off the dress
- and we don't want to
discuss it.
- Stop with "we."
Do not "we" me.
Finn is downstairs.
- With Callie.
- So? What's Callie gonna do?
Just don't ask. Go.
Fine.
I don't know what to say to you.
I don't know what
to say to me either.
When Dylan died...
when the bomb went off...
how did you feel?
It's not the same. We weren't...
He wasn't...
But when he died,
did you feel...?
What?
Like you were
moving in slow motion.
He was there and then he wasn't.
Like I blinked and he was gone.
I feel like I'm moving
in slow motion.
Like I'm moving in slow motion
and everything around me
is moving so fast and
I just wanna go back...
to when things were normal.
When I wasn't poor
Izzie laying on the floor
in her prom dress with her...
Her dead fiancé.
But I am.
So I can't.
And I'm...
just stuck.
And there's all this pressure
'cause everyone's
hovering around me
waiting for me to do
something or say something
or flip out or yell
or cry some more.
And I'm happy to play my part.
I'm happy to say the lines
and do whatever I'm
supposed to be doing
if it will make everyone
feel more comfortable.
But I don't... I don't
know how to do this.
I don't know how to
be this person. I don't...
I don't know who this person is.
Izzie...
How did this happen?
How did we end up here?
Why am I alone?
Where's Denny?
You're not alone, Iz.
Trail mix and warm soda.
Who puts warm
soda in their locker?
As usual, Cristina's too lazy
to stock her locker with food.
Oh, now I hit he
mother lode here.
I got granola, cookies,
muffins. Who eats this much?
That's Izzie's locker. She ate
a lot. Said it kept her energy up.
- Eats.
- What?
Eats. You said "ate."
Eats, present
tense. She didn't die.
Feels a little like she did.
She's never coming back here.
You know... I don't think
she's ever gonna be the same.
There are moments, O'Malley,
all of a sudden,
in a split second,
your life changes forever.
Before you know it,
you're somewhere else.
- Gentlemen.
- Chief.
Can we please get
out of here now?
No.
A split second.
Straight tequila, really? You're
gonna be sorry in the morning.
I'm always sorry in the morning,
but tomorrow I start my first
day of work so keep them coming.
How you doing?
Double scotch,
single malt, please.
So is this a good
place to hang out?
♪ I think about the
loveless fascination ♪
I wouldn't know.
Never been here before.
You know what? I haven't
either. First time here.
I'm new in town. I've
never been to Seattle.
A new job, so...
♪ Lower the curtain down ♪
Wow, you're ignoring me.
- Um... Trying to.
- You shouldn't ignore me.
Why not?
Because I'm someone you
need to get to know to love.
- Really?
- Oh, yes.
- So if I know you,
I'll love you.
- Oh, yes.
You really like yourself, huh?
Just hiding my pain.
♪ Under the milky way tonight ♪
So what's your story?
I don't have a story.
I'm just a girl in a bar.
I'm just a guy in a bar.
♪ Wish I knew what
you were looking for ♪
♪ Might have known
what you would find ♪
How do you not know
your kid's pregnant?
You love your kids. You
wanna see the best in them.
OK, then, how do you have a
baby and then throw it in a trash can?
Something happens and you panic.
You freeze and you
wanna hide it and...
pretend like it didn't happen.
- I get that.
- You get that?
I do.
I just don't get what
happens afterward.
I don't get how
you go back to class
and pretend like
everything's fine.
Everything's not fine.
Oh, it's the blood results.
Karen and Lisa are not a match.
And then there were two.
Miranda, I'm feeling
better. A lot better.
I think the fever broke,
which is good, right?
- Yes, that's very good, Omar.
- How's Giselle?
Is she asking for me?
Omar, for Giselle, being
exposed to the plague, it...
It complicated things.
Complicated what things?
We did everything we could.
No.
- I'm so sorry.
- No. No.
No, no, no!
Omar.
Come on, breathe.
Stop. No, no, stop.
He's hyperventilating.
- I have to go in there.
- You can't go in there!
Somebody has to go in!
- Omar!
- Oh, God! Oh, God!
- Can you hear me?
- I want my wife!
I need my wife. I need Giselle.
I have to save her! I have to
help her! Let me out of here!
Omar, look at me.
Omar, look at me!
Look, I need you to put
your hand against my hand.
Come on.
- Oh, God...
- Omar, look at my hands!
Put your hands on my hands.
Come on. Good.
Good.
OK. Look at me. Look at me!
Can you tell me my name?
Do you remember my name?
- Miranda.
- Miranda. That's right.
I want Giselle.
I have to save her. Please help.
Please let me out of here.
I wish I could help you.
Omar, I wish I could
turn back the clock
and make it yesterday.
You don't know how
much I wish that, but...
I can't turn back time.
Oh, I shouldn't have let
her drive. She was sick.
- I should've taken over.
- I know.
Come on. I know... I...
I should've taken
over too, but...
We can't go back.
Look, even if I could
let you out of here,
you can't help Giselle now.
Do you believe in God, Miranda?
I mean...
do you believe in the afterlife?
I have to believe.
With what I do,
Omar. I have to believe
that when our time comes
that we go to a place...
A beautiful place.
A... a better place.
Omar.
That woman died.
- She actually died.
- Doesn't mean we will.
- Is it hot in here?
- No.
- Then why am I sweating?
- 'Cause you're pacing.
- My pulse is rapid.
- Because you're still pacing.
- Feel me.
- I'm not gonna feel you.
- Seriously.
- Seriously, no.
You know, you're an ass.
You've lived.
You've done things.
And you've got the hair.
And the hot wife and the beautiful
ex-mistress who pines for you.
- She's pining for me?
- My point is you've lived!
If you die, who
cares? If I die...
What, this is it?
Callie told me she loved
me and I just sat there.
I mean, I wasn't ready...
What, and now I'm gonna die?
I'm not even going to get a
chance to say "I love you" back.
Do you? Do you love her?
- She loves me.
- That wasn't the question.
Maybe.
Eventually.
I could.
One day, soonish.
"Soonish?" "I will
love you soonish?"
You ever tell Meredith?
You ever tell her
that you love her?
No.
I did.
But... then with Callie...
you know... it's
different, but...
You should tell her.
Even if it's soonish.
You should tell her
before it's too late.
You mean before
I die of the plague?
Before somebody
else comes along.
I once set the bone
on the hind leg of a cow.
Come on. Now, that I believe.
He does boring animal stories,
and she's too stupid to care.
Oh, I'm gonna...
Oh, I'm gonna leave the room for a
period of time for no reason whatsoever.
I don't know what
happened last night.
- Between you and Derek.
- Finn.
And I don't wanna know.
We never said that
we were exclusive.
- But you have plans.
- Yeah.
Well, I didn't say I
wasn't pissed off.
I said we weren't exclusive.
That's all I wanted to say.
Oh, and... And this.
I know you think you're
scary and damaged.
Dark and twisty.
It makes you feel like you
don't deserve good things,
but you do. And
Derek... he's bad for you.
But me, I'm a good thing.
And if there's a race, if
there's a ring, my hat is in.
I made an appointment
for a reason.
I scheduled the time because
I had something
important to say and you
- made me wait.
- I have a situation.
I spent my life waiting. Waiting
for you to finish med school,
waiting for you to
come home at night,
leave that... woman.
- I'm done waiting.
- Adele...
It's time for you to make a
choice. Me or this hospital.
It's time for you
to retire, Richard.
It's obvious then. This baby
can't possibly be Shannon's.
Look at her. No one can stay
a size two and be pregnant.
- I've tried it.
- What're you saying?
- Sara's a little pudgy.
- At least she's not
sleeping around.
- I am short on time.
- Shannon didn't think
- about boys until Sara.
- You have some nerve.
Do I need to remind you
two who the teenagers are?
- She started it!
- Enough, OK?!
Both of you come
with me. Let's go.
- Let go of me!
- No. Move.
There he is.
That's your son.
I want you both to look at him.
Because it's not true
that you did nothing wrong.
You both are wrong.
You're wrong for
covering this up,
you're wrong for lying about it,
you're wrong for
letting this little baby,
this sweet, innocent, beautiful
little boy suffer like this.
He's dying and it's your fault.
It's both of your
faults, and the thing is,
the truth will come out.
In time, it will come
out. It always does.
It just...
It just does.
And when it does,
this baby will be dead.
Shannon.
Don't tell my mom, OK?
Thank you.
Thank you for telling the truth.
You really don't feel anything?
I feel like I've been
here for a very long time.
I feel like it
might be too late.
Too late for what?
Thank you for your patience
and cooperation, doctors.
You'll have to
go on antibiotics,
but the threat has
been contained.
Good.
- What?
- You're free to go.
Poor little guy.
The minute he's OK we have
to turn him over to a mother
who's going to juvie and
grandparents who are so clueless
they didn't even realize
their own kid was pregnant.
Imagine the kind of
childhood he's gonna have.
You can get over
a bad childhood.
I mean, you can have the worst
crap in the world happen to you.
I mean, you can get over it.
All you gotta do is survive.
Hello?
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. I was so worried.
But... I'm fine.
I'm 100 percent plague-free.
- I was really, really worried.
- Yeah, I know. Me too.
George, I really,
really love you.
- Hi.
I was gonna come
over this morning, but...
- I heard. The quarantine.
- Yeah.
So... what does this mean?
It means you have a choice.
You have a choice to make.
And I don't wanna rush you
into making a decision
before you're ready.
This morning I was gonna
come over, and I was gonna say...
What I wanted to say was...
But now, all I
can say is that...
I'm in love with you.
I've been in love
with you forever.
I'm a little late. I know I'm a
little late in telling you that.
♪ They're burning
on the bridge ♪
I just want you
to take your time.
You know?
Take all the time you need...
because you have
a choice to make.
And when I had a choice
to make... I chose wrong.
♪ One more day and it's
all slipping with the sand ♪
All right, good night.
♪ You touch my lips and
grab the back of my hand ♪
♪ The back of my hand ♪
Time flies.
♪ Guess we both know
we're in over our heads ♪
♪ We got nowhere to go ♪
You're not going
to retire, are you?
Adele, you spring
this on me today.
I need to think. I
need more time.
♪ It all might be OK
or we might be dead ♪
I don't have any
more time to give.
♪ If everything we've
got is slipping away ♪
Time waits for no man.
♪ I meant what I said when
I said until my dying day ♪
♪ I'm holding on to
you holding on to me ♪
Time heals all wounds.
♪ Maybe it's all gone
black but you're all I see ♪
Where have you been all day?
Sitting shiva for Denny.
How are you?
Ooh...
♪ Glass is breaking so
don't let go of my arm ♪
♪ Grab your bags and a
picture of where we met ♪
Don't ever die.
I'll do my best.
OK... OK.
♪ If everything we've
got is blowing away ♪
All any of us
wants is more time.
Good night.
♪ I'm holding on to
you holding on to me ♪
Isn't this so cool?
I mean, can you believe it?
Tomorrow we're
gonna be surgeons.
♪ You're all I need ♪
Time to stand up.
Time to grow up.
I'm ready.
OK.
♪ The tears are coming down
They're mixing with the rain ♪
Time to let go.
♪ I know I love you if
that's all we can take ♪
Time.