Previously on Grey's Anatomy:
What is going on with you?
We grant you four months
to retake the medical board exam.
- Karev, take the scalpel.
- Alex, come on.
Your choice. It's simple. Her or me.
Addison is my family. I'm supposed to
sign a piece of paper and end my family?
- Your date?
- My husband.
- You're married?
- Ten years today.
Burke wants a relationship.
OK. We're a couple.
So pick me. Choose me.
Love me.
I'll be at Joe's tonight. If you decide
to sign the papers, meet me there.
Tell me what to do.
I actually said "Pick me."
Right? I did? "Pick me"?
- I think it's romantic.
- It's not romantic, it's horrifying.
Horror movie horrifying. Carrie at the
prom with the pig's blood horrifying.
OK, fine, it's horrifying.
But Carrie took out
an entire senior class as revenge.
Gotta say, I like that in a girl.
I said "Pick me."
When you say "I'll meet you later"
how long does that mean
you should wait?
- Do you think he's really not coming?
- It is getting a little hard to watch.
It was hard to watch an hour ago.
Now it's pathetic.
Who's pathetic?
- What?
- You, who pretend to be my friends,
are calling me pathetic
behind my back in front of my face.
Why don't you just dump the pig's blood
on me now and get it over with?
He's really not coming.
Joe, turn up the TV.
A massive train wreck occurred
just outside Seattle minutes ago.
- 911.
- We just worked a 30-hour shift.
I don't have any clean underwear.
The Vancouver-bound train
was carrying 300 passengers.
- Looks ugly.
- Paramedics are helping victims.
You're leaving?
No, you can't leave.
Sorry, gotta go tend
to someone else's train wreck.
You gotta at least stay
for a cup of coffee.
You're in no shape to cut people open.
I want to hear the ending.
Meredith?
Maybe it's for the best.
Maybe I don't want to know.
That's the stupidest thing
I've ever heard.
-  In general...
- Bye, Joe.
... people can be categorized
in one of two ways.
He was in the front of the train.
Those who love surprises,
and those who don't.
I don't.
Dude, you're late.
Once again, a massive train wreck
occurred outside of Seattle minutes ago.
I've never met a surgeon
that enjoys a surprise,
because, as surgeons,
we like to be in the know.
We have to be in the know.
Because when we aren't,
people die and lawsuits happen.
Am I rambling? I think I'm rambling.
I think I saw a pneumothorax.
I hope I get a pneumothorax.
- Hey.
- Thought you weren't talking to me.
Thought you needed a friend,
so I'm rising above.
- Why would you think that?
- Because you freaked out.
- I did not.
- Missed out on open-heart surgery.
- O'Malley plugged the hole.
- I thought you needed to talk.
- Well, I don't.
- To someone who cares about you.
- What are you looking at?
- Is that a dress?
Nothing. What?
Go get me my damn shoes.
Let's move, people.
Hello. I seem to be a little bit drunk.
I was off duty.
So was I.
Anybody else half in the bottle?
- No.
- All right then.
Stay out of the way.
I'll deal with you later.
The rest, stick with me
and wait for assignments.
I know you get all a-quiver
at the sight of blood,
but it'll be a long night and you're
tired. I want no mistakes. Come on.
I'm done. Done.
- I'm so not tired anymore.
- Me neither.
I've got a third-trimester burn victim
here. I'll need some help.
- Izzie, go.
- Yes. Have a nice nap.
- Have you had any contractions?
- No.
Hey. Joe told me to tell you that
McSteamy came looking for you.
You mean McDreamy?
Joe said McDreamy came looking for me?
No, I'm pretty sure it was McSteamy.
Yeah. Yeah.
Dr. Shepherd,
could you take a look at this?
Does that mean he picked her?
If it does, I just lost 50 bucks.
Got the leg!
- I want that leg.
- He lost a lot of blood at the scene.
Pressure dressings applied,
two large-bore IVs started.
- Anything for pain?
- Morphine. Five migs given so far.
Dr. Bailey, who you got?
- Cristina, go.
- Yes!
Rule out other injuries and book an OR.
- Dr. Webber?
- We have a train wreck, Derek.
We need all hands on deck.
Clear me for surgery or you're fired.
- Any headaches today?
- No.
- Dizziness? Nausea? Blurred vision?
- No, no and no. Out of my way.
Fine. But I'm coming with you.
Or I'm fired. Up to you.
If you're a resident, page the operator.
- Was that a nod?
- Yes.
- Do we know what it meant?
- No.
Am I invisible?
OK, so my point actually,
and I do have one,
has nothing to do with surprises
or death or lawsuits or even surgeons.
My point is this: whoever said,
"What you don't know can't hurt you"
was a complete and total moron.
Because for most people I know,
not knowing
is the worst feeling in the world.
OK, fine, maybe it's the second worst.
His BP's steady at ninety over palp.
She's had two hypotensive episodes
to the low seventies.
- Couldn't get a saw in?
- Not without moving them.
- Which would've been a bad idea.
- Did you bolus her with fluids?
We're pushing it open...
Is this the craziest thing you've seen?
Uh... Yeah.
Yeah. Me too.
OK, then. You guys got it from here.
Hey, uh... You were at the scene?
Yeah. Won't be too bad for you.
Lot of carnage. Not a lot of survivors.
They're never gonna fit into CT.
We're gonna be flying blind.
Get X-rays and labs, then page me.
Excuse me?
Hi, I'm Dr. Burke.
You shouldn't turn your head. You want
to try to move as little as possible.
Oh. OK.
So are you gonna pull this pole
out of us anytime soon?
Touch uncomfortable.
Sorry, we can't until we get a better
look at what's going on internally.
I assure you we will work
as quickly as possible.
Well, in that case,
does anybody have a breath mint?
For me, not for you.
- Keep them going.
- O'Malley? Get them to X-ray.
- Thanks.
- Move them extremely carefully.
This never would've happened
before the elevator.
You go, George.
Alex, cover the ER.
You can do sutures while you get over
your newfound fear of scalpels.
That was mean, even for you.
You are drunk.
Go get yourself a banana bag IV,
put it in your arm and then find me.
Do not speak to any more patients,
do not practice any medicine.
Well, should I just go home?
Unless you drank the whole bottle,
you'll be sober in a few hours.
And the IV fluids
will head off your hangover.
Then you can assist
with the many mangled victims here.
Besides, if I'm not going home,
nobody's going home.
Ten years of marriage. I didn't even
get to finish my damn lobster.
Well, is there anyone
you'd like me to call?
They called my wife from the ambulance.
And my fiancé. They're flying down
from Vancouver together.
Normally, Amanda would be upset to find
me pressed up against another woman.
But in this case,
I think I'll get a pass.
- You two weren't traveling together?
- No. We just met.
- Bit of an awkward introduction.
- You have very nice pores.
Hurts to laugh.
- Hey.
- Whoa. You can go ahead and just...
- Oh, thanks.
Oh, wow.
- Do you think I could...
- Yeah, go ahead.
Dr. Stevens, did you need something?
No.
- Ow!
- I'm sorry. Am I doing this too...
- Ow! Was that a... Did I have...
- A contraction.
It was definitely a contraction.
We need to book an OR.
You are in no shape to push,
and the baby is still in some distress,
so we're gonna have to proceed
with a C-section.
OK. OK.
But can we call a lawyer first?
I don't have a will.
And there's no father.
And in case something happens to me...
There's no cause for panic, Brooke.
We have some time, OK?
OK.
Hello.
Oh, no, no, no, we're fine, honey.
Some redneck tried to outrun the train.
The train slammed into his ass
and then it rolled...
- That hurt?
- Uh-uh.
Oh, no, no, that dude is toast.
Him and about 200 other people.
- And Mary got her face all cut up.
- Does it hurt anywhere else?
Here.
A whole bunch of luggage, when they hit
the brakes, it just came flying at us.
We'll do an X-ray, see if anything's
broken, or if there's internal injuries.
OK.
Yeah. Wait. Hold on.
I'm gonna have to call you back.
- Hey. Excuse me. Where you going?
- I'm taking your friend for an X-ray.
No offense, little boy,
but you look like my oldest son,
- and he's nothing but trouble.
- Yvonne, shut up.
I said "no offense."
I'm just saying, sure you're a doctor?
Yeah? Yeah, we're fine.
Yeah, this redneck
tried to outrun the train...
Ow! Ow. Ow.
- What are you doing?
- Trying to insert my banana bag.
Which sounds vaguely dirty,
but it isn't.
I can do it.
So, how's it going with Addison?
Bad mood? Good mood?
"Yay, my husband picked me" mood?
I think it's more of an "I hate
the smell of charred flesh" mood.
Before you judge me,
I know there was a train accident.
People are very badly hurt.
And that I'm a vapid narcissist
when you mix me with alcohol.
In case you were wondering, I know that.
Well, for what it's worth, I take issue
with her salmon-colored scrubs.
I mean, what self-respecting surgeon
wears salmon-colored scrubs?
- This is what I'm saying.
- Yeah.
Thank you.
Yang, how's that wound looking?
Pretty clean. Some dirt and gravel.
He was lucky. It's a guillotine injury.
We do this right,
he'll have full use of his leg.
More irrigation.
Dr. Shepherd?
It'll wait.
I'm fine, Derek.
Just adjusting to the light.
There's no shame
in taking more time off.
It doesn't make you old
or tired or rusty, it...
OK, that came out wrong.
You're the only attending neurosurgeon,
you're needed elsewhere. I'm fine here.
Dr. Shepherd?
OK. Page me if you need me.
When you're finished cleaning
that wound, you can help me, Dr. Yang.
Is the wound clean, Yang?
- Yes, sir, I... But...
- But what?
If your plan is to be a watchdog
for Dr. Shepherd
or if you think your job here is to
baby-sit me, then you can think again.
I've been a surgeon
longer than you've been breathing.
If I were not ready to be in this OR,
I would say so. Is that understood?
- Yes, sir.
- Now do we have a problem, Yang?
Yes. No, sir.
I'm thrilled to learn.
And I'm grateful to be here.
It's just that...
Um...
Sorry. His legs...
What about them?
They're both left.
- Find the man's leg, Yang. Find it now.
- Yes, sir.
Is it going straight through her spine?
It is. T8's completely crushed.
Hey.
What happened?
Uh, tequila.
I'm keeping an eye on her.
Look at this.
These people are still alive?
They're still making small talk.
Pole's tamponading the wounds
as far as we can see.
It's hitting the aorta.
And look at him. It's right in line
with his inferior vena cava.
Is there any way to operate
without separating them?
- No.
- But if we move the pole then...
They'll both bleed out.
What if we don't move the pole?
What if we move one of the patients
off the pole to get the saw in there?
Then we can hold the pole steady
in the other one.
Move it very slowly,
and repair the damage as we go.
Who? Which would you move?
With her aortic injuries,
her chances of survival
are extremely slim no matter what we do.
But if we move her,
we have a real shot at saving him.
Well, I could argue since her injuries
are more extensive, we should move him.
Give her the best shot we can.
So basically whoever you move
doesn't stand a chance?
So how do you choose?
How do you decide who gets to live?
We have to decide soon
if we want to save one of them.
- I'd like to examine them first.
- I'll wait for your page.
Thank you. Dr. Grey?
Dr. Grey needs to get a blood alcohol
test before practicing medicine tonight.
What? No, I'm totally fine, look.
Totally fine.
Right. OK.
- I'm fine.
- Regretting that last shot about now?
What are you doing in here?
The leg you brought with the amputee...
- I didn't bring in an amputee.
- OK, well, one of you did and it's...
'Cause all paramedics look alike to you?
OK. Really. I cannot straddle
another giant ego right now.
I'm already doing the splits.
I need a right leg, right now,
or the Chief of Surgery
will take away my pretty blue scrubs.
When the train derailed,
it hit an overpass.
The dining car roof sheared off
and sliced through a passenger car.
There were multiple decapitations.
Your guy can live without his leg.
This is so not about the leg.
Or the guy.
But thank you. For all that you do.
Really. Thanks.
Yeah, honey, we're fine.
Some redneck tried to outrun the train,
then they give us this boy doctor.
All right, scar shouldn't be too bad.
Can you tell me...
My friend... She's pregnant too.
She went in a different ambulance. She
was burned. Do you know where she is?
If she's not here,
she should be in Maternity.
I need to see her.
- We're not finished here.
- My baby's fine. I feel her kicking.
- I've got to see Brooke.
- You can't just leave.
Just wait. Come here, come here.
Ow! Ow!
Sorry.
So you operated on a heart earlier.
You'd think you could draw blood.
- I rocked that heart.
- Yeah, you did.
I think I'm strung out on the scalpel.
Nothing wrong with that.
So any news? About...
No. I can't read him.
I think it's pretty amazing
you even gave him the choice.
And I think, for what it's worth,
I think he's crazy
if he doesn't pick you.
Please tell me you've seen a right leg,
a cleanly severed right leg.
No.
How weird is this job?
Weird.
- Brooke?
- Jana?
- Thank God.
- Dr. Karev?
- I couldn't stop her.
- She was on the train?
- Yes, but...
- Have you done an ultrasound?
Cleared her C-spine?
Is there a reason why she is wandering
around the hospital unattended?
She's not unattended.
I came up with her. She's...
You can leave now, Dr. Karev.
Irresponsible even for an intern.
What? You disagree?
She wanted to see her friend. I mean,
what was he supposed to do, tackle her?
Dr. Stevens, why don't you get
our new patient into a bed? Shall we?
Can you feel that, Miss Krasnoff?
You're a cute doctor. Cute doctors
get to call me by my first name.
- Bonnie?
- Mmm.
OK, Bonnie. Can you feel that, Bonnie?
Can I feel what?
Oh. Well, I guess that's a no.
- Dr. Shepherd?
- Yes.
- I got the labs.
- Great, thank you.
Here you go. Hold that, please.
Could you try to wiggle your toes,
Mr. Maynard?
- Are they moving?
- Yes, they are.
- Good. That's good, right?
- Yes, it is. Yes, it is.
What about me? Are mine moving?
Yes, they are.
Yay me.
- Dr. Shepherd, is it?
- Yes, it is.
Dr. Shepherd, Bonnie and I...
- are we going to live through this?
- Now that's just morose, Tom.
I'm sorry, dear.
Doctor?
We're going to do everything we can,
Mr. Maynard.
About time. I was starting to
think my work here would be wasted.
So sorry. It wasn't easy to find.
I checked the wound
and it's very clean cut, well preserved.
Dr. Webber?
Sir?
Notice anything else about that leg?
Anything other than that very clean cut?
Did you happen to notice, for example,
that it was shaved recently?
And manicured?
Take a look at my patient, Dr. Yang.
Does he look like a man who woke up
and shaved one of his legs this morning?
No.
I'll go find the right...
the right right leg.
- The right...
- Thank you.
- Where are we?
- You were right. Vitals are erratic.
Pulse is weak. The spine's severed.
I was hoping that it didn't hit.
But from that angle,
it just can't have missed the aorta.
What about him? Think he can live?
- He's got better odds.
- Let OR One know we're coming.
And, O'Malley, close off the gallery.
We don't need an audience for this.
She's cracking jokes.
How do you tell someone she'll be dead
soon when she's cracking jokes?
Excuse me? Is there any chance that we
can get out of here some time this year?
Well, the lab's backed up
and so is Radiology.
I can't discharge her until I know
she has no internal injuries.
Hello? Yeah, we're still here,
'cause the doctor's friggin' useless.
Mm-hm.
I realize you're dealing
with a lot of carnage.
I'm asking if you could maybe
sift through some of that carnage
and find a...
Hello... Dammit.
Cristina. You paged me?
If I don't find this leg, the chief
is gonna cut me from this program.
And I cannot go back home, Burke.
It is too sunny in Los Angeles.
It's sunny every day.
And you paged me because?
I need you to help me find the leg.
I checked the board.
You're not in surgery, right?
You're my boyfriend. I mean...
I know I don't have much experience
with this kind of thing,
but aren't boyfriends supposed to help
in situations like this?
Cristina, when we're on duty,
I can't be your boyfriend.
OK, so when we're on duty,
I can have sex with someone else?
Dr. Yang, I'm walking away now.
Fine. Fine. But when the chief cuts me,
you might rethink this.
Addison yelled at you
in front of a patient?
She didn't exactly yell.
- Fine, she's Satan's whore.
- Thank you. So did you yell back?
- No.
- Dude, you lost your mojo.
- Excuse you?
- I was trying to talk boy.
O'Malley plugs a hole with his finger
and he's a hero.
- I have one off day...
- You chickened out.
I hesitated briefly.
Why didn't you kiss Izzie?
- And now I'm leaving.
- It's not in the morgue.
I've looked in the ambulances,
in the ER...
How is one bloody, hairy leg
going to destroy my career?
Dr. Karev?
I hope you find your mojo, Alex.
I find you disturbing without it.
Me too.
Ow!
This is hard, because your body
is in a certain amount of shock.
It's preventing you from feeling pain,
feeling the extent of your injuries.
Dr. Shepherd.
We have a metal pole
cutting a path through our insides.
I don't know about Tom here,
but I didn't expect
to walk out of here anytime soon, so...
whatever it is you have to say,
just please, say it.
OK, Bonnie.
In order to operate on Mr. Maynard,
we have to separate you two.
In order to do that, we have to
move you backwards off the pole.
Can't you just pull the pole
out of both of us?
If we did that, you would both start
bleeding very quickly. Too quickly.
Right now the pole
is plugging the wounds.
Once removed, the organs will shift.
And there is a great deal of damage.
So, if you move me, I'll die?
We're gonna do everything we can to...
No. No. If anybody has to go,
it should be me.
- You just move me...
- No, Mr. Maynard.
Mr. Maynard.
Your injuries are less extensive.
If we pull the pole from you
as we operate around it,
we have a better chance
of repairing the damage.
It's not right.
It's not fair.
Tom.
It's not fair either way.
Is um... Is my Danny... Is he here yet?
There are delays at the airport.
The storm...
We could wait.
But the longer we do,
the higher the risk of infection for...
No. No.
This is better.
Danny, he wouldn't understand.
I've had a couple of hours
to, you know, process all of this,
but if... if he had to see me,
talk to me like this...
Well, I just think it would be too hard.
Right there.
In between the vertebral spaces.
Don't be shy about pressure.
That's good. You are doing so good.
- Somebody called for a notary?
- I asked for a lawyer.
I couldn't get one
at this time of night.
But the hospital has
pretty standard forms.
It says that in the case of death
or permanent vegetative state,
your child remains in the custody of...
We put her name in.
Wait. What?
What are we... Who's dying here?
There's some danger.
With any surgery, there's danger.
But with the trauma of Brooke's burns,
there's an additional risk of shock.
- She wants to be certain.
- That's ridiculous.
You're going to be fine, do you hear me?
I hear you.
But we still have to sign the forms
unless you want our son
to end up with my mom.
How long have you two been together?
Since third grade.
We're not lovers, we're best friends.
We wanted our kids to have two parents.
- So we got a sperm donor...
- The same donor?
So your babies are brother and sister?
How cool is that?
That's... Wow.
- Wet.
- What?
I'm wet. I think my water just broke.
Good news. You've got a broken rib,
we're gonna give you some painkillers.
- After that you should be good to go.
- Thank you.
Yvonne, answer your phone.
Yvonne? Yvonne?
Yvonne!
- Code blue! I need some help here!
- Yvonne!
Push one of epi. Hold CPR.
Her abdomen is rock solid.
She's lost too much blood.
- She's been bleeding for hours.
- There's no blood.
- She was bleeding internally.
- She didn't say anything.
She was... She wasn't even a patient.
I didn't know.
Dr. Karev, she's gone.
No! No!
No! No! Yvonne!
I'm sorry.
Time of death, 2:51.
No, no, no, no.
Don't. Try again. Try again.
Jana, this is our OB resident,
Dr. Hoffman.
She's gonna be taking care of you
from here.
Uh-huh.
You're doing great, Jana,
keep breathing.
I'm gonna check your cervix now.
We've booked an OR
but they won't hold it for long
- so we need to go now.
- Right now?
But we're supposed to be together.
We took classes.
- I'm sorry, but we can't wait.
- That's OK, Brookie.
You go have your C-section.
And enjoy those drugs.
- This is already not fun for my vagina.
- Dr. Stevens?
- No. If I have to go, she has to stay.
- Someone has to stay with Jana. Please.
Brooke, Dr. Stevens is a surgeon,
but I'm gonna...
It's OK. I'll stay.
OK.
Brookie. Stay alive, OK?
You too.
Dammit!
- Hey, Doc.
- What?!
Easy, killer. Jill said you guys were
freaking out looking for this leg.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
Right on.
Chief Webber, I'm extremely sorry, I...
Pull that tendon down
with those pick-ups.
- You found the leg?
- I found the leg.
You missed out on this, but
I'm sure they could use a hand in ER.
Karev and I can handle it from here.
Suction.
- Can I ask you a question?
- Mm-hm.
Do you believe in heaven?
I do.
Don't you?
I want to.
Bonnie...
I just want to say...
Shhh!
I know. I know.
This is Dr. Adams,
our anesthesiologist.
When you're ready,
he's going to put you to sleep.
So it's not gonna hurt?
It won't hurt a bit.
Good.
That's good.
- Dr. Shepherd?
- Yes?
You're gonna be the one
to talk to my Danny, right?
Yes.
- OK.
What would you like me to tell him?
Why do I feel like
we're about to kill this girl?
Dr. Bailey, my labs are in.
- Sober?
- Can I scrub in?
Do it fast.
- George.
- Right.
Hey.
Hi.
- You know, I went to the bar.
- I heard.
You take some aspirin with the
banana bag? Helps with the hangover.
Oh.
You're staying with her.
Yeah, she's my wife.
Dr. Shepherd, she's crashing.
What happened?
- I just put them under.
- The pole must've shifted.
I barely touched her.
This isn't my fault.
It's nobody's fault.
We need to remove her now.
- How do we do this?
- Team One, stabilize his body.
Team Two, move her back
and let's get the saw in there.
This has to be fast and smooth, people.
O'Malley, you hold the pole in place.
- Whatever you do, don't let it move.
- OK.
On the count of three. One, two...
Three!
That's great. That's great.
Take another breath. One, two...
He's wedged under her ribs,
we have to pull him out.
On three. One, two...
- Watch her head.
- Clean towel.
- He's stable.
- Retract.
Let's start with her
and see what we can do.
- We'll need more blood.
- Scalpel.
- Hold onto the blood bag.
- Grey, help retract.
Richardson retractor.
- Lap.
- Got it.
Clamp.
Retractor.
Quick, please.
Give me some sponges. Sponges.
- Bovie suction here.
- I'm in.
Lap sponges. Hand me the cautery.
Her aorta's shredded.
She's gonna bleed out.
We have no rhythm.
Doctors, he's losing pressure.
- He's bleeding.
- Let's go.
Transitioning.
Change out.
Everybody change gloves.
What about her?
We can't just abandon her!
- I'm going in.
- We can't abandon her!
I'm going in stem to stern. Scalpel.
Sternal saw.
Give me the sternal saw.
Cautery.
- Let's go.
- Meredith.
Dr. Grey.
- Meredith!
- What about her?
We cannot just abandon her.
We have an obligation.
I'll take care of this.
Meredith, come on,
there was too much damage.
There was never anything we could do.
We have to let her go.
Time of death 3:49.
- Good morning.
- How's Brooke?
She's good.
- And the baby?
- He came through, too.
So, have you made a decision yet,
Dr. Stevens?
I'm sorry?
Whether or not you're going to hate me.
You're Meredith's friend. I'm
the wicked witch who cheated on Dr...
Wait, what is it that you guys call him?
McDreamy.
Right. God, doesn't that embarrass him?
Yeah, I think it does.
- By all rights, you should hate me.
- I guess.
Except that I'm gonna
be staying in town for a while.
- You are?
- Yes.
And you show a real gift
with my specialty.
And I have a lot to teach,
if you want to learn.
So...
So, when you decide how important it is
for you to hate me, let me know.
Did she uh... Did she suffer?
No. Her injuries prevented her from...
No, she wasn't in any pain.
Good. That's...
She asked me to... to tell you that...
She wanted you to know
that if love were enough...
that if love were enough,
that she'd still be here with you.
As surgeons,
there are so many things
we have to know.
- Fine work, Dr. Karev.
- Thank you, sir.
We have to know we have what it takes.
We have to know
how to take care of our patients.
Tom is doing just fine.
And how to take care of each other.
- OK?
- Yeah.
Eventually we even have to figure out...
how to take care of ourselves.
As surgeons, we have to be in the know.
But as human beings,
sometimes
it's better to stay in the dark.
Because in the dark,
there may be fear...
but there's also hope.
Better get cleaned up.
Rounds. Five minutes.
www.tvsubtitles.net