Previously on "Grey's Anatomy"...
I had sex last night
with the wrong person.
But the thing is,
it didn't feel wrong.
This is our secret,
okay
We heard about your mother.
We're here to make sure
that you're all right.
What if my husband shows up
tomorrow with a picture
of what I'm supposed to
look like, but it's too late,
and I'm stuck with the wrong
face for the rest of my life ?
Cristina and I were together
for three years.
Are you gonna invite me ?
Where ?
To the wedding.
Please leave.
A patient's history
is as important as their symptoms.
It's what helps us decide
if heartburn's a heart attack,
if a headache's a tumor.
Sometimes patients will try
to rewrite their own histories.
They'll claim they don't smoke
or forget to mention certain drugs,
which, in surgery,
can be the kiss of death.
We can ignore it all we want...
but our history...
eventually always comes back
to haunt us.
Meredith... she'll accept
a certain amount of help,
and then she start
to feel suffocated.
Oh.
Is this... am I suffocating ?
No. The groceries are just right.
It's... it's me. I sometimes overdo it.
Well, who could blame you
with everything ?
After Ellis died, I gave her some time,
but I want to be here.
- I want to help make things easier.
- Good. Yeah.
That's great ! Just try to keep it light.
You know, be helpful...
- Good morning.
- Want some coffee ?
- Yes
This all you ?
I just picked up some things
to restock your fridge.
Well, you bought groceries last week.
Yeah, you have to get it
every week if you want more.
Well, thank you.
It's unexpected,
and you didn't need to do all this.
Is this for everybody ?
Absolutely.
I gotta run. I'm gonna go talk to Richard
before things get too busy in the hospital.
- See ya.
- Mm.
Are you gonna talk
to him about the, uh...
- Yeah. Wish me luck.
- You don't need it.
Just make him listen to you.
You deserve to be chief.
Nice sweater.
Uh... my wife.
What ?
My wife,
she gave it to me.
The sweater.
Actually, it's my ex-wife.
It's amicable.
I'm sorry ?
The divorce, It's... It's amicable,
very friendly.
I'm a friendly guy.
"I'm a friendly guy" ?
Sloan.
She pressed five and got off at three.
She'd rather walk up two flights
of stairs than flirt with you
Hell, she'd rather climb up
the outside of the building.
- I wasn't flirting.
- You're telling me.
There's no need to be embarrassed.
Time for you to shake off the rust
and get back in the game.
You need a wingman.
I have patients to see.
We'd make a great team.
Nothing like a quick
ventricular reconstruction
to jumpstart your morning, eh ?
Okay, you're officially becoming
creepy, creepy and...
stalking.
Burke and I have set our date.
We're getting married ne month.
We both know you're not
the marrying kind.
Well, you don't know that.
You don't know me anymore.
Well, just to be sure you're
fully aware of what you're passing up,
I'd like you to assist me on my
heterotopic heart transplant today.
What, a piggyback transplant ?
Seriously ?
Burke will want to scrub in,
too, I imagine,
See how it's done.
Heterotopic transplant.
He is upping his game.
I need a gambit.
I need to force him into the defensive.
Take his queen.
You've never played chess ?
I'm not a geek.
I've gotta crush him.
I've gotta annihilate him
at his own game.
So it's weird, right, that Susan
keeps stopping by like this ?
I mean, we just became friends
or semi-related or whatever you call
your estranged father's wife.
You may be confused since you
were basically raised by wolves,
but this is what mother's do.
They stop by, they stock the fridge.
Hey, dude, you think she might do
our laundry ?
Hey,
get your own fake mom.
Hey.
Bad night on call ?
Oh, god.
Yeah, when my patient's gooey abscess
exploded all over me at 4 :00 A.M.,
That was a highlight.
Holy mary, mother of god,
pray for us sinners now and at the...
Iz, you look nice.
Did you just come from
confession in a church ?
Shut up.
Izzie Stevens does penance.
You did something bad.
Oh. I feel like poo.
I just hope I can make it through
the day without falling asleep.
Do you want to make a coffee date ?
3 :00 P.M. You could use
a little pick-me-up.
Yeah.
- That sounds nice, really nice.
- Good.
Okay.
Smile.
Oh, come on, man. That's not a smile.
Can I see ?
That's me ?
Oh, my God.
I know this is gonna sound terrible,
but I'm not bad-looking.
I think beautiful is the word
you're looking for.
I was gonna say hot.
I was, too, but I think
I would've gotten in trouble.
You would've.
Still a little swelling.
In a day or two, I'll raise
that hot to smokin'.
Then shouldn't we wait
to take the "after" pictures ?
We could, but the sooner we take them,
the sooner we get them out there.
Your picture's gonna be everywhere...
the police, the news, the internet.
But if my face
looks completely different,
then what good would pictures do ?
I was able to maintain
aspects of your bone structure,
so your face bears some similarities
to your old face, plus, your...
your hair and your eyes are the same.
You think...
do you really think someone might
recognize me ?
I think you should smile.
I'm telling you,
this confession thing, it...
it really works.
It's like we have a do over.
Our sin is gone.
So you don't have to keep
avoiding me.
Yeah, I do. Until this thing
blows over, I do.
Javier Ruggero ?
Javier, uh, Ruggero ?
Blows over ?
What does that even mean ?
When Meredith and I, uh...
eventually, you know,
it blew over. It passed.
You mean the sad sex ?
The sad, tragic, depression-inducing sex
you had with Meredith
- is the same as what...
- I can't.
Okay ? Back off. Just for now,
back off.
Javier... ruggero ?
You're Dr. Isobel Stevens ?
Yes.
Uh, if you're Mr. Ruggero, though,
you're with Dr. O'Malley.
- Uh, Dr. Stevens...
- We, uh...
our d... our daughter has leukemia and
needs a bone marrow transplant.
You, uh, you're looking for hematology.
It's third floor west...
through these double doors,
second set of elevators on the...
on the right.
I'm so sorry about your daughter.
But Seattle Grace has one of the best
bone marrow transplant centers
in the country.
If you'd like, I can
take you up there myself.
No, no, it's just that
you look
so much like our daughter.
We're Dustin and Caroline Klein.
We're Hannah's parents.
We're her...
we're your daughter's parents.
You're Hannah's birth mother.
S03e20
Ain't nothing but the real things
Hannah was diagnosed a few months ago
with acute myeloid leukemia.
We, uh,
we looked you up, and we know that
that's wrong, but...
she needs the transplant.
We...
we were set to go.
We had a donor.
Yeah, her donor died.
The registry called
Hannah's oncologist last night.
'Cause apparently Hannah hasn't
had enough bad luck.
And we'd never ask.
I mean, we had no intention
of bothering you, ever.
But last night, everything changed.
No. Of course.
Of course I'd donate. It's just...
a biological parent isn't usually a good
donor. I'm only a half match.
Hannah would probably do better getting
back on the donor list and waiting.
I know...
when you gave her up,
we promised to take care of her,
to keep her safe,
but I... I can't protect her from this.
It's genetic.
You have to take care of her.
Every day we wait, she gets sicker.
And... and if we're lucky,
you... you could be better
than a half match.
Yeah.
Is she...
she's here ?
God, she must be scared.
She's upstairs with my mother.
Can I...
um...
I'd... I'd like to meet her.
We... we'd have to check with Hannah.
But I...
if she agrees,
of course we'd be okay with it.
Isobel...
our daughter could die.
Charles...
this is Dr. Burke.
I've invited him to assist
on the surgery.
How do you do, Dr. Burke ?
Oh, you're playing yourself ?
It distracts me from the fact
that you're going to have your hands
in my chest in a few hours.
And this, Charles, is a former student
of mine...
a formidable chess player herself...
- Dr. Cristina Yang.
- Soon to be Dr. Cristina Burke.
We're getting married
next month.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you, sir.
Perhaps you'd like to explain...
the procedure,
- Dr. Yang.
- Absolutely.
Mr. Redford,
instead of replacing your current heart,
we're going to attach it
to the new heart,
essentially piggybacking it.
The two hearts pump together,
share the workload. It's, uh...
it's a perfect team.
More accurately,
the new heart will circulate blood to
the body,
while the native heart will
pump blood to the lungs.
More of a divide-and-conquer approach.
Wouldn't you say, Dr. Yang ?
Sounds risky ?
All surgeries carry a degree of risk,
but Dr. Marlowe pioneered the procedure.
And Dr. Burke is one of the foremost
cardiothoracic surgeons in the country.
Well, I'll be the one
on point, of course.
So you've nothing to worry about.
You've picked the best man for the job.
What was that ?
That was my smug, passive-aggressive,
limey ex-boyfriend trying to show me
I picked the wrong guy.
I... I know, and I'm fine with it
as long as I'm learning something.
I was actually talking about you.
What was that ?
You're gonna have to put up
with me being
nice and sweet
for a little while.
That'll be a nice change of pace.
Shut up.
That's more like it.
Hey, I saw Ava.
She looks terrific.
Yeah, yeah, she does.
Sloan kicked it out.
Yeah, well, you had something
to do with that, too.
Just doing my job.
Jeez. You cannot take a compliment.
Well, I just don't want
people thinking...
what, you're trying to build
the perfect woman ?
Dr. Montgomery,
the police just called.
They're on their way over.
They think they found Jane Doe's family.
I'm sure you felt that you needed to be
even-handed when you announced
that you were looking for someone
to take over as chief.
Give everybody a shot at the brass ring.
I did.
Can we drop that ruse soon ?
It's not a ruse.
You promised me the job
when I came here.
It's why I came here.
No, you came because your marriage
fell apart
- and you had to get the hell out of dodge.
- We had an understanding,
and now you're having me jump
through hoops
with every other attending
in this hospital.
And I hear you're giving Marlowe special
privileges to do a piggyback surgery.
This is a teaching hospital, Derek.
Yeah.
My interview didn't go
as well as I had hoped.
I would like your support
with the board.
You know my credentials.
You know I'm ready.
- I only have one vote.
- It's a strong vote.
I'm not feeling well.
What's wrong with that girl ?
Oh, look, I can't talk to you when
you're making all that noise,
so pull it together and get out here.
Now.
I have an 11-year-old daughter.
She needs a bone marrow transplant.
I'm potentially a good match.
Please don't tell anybody. Please.
This isn't a chapter
of my history that...
I understand.
She's here...
my kid...
and I'm supposed to go up
to pediatrics and meet her
right now, and...
I mean, I've thought about
this moment...
wh... what I would look like...
what I would say.
But I thought I would be older,
more together, more mature.
I thought she would be older. And I
never thought that she would be sick.
Oh, God. I don't know what to do.
God, I don't know what to do.
What do I do ?
We love our Shannon,
but we
never got along wither husband.
- So she has a husband ?
- Had.
One day while she was at work, he
packed up and disappeared.
He didn't want a baby.
But she went after him,
even pregnant like that.
We hadn't heard from her in months,
and then today we
saw her picture on tv.
Mr. and Mrs. Waring, uh, the woman we
found, if she is your daughter...
Well,
her nose is different, and her chin, but
they said that her face had been,
you know, changed.
Do you happen to know
your daughter's blood type ?
She's B positive.
Any medical conditions, surgeries
we should know about ?
Um, she had her tonsils out
when she was 12.
It's her, isn't it ?
It's Shannon.
Susan.
Meredith, hi.
I'm so glad I found you.
Twice in one day.
Is this a bad time ?
I mean, I know you're always busy, but...
Yeah, no, I'm busy. I'm at work.
Okay, I was, um...
you knowI'd really just love
to talk with you.
- I would love to find a time for you
and me to sit down...
- I'm sorry.
This is too much.
Way too much.
You keep showing up.
I cannot be your daughter
or your charity case
or the thing that you need to fix.
- I'm not trying to...
- No, no. Stop talking, okay ?
Stop mothering.
Just stop.
She is mid-30s, brunette
and 8 months pregnant.
If you recognize her, please...
My glamour shot's been on the news
at least a dozen times already.
Admit it... You're gonna miss me when my
fancy family shows up to take me away.
You don't know they're fancy.
Open up.
Why, what's wrong
with my throat ?
How would I know? I haven't even
seen it yet. Now open up.
No, not till you tell me...
Wait.
Someone has recognized me,
haven't they ?
Alex... Alex, you have to
tell me who it is
please.
Their daughter's blood type
is b-positive.
She's your age. She's pregnant.
Your height,
your hair color,
and she has no tonsils.
So now are you gonna open up ?
Yes. Please tell me
I have no tonsils.
- Say ah.
- Ah.
No tonsils.
Shannon ?
Mr. And mrs. Waring, I asked you
to wait. I have tests to complete
Alex...
It's okay.
Your name...
- is Shannon Marie.
- Marie was my mother's name...
your grandmother.
Shannon Marie.
Okay, discharge
beds one and three.
Two needs a social worker.
Hold this down for me, O'Malley.
I'm gonna be out for a while.
Why ?
What's going on with Izzie ?
What's going on with Stevens
is none of your concern.
What is your concern ?
Sick people...
all these sick people...
until I get back. Understand ?
Dr. Bailey,
just did a consult in trauma one.
The guy has a perf.
Can I scrub in ?
No, you cannot scrub in.
Uh, you're here with O'Malley for now.
Hey, what's wrong with Izzie ?
Beds 7 through 13. Start with number 8.
He doesn't have much bladder control.
First, mr. Redford, while dr. Marlowe is
preparing the surgical area,
I will be examining
the donor heart.
Actually, I'm sorry.
I'll examine the donor heart.
I want to be sure
the I.V.C. Orifice is oversewn.
Well, carry on.
Then I'll open your chest
and put you on bypass,
at which point we will
connect the left atrium
- then the right atrium...
- Superior vena cava.
It simplifies the subsequent
cardiac biopsies.
You didn't read my article in the
"cardiothoracic monthly" last year.
Did you ? Huh ?
Well, I think Cristina has
a copy of it. Cristina,
- may I ?
- Oh, of course.
Oh, what on earth is that ?
Oh, testing colors.
For the big day, I assume ?
I'm thinking, um,
coral.
Hey, chief, come here.
I want to show you something.
I'm busy, Sloan.
I need an update on my patient
in room 3129.
Oh, hi.
Hi.
Okay.
I have that right here.
I like those sneakers.
You a runner ?
Yeah.
Me, too.
Maybe we should
go running some time.
Sure.
Anything else I can
help you with, dr. Sloan ?
No. All good.
Wingman.
- Hannah is in there right now ?
- She is.
You see her,
you'll know what to do.
Must be nice to know she has parents
like this, who fight for her, think about
what she wants, try to make her happy
like you would've.
Doesn't mean you don't want
that girl to want you.
Yeah.
I'm...
she's so, so tired.
We left it up to Hannah, and, uh,
she's just not ready. I'm sorry.
We don't want to force it.
- Maybe another time ?
- When she's feeling better.
No, of course.
I understand.
I'm sorry, but...
the transplant ?
Stevens.
Hey, look at me.
Look at me.
Your girl... you can want her
to want you all day long,
but she has to be here if she's ever
gonna have that chance again.
I'm sorry.
Of course. Yeah.
I'm ready. Let's get started.
Hey guess what. I'm a teacher.
I teach second grade
at North Bend Elementary.
Or at least I did
- until...
- you can get your job back
whenever you want.
They love you there. When will
we be able to take her home ?
You want to take her back to...
North Bend. We've got a room
all setup for her.
Your mom's got all of your books
and your letters and diaries.
I kept diaries ?
about 800 of them.
So even if you don't
remember everything now,
you will.
You hear that ?
I can go, right ?
Well, you're still getting
I.V. Antibiotics,
and we're monitoring the baby
very closely right now.
Yeah, but you can
make it happen, right ?
Come on, Alex.
Don't doctor me.
Help me get outta here.
Dr. Montgomery's got you
on strict bed rest until your delivery.
But I'll ask. Maybe... maybe you
can do it from home.
Home.
- Hey.
- You okay ? You look...
- horrible.
I'm in a horrible mood.
I yelled at Susan.
I think I scared off
my fake mommy forever.
- Need cheering up ?
- No.
Me either.
It's gonna be ok.
- You think ?
- Yeah, Susan will be okay.
How'd it go with the chief ?
- About as well as you and Susan.
- Wow. We make a good team.
I've been waiting for you in
really-old-guy's room for 20 minutes.
What gives ?
Sorry. We decided
to eat down here today.
Nobody told me.
Anybody...
move.
Anybody know what's
going on with Izzie ?
Something's going on.
Why don't you
just ask her yourself ?
Fine. I would if I knew
where she was.
I brought you lunch.
You've got stuff
on your hands.
I'm trying to scare
away cardio God.
With pretty, pretty fingers ?
He takes my rook,
I take his bishop.
Hey, pouty head.
Oh, are you so sad 'cause no-face
girl's family is taking her home ?
Really? Someone claimed Ava?
Yeah, her parents.
She must be so relieved.
Yeah, unless they suck.
Can you imagine, you can't remember
a family, and they show up,
and it turns out
they're psycho killers ?
- Or over sharers.
- Whatever.
She's a patient.
I don't give a crap who her
parents are, where she goes.
Can we move on ?
One second.
What's up with Izzie ?
D... I told you, it's none
of your concern.
No, it is my concern.
I demand to know.
I hope I didn't just hear you
say you demand.
Well, are you her father ?
Are you her husband?
Then stay here and keep
your mind on your job.
You hear me ?
Grey.
Look, I need to be
upstairs, so
do not let this
out of your sight.
Walk this to the lab,
watch the lab run the test,
bring the test results
directly to me, nobody else.
It's Izzie.
What's the matter ?
You will be discreet
and not ask a bunch of questions.
Now this is a private matter.
She needs these results now.
Okay.
Wow. That's a big needle.
It's standard.
You should start to feel numb about ten
minutes after I inject the lidocaine, okay ?
Yeah. No, I know. I've given epidurals
before. I know that's the needle.
It's just that somehow
it seems so much bigger
now that it's going
into my spine.
Little stick.
Oh, my God.
You sure I can't call someone ?
One of your friends? You're gonna
need somebody to hold your hand.
No.
Thank you.
You sure ?
Yeah, well, I can take
a lot of pressure, just...
it's rough as sandpaper.
A little pressure.
Meredith...
tell me where she is.
- I can't. If she wanted you to know, George
- She does. She just...
We're just having
one of our stupid fights.
Do you know how wrong it is if she's
really in trouble and I'm not there
because we're being idiots ?
Come on.
Meredith, please.
She's upstairs
in procedure room "A."
- That's all I know.
- Thank you.
So...
Dr. Montgomery says you can
take your daughter home.
But she wants to talk to
her local O.B.-G.Y.N.
There are some things
she wants to go over
before we release her.
I can't.
Okay. Well,
I can go through all this
with your husband if...
No, you don't understand.
I can't take her home.
That girl is not my daughter.
She does look an
awful lot like Shannon.
Sometimes she even
sounds like her.
You know, with the surgery
and, the loss of memories...
a mother knows
her own child, dr. Karev,
and that is not my child.
- But your husband, he's...
- Look,
if that's not Shannon, we still
don't know where our girl is.
Do you understand ?
He needs it to be her.
How am i supposed to tell him ?
How do I tell either of them ?
- Mrs. Waring...
- dr. Karev...
would you ask my husband
to meet me in the lobby ?
- You need to face her.
- Please... tell her I'm sorry.
Things have changed.
No, no. Nothing has changed.
I deserve your support, Richard.
Tell me I have it.
Tell me I didn't move
to Seattle for nothing.
You moved to Seattle
to start a new life,
and you did.
You have a fantastic woman
who loves you.
This is not about my personal life.
This is about my career.
Do you know what being chief
will do to your life ?
Why the hell do you think
I'm getting a divorce
or dyeing my hair ?
You can't do it all,
- not if you want to be chief.
- You couldn't do it all.
- And neither can you.
- Don't put your mistake on me.
Don't. I am the best
candidate for this job.
You know it, and I know it,
and that is the only factor
you need to take into
consideration here. I don't
need your protection, Richard,
and I don't want it.
I'm not trying
to protect you, Derek.
I told Ellis...
I promised her
that I would look after her daughter.
O'Malley, did Stevens
ask for you here ?
No! No, I did not.
- Then you need to turn yourself around.
- You're giving bone marrow ?
This is a private matter.
I'm not leaving.
- George.
- No.
Make me.
- Hey !
- Sorry, I'm starting now.
- Just...
let me know when you're
gonna do stuff, okay ?
you're okay.
I got it here.
Fine. Stevens, I'm going.
Unless you need me
to call security.
I'll manage.
Thank you.
You said back off.
You didn't tell me you were having
a hole drilled in your damn hip.
For who ?
What's this private matter ?
Okay, I'm going in
when you're ready.
Ready ?
Hey, Callie.
Hey.
so if you could
just take these two,
- then that'll free me up...
- Oh, no, no, no, no.
No, I'm not here to work.
I'm... I'm... I'm, uh,
I'm... I'm sorry.
I haven't slept in like two days,
and, uh, I'm actually
looking for George.
We're supposed to meet up for coffee.
- Oh.
- So...
he's, with Izzie, I think.
So if you're not here to work,
I'm just gonna take these back. Thanks.
15-blade.
Suction, please.
Dr. Burke, you're not using
the superior transseptal approach
for the atriotomy, are you ?
Is that a problem?
Not at all unless
your intention is to kill the patient.
Dr. Marlowe, from what I've read...
Yes, well, reading about
a procedure is one thing and, uh,
performing it is quite another.
It was my mistake. I should never
have allowed you to scrub in.
I think it best
from this point on
that you simply observe.
Suction, please.
Hurry up.
You should use the wheelchair.
You're gonna be sore.
I'm aware.
I'm fine now. Thank you.
Uh, you mean
pantless but fine ?
Crap.
stand.
- I got it.
- Okay.
Hannah... an 11 year old girl.
That's the private matter. She's mine.
Don't...
don't look at me.
My mother wanted me to keep her.
But I knew even at 16...
I knew that baby deserved better
than life... at a chehalis trailer park.
And now she's here
and she might be dying
and she doesn't want to meet me.
Oh, crap.
I didn't think I really cared
until she said no.
How about that ?
I can say hail mary's until...
until I turn into mary,
but I still miss you.
Not the...
the sex.
It was not tragic, George.
But I'll live without it.
I won't make it
if you can't be my friend.
If we can't...
What you did today...
You should be proud.
I'll get an orderly
to take you downstairs.
But I have to go.
You understand ?
Some surgery.
- And Colin was a compl...
- Brilliant.
He's a gifted surgeon.
Listen, I had a question.
When you moved the atrium to
the vena cava, why did you switch
from 3-0 to 5-0 sutures ?
You want to use the finest sutures
you can for vascular structures.
A delicate
tissue demands a delicate touch.
Right.
That makes sense.
Thank you.
Of course.
- I'll see you at home ?
- Yeah.
- How long have you been standing there ?
- Long enough.
We've been playing our
little game all day long.
But what I just saw...
that was real.
The question you asked him
about the sutures,
that was from my paper,
the paper you helped me write.
You already knew the answer.
The Cristina Yang I knew...
was concerned with excellence.
She would never play the
part of the helpless girl trying to
build up a grown man's ego.
What has become of you ?
I have learned that sometimes
you have to think about
other people.
- You've compromised yourself.
- No.
I'm going home.
You're right.
It's senseless,
coming here, chasing after a job
that was beneath me
just so I could be near
a woman who...
a woman who apparently
no longer exists.
Best of luck...
with the wedding.
No, there they are.
I can't.
You look.
- Please. You look for me.
- Okay
She's getting the infusion.
You did it.
Is she, um...
How does she look ?
You can... You can see for yourself.
It's okay.
She can't see us from here.
She's got your eyes...
and your mouth.
that means she probably
talks a lot and eats a lot then.
If she's in pain,
she's not letting on.
Man, she's tough.
That's her, George.
That's Hannah.
She's beautiful, don't you think ?
She's really... beautiful.
Yeah.
Yeah, she's a heartbreaker.
You need some help with that ?
I know you didn't just wander in here
to help me change pillowcases.
You warned me she could
become a problem.
Who, meredith ?
You love somebody,
You think you can handle it all.
You've done all right.
Both of you
I came out here
to be chief,
and Meredith
complicates that.
Well, if this turns into an either/or,
you pick the person you love,
end of story.
Look, all of this means
nothing if you're alone.
oh, Crap !
Our coffee. I'm... I'm sorry.
I've... I forgot. I got...
- I got so busy...
- Oh, yeah ? With what ?
Oh, j... the clinic, patients and...
Well, you know how it is.
Oh, man.
Yeah, I know how it is, so...
I'm really tired. I'm really, really tired.
So I'll just... I'll see you at home.
Okay.
Okay, okay.
Solitaire.
My dad taught me.
That sounds so weird.
"My dad."
Good weird, though.
So you and the redhead
gonna let me go home ?
Or were you too busy making eyes
at each other to even ask ?
What?
- Ava...
- No.
It's Shannon.
- Listen...
- My name is Shannon. Shannon Marie.
I'm sorry.
Those are supposed
to be my people.
I belong with them, Alex.
I'm supposed to go
with them.
Your people, we... We don't
even know who they are yet.
You don't want to find them.
You want to keep me all to yourself.
Well, here I am,
your pathetic
captive audience.
Isn't it sad that I'm
the best you can do ?
- Ava...
- My name is not Ava!
You made it up !
It's not me !
Get out!
Get out !
Some people believe
that without history,
our lives amount to nothing.
Sloan,
you brought me to a bar.
- You know I don't drink.
- Which is perfect.
Better to keep your mind sharp.
Let the ladies do the drinking.
You think if you get me laid,
I might make you chief.
At some point,
we all have to choose.
Do we fall back
on what we know ?
I hear dr. Marlowe
is going home.
About time.
The fingernails,
the hand holding,
well played.
Now you can get back
to being Cristina.
Or do we step forward
to something new ?
It's hard not to be
haunted by our past.
our history is what shapes us,
what guides us.
Seriously ?
Okay.
That stops right now.
It's just, I'm... I'm waiting
for Derek, and I'm very tired.
I don't care.
Let me in.
- Excuse me ?
- It's freezing out here, and I have
been working myself up
to saying this,
well, for a while now, so I need you
to let me in now, please.
It's my fault your father
didn't fight harder for you.
I knew about you.
I could've pushed him to be a part
of your life. I should've pushed him.
You were a child.
We were the adults.
But we were just married,
and it was new and...
that's what I cared about.
And I know the groceries
and everything are a little much,
but that's just what I do.
I mean, quit looking at me
like I'm crazy
'cause that's not fair.
I'm just trying to find a way
to be there for you
the only way that I know how,
and if you can't accept that, fine.
But just stop being so rude.
And I...
Okay.
I'm overstepping again, aren't I ?
As mothers go,
I've only ever known
overbearing,
never overprotective.
This is all new.
It's okay.
It is ?
Yes.
Our history resurfaces
time after time after time.
Not just surgery,
but chief of surgery.
Really ?
Oh, well, not for much longer, really.
I'm gonna go...
over there.
Hold down the fort, chief.
So, um, you come here often ?
Sometimes. It's on my way
home from bio class.
Excuse me.
- Is this seat taken ?
- No.
- It was, it was nice talking to you.
- You, too.
the last time I tried
to pick up a woman,
I had a harvey wallbanger
in one hand
- and an afro pick in the other.
- Oh Richard
Well, you think about it.
I mean, when you're married,
you'd like to think you still have game.
Practice on me.
I'm sorry ?
Mark's right. I mean,
he's wrong about
so many things, but
he is right about this.
You need to get back out there. So...
Practice.
Oh, Addison, I wouldn't know
where to start.
Ask me to dance.
Well, there's...
There's no dance floor.
So ? Ask me anyway.
So we have to remember...
Sometimes the most important history
is the history we're making today.
Transcript : Raceman
Synchro : ChipounetteF et Mickeyte
www.forom.com
http ://experts.heberg-forum.net/