Previously on Grey's Anatomy:
This is Mary. She
lost consciousness.
How's Shane? My partner?
I didn't want her to see.
She might take offense.
- Can you get my wife?
- Baby?
You're gonna
drill into my skull?
The navigational system is dead?
Damn it, Stan! Stan. Stan.
Can I watch the surgery?
Can you sneak me in?
You're busted.
Gonna tell him. Don't want
him seeing other people.
- What?
- Nothing. I'm gonna be late.
We need to talk.
- My wife gets panicky.
- I will keep her updated.
You seeing anyone?
At the end of the day,
the experience of
practicing medicine
bears little resemblance
to the dream.
♪ Got no need for
the fancy things ♪
Hey. Are you... Are
you... Are you really OK?
Yeah. Yeah.
Alex. Come on. That was intense.
Intense and crazy
and just awful.
How can you be OK
after a day like that?
We go into medicine
because we want to save lives.
You did a good job
today. That was not easy.
What you did was
not easy. It was brave.
We go into medicine
because we want to do good.
♪ Me, I'm a taker Know
what the stakes are ♪
♪ Can't roll it back It's
understood Got to play our cards ♪
We go into
medicine for the rush,
for the high, for the ride.
But what we remember,
at the end of most
days, are the losses.
What we lie awake at night
replaying is the pain we caused.
♪ Must hurt real bad Fakin'
what you wish you had ♪
The ills we couldn't cure.
I don't want you to
date other people.
It may not be enough
for you, but I'm trying here.
I don't want you to
date anybody but me.
The lives we ruined...
or failed to save.
Can I get some help?
The end of the day,
the reality is
nothing like we hope.
The reality is, at
the end of the day,
more often than not, turned
inside out and upside down.
Over here!
Meredith, get in there!
We don't have time to lose!
OK! I got the shirt
open. I'm almost there!
Stop! Stop! Stop! Hold still!
OK. OK, that's it. I got
it. It stopped. I got it.
Holy crap. My artery blew.
- Your artery blew.
- I didn't think that'd happen.
Thought it was something
they say might happen
because they have to,
but didn't think it'd happen.
Me neither.
- Their local tech's in Spokane.
- That's five hours away.
Tell them I was in
somebody's brain?
Yes. The tech is
still in Spokane.
You can't just pull the probes
out and go to a full craniotomy?
- No. Why not?
- The probe is in the tumors.
Pulling out without navigation
system could damage brain tissue.
Can't leave the probe
in without swelling.
Good. What's your name?
Two. Steve! Steve Mostow.
- Dr. Steve Mostow. Intern.
- Hi, Steve.
Run to the nurses.
Make an announcement.
We need computer
technicians in OR Three.
- Go fast and scrub in.
- Yes, sir.
- Dr. Shepherd?
- Yes.
I did three semesters in
computer science before nursing.
I don't know what's wrong, but if
it's something reasonably basic, I...
I'd feel better if your
voice wasn't shaking.
Shakes when I'm
nervous. I'm imperfect.
It doesn't mean I can't fix it.
Rose has semesters of
computer science at what school?
- Santa Cruz.
- That's a party school.
Insult my education or want
me to help you save your patient?
Who can beat three semesters
of computer science at
Santa Cruz? Anybody?
- OK. Give it a shot.
- I appreciate the vote
of confidence.
Can you see anything yet?
Uh, I see the diaphragm
moving. Move it up a little more.
- Meredith?
- I'm working on it!
You're not doing
a very good job.
I am doing a damn
fine job. Don't you worry.
Can you... Can
you close his eyes?
- What?
- Stan. Can you close his eyes?
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Stop. Stop right there. I
want to freeze that frame.
Yeah, his pericardium's
full of blood.
That's not good.
That's not good at all.
Oxygen, IV start
kits. Arnie, monitor.
You, pericardiocentesis kit.
His anatomy's all screwed up
because he's hanging upside
down. Get someone from cardio!
I've got Tucker waiting
for me and I'm late.
Do me a favor and take the
patient through to post-op.
- What?
- OK, I wanted to say
- when you took me
off Hahn's service...
- Something's wrong.
- Blood pressure's bottomed out.
- I'll hang it. Here.
- Dr. Bailey!
- O'Malley...
OK. Need you to talk to Tucker.
I need you to ask him to wait.
He's not going to be
inclined to, so ask him nicely.
Can you please go and
ask him nicely to wait?
- Yes, ma'am.
- I won't be long.
Do you see this, Stevens?
Sternum's cleaned out.
Which means we're
almost out of here.
Don't want to watch me work?
It's offensive,
Dr. Sloan. Flat out.
I asked if you wanted to
watch me work. Offensive?
Play dumb? Does that work for
you because of the way you look?
- What are you talking about?
- If you were homely,
you would have lost
your job a long time ago.
The chief needs you
in the ambulance bay.
Paramedic with
cardiac tamponade.
Alrighty then.
Let's go, Stevens.
OK, um...
Nick, can you reach
your call button?
- I think so.
- No, no! Don't move that much!
OK.
Uh... just...
Can you reach your phone?
Without moving very much.
I think so. I got it.
OK. Good. Good, good, good.
OK, dial eight, OK? OK.
- Is that eight?
- OK. OK.
Put it to my ear, OK?
- Nurses Station.
- Hi.
Hi, this is Dr. Grey.
Mr. Hanscomb's
carotid just blew and...
Can you page Dr. Sloan for
me please? And also Dr. Yang?
I'm gonna go ahead and call
this a code blue. Yes. Code blue.
Can you announce
that please? Thank you.
- You can put it down.
- Code blue. That means I'm dead, right?
That's what they call when
people go, like, flatline.
I figure we can use
all the help we can get.
I don't care who it is. I
don't care who it is, Jolene.
I am leaving when I am finished.
If the patient is on fire,
I'm not scrubbing in.
It's Dr. Yang's. Lexie
Grey is paging you 911.
Your intern called a code
blue on a patient who's not.
What? Why would
she call a code if...
Go find out.
You needed me here. That's
why you pulled me off of cardio.
No, I'm fine. Go
kick some intern butt.
- How you doing, Dr. Grey?
- Lexie. I'm OK. Are you OK?
I'm a little freaked
out, if I'm being honest.
Mostly because you look
like Carrie at the prom.
- You're wearing half my blood.
- Why we're hanging more.
- Having trouble getting a vein.
- Why?
Hypovolemic. Is
veins are flaccid.
That's not a nice thing to say.
That's not a nice
thing to say at all.
Ow! Ow!
- Son of a bitch!
- It's OK! It's OK!
- It's OK!
- Stop the bleeding!
- My hand slipped. I got it.
- That can't happen anymore.
- Apply steady, firm pressure.
I called for Sloan. Should
we take him to an OR?
No, there's no OR. I
was just down there.
Tyler? You should run and get
more blood. Just in case, OK?
- Apply pressure. I'll get Sloan.
- Leaving?
I'll be right back.
You're doing this.
You seeing this? How I'm
tightening the cable by hand?
Yeah.
- That's my face.
- What?
In the gallery. I built that
face. That's Jane Doe.
The one with the
amnesia. She a surgeon?
- Uh, I don't...
- You are so busted.
Nick Hanscomb's carotid blew.
Karev, irrigate thoroughly,
finish up, pack the wound.
- Leaving?
- Other guy can't survive.
- There's no OR available.
- This one will be.
Get this room turned around ASAP.
I'm bringing down my carotid bleed.
Tucker! Hey.
She's busy, right?
She can't make lunch?
She can make a slightly
later lunch. She's in surgery.
- Always is.
- Taking a little longer.
Always does.
She's having a really bad day.
She's saving the life
of a white supremacist,
which is not a good day.
So she asked me to ask you
if you wouldn't mind
waiting a little while longer.
Please? She did said please.
Which, as you may know, is not
a word she uses that frequently.
She really is sorry. It
shouldn't be much longer.
Fine. Tell Miranda I said don't
keep me waiting long. Please.
OK.
Lucy.
If it's all right, I'll update
Mr. Nolston's family
and meet you in
the ambulance bay.
He's your patient. Keep
the family informed?
Think like a surgeon. You're
thinking like a social worker.
If you want to be a social
worker, save yourself effort
because the training
is two years, not 12.
Want to be a surgeon,
you can update the family
when the crisis has passed.
You're right.
Absolutely. I'm sorry. I...
- Steve.
- Yes, sir?
- Did you bring
anybody with you?
- No.
The nurses made an
announcement. I waited, no one came.
- Rose?
- Damn. Damn it. Damn it.
- I don't have
the steadiest hand.
I need to reconnect wires, and
when you talk to me, it is less steady.
- It's about the wires?
- I think so. I'm pretty sure.
- I'll do it.
- What?
I'll do it. You don't
have steady hands.
- Because I'm nervous.
- Got that.
Let me take care of the wires.
I'm a neurosurgeon.
Steady hands.
You're holding the
leads in the brain.
OK. Steve, how's
your hand? Is it steady?
- Hell, yes, sir.
- Better be,
or you kill my patient. I
need you to hold this very still.
- Yes, sir.
- Very, very still. Good.
Sterile sleeves, gloves,
please. Tell me what I got to do.
- You talked to Tucker?
- Yes.
As long as you're
out soon, he'll wait.
Mother of... The
hepatic vein was injured.
- Can you check
for a new murmur?
- Checking now.
O'Malley, go talk to Tucker.
Just ask him to
wait a little longer.
- I just scrubbed in.
- O'Malley, ask him!
Yes, ma'am.
A person can only rise so high.
I'm rising above, but there's
a ceiling and I'm about to hit it!
Let me guess, air embolus?
We're about to start
the pericardiocentesis,
but with the position of his body, the
blood won't be pooled to the heart...
I'd still use the subxiphoid
rather than the parasternal.
Right. OK. Meredith,
did you hear that?
- Yeah. Is the kit ready yet?
- Getting it ready for you now.
How you doing, Ray?
You've got to be careful
with this technique.
If you aim the
needle incorrectly,
you could nick the very
thin-walled right atrium.
Cause a cardiac rupture.
Rupture, a tension pneumothorax.
There's about six different
ways she could kill him.
- Are they talking about me?
- No. Don't listen to them, Ray.
Dr. Hahn?
Shut up.
Sir, you're gonna be fine.
Stevens, go get me
an 18-gauge needle
before this man's
heart explodes.
Got it.
- How you doing, Karev?
- Yeah, good. I'm fine.
My nose itches.
Itches like crazy.
That's the anxiety. Can't
scratch it, so it itches.
- Whoa! What did you do?
- I was irrigating.
I need more suction.
Coming from the
side of his chest.
I think his heart's
starting to bleed.
Hang a unit of blood!
Page Hahn and Sloan now!
Right away.
Tyler, could you get
me more gauze, please?
Why do you need more
gauze? 'Cause I'm bleeding?
- I'm still bleeding?
- We have blood going in, too.
Is it going in as
fast as it's going out?
I'm asking because I'm starting
to feel, like, queasy. And weak.
Maybe like a person
who's losing a lot of blood.
OK, I'm transferring
now, Nick. You ready?
Yeah.
Lexie? Should I
be calling people?
Should I be calling my
family or somebody?
I think... I think the
bleeding's stopped.
- How you doing, Nick?
- Dr. Sloan. It's Dr. Sloan.
- I think the bleeding stopped.
- You OK?
- Do I look OK?
- Actually, you do.
- You've got
bleeding under control.
- Why would it stop?
The herald bleed, which
means there's a possibility
- of it bleeding.
- I'm gonna get it closed up.
- There's no OR.
- There will be in ten minutes.
Get a pressure
dressing on this wound.
Get him prepped
straight to OR Three.
Make sure it's cleared
out. Good work, Grey.
Thank you.
Hey.
I'm in love with you now. I've
forgotten entirely about my ex.
- Come on! Are you kidding me?
- What?
I have a patient on
the table... I got to go.
- Erica!
- Page the cardio fellow,
then book an OR. Have it
waiting when they get him free.
Why am I not surprised?
Dr. Bailey is very sorry.
She's very, very sorry.
- I'm out of here.
- She just asked me to ask
if you could wait longer. She's
almost done with the surgery.
It's more complicated than
expected, but is almost done.
Fine, I'll wait. But
you tell her I'm tired
of her choosing everything
over our marriage.
The last time. I'm finished.
Tell her the only reason I'm
staying is to tell her myself.
- What the hell did you do?
- Nothing. I cut the cable.
You cut the cable? Showing
off for your girlfriend?
Any idea how screwed you are?
It's not his fault. I'm
holding this guy's coronary.
- Did somebody page Hahn?
- - What the hell happened?
- Graft blew.
- Damn it!
- If you need me to...
- Need you to stay quiet.
- Get more suction in here.
- Just hold onto that.
O'Malley?
- Your husband is waiting.
- Good.
- He's waiting and...
- Look, I heard you.
Why aren't you scrubbed
in? I could use a hand.
He said something about you
choosing everything over your marriage.
He said that?
- What else did he say?
- I think that was about it.
You think or you know?
He said this was the last
time, and he was finished.
I'm in surgery, O'Malley.
Did you tell him that I'm
trying to save a man's life?
- Yes.
- That I want to be there
with him now, but if I were
to leave, this man would die?
- Tell him that?
- Yeah. Yes.
You need to go back out there
and tell him that I took a vow.
A vow to save lives.
Remember that he also took
a vow. For better or for worse.
You tell him that it's his job,
as a husband, to
understand that.
You tell him that I'm standing
by my vow. For better or worse.
Tell him I'm holding
him to his vow.
You tell him if he's thinking
about leaving right now,
that he might find
himself hurt and wounded
and needing an operation.
He may not get a surgeon who
is as married to her vows as I am.
You tell him that!
- Can I just go do some charts?
- Go!
- It's in.
- It's in?
The wire's in.
- Steve, are you still?
- Yes, sir. Very still.
Stop looking at me
like I killed your patient.
I am not a technician.
- I did my best.
- You didn't.
Yes, I did do my best, damn it!
Calm down. Take a
deep breath and think.
What did you miss?
What are you forgetting?
- You forgot the restart button?
- I forgot to press restart.
Yeah, working. It's working.
It's working. It's working.
Santa Cruz is not
just a party school.
- Dr. Shepherd?
- Yes?
Your sleeves.
This was never my
plan. To die this way.
- You're not dying, Nick.
- - You're going to the OR.
I know. That's what I'm saying.
I think we kind of have
some say. Or at least a feeling.
But I never had that
feeling, so I can't die, right?
I don't feel good. I feel...
- Oh! Nick? Nick?
- Can you squeeze my hand?
- Oh, my God! What happened?
- The blood to his brain...
It looks like he had
a stroke. Let's go.
Let's move him
carefully. Let's go.
You can't cry, Lexie. This
isn't over. You can't cry.
Hey, you need to find the
xiphoid process. You feel it?
- Got it.
- Go two finger breadths
to the left
- of the xiphoid.
- I'm there.
Here.
- Eighteen-gauge.
- Yeah.
- That is a very big needle.
- I know. I'm sorry.
Angle the needle toward
the left shoulder. Don't stab.
Don't hit the ventricle,
don't drop the lung.
That wouldn't
help matters either.
I changed my mind. I want out.
This is gonna help you, Ray.
I'm gonna go on three, OK?
- One, two...
- No, wait.
Tell Stan's wife I'm sorry.
Tell Sara I'm sorry about Stan.
Tell her yourself. One, two...
Wait. Wait.
We're running out of time.
- Just wait.
- OK.
- What's taking so long?
- He's not ready.
I'm trying not to be scared.
I don't want to die scared.
- I want to not be scared.
- Ray, listen to me.
It's good to be scared.
It means you still
have something to lose.
Yeah? Are you scared?
All the time.
OK. That's good.
OK, I'm ready.
But don't count. Just do
it. Do it so I don't know it's...
The infection went to his heart.
His hack of a surgeon
didn't check grafts.
Should've caught it.
Should've checked. I missed.
Damn it, how did I miss
it? Stupid, stupid, stupid.
- That's fascinating.
- What?
You're as unkind to yourself
as you are to everyone.
Sloan.
Dr. Sloan, his artery blew and he
appears to be having a left-sided CVA.
- Where is he?
- You told me bring him here.
- Hahn, you close?
- No.
Yang, get him to a sterile
procedure room. Run!
- Let's go.
- I can help. What do you want me to do?
Anesthesiologist,
nurse, equipment.
I'm on it. Stay with Hahn.
This man has four children.
He has four children.
I feel like I'm
going in too far.
Pull back! Pull back!
- Pull back! Pull back!
- Chief, what am I doing?
Too far in. There's some ST
elevation. Try angling more forward.
I got it! I got it! Ray?
That feels good. I can breathe.
He's almost stable!
Get ready to cut him out!
All right. All right.
We're gonna get you out of here.
We're getting you out right now.
- You're bleeding.
- It's Ray's blood.
I can see that.
It could use a
couple of stitches.
But you stayed calm and focused
and efficient in a
very stressful situation.
That's impressive.
I was scared.
You did it anyway.
Like I said, impressive.
Do not tell me that
there isn't an OR.
This is for the chief. A
paramedic's life is on the line.
- You need to find one now.
- I'll see where we are.
Dr. Stevens? Thank
God. How is he?
I... I believe he's
still in surgery.
- But I don't know.
- You don't know?
Why don't you...?
You said that you were
gonna keep me informed...
I'm sorry. I'm on another case,
but I was gonna check back...
- You're on another case?
- I'm sorry.
I have four kids. Four
terrified children who think that
their dad's gonna die.
Did you have instructors
who didn't teach you
how to be a doctor,
or bad parents who didn't teach
you how to be a decent human?
- OR Two is clearing out now.
- Thank you.
My husband, Jacob Nolston,
went into surgery hours ago.
Please find someone who
can tell me if he's dead or alive?
- She said that?
- If you could wait
a few more minutes,
you guys can talk to each other.
Because things
get lost in translation
because this is clearly
not a way to have what is
a very, very important
conversation.
It's clearly not very important.
Our marriage is falling
apart and she sends you.
Tucker. She's in surgery.
She's literally saving a life
and she's gonna be here soon.
She's always
saving a person's life.
She'll always be here soon.
You go ask her, when
exactly is soon gonna come?
Excuse me. You're... You're
the one who came to get me.
- Who told me about Stan.
- Yes.
- Is Ray...?
- He's in surgery.
OK. I have to go.
I have to get out of here, so...
Look, can you tell
him that I'm sorry?
I can't stay here? I just can't
come back here right now?
Ray wanted me to tell
you that he's sorry too.
He's sorry he
couldn't save Stan.
He wanted me to tell you
that in case he didn't make it.
- Think he's not gonna make it?
- I hope he makes it.
But you won't be here, so...
My husband is dead.
He's dead. Somewhere
in this hospital.
How am I supposed to stay here?
♪ Her heart in her throat ♪
I don't know.
But I know that if Ray makes it,
he's gonna wake up and
he's gonna have no one.
And you're gonna go home
and you're gonna have...
No one.
I think it's better to have
someone. Even if it hurts.
Even if it's the most
painful thing you have to do.
Even if it's the most painful
thing you've ever had to do.
I think it's better
to have someone.
See this skin, O'Malley?
It looks a little jagged.
Does it look jagged to
you? Because if it is, jagged,
I'm going to have to
reposition the incision
so that it approximates
more correctly.
If I do that, this
man's swastika tattoo
might be unrecognizable.
- Yeah, it's a little jagged.
- I thought so too.
- He left, right?
- Yes, he left.
Ten-blade.
More lap pads. Pack
them all around the heart.
♪ Take this moment It is safe ♪
Suction.
♪ It's true pure and beautiful ♪
Come on, Ray. Fight.
You will not die.
♪ Eyes wide and heart warm ♪
Don't do this, Mary.
Come on, don't do this.
I need more light.
Can I get more light?
Come on!
- He's coding.
- Come on.
Live, please live. Please.
Please live.
He looks bad. He
looks really bad.
His heart was severely damaged.
And his lungs were compromised.
But he's young and strong
and our hope is that he'll be fine.
Ray?
I'm here.
Well, your liver had more
damage than we saw on the CT
and then we found a
perforation in your bowel.
But we took care of it all, and
you should have a full recovery.
Not a full recovery.
Dr. Bail... She did
this on purpose, right?
I don't understand. You
have a black partner, right?
- Yeah.
- Mary?
Yeah. Do you know how she is?
Are you two are friends?
Look, I'm not the devil, OK?
I'm just a guy with
a belief system.
Mary's a nice girl.
We save lives together.
That's a good time.
If she wanted to marry my
brother, I'd have a problem with that.
But so would a lot of people.
I'm not that much different than
most of the people you know.
Well, Dr. Bailey did
save your life today.
A black woman saved your
life at a great personal cost.
Next time you're looking at
your tattoo and you're thinking
how much better white guys are
than everyone, think about that.
Because between you and me?
If I had been alone in that OR,
you'd probably
be dead right now.
And, since we're
sharing belief systems,
I believe if you were dead, the
world would be a better place.
How's he doing?
He's OK. Surgery
was pretty hairy.
He blew a graft
when we were closing.
- But he's starting to rally.
- Good. That's good.
- What are you doing here?
- I was just checking...
We did fine without
your help. Do you mind?
You're not heading home?
Just easier, at this point, to
stay here until Tucker's asleep.
You know, I rose
above too today.
- Yes, you did.
- You were having a hard day.
You were busy rising
above. But so was I.
Which is why I
haven't said anything.
But now the day is
over and I'm done.
- Excuse me?
- Pulling me off
of Hahn's surgery
was an abuse of power. You
know, you needed help, OK.
But you used me. Because
of the color of my skin.
I mean, you compromised
the quality of my education
because of my
color. I resent it.
You saved her life.
No, I fixed her brain.
Restored motor skills.
A stressful, extremely
difficult procedure, but no.
You saved her life.
OK.
Thanks. That was...
- Your voice is shaking.
- I'm an imperfect person.
Are his parents coming?
They're on a plane from
California. You gonna wait?
Yeah. I'm gonna wait.
- Hey.
- I don't want you
to date other people.
It may not be enough
for you, but I'm trying here.
So I don't want you to date
anybody but me. That's it.
Except... I'm scared
as hell to want you.
But here I am
wanting you anyway.
And fear means I have
something to lose, right?
And I don't want to lose you.
- Meredith.
- Don't. Don't say anything.
I'm gonna leave and you
can say something tomorrow.
That's progress, right?
Hey. Hey. Hey. Are
you...? Are you really OK?
Yeah. Yeah.
Alex. Come on. That was intense.
Intense and crazy
and just awful.
How can you be OK
after a day like that?
Alex. Alex. Why
won't you talk to me?
What do you want to
talk about, Rebecca?
How a guy almost bled
out while I watched?
How I got suspended
because you were there?
Ava. It's Ava. Not Rebecca.
Right. You're playing dress up.
You're here playing dress up.
You have a husband, Rebecca.
You have a baby.
And I have a life.
That girl you were talking to
when playing med student?
I'm screwing her. She might
be a bigger wreck than I am,
but she's not married. She's
not gonna get me suspended.
She's not pretending to
be somebody she's not.
- Alex...
- Ask yourself
what you're doing here.
Because, I think if
you can get honest,
if you could just tell the
damn truth for one minute,
I think you have to admit
you're not here to talk.
You did a good job today.
That was not easy. What
you did was not easy.
It was brave.
We killed him.
The hospital...
Sloan, us...
We were not prepared.
Yeah.
Yeah, that happens sometimes.
That's...
Do you have any idea
how backwards that is?
We help more than we hurt.
I have no one.
This is gonna sound bizarre.
I realize, at this point, that
this is gonna sound bizarre,
but any chance you people
want to get a drink with me?
Why would we want to do that?
She's saying she needs a friend.
- OK. Fine. Let's drink.
- You won't hit on me?
- I can't promise that.
- If I say please?
He still can't promise that.
Fine.
Hey. I brought supplies.
♪ That's it I'm all better now ♪
Some days, the world
seems upside down.
She's got no one.
♪ And I feel light
as a feather now ♪
♪ At last I finally
know my worth ♪
I'm drinking.
Are you drinking, Lexie?
Yeah. A drink would be good.
♪ Turn the ringer
off the phone ♪
♪ Light my orange
candles at night ♪
♪ And I'm wishing
on a new moon ♪
- Hey.
- I was Hahn's right hand today.
That's good,
right? That's great.
♪ I feel it coming ♪
I think a patient feels better
if they know their
kids aren't terrified.
They're more likely
to pull through surgery
if their wives are not
panicked. Those things matter.
Well, they do matter.
♪ I close my eyes ♪
I'm never gonna be Cristina.
Not gonna happen. I'm
never gonna be Erica Hahn.
I am not kick-ass.
Thank God for that.
♪ But somewhere in
the air I'll learn to fly ♪
♪ And I'm wishing
on a new moon ♪
I love you.
We're not gonna
make this work, are we?
♪ I feel it coming ♪
Marriage is hard. I
mean, even when it's right.
It's hard.
♪ I feel it coming ♪
And... the next time I do it,
I just want it to be forever.
And I don't think
it's our chemistry.
I think it's our timing.
But I don't think
it's our chemistry.
So we're saying maybe someday?
♪ It's so easy to complain
but it'll make you insane ♪
♪ That same routine ♪
Yeah. Yeah, we're
saying maybe someday.
♪ But the grass
is oh, so green ♪
♪ After winter rain ♪
♪ And I feel it coming ♪
♪ I feel it coming ♪
♪ I feel it coming now ♪
Come on, Izzie.
Dance party.
You want to dance?
I will if you want me to.
And then, somehow, improbably
and when you least expect it,
the world rights itself again.