Come on.
Come on, come on...
Ow! Damn it.
Any first year med student knows
that an increased heart
rate is a sign of trouble.
- All day of this.
- Stuck with Stevens.
Why are we in a clinic?
I thought we're
supposed to be surgeons.
Not today we're not. Today's
gonna be about flu shots.
- And enemas.
- What a colossal waste of time.
Morning.
A racing heart could
indicate anything...
from a panic disorder...
- Oh, God! Sorry!
- No, I'm sorry.
I... No, I didn't
even look, I'm sorry.
Where...? No, no.
I'll leave. I'll leave.
No. Sleep. You've
been here all night.
Uh... How did you know
I've been here all night?
To something much...
I just knew.
Much more serious.
♪ You got me stuck to you ♪
You should wear
your hair up more.
Shows off the back of your neck.
I like the back of your neck.
♪ If you a case I be a jury ♪
♪ If you a sin I be your mercy ♪
♪ If you the beat
I be the moves ♪
A heart that flutters...
or one that skips a beat...
Hey. I thought
you were sleeping.
- Hunt was in the on-call room.
- You had dirty sex with Hunt?
No. It's not dirty
and it's not sex. It's...
- I don't know what it is.
- Could be sign - of secret affliction.
- Hey, how's it going?
- Oh, my God. Thank you for asking.
It's great. I mean,
he's fun and funny.
Even with no sex
allowed, we just laugh.
- We talk...
- I don't want to hear this.
Come on! But you have to!
You're the only one who knows.
I'm terrible at keeping
secrets. It makes me sick.
Alone people don't like to
hear about together people.
Even if alone people are
alone by choice. It's mean.
It's like bringing a six
pack to an AA meeting.
Keep it to yourself.
I am.
I need a favor. My
mother's ninth journal.
- I need you to pre-read it.
- Why?
She had an affair
with the chief.
Your mother had an affair
with her chief resident?
- Rock on, Ellis.
- No, no, no. Not her chief.
Our chief.
Yeah, you'll go
blind reading that.
Or it could indicate romance...
which is the
biggest trouble of all.
- Whoa. What is that?
- What you think it is.
Dangerous. People who
carry guns are likely to fire.
I'm ready to fire it. She's the
problem. She spooks easy.
I have to fire at the right
time, in the right way,
or she'll panic and bolt.
She's not ready.
Think she's ready?
I don't know. More importantly,
if you don't know,
don't do anything.
- Dr. Sloan.
- Dr. Hunt.
Let's make this quick.
- So we're good to go?
- Yep. Use it wisely.
- Hey. I'm with you today.
- What's going on
- with you and Mark?
- What? Nothing.
Why? What did
you think is... was?
You've been on his
service for over a week.
Yeah, I'm really
interested in Plastics.
As a specialty. Fascinated.
- I like faces.
- Mmm-hmm.
Vehicular blunt trauma,
right shoulder
stabilized in the field.
- Somebody help us! Please!
- Jen, slow down. We're here.
Can you help my husband?
I ran him over with the car!
Sweetie, sweetie.
You have to calm down.
- I'm gonna be fine.
- OK. I'm calm.
- I'm calm. I'm calm.
- All right.
Oh, my God. That's my
stupid pregnant brain!
I left the car in drive.
Baby, I'm so sorry.
- It's a normal neuro exam.
- He's got an inferior
shoulder dislocation and
fractures. You'll need surgery.
Sloan will débride
burns in surgery.
Surgery? Oh, baby!
- Her BP is 170 over 100.
- Give her five of hydralazine.
- Calm down. How's the baby?
- Kicking.
- Pressing right on my bladder.
- Look on the bright side.
She's not running
you over with a truck.
Hey, you wanted the SUV, right?
Pregnancy-induced hypertension?
Yeah, I have to get
her BP down before
- it affects the baby.
- Nice couple.
- They'll have cute kids.
- Not as cute as ours, but cute.
- What?
- Nothing.
It's been three days.
Three days of vacation.
The only days I've taken,
other than my maternity leave.
- I know I'm behind, but...
- Bailey, I get it.
Jackson Prescott
was not an easy case.
Frankly, sir, I would rather not
work on another dying kid again.
But no need to worry.
I will catch up and I...
I'm not worrying.
I'm promoting you.
I need another attending
in General Surgery.
I'm submitting to the
board that it be you.
And that it starts this July.
The minute you've
completed your residency.
I know there was
some talk a while back
about you getting tired of
appies and gall bladders...
A full roster of appies and
gall bladders sounds perfect.
All right. But not
today, though.
Dixon's requested
you on her service.
This is subject to
board approval, Bailey,
though I'm not worried.
You have less to say now, huh?
Get out of here.
Dr. Dixon is not
big on eye contact,
so don't be surprised if
she doesn't look at you.
Also, try to avoid
physical contact,
loud or disruptive noises.
- She's OK? She's a good doctor?
- She's amazing.
You couldn't ask
for a better surgeon.
I'm telling you so
you'll be prepared.
Dr. Dixon, Dr. Bailey, this
is Dan and Lisa Pollock.
I need to see the patient.
Where's the patient?
Hi.
Stacy Pollock, age nine.
She's suffering from pulmonary
hypertension due to a VSD.
Her EKG also shows a left
ventricular hypertrophy, also...
- Hi. Can I help you folks?
- Not him.
- What's the trouble?
- Not him either.
Thank you. We'll wait.
What about him? Hello.
Could you help us, please?
- We need to talk to a grownup.
- This is the chief of surgery.
Just hold on. That doesn't
mean I'm not a doctor.
How can we help?
- My husband...
- Our children went to college.
One's at Stanford,
the other at U-Dub.
We tried something...
a new thing.
- Something slipped
and we lost...
- Rachel.
We were reading this
thing in a magazine...
Here.
"Twenty Techniques to
Re-Ignite Your Nights."
We did Number Nine.
- Let's get you in a gown...
- No. He did Number Nine.
We did Number Nine.
I'm not the one
with it stuck in my...
It's him. He's the patient.
Um... Have a seat.
We'll... take care of you.
Uh... I'll stand.
- Taking him now? For surgery?
- It's a good thing.
We'll get his dislocation fixed
so we prevent
problems with circulation.
Her last BP was
still up: 162 over 102.
The OB was worried
about placental blood flow.
Stay with her. Try
to keep her calm.
- OK.
- Cheeseburgers and...
- Painkillers are working.
- Anything else I can get you?
I'm OK. Are you
really taking him now?
Yeah.
Hmm, Cheeseburgers...
Cheeseburgers.
She's more relaxed
when she eats.
- Cheeseburgers calm her down.
- Thanks for the tip.
Stacy has a VSD, which
has gotten worse over time
and created
pulmonary hypertension.
- Does she need surgery?
- Are you OK?
That child looks like she's
gonna die, I am walking out.
I'll perform a transcatheter
closure to repair
the defect in the septum.
That baby doesn't
understand a word she's saying.
Uh, she says we're gonna
fix the part of your heart
that pumps the
blood to your lungs.
A simple patch repair.
Probably something easy to fix.
A midline sternotomy incision
- may be required.
- Now she's making stuff up.
- I like your socks.
- Thanks. They're for soccer.
I'm the best on my team.
Mom says that's bragging.
Dad says it's not,
it's just the truth.
You can't fight who you are.
If you're the best,
you're the best.
When you fix my heart,
how soon will I be able
to play soccer again?
- I missed half
the season already.
- Well, um...
we'll have to see.
Cristina. Did you tell
her about the ring?
Don't want to talk
about your ring.
Good. Don't.
You're not doing a big,
McDreamy thing? She'd hate that.
She built a house of candles.
She built you a
house of candles.
- You like that sort of thing.
- OK, thanks.
How is it? The journal? Is
it gross? Are they naked?
No, not yet. It's kind of, um...
hot, actually. But,
like, chastely hot.
It's all stolen glances
and loaded exchanges.
The thing reads like a
Victorian romance novel.
Chaste is good.
I'll let you know
when they do it.
She said a thing about babies.
Like babies were a
totally ordinary idea.
- Not afraid. She's ready.
- When are you gonna do it?
- What?
- Shepherd's proposing.
- No kidding! Outstanding!
- Thank you.
- How are you gonna do it?
- I don't know. I just decided.
- Morning.
- Shepherd's proposing.
- Congratulations. Big step.
- Thanks. Telling everybody?
You need advice. Hunt,
you ever proposed?
Uh, I'm not the guy to ask.
When are you gonna do it?
More importantly, how?
What do you use, a twist-drill?
Not if you don't want a
partial-parietal hematoma.
- Hi.
- Good luck.
Don't tell anybody else,
OK? I thought I could trust you.
Of course you can trust me.
We got the short
end of the stick.
Quit laughing! We're
gonna get reamed.
Dudes...
The patient can see you
giggling over here like schoolgirls.
- Enough wise cracks.
- Cracks!
- What's funny?
- Sorry, sir.
These idiots were
screwing around,
and I kind of
got... sucked into it.
Enough.
If you children need a
lesson in professionalism,
then come and see how it's done.
Mr. Kramer, your biplane
abdominal radiographs
show a foreign body. We'll
perform a sigmoidoscopy
and proceed with
manual extraction.
- You'll get it out?
- We'll get it out.
- Hold it.
- That's the third time!
- What's the problem?
- She can't find a vein.
And she's pokin' me
like I'm her needlepoint.
What is wrong with you people?
Didn't you practice this
on each other? Look...
All right. When you have a
good vein, it should feel bouncy,
like this one, OK? You go in
at an angle, not at 90 degrees.
Yeah. Yeah, like that.
Good.
Next time she'll do it on you.
You know, why don't
you run them both.
Listen up, you guys.
Before you run any more
procedures, come see me first.
So, clean bill of
health from Hunt?
Gonna get back on the horse?
I wouldn't use the word "horse."
That's not gonna work out.
Things changed. I'm
gonna break up with her.
You're what? What
is wrong with you?
I had to make sure the
patient's wife is stable.
She's hypertensive.
I think this surgery's more
stressful on her than him.
Damn it. There's a huge tear.
Clavicle jutting into
the artery. Hold this.
I'll hold pressure.
Page Hunt. Get him in!
No, they can't.
Patient's unstable.
Subclavian's bleeding
out. It doesn't look good.
OK, thanks.
What'd they say? Did
they say it's going well?
It's taking... a little
longer than expected.
OK...
But don't worry,
because it's going great.
- It is? Are you sure?
- Yes.
You know, it's good
when they take their time.
Right now, there is
no reason to believe
that he's not gonna be...
- just fine.
- OK.
Oh, thank you.
Hey, your pressure's way down.
Jen?
Jen!
- What's happening?
- Tamponading.
Her BP crashed, she
has muffled heart sounds.
Damn it. Gloves. Yang,
Betadine and give her local.
Stacy, sweetie, you're
gonna be all right, OK?
Don't worry. 18-gauge.
- What are you doing?
- Lisa, turn around or leave.
You're not gonna
wanna watch this.
Keep the ultrasound
over the effusion.
Stacy, honey, you're
gonna feel a little pinch
and then a lot of pressure.
And then you're gonna be
all better, OK? Here we go.
Good. Oh, good job, Stacy.
There. See? It's
all better. Good job.
Good job, honey. All better.
Her pulmonary pressures are
high. She's got cor pulmonale.
I'm moving up her surgery.
Yang's getting an OR now.
See you in there.
Let me know how it goes.
Great save, Dr. Bailey.
I think you better stay.
I'm not scrubbing
in on this one.
Bailey.
- You can handle this surgery.
- I can.
What I can't handle is feeling
another child slipping away,
- right in front of me.
- Mostly, they don't slip away.
Even the really sick ones.
Jackson was a special case.
- Even he survived.
- By the skin of his teeth.
But he survived.
Children are resilient.
In all likelihood,
you'll open this girl's chest
and fix something simple.
Then you'll hand her
back the rest of her life.
I'm telling you, Bailey, you
want to be there for that.
Come on, come on,
come on, stabilize.
BP's going up. Going up.
- Thank you.
- He should be good to go.
- Dr. Grey? Jen Harmon...
- Tell Jen he's stable.
She's not. She had a seizure.
- A seizure?
- We got him, Grey. Go help her.
OK.
- You're an idiot.
- Excuse me?
You're an idiot.
What is your problem?
He is proposing to her.
That makes Little
Her his little sister.
And I can't sleep with any more
of his sisters. And she's young.
- And I'm her boss.
- And I'm celibate.
What's that have
to do with anything?
Celibacy's lonely.
Don't spend time
wondering what you
are or who you like
or whether it's right
for you or wrong for you.
Let yourself be happy.
Before you find yourself
alone... and celibate.
Does she really need a
chest x-ray? She's got the flu.
Say that after you've
ruled out pneumonia.
Be quick and efficient,
keep a smile on your face
and make stupid, happy small
talk to keep them distracted
- and not panicky.
- OK. Should I do
small talk now?
No.
Just tell me to lie still
and take a deep breath.
OK. Big breath in,
and then don't move.
So... how are you gonna do it?
You gonna... go big?
Grand, romantic gesture?
I... I don't know yet.
I'm not sure Meredith's
a grand gesture girl.
You want to do
the grand gesture.
It's the opening pitch. It
determines the entire game.
You've gotta go all out.
Your plans should
include flowers,
candles, exotic foods, live
musicians and a rowboat.
Skywriting is not
out of the question.
- Dr. Shepherd.
- Yes.
You gotta...
- Hi.
- What's up?
- I need a neuro consult.
- OK.
- That's big. You better go.
- Thanks, chief. OK.
OK.
- How we doing, Mr. Kramer?
- Oh, fantastic.
They didn't cover this in
the What To Expect books.
They didn't say
"Expect seizures."
That's why we're doing an exam.
- Look down for me.
- OK.
- Oh, what's that?
- Oh, uh, Dr. Grey.
Could you set up an MRI
for Mrs. Harmon, please?
- Did you see...?
- Now.
OK.
- Oh, you saw something.
- No, no.
No, I'm sorry. Can
you keep a secret?
You bet I can.
This is intended for Dr. Grey.
- Supposed to be a surprise.
- Oh, my God, I almost blew it!
When are you gonna
do it? Please do it today.
- Do it here.
- No. I don't know.
I was told it's supposed
to be a grand gesture.
Rob proposed to me
in a supermarket aisle.
He said that was the place
he saw me for the first time.
So I said yes between the
cat food and the tampons.
- Oh! That's romantic.
- It was, actually.
We still have to do the
MRI, OK? Just to be safe.
- OK. Dr. Shepherd?
- Yes.
- Should I be scared?
- No. Should I?
No.
Eisenmenger's complex.
- Can it be repaired?
- Children are resilient.
Nine times out of ten you'll
find something simple to fix.
What is it?
I can repair the VSD,
but this heart is finished.
This is one of the most
diseased hearts I've seen.
ECMO might hold her over, but
without a heart-lung transplant,
she's going to die.
Dr. Bailey? Dr. Bailey?
Dr. Bailey?
It's OK. I can
take care of this.
Her heart is too far gone.
There's far too much
scar tissue to repair.
We've started her
on IV medications,
which she'll need on
a continuous basis.
For how long? How
long does she...?
Until she can
receive a transplant.
- Months?
- Years, possibly.
Years? She'll lay
in a bed for years?
I'm afraid so, yes.
Where's Dr. Bailey gone?
♪ I can feel it coming ♪
♪ I've seen the road ahead ♪
♪ It's simply stunning ♪
♪ And you know I'll
never turn my back ♪
♪ On you ♪
♪ Cuz that's what
souls were born to do ♪
You want to take narrow
slices with the scans,
so you get a more
comprehensive look.
OK.
What do you see?
Uh... I see a crazy person,
taking expensive
tests for no reason.
And I see the chief finding out
and expelling the crazy person.
Then I see joblessness,
homelessness and depression.
It does not look good,
Izzie. It doesn't look good.
Somebody kick
Dr. O'Malley out of the booth.
- Have you seen Bailey?
- No, but I have to talk to you.
Derek is going crazy.
I said something about
having cute babies,
and he's been acting
weird and avoiding me
and dropping conversations.
He wants babies. He's
always wanted babies.
- Aw, he wants babies.
- Maybe not my babies.
No, that's not it.
My babies will have Alzheimer's.
And suicidal tendencies.
And split ends.
- You might have something.
- I don't think you do.
- Who are you?
- I'm Jen.
How are we doing? All set?
If you're gonna do it, do it
soon. She's really freaking out.
Thank you.
They tried Nine? Who does Nine?
Personally, I'm a fan of Five...
Seven, Eight...
Pretty much 12 through 20.
- I would try 15.
- Don't try 15.
♪ We don't fuss We don't fight ♪
♪ Get together when
we're wasting time ♪
I would try 16. Yeah. I've
never done that before.
- You'd try 16?
- Hmm-hmm. I would.
I totally would.
Um, don't do 16 too fast!
You can get hurt. Badly.
- I've heard.
- You know who likes a good 12?
Hmm-hmm.
- You on-call tonight?
- Looks like it. You?
- Hmm-hmm.
- ♪ Rise above ♪
♪ And make a stand ♪
If she misses one dose of
medicine, it would be bad?
- It would be fatal.
- The drug needs to be
administered
- at 3-minute intervals.
- She'll live in a hospital...
No. There's another way.
There's a way she won't have to.
With a diagnosis of
pulmonary hyper...
The girl needs a backpack.
A backpack that has a portable
pump that will deliver her meds
and allow her to play
and go to school
and have a childhood.
Until she gets her new heart.
This is something
we should discuss
- privately...
- She can leave?
She can. She has to wear
the backpack at all times.
Put you in a program,
teach you to
administer medications.
Do you have a prettier one?
- My God, Dr. Bailey. Thank you!
- Dr. Dixon, thank you so much!
- So much!
- Dr. Dixon!
- Thank you!
- No! No, no!
No!
Oh, uh... Dr. Dixon, what
can I do? How can I help?
You can observe protocol.
I was getting to that option...
It was too much. There was too
much yelling, too much touching.
Too much.
OK. I'll leave you alone.
No, no! I don't need
alone. I need pressure.
- I...
- I need my nervous system
suppressed.
I need tight constant, deep,
tight pressure across
large areas of my body.
I need you to hold me!
- OK, um...
- Tight... tightly.
Tighter.
You're a very tiny person.
I need a bigger
person. I need more...
Should I...?
- Oh... What can I do?
- Get over here
and hug on Dr. Dixon.
I was thinking a
shot of Thorazine.
Get over here.
- Just...
- Yeah. Good.
An aneurysm? A brain aneurysm?
Your symptoms,
forgetfulness, dizziness,
chronic headaches, can be
associated with pregnancy.
The reason we discovered yours
- is because of the seizure.
- So, what? You can fix it?
You can take it out?
First thing in the morning
after Rob's recovered from
complications with surgery.
Complications? What?
You said... You said it was
fine. You said he was OK.
You lied to me?
I'm sorry. I didn't
want to worry you
- until I knew. He's fine.
- You'll be fine, too.
- But it could burst, right?
- Jen, you have to stay calm.
You just told me there's
a time bomb in my head!
I promise you that I'm
not gonna stay calm!
Cows are squeezed in a
chute before they're slaughtered.
The chute applies
intense pressure
resulting in
decreased pulse rate,
metabolic rate and muscle tone.
- It calms them down.
♪ This my excavation ♪
The same principles apply to me.
A hugging machine
is used to relax
the sympathetic nervous system.
Slows the heart.
This is good.
This... It's working.
- So we can stop now?
- No.
Almost there, Mr. Kramer.
- Hold on... There.
- Oh, my God!
Oh, thank you! Never again
will I try to spice things up.
- I'm not spicing anything up.
- You tried to step it up.
Anything above
Five deserves props.
Sounds to me like you're
doing good. You're together,
and you're both bending over
backwards to find new ways to...
make each other happy.
Take a step back, you realize
that you're doing just fine.
"Bending over backwards."
♪ When your money's gone ♪
♪ And you're drunk as hell ♪
♪ It's the sound
of the unlocking ♪
♪ And the lift away ♪
♪ Your love will be ♪
♪ Safe with me ♪
You can let me go now.
- You can let me go now.
- Sorry.
Dr. Stevens, I have
the blood test results.
- What is it?
- You're anemic.
Anemic?
Oh, my God!
Do you realize what you did?
Your face said I
was going to die,
- not, "Go get a hamburger."
- Well, see I...
That's part of patient
care, controlling your face.
- I just...
- Anemic.
This is fine. This is no
big deal. It's like nothing!
How's Mrs. What's-her-name?
That's not good, is it?
Yeah. No.
Her LDH is off the charts.
What is it? Is it cancer?
Consult Oncology.
Start a work-up.
Um...
It's OK. We'll
tell her together.
Thank you.
Hi.
- I don't want to keep secrets.
- Sorry?
I've been keeping
secrets all day.
About surgeries
and rings and you.
And that secret, the you secret,
it's giving me high
blood pressure.
I don't want that secret.
We're having... a relationship.
And if we are, if
we're in a relationship,
then I need to be in it,
in front of my sister.
And Derek Shepherd.
If we can't do that,
then I can't do this.
What's going on? What happened?
Sorry. I can't.
You're shaking.
Leave me alone. I saw someone.
Someone I knew. I
can't do this. I can't.
- OK.
- Please, go away.
OK. It's all right.
- It's OK.
- No, I don't want this.
- I don't want this!
- I'm applying pressure.
- I can't do this!
- To relax your nervous system.
Decrease your metabolic rate.
You'll feel more
panicked at first.
You'll try to resist it,
but eventually you'll
feel your pulse rate slow.
Your pulse rate
will slow. It's OK.
Your breath will come easier.
Your breath will
come easier. OK.
Breathe.
OK.
I'm sorry for my outburst.
I should have
spoken to you first.
It was inappropriate,
but I've come to expect it
from pediatric surgeons.
- Always breaking protocol.
- I'm not a pediatric surgeon.
I've landed a few peds
surg cases recently,
but I'm getting back to general
surgery the first chance I get.
You touch the child
whenever you speak with her.
You explain conditions to
the child, not just the parents.
You react to the patient
as if it was your own child.
You break protocol,
which is inappropriate.
Except in pediatric surgery,
where protocols are
constantly evolving.
You are not a general surgeon.
You're a pediatric surgeon.
Hey! Did you eat? Let me
change, I'll come with you.
No, no, no. I can't.
I have to... work.
OK, listen.
You have been acting
like a basket case
since I dropped that stupid
comment about babies.
If you don't want babies
or if you don't
want babies with me
and my crappy DNA, just say so.
You don't have to avoid me
or make up lame
excuses about work.
Meredith, I want
your crappy babies.
- You do?
- All of them.
- OK. Do you wanna eat?
- No. I have... I gotta...
I have to work.
Oh, my God.
- Did you use a BeDazzler?
- Circa 1986.
As seen on TV.
Dixon's right, you know.
You do belong in Peds surgery.
My own baby
almost died last year.
The doctors in this
hospital, my friends,
they all worked
to save his life.
And I stood outside the
room feeling so useless,
so pointless and helpless.
Like I was losing
everything in the world.
And when he didn't die,
I knew I didn't want
to be anywhere near
that feeling again, so...
I think that makes
me pretty unsuitable
for pediatric surgery.
I'd say...
that makes you
uniquely qualified.
♪ Who do you love? ♪
- Hey. You mind if I sit here?
- No, no. I'm just...
overthinking.
You think he'll tell him?
♪ Who do you hunger... ♪
If he's not an idiot.
♪ ...in this great unknown? ♪
- Are you OK?
- Um, uh...
I don't... I'm fine.
♪ Memories of me will fade ♪
♪ And you'll find someone new ♪
- Derek is act...
- Shh...
What are you doing?
I don't know. I'm just...
- staying here.
- OK. Good night.
Uh, he's planning to propose.
- What?
- The chief.
Your mother writes he told
her he would leave Adele.
And come back and get
on one knee and propose,
but I don't think he ever did.
That's sad.
- Is it?
- Or romantic.
It seems we have no
control whatsoever...
over our own hearts.
♪ For you ♪
- Hey.
- Ortho, right?
- Yeah. Right. Hi.
I'm Arizona Robbins.
Peds surgery.
I've seen you at the hospital.
Are you OK?
You know, I'm fine. Fine.
People talk. Where
we work. They talk.
A lot. So for the
sake of being honest,
I think I should tell you
that I know things about you.
Because people talk.
Oh... You mean...
- Terrific.
- It is, actually. The talk.
People really like
you over there.
They respect you and they're
concerned and interested.
They really like you.
Some of them really like you.
You just look upset.
And I thought that you should
know that the talk is good.
And when you're not upset,
when you're over being upset,
there will be people
lining up for you.
You want to give me some names?
Conditions can
change without warning.
I think you'll know.
♪ Coming home
to an empty house ♪
♪ A passing
moment A little mad ♪
Romance can make
the heart pound.
♪ I never want
to say it's love ♪
Just like panic can.
♪ But it's really
what I'm thinking of ♪
This is stupid. She's
gonna hate this.
What, the flowers?
Girls love this crap.
It's a cliché. I'm a cliché.
Clichés became
clichés for a reason.
Because they worked.
It's great, isn't it?
When you feel so
strongly for someone,
and it's not just about the sex.
It is...
It's true.
You should not talk like that.
Yeah. You're right.
You're all set here. I'm
gonna leave you to it.
Thanks.
Congratulations.
And panic...
Addison?
Can make it stop
cold in your chest.
What happened?
♪ My home is home ♪
♪ And I'm settled now ♪
♪ I've made it through
the restless phase ♪
♪ I have no reason to
get bored anymore ♪
♪ My friends are around
and your name comes up ♪
It's no wonder doctors
spend so much time
trying to keep the heart stable.
♪ But it's really
what I'm thinking of ♪
- ♪ I felt the same today ♪
- To keep it slow.
♪ As I was feeling yesterday ♪
Steady.
Regular.
♪ From an only one change ♪
To stop the heart from
pounding out of your chest,
from the dread of
something terrible.
♪ I never wanna say it's love ♪
Or the anticipation...
♪ But it's really
what I'm thinking of ♪
♪ I never wanna say it's love ♪
♪ But it's really
what I'm thinking of ♪
of something else entirely.