Previously on Grey's Anatomy:
You got some problems.
You got some big problems.
I kissed a peds surgeon.
Calliope, this is
Julie. My date.
I'm seeing Lexie.
- Oh, my god,
I think I broke it!
- This is Patient X.
She's a 29-year-old female
we misdiagnosed with anemia.
I'm applying for a
fellowship in Pediatric Sur...
Which is not what
we had discussed!
Where's my wife? You killed her!
You're a murderer.
Every surgeon I
know has a shadow.
A dark cloud of fear and doubt
that follows even the
best of us into the OR.
- Dude, he is fried.
- He is not fried.
He lost a patient and got a lawsuit
all in one week, he just needs time.
He's been there for three days.
The cushions are bonding to his ass.
- And he's eating all my cereal.
- He's taking stock.
Something huge and
life-altering happened to him,
and he's taking stock,
figuring out his next move.
We shouldn't judge and rush him.
Whatever. Sylvia Plath's
picking out the marshmallows.
They're the best part.
I'm pretty sure he's
sitting on my keys.
I'd ask him to move,
but he looks so... comfy.
You guys are cowards.
Hey.
You're eating, that's
good. Appetite is good.
You know what else is good?
Showering. Cleansing. Water.
Are you thinking you'll
shower, go in to the hospital?
I have to for the deposition.
I have to go explain in detail
how I killed a
man's pregnant wife.
That's good. Not
the killing part,
but the... I think you'll
feel better once you...
go to... work.
He'll be fine.
We pretend the
shadow isn't there.
Hoping that if we
save more lives,
master harder techniques,
run faster and farther,
it'll get tired and
give up the chase.
But like they say...
You can't outrun your shadow.
Hey.
Morning.
I dreamt once I was falling out a
window, hanging on to the drapes.
I woke up pulling
Meredith's hair.
Ha.
So we have a trauma coming,
a trampling on a football field.
- I don't need your help.
- I'm on your service today.
I'm telling you, Dr. Yang,
to take care of that elbow.
There you are. What
happened to you?
- I tripped and fell. It's fine.
- No, no, it's not.
It's... It's nothing.
It was an accident.
What's wrong with you?
Derek won't get off the couch.
So the weaker sex.
It's still swollen. I'd
give it another day rest.
- I haven't operated in days.
- Don't hit with
your scalpel hand.
- Have you talked to him?
- He threw the first punch.
- You did catch him
at a bad time.
- So he lost a patient. Boo-hoo.
We're surgeons, we're
men, we lose patients.
Doesn't give him the right to go
around behaving like a drunk frat boy.
Now I'm supposed to go crawling
back, begging for his forgiveness?
- What... What are you doing?
- Shh, shh, shh.
I went Say Anything on the ped
surgeon in front of the ped surgeon's date,
- so I am hiding
from the ped surgeon.
- Mature.
You got in a fist
fight. No judging.
- Hi.
- Hand!
Hand! Oh, God,
I'm sorry. I forgot.
I am so sorry, I feel terrible,
about everything, about the fight,
and your hand, and Derek and...
He's not doing so well, I
think you should talk to him.
- I should talk to him?!
- Mm-hmm.
Look at you, with your stethoscope
around your neck, charting...
I can totally see
you in ten years,
little salt and pepper in
your hair, big shot attending...
You're gonna be
a rockstar, Alex.
- What is this?
- What?
I can't fantasize about my
boyfriend and his bright, bright future?
- Shut up.
- Dr. Stevens?
We've been working on the Patient
X case and we have a couple of ideas.
Great. Let's get to work.
What's this Patient X
that's taking the interns?
When's it gonna be over? I
need minions to do my crap work.
Some new teaching thing.
We're killing
ourselves to get OR.
When is the last time
Izzie held a scalpel?
She's falling behind.
She's like the new O'Malley.
- Izzie's nothing
like O'Malley.
- Hello...
OK, O'Malley,
you're in the clinic,
Grey and Yang, with me.
Karev, you're in the pit with Hunt.
Dr. Bailey, I'm on trauma today.
Save it, Yang. Hunt wants Karev.
Oh! Sir, there you are.
Shepherd planning to
grace us with his presence?
Yes, he's fine.
Sir! I've been trying to
page you all morning.
- I could use help on a case.
- No peds today?
Uh, no.
- Must be slumming.
- Excuse me? Sir...
Tricia Shelley, 31,
Megan Shelley, 27,
Michael Shelley, 23.
Genetic testing revealed
they all carry the CDH1 gene
for hereditary
diffuse gastric cancer.
Which means what, Dr. Grey?
Which means they all have a 3-in-4
chance of developing the cancer.
Dr. Bailey's taken tumors out of
everyone on our mother's side.
Unfortunately, it's a highly aggressive
cancer, the tumors grow quickly,
- by the time I get in...
- Our family's tree's
down to a branch.
How is... Uncle Bud doing?
Dead.
- And Aunt Helen?
- Dead.
- What about
the Minnesota cousin?
- Not dead!
- She's 90 pounds
and in hospice, Meg.
- Still. Not dead yet.
So, uh, you've decided you're
ready to take the next step.
We've made a pact,
we're all in this together.
Cut our stomachs
out, Dr. Bailey.
Beth Dearborn, 17-year-old
with a history of seizures,
had a grand mal during band
performance, started seizing on arrival.
Push two of lorazepam.
She's in v-fib! Charge
the paddles to 200.
The v-fib could be from the seizure.
If she's not in v-fib, she'll flatline.
- You got a pulse?
- I don't think so. It's hard to tell.
- Lorazepam's not working.
- What do we do?
We shock her and save
her or shock her and kill her.
What the hell. Clear!
Clear!
- Sinus tach.
- Good call, Dr. Hunt.
The odds are 50-50 shot.
Oh, no... it happened again?
I'm Dr. Robbins, the pediatric
surgeon on call, this is Dr. Hunt.
You got beat up while marching,
I'm going to check for internal injuries.
I seized during the
performance? But I took my meds...
Relax, it's not like you
crapped your pants.
It is like I crapped my pants. I had
a seizure in front of the entire band.
It is exactly like I crapped my
pants. They're going to kill me.
- Who?
- Seizure patrol.
- You're the seizure patrol?
- I'm first clarinet,
he's drum major.
Whenever Beth has a seizure,
we drop our instruments, roll her on her
side so she doesn't choke on her tongue.
We were in the Northwest Regional
Parade. We were favored to win.
Yeah, until Beth took down
the snare drum, woodwinds...
the tubas tried to avoid
her but she was in formation.
Yeah. Why don't you
go call her parents?
I'm gonna run some tests, but
she's coded once, so watch her,
- standby with a crash cart.
- You want me to baby-sit?
- That's an intern job.
- I don't see
any interns around.
Dr. Grey?
Patient X, a previously
healthy 29-year-old female
presented with stable vital
signs, a normal physical exam,
with symptoms of right upper quadrant
pain, nausea, and hallucinations.
Head CT, chest X-ray,
CBC were normal,
but chemistries revealed
an elevated LDH.
You are this girl's doctor, she comes to
you, scared, doesn't know what's wrong,
you have to diagnose
her. What do you do next?
- What test do you run?
- A retic count
or peripheral smear?
You'd be wasting your time.
The CBC was normal, remember?
You said there was abdominal
pain, what about an upper GI?
Good.
That is exactly what
Patient X's doctor did next.
What does this tell us?
- What is this?
- Side effects
and complications
from prophylactic gastrectomy, so
post-op you know what to expect.
Malnourishment, weakness,
fatigue... dumping syndrome?
- That doesn't sound good.
- Possible anal leakage?!
A gastrectomy isn't like
getting your appendix out.
We're changing the way your digestive
system works, a serious adjustment.
I'm president of my frat, have
a girlfriend, go snowboarding!
How am I supposed to do that when
I'm a weak old man with anal leakage!?
You know how
important this is to Trish.
Trish has run our lives
since we were kids,
she decides where we go to dinner,
vacation, where we do Thanksgiving...
I'm 23. If I don't want to butcher
myself, she can't make me.
So you'd rather die like Mom?
Or Grandpa? Or Uncle Bud?
It's not quick, Mike. It's
a slow, painful way to go.
There's a 1-in-4 shot
we don't get it, right?
- That's something!
- Don't be stupid.
You are doing
this, we discussed...
You're not in charge
of me anymore!
Meg?
I didn't realize it
was such a big deal.
I just... I need a little
time to think about it, OK?
No, Callahan on the
bypass, Levin on the appy.
Damn craniotomy. Where
the hell is Shepherd?!
You can't rely on Shepherd.
Is there anything I can do?
My neurosurgeon has been missing
for days, I have no head of cardio,
general surgeons quitting
on me left and right,
surgeries piling up like
dead fish and no surgeons!
Now would be a
bad time to tell you
my hand's still out of
commission and I can't operate.
Leave me on the board,
chief. I won't let you down.
I could do that craniotomy.
Um...
Put Dr. Nelson
on the craniotomy.
- Appreciate it, John.
- It... It's Jim.
You must be new.
Welcome to Seattle Grace.
I've been here ten years.
I was interim chief of neuro
before Shepherd in his red cape
swooped in from New York.
- Mark Sloan, plastics.
- We've met. Three times.
I don't know why Mr. Bimm
ever let her join band.
- Not like she's
a master flautist...
- OK, get out!
Mr. Bimm said
to stay until her...
I got it! I'm
seizure patrol now.
- Your friends are asses.
- They're not my friends.
Once you spazz out in school,
friends are hard to come by.
You can't help the epilepsy, but
nobody made you join the marching band.
- It's spreading nerd on nerd.
- I like being in the band.
It's the one thing I'm good at.
What'd you do in high school?
- I wrestled.
- You're a wrestler?
- You wearing tights under that?
- It was a long time ago.
That was high school,
I'm a surgeon now.
How would you feel if you seized every
time you went into the operating room?
Yeah, OK.
You realize, as your doctor,
I'm not recommending this, right?
I need to get through
my surgeries today.
You're gonna get through
them, just hurt later.
You heard of a
Dr. Nelson in neuro?
Oh, yeah. Shadow Shepherd.
- Shadow Shepherd?
- Yeah.
He's a solid surgeon,
but sort of the JV player
to Shepherd's varsity.
The B team to Shepherd's A. The
bricklayer to Shepherd's architect.
I get it.
Just 'cause the guy doesn't
publish fancy clinical trials,
or take on flashy surgeries, or have
creepy perfect hair, he's less of a man?
Kinda.
How'd it go with the lawyers?
They told me my death rate.
These are the people I saved.
These are the people I killed.
Most of those were terminal when they
came to you, you were their last chance.
And you take on impossible
cases. Look at the clinical trial.
There's so many people.
More than Dahmer,
Manson and Bundy combined.
You're not looking
at the big picture.
This is the big picture.
Shepherd! Thank God you're back.
- Can you swing
two brain biopsies?
- I'm not operating.
I know you've got a big lawsuit
breathing down your neck,
I know you lost a patient,
but I need you back,
- doing the job
I hired you to do.
- I am not operating.
I'm not asking, I'm
telling as Chief Surgeon,
if you don't get back into
that OR today, Shepherd...
And he just walked out.
Without saying a word.
Hunt won't look at me since he
went all Apocalypse Now this morning.
Had to get scalpel happy in that
patient's brain and can't face it.
He thinks I'm this wilting
flower. I'm the strong one.
- I'm the strong one.
- If I had that
stomach cancer gene?
I'd get that gastrectomy. I
face things, I don't walk away.
Derek walks away. Maybe
walking away is the answer.
It's not emotional, it's science.
Have a problem, don't ignore it.
If you have to pee, and you
ignore it, it does go away.
You guys are hilarious!
Do you even know what she
just said? Or what she just said?
I see you guys in 50
years in a nursing home,
just talking at each other with
your hearing aids off. Hi-larious.
Oh! I love lunch.
What the hell?
Beth?
Code blue!
After I take out the
stomach I'll do what, Yang?
- Sew the esophageal
anastomosis.
- Or the other option is, Grey?
You could staple
the anastomosis.
Now why would I want to do that?
Fistula rates can be
higher when you hand sew.
You might say that using the
old stapler is sort of my specialty.
Thought your specialty was baby-sitting.
I'm sure you'd rather be doing that.
Frankly, sir, I feel like I am.
Excuse me, sir, I think
you should feel this.
Right here.
Tell me that's not
what I think it is.
Wait, I think I got it.
Liver enzymes are normal,
cardiac workup's negative...
- If LDH is a false positive...
- It's a trick question.
- What?
- She's fine. Patient X is fine.
- She's not fine.
- Her SED rate
is slightly elevated.
- Did we check for
autoimmune disease?
- ANA and CRP were negative.
At worst, she's got an anxiety
disorder. The girl is totally fine.
She is not fine!
She had hallucinations.
She had visual, auditory
and tactile hallucinations
about her dead fiancé.
She thought she could
talk to him and touch him.
She is not fine.
You're missing something.
You're not looking in the right place.
Go back, figure out what you're missing.
She has it? Trish has cancer?
The cancer was stage one. We got to it
so early, the gastrectomy was curative.
She had her endoscopy
a few months ago.
It was an aggressive
cancer that grew quickly.
- The fact we took
her stomach today...
- It saved your sister's life.
The reason Trish
decides everything,
Thanksgiving,
dinners, vacations...
She's the only one left who
knows how to cook a turkey, Mike.
She's the only one left
who likes planning vacations,
who ever remembers to
make dinner reservations.
She's in charge of us
because everyone else is dead.
I want it. Now.
I want the surgery right now.
Why is she coding when she
seizes? It doesn't make sense.
Not this young. Her
heart should be fine.
Beth coded before her seizure not
during. I saw her heart go into v-fib.
- She's 17 with
no heart history, Karev.
- I saw it on the monitor.
You think you saw it on the monitor.
Seizures are chaotic. Doctors panic...
I didn't panic. I
know what I saw.
You suggesting
I tell her parents
she's been wrongly
treated for six years?
We should run a cardiac
workup with an EP study.
You want me to deliberately shock a
perfectly healthy heart? Absolutely not!
- Dr. Hunt?
- If right, it'd explain
the coding.
- If he's wrong,
it will kill her!
- I'm not wrong!
Then it's your call, Karev.
Maybe Cristina's right.
Maybe trying to teach
the interns is pointless.
Don't listen to Cristina. She
thinks because you'd rather teach
than take out a gallbladder,
that you're the new me.
- O'Malley the sequel.
- O'Malley 2.0.
You read more journals
and do more research
and log more hours in the skills
lab than any other resident here.
You never give up trying
to be a better doctor.
And you don't step
on other people to do it.
I would be lucky
to be the new you.
You gonna tell me
about Patient X?
- I know what we missed.
- I gotta go, George.
She had enlarged lymph
nodes, but it's not mono.
What if we missed a
malignancy in her brain?
- You ruled that out
with the CT.
- That was a mistake.
I'd like an MRI with contrast,
maybe biopsy a lymph node.
Whatever's wrong,
it's already in her brain.
Yeah.
Clamp's going in.
I don't feel any masses.
2-O vicryl please.
Sir, if I may one more time,
I think stapling would
be a better choice.
Dr. Bailey, you no longer wish
to be a surgeon in this hospital.
So leave the technical
calls up to me.
I was expressing my opinion
what would be best for my patient.
You don't get an opinion! This is
my patient because it's my hospital.
When it's your hospital you
make decisions, but until then,
this is my hospital and I want
all of you people to do what I say!
Yes, sir.
2-O vicryl, please.
You're gonna be OK.
You're in really good hands.
I'm going to ask you
one more time, Karev.
Are you sure about this?
Yeah.
Then you're on crash cart.
If you're wrong...
be ready to use it.
Your path report
came back clear,
there were no cancerous cells in
your stomach. How's your pain?
The wound hurts a
little... not too bad, right?
Yeah.
Don't you remember how much
pain Mom was in at the end?
No.
You used to help me wet
her lips with an ice cube.
It was awful. She
couldn't even drink.
She had so many
tubes everywhere.
I don't remember. I was two
years old when Mom died.
The only reason I know
it was sad and horrible
is because you
tell me all the time.
I don't have nightmares
about funerals.
I don't freak out and think it's cancer
every time I have indigestion. You do.
- Mike...
- This is your fear.
It's not mine.
So just let me decide
when I'm scared.
- Let's take the pace
down to 300.
- Vitals are still stable.
This is pointless. The study is
showing no sign of arrhythmia.
- Wait. She's in v-tach.
- Let's pace her
out of it at 330.
- BP's down to 60 over 10.
- 340. Damn it.
Karev, get in there, now.
Wait, hold the shock.
She's coming out of it.
This could be ARVC. The right
ventricle's causing arrhythmia.
- The brain doesn't get oxygen.
- And she seizes. Oh, my God.
Karev, you just
saved this girl's life.
It's OK. It's OK, just breathe.
Put the paddles
down and breathe.
It's OK... it's OK.
Well, it wasn't easy.
Not only did I push through my hare
lip reconstruction and a tympanoplasty,
but I pulled out a burn graft so
beautiful it could bring a man to tears.
Chief?
You haven't heard from
Shepherd, have you?
No, sir. I haven't.
Sir, I have tried to let it
go, I know it's not personal,
I understand it's
very hard for you,
I understand you're under
a great deal of pressure,
but the way you
yelled at me in the OR,
today, in front of my residents?
Not OK, sir. Not OK at all.
Now you and me, we're going to have
to find a way to work together so you...
Not talking to me now?
Oh! Well...
That's just real mature, sir.
Real mature.
We have a diagnosis.
Go ahead, Dr. Grey.
Patient X. An elevated
LDH was our only clue.
We found out she had enlarged lymph
nodes and a mole, which was biopsied.
Meanwhile, this MRI with contrast
showed a met on her right temporal lobe.
The biopsy revealed
dividing cells.
That, coupled with
further staging tests,
led to our final diagnosis
of metastatic melanoma
with mets to the
liver, skin, and brain.
- Your prognosis?
- With chemo
and radiation...
- a few months.
- At best. The girl's toast.
Survival rate's five percent.
If I were her I'd go on
a really good vacation.
Good job, everybody.
That's it?
- The last contest,
we got a prize.
- What's our prize?
You think every time you hand
someone a death sentence there's a prize?
The prize is, you didn't
screw it up this time.
The prize is, you people
actually did something right.
The prize is, you were doctors today!
You are doctors. That is the prize.
- Adele, what are you
doing here?
- Conference room, Richard. Now.
You too, Miranda. Let's go.
It's a pacemaker. It's gonna
regulate your abnormal arrhythmias,
so you won't have
any more seizures.
So... I'm not sick anymore?
A wrestler fixed me.
Not exactly. You have
a serious heart condition,
we're gonna set you
up with a cardiologist...
But no one has to know. I
won't be frothing at the mouth,
I don't have to wear
a bracelet to school.
- I can cover this with a shirt.
- Yeah. That's something.
It's everything.
Once people see you as sick,
they don't see anything else.
Mr. Bimm just called.
We didn't get a trophy.
There's next season.
Yeah, we were thinking, maybe
you should try out for choir or debate.
Something requiring less movement.
We're just worried for your safety.
You don't have to be. We
fixed her. Epileptic bone.
What?
There's no such thing
as an epileptic bone.
Are you a doctor?
So she's like...
totally normal now?
Dude, none of you are normal.
You're freaking band nerds.
Of all the petty,
ridiculous, infantile...
Are you running a
hospital or a playground?
- Adele, I will not be
spoken to...
- Hospital or playground?!
- Hospital.
- Then start acting like
the chief of a hospital and
apologize to that woman. Right now.
- Sorry.
- You call that an apology!?
Now you better not leave this
room until you work this out.
If I have to drag myself here
through rush hour traffic again
- to police this damn
jungle gym...
- Adele, you've made your point.
And you wipe that smile off
your face. You're no better.
Tattling on a man to his wife.
When you have your stomach
out, you can't eat sugar.
If he's doing this because he doesn't
want to give up damn jelly beans...
- It's more than that.
- Or football
or girls or snowboarding,
whatever, it doesn't matter.
Not compared to the alternative.
We'll be as vigilant as we can.
- Use every screening
tool available.
- That won't be necessary.
Mikey's gonna have the
surgery. Maybe not today,
but I'm gonna be on him like glue,
to my dying breath, until he does.
And if he just wants
to be left alone?
You don't leave the people
you love alone, Dr. Grey.
That idiot may not know it, but my
fear is what's going to save his life.
♪ Hold on ♪
I learned a lot, diagnosing a
patient from beginning to end.
So... thank you for teaching us.
What would you say?
To Patient X. How would
you break the news?
Um...
I would say that
I was very sorry
and that there were
support groups...
I don't know. What do you say
to somebody who's going to...
You say they have a choice.
They can run away
and hide from it,
or they can face it.
You say to be around
people who love them,
it's gonna be the toughest fight of
their life, no one should do it alone.
And then you give them the odds,
and even though a five percent survival
rate is bad, it's really bad, you say...
- You say...
- Screw the odds.
People die of the hiccups.
My mother died of the hiccups.
Survival rate for that
is, what, 100 percent?
The odds are that she
should be alive right now.
The odds are that
the odds mean crap.
So people should face
it and they should fight.
Maybe not those words.
No... exactly those words.
Thank you, Dr. Grey.
How's she doing?
- Uh, she's stable.
- Hmm.
You did a hell of a job.
The chief's gonna hear about it.
Pretty impressive
for a resident.
Fix that attitude, you could
be the future of this hospital,
the one to watch. You go, Karev!
Iz!
Hunt's letting me do the distal
anastomosis on his fem-pop.
- That's awesome.
- It's crazy.
They told me I could be the future
of this hospital, the resident to watch.
I mean, I'm not the
kind of guy who...
I don't rise, OK? I
sink to the bottom.
And now I'm getting
all this... this respect.
And... And you... you gotta stop
wasting your time with this Patient X crap.
- Alex...
- I know you like teaching,
but you need to start treating
real patients with real surgeries
because once they see you
as weak, it's over, and Iz...
you could be a great surgeon.
We could be great together.
You just, you gotta
stop screwing around.
I don't wanna be the future of this
hospital if you're not with me. OK?
OK.
- Alex!
- What?
♪ 'Cause I remember
what we said ♪
♪ As we lay down to bed ♪
♪ We'll be back as
soon as we make ♪
♪ History ♪
- You told Adele on me?
- You stopped speaking to me.
That didn't exactly
leave me many options.
Would you have reacted like this
if I left general surgery for neuro?
- Or cardio?
- I don't follow.
Is it because you regard
peds as a soft specialty,
is that what's bothering you?
- That's ridiculous.
- Maybe. But...
It seems that every time I do
something you perceive as "soft,"
like having a baby, taking
some time off to see my baby,
specializing in
babies... I'm dead to you.
- Wanna know what I think?
- Not particularly.
I think you're scared
that you've gone soft.
You blame this hospital's
decline on it. Know what I think?
- You're gonna tell me.
- It's not doing
you one bit of good!
Surgeons are
dropping like dominoes.
So, maybe it's time you got in
touch with your feminine side.
Maybe you need a little soft.
You still shouldn't
have ratted me out.
- Sorry.
- Me, too.
What are you doing?
Assigning myself to
trauma with you tomorrow.
I'm a big girl. I can
handle my share of trauma.
And I get to decide
when I've had enough.
It's gonna take a lot more than
a bad dream to scare me off.
It is more than a bad dream.
I know.
♪ Didn't know that
they were dying ♪
♪ You varnished
all the leaves... ♪
I know I have no business
asking you for anything,
but I need your help.
I need you to bring Derek back.
And he's not "fine."
Sometimes people
just want to be left alone.
He's planning to propose.
He's been carrying
around a big ring for weeks.
That's not a man who
wants to be left alone.
I just thought you should know.
♪ With a tin of creosole ♪
♪ What on earth... ♪
Yes, the odds are against us.
I'm a one woman wrecking ball.
All I do is break you. Your hand,
penis, relationships, your life...
I'd say our survival rate is about
three percent. And that's bad.
But it's not nothing.
I don't think we should
give up on this. Not yet...
OK.
You think you broke
me, Little Grey?
You're the one who
put me back together.
- Hand.
Mark. I've got a couple of
Shepherd's post-ops to check in on,
- but after that,
feel like a drink?
- How about a rain check, John?
Jim.
It's Jim.
So I've had quite a day. Got my
ass handed to me by Alex Karev.
A second year resident.
Which is humbling for a surgeon,
- especially a know-it-all...
- We don't have to do this,
be friends.
It's a big hospital, lots of
floors, lots of places to hide.
I'm perfectly OK with doing
that for the next few years.
You're not hearing me, Calliope.
Sometimes I panic in
the moment, I call it wrong.
I misjudge a situation.
So if you're up for it, I'd
like to take you to dinner.
Maybe.
Maybe?
My schedule's kind of
insane right now, so...
I'll get back to you.
How's, uh, tomorrow?
♪ Black crows
circling up above ♪
♪ Crying out "Do you
hear that sound?" ♪
♪ I'd never thought
it'd come to this... ♪
- Good night, Iz.
- Night.
Um...
I've been keeping my
distance 'cause you're with Alex.
I just want to let you know
I'm still here. I still care.
Thanks, George.
And you don't
want to talk about it?
Not yet.
- OK. Good night.
- Night.
♪ Some are blind
but choose to see ♪
♪ Lies into the truth... ♪
You don't like me
very much, do you?
- Uh...
- No. That's good.
It's good. Because I
need to tell you something.
I need to tell you because I need to
tell somebody and... you're a robot.
You can take it.
OK.
- I can't tell you here.
- OK.
- I can't...
OK.
♪ The thunder has begun ♪
♪ A storm is gonna come ♪
You cleaned all of your
clothes out of the house.
Go home, Meredith. Just go home.
How long are you
planning on hiding out here?
That's what you're
doing. You're hiding.
You made a mistake, she's
dead. You can't hide from that.
I'm not hiding, I'm done.
I'm done operating.
Oh, OK, so you're just quitting?
You should understand,
you wrote the book on quitting,
running, hiding... You've
written a lot of books, Meredith.
That may be true,
but I'm here now.
You're here now?
- You wanted me out
since I moved in.
- That is not true.
You are incapable of anything
that resembles commitment.
You lied to me. You
said you were healthier,
you were healed.
There's no fixing
you. You're a lemon.
Derek Shepherd, you are drunk.
And you're angry. And
I've been there, so I get it.
- That doesn't
give you the right...
- Go home.
- You don't get to...
- This is what you want,
I'm giving you an out. Go!
- I'm not going anywhere.
- I said leave! Meredith, leave!
I know there's a ring.
- What?
- The chief told me.
I know there's a ring.
♪ Black crows
circling up above ♪
You want the ring?
♪ I never thought
it'd come to this ♪
♪ Paradise razed to the ground ♪
Here's your ring.
Every surgeon has a shadow.
That the best you've got? I'm
not bailing. We're in this together.
Go home, Meredith.
And the only way to
get rid of a shadow...
is to turn off the lights,
to stop running
from the darkness...
and face what you fear...
head on.
♪ A storm is gonna come ♪
♪ Find a sister,
find a brother ♪
♪ A storm is gonna come ♪
♪ Find a haven, find a shelter ♪
♪ Find a port, find a harbor ♪
♪ A storm is gonna come ♪
♪ Find a friend, find a mother ♪
♪ Find a sister,
find a brother... ♪