The problem with
being a resident is
you feel crazy all the time.
You haven't slept in years.
You spend every day around
people in massive crisis.
You lose your ability
to judge what's normal...
Move your crap off the
floor before this eats it.
OK, OK, OK.
In yourself or anyone else.
And yet people are constantly asking
you to tell them how they're doing.
How the hell are you
supposed to know?
- Eggs good?
- Uh-huh.
- The baby didn't
like the breakfast.
- All right, into the can.
You don't even know
how you're doing.
We had our first honest
conversation about your feelings
and now you want to leave.
That doesn't strike you as strange?
No. And I'm still firing you.
- No, you're quitting.
- I'm not quitting.
- I don't quit things.
- Well, actually you do.
Your mother quit your
father, your father quit you,
you quit your boyfriend, and
if I read your chart correctly,
you quit your life, momentarily,
on a couple of occasions. You quit.
- It's what you know how to do.
- Now, you're really fired.
Now, we're getting somewhere.
I want you to handle my consults.
Anything you can do without me, do it.
Book time in the robotics lab, I
want to give him a tour. Hahn.
Walter Tapley's coming in. Do we
have anything he can scrub in on?
- Walter Tapley is coming here?
- - The chief was his student.
You studied at the
right hand of God?
- Wow.
- We need something impressive.
I will stab someone
in the chest if I have to.
O'Malley, get
Boyer ready for a CT
and prep my lap chole.
I need to be out of that OR by
ten. Hahn! Plan to be free at ten.
O'Malley, did Patricia
say I had any messages?
Yeah. She said...
She said to tell you your wife
hadn't called in the 20 minutes
since you last asked
if your wife called.
All right.
- Hey.
- I'm very optimistic about
this new viral cocktail.
Adding an IL-2 should make
a big difference. We're close.
- We're going to open
champagne soon.
- I know.
- Are you OK?
- I'm fine.
Listen, clinical
trials can be a grind.
If this is getting to you,
I can do this on my own.
I'm not a quitter. I don't need
you to rescue me. Let's just do this.
Waiting is a bad idea. We're
talking about your health.
Dr. Shepherd can
say no if it's a problem.
What am I saying no to?
Is there any way to push
back the surgery a few hours?
My boyfriend's flight was
canceled. I want him to be here.
- Greta.
- He has some questions.
He's so smart about this.
I don't know what to ask.
Are you reconsidering
the procedure?
Andre and I have had so little
time together. We met in January.
I mean, this treatment
could kill me, right?
An aggressive tumor. Don't
operate, you're looking at months.
But I'd spend them with Andre.
Do you know how precious that
is? Time with the person you love?
- Greta.
- I'm not saying I want to cancel.
I'm just saying I want to wait
for Andre. He'll help me to decide.
- OK, we can't wait for...
- He'll be here at three.
Dr. Mark Sloan. I used
to be a patient of his.
Rebecca?
- Where have you been?
- Hi, Izzie.
I've called you and
left, like, 50 messages.
- You seem kind of upset.
- You're not pregnant,
first of all,
and Alex has been turning his life
upside down to be your baby-daddy,
and I can't tell him because of
confidentiality. So, yeah, upset.
You can talk to Alex about
anything. I want him involved.
And I am pregnant.
You kind of know.
OK. So if you're not trying to
trap Alex with a fake pregnancy,
you won't mind if I do
another test just to be sure.
Trap him? Are you
out of your mind?
I'm pregnant. And
that's a good thing.
Because I want this baby.
I've always wanted a baby.
You have a baby.
Of course I do. I mean
I want another one.
Do the stupid test
again, it'll be fine.
I need to see Dr. Sloan.
Can you help me with that?
Yeah, I'll see what I can do.
- Dr. Shepherd?
- Yes?
- There's no Andre.
- What?
She made him up.
He doesn't exist.
My sister, she's not a woman
who has boyfriends, OK?
Then four months ago,
she goes on a cruise, comes
back saying she met her soul mate.
Around the time her
symptoms started?
There are no pictures and nobody
has ever seen him. Can you talk to her?
Can you tell her we
can't wait for Andre?
Because we could
be waiting a long time.
- Is Tapley in there?
- No.
- You're lying.
- Yes.
- Tapley in there?
- No.
- Liar.
- Yes.
- Something is wrong with her.
- No, I'm fine.
She cleaned. Cleaned the apartment,
which she has no idea how to do.
- She pushed dirt around.
- Leave her alone.
Not everybody has to be happy.
That's not mental health. That's crap.
Walter Tapley's here and
she doesn't want to meet him.
- Well, that's bad.
- You know what, Torres?
- Mind your own business.
- You need to get help.
You're killing me.
Hang out until Hahn gets
here, you might meet Tapley.
- I don't give a damn
about Tapley.
- Cristina.
- Are you in the dark place?
- Yeah.
Me, too.
There she is. Dr. Erica Hahn,
our chief of cardiothoracic surgery.
It's an honor to
meet you, Dr. Tapley.
I use your modified bypass
procedure all the time.
Yeah, well, that was
an afternoon well spent.
- You came up with that
in an afternoon?
- It took him six years.
You're a killjoy, Webber.
I didn't really come
here for a visit.
I have aortic and mitral
stenosis with tricuspid regurg.
I need a double valve
replacement and tricuspid repair.
Are you sure?
Charts, echoes,
chest X-rays...
everything you need.
I may have invented the modified
bypass, but I can't operate on myself.
And my colleagues won't touch me
because I have chronic
a-fib, pulmonary hypertension
and a clot in my left atrium.
They think if they
operate, they'll kill me.
What makes you think we'll
do it, if your colleagues won't?
I didn't start their careers.
They can say no
to me. Webber can't.
Absolutely not.
- Now, hold on...
- Have you read the file?
His arterial pressure
is through the roof.
- He's aware of the risk.
- Well, in that case, fine.
What was I so worried about?
I may go down in history as the
surgeon who killed Walter Tapley,
- but at least they're
writing about me.
- Erica, sit down.
Let me tell you a story. Thirty-eight
years ago, when I was a...
I'm sorry. Is this
gonna be a story about
how you were a struggling black med
student who wanted to be a surgeon
and no one would give you a
chance and Walter Tapley did?
He mentored you, without him
you wouldn't be in this hospital?
- Yes.
- I'm still not gonna
operate on him.
I thought the sex was mind-blowing, but
I get the impression you had a bad time.
- What?
- Why are you avoiding me?
I'm sorry. I lost a patient.
I'm not trying to avoid you.
Not calling me after sex
is you being a lifesaver?
- It is.
- So I'll see you later?
You didn't call her?
When was the last time you
called a woman after having sex?
Well, that's gonna change.
I'm turning over a new leaf.
What was wrong with the old leaf?
They called you a whore, you're happy.
Walter Tapley needs a double
valve replacement and Hahn refuses.
- What?
- Thinks she's gonna kill him.
- Lightweight.
- Since when do surgeons
turn me down?
- It's her choice. She's opening him up.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Another thing. If you spend the night
with a woman, call her the next day,
she doesn't call back, does
that mean she had a lousy time
or her answering machine
was consumed in a fire?
- Chief calls the next day.
- You don't have to call.
You just met this person.
It's new, it's fun, it's casual.
- It's my wife.
- Oh!
- Do I call again?
- Well, another call looks
desperate.
Send her an e-mail. Invite her to
dinner. Just be casual, confident.
Sexy.
- I mean, romantic.
- Mmm.
- O'Malley!
- Yes, sir.
Tapley's in 2062. He's getting an
EKG and an echo. I assigned Yang.
All right. Oh, one more thing.
I know I said I wouldn't use you to get
my wife back, but I am a desperate man.
- Lay it on me.
- Draft an e-mail.
Ask her to dinner.
No, no. Don't ask her.
Tell her. She
likes a strong hand.
You want me to ask your wife
on a date with a strong hand.
- Confident. Casual.
Sexy. Tell her...
Tell her the train is leaving
the station, she'd better get on it.
Yeah.
- Can I talk to you? About Rebecca?
- I'm busy.
Alex, I gave her a pregnancy
test last week. She's not pregnant.
- I wanted to tell you.
- You're telling me now.
When I told her, she...
she said I was wrong.
She thinks it's some
false negative. It isn't.
She was puking and her
boobs are all blown up.
- I ran it twice.
- Well, labs are wrong
all the time.
You're wrong all the time! Mind your
own business and stay out of my life!
You have my chart
and I prefer you didn't,
because I fired you.
Can I have my chart?
It's not appropriate to
show up unannounced.
You didn't fire me, you quit.
So, if you would like to
un-quit, make an appointment.
You know...
Make an appointment,
Grey, it's what we do.
At the moment no
surgery's scheduled,
so focus on keeping him
stable and comfortable.
Anything he wants. He
wants a steak, kill a cow.
Karev, bedside PFTs and an ABG.
Yang, run a
central line... Sorry.
Damn daycare pages me
every time he gets a runny nose.
Find out what they want. I
need Bailey focused on Tapley.
- To the daycare?
- Quickly.
Right man for the job.
Grey. Tapley
needs a central line.
Do it.
- I don't understand.
- Take a needle,
jab it into his subclavian so he
can receive medicine and not croak.
- A central line.
- But I've never done one! Dr. Yang?
Hey! How'd it go with Greta?
- I haven't spoken to her yet.
- You haven't?
I mixed the virus and the
IL-2. We have six hours.
We're not gonna wait
six, we're gonna wait three.
The guy we're waiting
for doesn't exist.
I want to give her a little
more time to enjoy him.
Or the idea of
him, if nothing else.
We remove the tumor,
it's gonna disappear.
It's not real. It's OK if it disappears,
she can go back to her life.
She was probably a lonely person.
She found a way to have love.
Of course, because that's where
love exists. In delusional fantasies.
Real love isn't like that.
Good to know.
He punched someone
named Harrison.
You punched a child?
There was a graham
cracker involved.
Over a graham cracker?
They said they want
you to talk to him.
He's 14 months old. What
do they think I'm gonna do,
lecture on nonviolent
conflict resolution?
- I really don't know.
- Uh...
My son punches
children. Perfect!
Hey! Dr. Yang, who's even more evil
than usual, asked me to do a central line.
This is the big day that
could change things for me.
In there is Tapley
and Tapley is God.
I'm the chief's intern, that
makes me close to God,
which means I can't help you right
now, as un-Christian as that may sound.
No. I'll do Tapley's line. So I
puncture his lung, he'll get over it.
She wants you to do
Tapley's line? I'll do it.
Yay! Yay for Georgie.
Georgie saves the day.
I give you Tapley and you
pass it over to your intern?
What the hell is wrong with you?
Do you think if you kiss the
chief's ass by taking care of Tapley,
something magical's
gonna happen? Like what?
You'll earn your magical
resident wings? Well, no.
No, not gonna happen,
George. You're stuck.
You are where you are.
The only way out of your
situation is if Burke were here
because you were Burke's guy.
For some reason he pitied your
pathetic ass, but he's gone now.
No wings for Georgie.
Was I happy when I was with her?
- Off and on.
- I think I idealize it.
I mean, you wouldn't hang on
to a woman who's unavailable,
unpredictable, right? You'd
move on, keep it casual.
Don't sell yourself short. Allow
yourself to grow with Rose.
- Share experiences. Build memories.
- Is this the new leaf?
- Yeah.
- Needs work.
Oh, my God. This
is gonna kill me.
Nice work. You found the
subclavian on the first try.
Got yourself a good resident.
- Actually, sir, I'm an intern.
- The best intern
in the hospital.
O'Malley, start Dr. Tapley on
a loading dose of Amiodarone,
- followed by a continuous infusion.
- - Yes, sir.
Why the hell would he
start me on Amiodarone?
O'Leary, would you give Amiodarone
to a man who's about to have
- an open-heart procedure?
- George, wait outside, please?
If you can't get the
head of cardiothoracics
to do a valve replacement,
then you're not the
chief I thought you were.
And this is not the
facility I thought it was,
so maybe it's
better for all of us
if I don't get cut open here.
Would you get these lines off me?
Would you get back in that bed?
I'll talk to her again.
You're not even gonna
watch the Tapley surgery?
I don't want five minutes with
Walter Tapley. I want five years.
Tapley's a star-maker.
That's why the chief's a star.
Five minutes is a slap in the face,
like giving an alcoholic a sip of wine.
Lexie's coming over. Let's try to
keep the carnage to a minimum.
Hey, can I talk to
you about something?
- Maybe some other time.
- Uh, but...
Look, you know, she hates you. OK?
She's not going to say it to your face.
She's too polite. But you're annoying.
Showing up here like the good girl
Daddy didn't abandon is the worst
that's happened to her in months.
And that's saying a lot
coming from Meredith Grey.
- It's gonna be OK.
- Wanna bet?
Mm.
Two minutes, I'll meet
you in the on-call room.
We're gonna sit and
enjoy a meal together.
- I don't get it.
- I turned over a new leaf.
From now on, if you want
this, you're gonna get this too.
Ew.
Shove over, Sloan. Torres and I
are gonna share a Sapphic salad.
- Did I miss something?
- Yeah, we're lovers. Didn't you know?
It's a love that dare
not speak its name.
Uh-hm. Look me in the eye and tell me
you're not thinking about a threesome.
I'm not. Old Mark
would, but that's no more.
Really? You're not thinking
about her and me and you
and a video camera.
- On-call room,
ten minutes.
- No!
- I am the chief of surgery.
- I am not killing
Walter Tapley,
I don't care who you are.
- Should I leave?
- No.
He's dying anyhow. You'd rather see
him die on my watch than under your knife?
- Yes.
- I should leave.
No. Is something going on with
all the women that when I speak,
they simply ignore it? You don't
leave. You review the file again.
If you see my wife, tell her the
polite thing to do is return a man's call.
See, a tumor in the
temporal lobe can blur the line
between imagination and reality.
It's possible that Andre
is part of that confusion.
She likes being the successful
sister with a husband and kids,
while I'm the
single, pathetic one
who has to send herself
flowers on Valentine's Day.
I found someone. And
she can't deal with it.
- But there are
no pictures of him.
- You want a picture?
There. There.
And there. And there.
Those are drawings made
from images in your head.
- I'm an artist,
that's what I do.
- The journals and writing?
- Did you do that before?
- Leave her alone.
I didn't have anything
to write about before.
There's a symptom
called hypergraphia.
- It's compulsive...
- Leave her alone.
I'm in love with a man.
I've touched him and held him. He
is not a figment of my imagination.
Tell them how you met.
I was on a cruise around the Greek
Islands and we'd stopped at Santorini.
I was running to get to the
ship and my shoe fell off.
The horn was blowing,
so I didn't stop. I left it.
That night, at dinner, Andre
found me. He had my shoe.
- Sound familiar?
- You're mocking me.
No, I'm not. I'm trying
to make you see.
Dr. Shepherd, does anything
about that sound familiar?
Sounds like Cinderella.
What else happened on the boat?
- Greta.
- I had my first blackouts.
Andre was there.
He carried me to...
A woman found you on
the floor of the bathroom.
- Prince Charming
didn't carry you...
- All of you, get out!
This is stupid, stupid!
Stupid conversation.
Greta, the serum that
we use to kill the tumor,
- it only lasts
a few hours. So...
- Is it going to expire by 3:00?
No, it is not.
- Dr. Shepherd...
- It is not.
We can wait until 3:00. We can't
wait all day, but we can wait until 3:00.
Hey, you! How's the...?
Some of my best work. Any
pulling around the suture lines?
No. It's perfect. I'm just not
sure if it goes with the body.
See what I mean?
Face is a head turner, but the boobs
aren't stopping anybody on the street.
You can close the gown.
It doesn't match! Doesn't go with my
face, doesn't go with my personality.
- It's all wrong.
- Didn't you tell me
you were pregnant?
I don't need a lecture. I just
need you to finish what you started.
Can you do that?
- I need to talk to you.
- Make an appointment!
I don't want an appointment,
just my chart back. Get it now.
I'd like to go to the bathroom in
peace. Everybody's dissatisfied here.
Where do you get off
suggesting I'm a coward, a quitter?
Are you trying to make me
feel bad so you can fix me?
- Talk about
it in therapy.
- No! I don't need therapy!
- I forgive you.
- Lexie.
No. I forgive you. I forgive
you for treating me like crap
and letting your friend
treat me like crap.
- Lexie.
- I don't know how you get up.
I honestly don't. Our
dad abandoned you.
Your mom, by all accounts,
was the meanest person ever.
You can't let Derek love
you and it all really sucks.
But ever since I knew you existed, I
had this fantasy about my big sister.
And you have failed, on every
occasion, to live up to that fantasy.
But I still love you, whether you
are capable of letting me or not.
So... I forgive you.
- 2:00 work for you?
- Yeah, OK.
If this man dies under my
knife, Richard, so help me,
I will tell every reporter in the
land that you insisted we do this.
- You will look like an idiot.
- Relax! I'll be fine.
She has impeccable judgment.
And this may be the
dumbest thing I've ever done.
Ted Ginsburg
would have done this.
But I wanted a friend, in case I went
into the OR and didn't come back.
I wanted an old
friend to say goodbye.
- I'm honored.
- Don't be.
I should have had a wife
and a bunch of kids...
so I wouldn't have to track you down
to get someone to be at my deathbed.
Stevens. What are you
treating Rebecca Pope for?
A pregnancy she doesn't
have but thinks she does.
Doesn't one of you have
science on your side?
Yes. She is acting really weird.
She wants breast enhancement
surgery. She thinks her new face
doesn't match her body.
May be acute stress disorder.
It happens when people have
massive plastic surgeries and trauma.
You look in the mirror, you're
not sure you are the same person.
It can lead to odd behavior.
Thinking you're pregnant when
you're not, forgetting you have a baby?
Make it clear to her she's not
pregnant and get her a psych consult.
- And have psych call me.
- OK.
Here you are, chief.
Read that to me. I can't see
anything on that tiny screen.
- Oh, no, that's a bad idea.
- Speak up, O'Malley.
"Dear Adele, eat with me.
The love train is
leaving the station.
- You know you want
to take a ride."
- O'Malley!
"Take a ride on
my love train..."
Sir, I didn't come up with
the train or the station.
- Give that to me. I'll do it myself.
- Yes.
Hey, so, let me
get this straight.
If I wander into an on-call room,
you are not gonna follow me?
You ever think about why you need sex
all the time? Is it replacing something?
I use it to clear my head. So...
on-call room.
We can sit there and talk,
but we're not having sex.
Why? What are we
gonna talk about?
At lunch, you wanted
to talk threesomes.
You are so not a new man.
I mean, I guess if you
had to have a threesome,
Erica Hahn wouldn't
be a bad choice, right?
She brings that whole,
"We're naughty, getting sent to
the principal's office" thing to it.
You never thought about reaching across
the OR table and pulling down her mask,
ripping off her scrub
cap, so that you can grab
a handful of that blonde hair...
Stop! Stop talking
about Erica Hahn.
Forget it.
Everything all right?
One of the founding fathers of
cardiothoracic surgery is on the table
and I'm about to slice open
his chest. Give me a minute.
OK, scalpel.
Don't screw it up.
I'm gonna kill you.
We've got this patient.
And she's got true love.
Do you want to know why?
Because her
boyfriend doesn't exist.
Derek is all broken up over her,
like it means something that she's
having an affair with a hallucination.
Derek wasn't ready to give up
on the relationship, you were.
No, I didn't give up. I wanted to try
again. And then he went and kissed Rose.
So he's the one who
messes up. Not me.
But it's a relationship.
People make mistakes.
And you stand back, waiting for him to
fail so you can say, "A-ha! Now I quit."
No! It wasn't working.
Was life not working when you
let that slip out from under you?
When are you gonna stop
suggesting I'm suicidal?
When you act like somebody
that wants to be alive.
- Give me my chart!
- Why?
I'm not suicidal. If it
says that, it's wrong.
What happened when
you fell in the water?
I almost drowned.
I did that for kicks?
You put your hand in a body cavity
that contained unexploded ordinance.
I was trying to save a patient!
Why is it that every other person in
that room had the sense to hit the deck?
You know, people run away from
this line between life and death.
You seem to stand on it
and wait for a strong wind
to sway you one
way or the other.
You're careless with your life.
You're not slitting your
wrists, but you're careless.
Probably because your mother
told you you were a waste of space.
The problem is you believed
her. If you don't watch out,
one of these days you're
gonna die because of it.
Hand me my chart.
Now!
And don't ever talk
about my mother again.
What the hell is...?
There's a leak. Go
back on bypass now!
Take clamps off the
aortic and venous lines.
- Grey, take the suction.
- The left atrium is torn
where that clot was adhered.
Metzenbaum scissors!
This was a mistake. It was
irresponsible and stupid,
and I cannot believe I
let you talk me into it!
My reputation's gonna
be in the toilet at the end.
Dan Slocum at Mercy is
gonna have a field day with this,
- condescending tool that he is.
- Erica.
Don't "Erica" me, Richard. It's not
your good name we're gonna destroy,
- much as I wish that it was.
- Dr. Hahn, it's done.
No leak. The repair's holding.
You were saying?
♪ Today ♪
♪ You were far away ♪
♪ And I ♪
♪ Didn't ask you why ♪
Is that clock right?
I'm sure it is.
Maybe his plane was delayed.
His phone is off. Maybe his phone
is off because he's still on the plane.
He's coming!
Here.
- My head did this?
- No.
Your tumor did this.
He was never there?
Oh, God.
Oh, God!
How can he not be real?
I'm sorry.
Oh, God!
Hey, there, baby boy!
You managed to make
it through the day?
Our son has been
punching other children.
- Yeah, I know.
- What do you mean, you know?
It's happened before.
I'm dealing with it.
Wait. I had to bribe the director of
the daycare center to get him back in.
I had to bring apple slices and give
free mammograms to the teachers.
Now, why aren't you
telling me what's happening?
I don't judge how you do surgery,
don't judge how I deal with the baby.
You didn't deal. He's
punching other children!
Of course he's punching!
He used to be with me all day.
Now, he's in day care so he spends
ten minutes with you every three hours.
So that's making him violent?
Hey, Tuck! Hey! Can I take
him to say hi for a minute?
- Uh... Yeah, sure, sure.
- Want to play with
the office supplies?
Look, if you can't communicate
well enough to tell me...
Don't lecture me, Miranda
Bailey. I'm not one of your students.
With all the time you spend
here, it's hard to differentiate.
No, I spend my time here
because I'm building a life for us!
I spend time here because
I don't have the luxury
of being able to take a year
off and spend it with our child,
knowing my career's waiting
for me when I'm ready to go back!
Luxury? So you think
spending all day every day
wiping noses and
changing diapers is a luxury?
No, I think it's a beautiful
thing that you get to do.
- You take it for granted!
- Take it for granted?
- Yes!
- I take our family for granted?
- I did not say...
- You did say!
- I work because we...
- You love your work!
- And I love my family, too!
It is going to be OK.
Uncle George says
it is going to be OK.
This happened when I
was a kid. I'd get a strep test,
it'd come back negative.
Look. OK, that's your uterus.
There is nothing in there.
No fetus, no sac. Nothing.
But it's too early. It's tiny,
you can't see anything yet.
- What the hell are you doing?
- I paged you 20 minutes ago.
Rebecca, look. OK?
This is a fetus at six weeks.
Right? It's a tiny spot, but it's there,
you can see it.
Look at your uterus, there's
nothing there. Nothing.
Get out.
Here are her labs. There's
a chart note from Dr. Sloan.
- I can get a psych consult
if you want.
- Look, just get out!
What?
There's no baby.
- I lost the baby?
- No, you weren't pregnant.
If you had been pregnant, your beta-HCG
level would be elevated. It's zero.
You didn't miscarry,
there never was a baby.
I can't believe I lost our baby.
Rebecca. You're not hearing me.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so... I'm so
sorry I lost our baby.
Shh. It's OK.
You're gonna be OK, all right?
Remember, we need to
stay in synch. Ready? Go.
Good. Easy, slow, slow down.
Right there, right there. Good.
Pressure's rising, she's
getting bradycardic.
So let's push one gram per kilo
of Mannitol, 20 Lasix, see if we can
avoid increased ICP.
Is there a problem, Dr. Grey?
Andre's here.
You run everywhere, or is
it just you're scared of me?
- I'm trying to stay
on top of things.
- You're doing a fine job.
It's very impressive work.
Sir, if you would mention to
the chief you like my work?
I was held back as an intern.
There was some
personal... stuff.
I'm good. And if you would
say something to him...
Webber would not have
made that decision lightly.
Learning is like healing.
It happens over time.
Listen. Keep running.
But not because you
want to cut corners,
because it makes
you a better doctor.
- You're not
supposed to be talking.
- O'Leary and I
were just marveling
at the fact that you
haven't killed me yet.
Well, there's always tomorrow.
Check his post-op echo, make
sure there's no residual prolapse.
Yes, sir.
♪ Someday my pain ♪
- Are you OK?
- Don't ask me if I'm OK.
OK.
You make me sick.
Have some fire.
Be unstoppable.
Be a force of nature.
Be better than anyone here and
don't give a damn what anyone thinks.
There are no teams
here. No buddies.
You're on your
own. Be on your own.
Dr. Yang, I just scrubbed in on Walter
Tapley's double valve replacement.
I watched Dr. Hahn excise a piece of
his pericardium from three inches away.
That's what I got to do while
you made notes in charts.
So whatever crap you want to
rain down on my head, go for it.
Because I just saw the
inside of Walter Tapley's heart,
and that is something you
will never take away from me.
Yeah. OK.
OK then.
Hey, Tuck! Here's Tapley's
file. The new labs are in there.
- Just put it on the pile.
- Tucker didn't take him?
I wanted the evening with him.
You guys get to the
bottom of anything?
Why don't I take Tuck for a couple
hours? You can go talk to him. Go fight.
You're not gonna fix anything in one
day, but you can go on and keep trying.
What are you doing?
I need clothes. She's staying with
me. She didn't bring enough stuff.
- Did you call her husband?
- She doesn't want to.
Did you get a psych consult?
Alex, she had a hysterical pregnancy.
Sloan thinks she may have a stress...
She's fine, OK? I can handle it.
I'm gonna take care of her. Just
give me some damn girl clothes.
Put your arms up a little bit.
There you go.
Tomorrow's board and Dr. Tapley's
echo. Hahn is seeing him now.
What are you doing
with Bailey's child?
Dr. Bailey and I are in love.
I'll be heading to Vegas with
her as soon as my divorce is final.
We need to write Adele again.
She replied to my e-mail,
but all she sent was a typo.
She's no better
at this than I am.
- That's not a
typo, that's a wink.
- A semi-colon and a
closed parentheses?
Turn it sideways.
- What the hell does this mean?
- She's flirting.
Oh!
- Oh, that's good!
- Yeah.
O'Malley.
Good work today.
You know what that was?
That was the "attaboy."
This may have been the most exhausting
day of my life, my back is killing me,
no offense, and I haven't
seen the inside of an OR in...
I don't know how long,
but I got the attaboy.
I'm turning it around.
And you're gonna get the
punching under control, right?
You and me.
Boy, it takes us a
while, but we get there.
We reached the tumor.
But there was swelling
in Greta's brain.
We did an MRI,
and it suggested that the swelling in
her brain caused a great deal of damage.
It doesn't look like
she's gonna wake up.
Mr. Barret, we're so sorry.
We should have waited.
We didn't think...
I didn't think you were coming.
The whole story just
sounded so incredible.
She told you about
the shoe, right?
It makes us both sound crazy.
I could never get that
image out of my head...
her running up the
gangplank with one shoe.
Wind in her hair.
Most beautiful
thing I've ever seen.
She might wake up, right?
I mean, it's been a fairy tale from
the start. They always wake up.
Don't wonder why
people go crazy.
Wonder why they don't.
♪ And you cried ♪
♪ Drying those brown eyes ♪
♪ Crying you're sorry ♪
In the face of all we
can lose in a day...
in an instant...
wonder what the hell it is...
that makes us hold it together.
Ladies.
He's thinking about a threesome.
- I am not.
- You are.
He has been... all day.
OK, fine. I got a new
leaf, not a lobotomy.
You couldn't
handle the two of us.
Oh, but I could. I
won't, but I could.
You wouldn't find
it intimidating?
Not at all.
See? Too much for you.
Damn it! On-call
room, right now.
♪ Open my eyes, I see sky ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, you know ♪
♪ the way to keep
me on my toes ♪
♪ I, I, I will be fine ♪
Rose.
- You want go have dinner?
- No, I'm sorry. I can't.
- Oh, come on.
- Derek.
We spent a night
together and you vanished.
I wish I was secure enough to handle
that without a bruised ego and sugar,
- but I'm not.
- Wait, wait, wait.
Can't we just make this easier?
I don't...
Look, I don't want... See,
I've done complicated.
I don't want to do that again.
Can't this just be easy?
Fun?
We don't need that
fairy tale thing right now.
We just need a little happy.
Hm?
My mother tried to kill
herself when I was a kid.
After the love of
her life disappeared.
I never told
anybody that before.
OK.
So you think I'm broken?
Fix me.
Because I'm no quitter.
Let's go.