Narrator / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Previously on Grey's Anatomy.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): We had sex once.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Go out with me.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You know you're my boss.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You know it's against the rules.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Do you like Izzy?
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Is that what this is about?
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Izzy?
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): No.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): She's not the one I'm attracted to.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Not the one, so there's a one.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Haven't you ever been attracted to someone you know you couldn't have?
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Meredith.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Just coffee.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Good.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Okay.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Okay.
Dr. Richard Webber / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Your mother's Alzheimer's is advancing, so while she's still lucid enough to consent, she needs to sign everything over to you.
Meredith Grey / Annie Connors OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Me?
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Thanks for the coffee.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): So you blew me off for a bottle of tequila.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): It's not nearly as much fun to wake up to.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You mind moving this tail wagon?
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You're blocking me in.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): A couple hundred years ago, Benjamin Franklin shared with the world the secret of his success.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Never leave that till tomorrow, he said, which you can do today.
Unknown Intern / Unknown (PVM): Save me.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): This is the man who discovered electricity.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You'd think more of us would listen to what he had to say.
Meredith Grey / Mr. LaVangie OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I don't know why we put things off, but if I had to guess, I'd say it has a lot to do with fear.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Fear of failure, fear of pain, fear of rejection.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Wouldn't it be easier to just ask her out?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): She's going to be late.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Maybe not.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): We should wait for her.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Definitely not.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I'm not her mother, and you are not her boyfriend.
Alex Karev / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Not yet, anyway.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Stop, okay?
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I told you I'm not interested.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Life is short, George.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Do you really want to die before you ever ask her out?
Dr. George O'Malley: I do not want to ask her out.
Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Do you really want to die or lie?
Dr. George O'Malley: I'm not... I'm not dying.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Sometimes the fear is just of making a decision.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Because what if you're wrong?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): What if you're making a mistake you can't undo?
Meredith / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Crap.
Derek / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Crap.
Dr. Meredith Grey: Hi, I'm late.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: You're avoiding me.
Dr. Meredith Grey: Yes, but also late.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: Oh, are we going to talk about this?
Dr. Meredith Grey: No.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: About us and Bailey and what she saw?
Dr. Meredith Grey: I don't need to talk about it.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: I experienced it naked.
Dr. Meredith Grey: Yes, this is getting complicated.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: Complicated for me.
Dr. Meredith Grey: I'm the intern sleeping with the attending.
Dr. Meredith Grey: Bailey isn't speaking to me anymore.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: Well, not that that's a bad thing.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: If I was a better guy, I'd walk away.
Dr. Meredith Grey: Yes, you would.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: Do you want me to be a better guy?
Dr. Meredith Grey: Yes.
Dr. Meredith Grey: No.
Meredith / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Crap.
Dr. Meredith Grey: I'm late.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: Take your time.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: Think about it.
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): That was definitely worth being late.
Cristina / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Is this a... Should we talk about this?
Meredith / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Mr. LaVangie OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Yeah, definitely.
Bailey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You're late.
Cristina / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): So are you.
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I know, and I can't afford to piss off Bailey anymore.
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Do you think she told anyone?
Cristina / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): About you and McDreamy?
Meredith / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Yeah.
Cristina / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): No.
Cristina / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He's her boss, too.
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): If they find out, what can they kick me out, or?
Cristina / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): No.
Cristina / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Not officially.
Cristina / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He'll just get edged out, blacklisted, banned from his surgeries, passed over for chief resident.
Cristina / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): It'll be humiliating, but he'll live.
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I have to end it.
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I definitely have to end it.
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I have to end it, right?
Cristina / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Meredith, shut up.
Meredith / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): What?
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Did you seriously just tell me to shut up?
Cristina / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, please.
Cristina / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Even a hot doctor likes to make you open up and say, ah.
Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): It's an American dream.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Stop whining about it.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): No.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): No good can come from sleeping with your boss.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Christina, you're late.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): So is Meredith.
Dr. Meredith Grey: Whatever it is we're afraid of, one thing holds true.
Dr. Meredith Grey: that by the time the pain of not doing a thing gets worse than the fear of doing it, it can feel like we're carrying around a giant tumor.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: When we walk in this door, you will maintain decorum.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: You will not laugh, vomit, or drop your jaw.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: We understood?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Why would we laugh?
Alex Karev / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Oh, Jess, you wait.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Good morning, Miss Connors.
Annie Connors: Good morning.
Intern (likely George O'Malley) / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): What is it?
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): A tumor.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: And you thought I was speaking metaphorically.
Dr. Burke / Annie Connors (PVM): Good morning, Annie.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): How are you?
Dr. Miranda Bailey: This is Dr. Bailey, and these are my fellow interns.
Miranda Bailey / Annie Connors OR Annie Connors OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Dr. Karev, we refer to patients as Mr. and... I told him to call me Annie.
Annie Connors: Miss Connors makes me feel old and fat, which I am, but why feel that way?
Dr. Burke / Annie Connors (PVM): Good morning.
Dr. Karev / Annie Connors (PVM): Oh, Annie, this is Dr. Burke.
Dr. Karev / Annie Connors OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Awesome surgeon.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Dr. Karev?
Dr. Karev / Annie Connors (PVM): Oh, uh, Annie Connors is a 43-year-old woman who presented last night with progressive shortness of breath for the past three months.
Dr. Karev / Annie Connors (PVM): Found to have a very large tumor of unknown origin pressed against her diaphragm.
Dr. Karev / Annie Connors (PVM): Stable vital signs.
Dr. Karev / Annie Connors (PVM): Scheduled for CT this morning, sir.
Dr. Burke / Annie Connors OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Thank you, Dr. Karef.
Dr. Burke / Annie Connors OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Are you at all claustrophobic?
Annie Connors: I've been housebound for the last year.
Annie Connors: How claustrophobic could I be?
Dr. Burke / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): All right, then.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Dr. Stevens is going to take you for a CT.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): It'll give us a better look at the tumor, and we'll know how to proceed from there.
Annie Connors: Could someone tell my mom?
Annie Connors: She'll worry if she gets back and I'm not here.
Dr. Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Yeah, of course.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Of course.
Annie Connors: And would it be possible for Alex to take me instead?
Annie Connors: I mean, he's just so fun to look at.
Dr. Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Annie.
Dr. Karev / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Sure.
Dr. Karev / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Sure, Miss Gars.
Dr. Stevens / Annie Connors OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Excuse me.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): How much do you think it weighs?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): 60 pounds.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): More.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): She's carrying around a whole extra person.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): This one's going in the books.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I've got to get in.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I almost did.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Have you ever seen Alex like that?
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He actually seemed sincere.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Seemed being the operative word.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): He was on call last night when she came in.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I am never leaving this place again.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Let's move, people.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Ms.
Richard Webber / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Conna's surgery, should we choose to proceed, will take most, if not all, of the surgeons off the floor, which means you people will have to work extra hard not to kill anyone.
Richard Webber / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): And we won't be there to fix your mistakes.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Dr. Burke?
Hospital Intercom: Trauma team to OR1.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I really want in on this.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I thought we weren't talking.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm not talking.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm just saying.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Find her mother, get a family history, and tell Bailey.
Intern (possibly George) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Mr. Harper had a coronary bypass yesterday.
Intern (possibly George) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): His blood pressure currently 100 over 65.
Intern (possibly George) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Was running low overnight, down to 70 over 30, but responded to medication.
Intern (possibly George) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Post-operative labs show crit of 30 and normal coagulation.
Intern (possibly George) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Chest tube output has halted over the last two hours.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): What's your plan?
Intern (possibly George) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Chest X-ray and check the tube for possible occlusion.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Good.
Intern (possibly George) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He's doing fine.
Dr. Bailey / Unknown (PVM): Thank you.
Dr. George O'Malley: I know you think I like Meredith, but I don't like Meredith.
Another Intern (likely Izzie or Cristina) / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): What?
Dr. George O'Malley: No, I mean, I like Meredith.
Dr. George O'Malley: I mean, obviously I like Meredith.
Dr. George O'Malley: I just don't have that thing for her.
Another Intern (likely Izzie or Cristina) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): OK.
Dr. George O'Malley: It's just this morning, you know, it's like, and I know you're probably just teasing, but I just don't want you to say anything like that to her, because, you know, we live together, and that would just be really awkward.
Another Intern (likely Izzie or Cristina) / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): George, stop talking.
Dr. George O'Malley: OK.
Unknown (possibly Dr. Bailey or another staff member) / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Morning.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Mr. LaVangie (PVM): Mr. LaVangie, this is Dr. Bailey and our fine staff of surgical interns.
Mr. LaVangie: Welcome to hell, kids.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Who's presenting?
Intern (possibly Cristina, Izzie, or Alex) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Edward LaVangie is a 63-year-old man admitted for pain management for dyskinesia.
Intern (Case Presenter) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He's been stable since last night and responding well to the bolus injections.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Is he possible treatments?
Intern (Case Presenter) / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): For Parkinson's disease, um, deep brain stimulation is shown very... Not for Parkinson's, for spinal pain.
Intern (Case Presenter) / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, um... Intraspinal catheter.
Intern (Case Presenter) / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): That way he can have constant pain medication.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Excellent.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Let's talk to Gray.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): She's gonna prep you for the procedure and assist.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Annie Connors OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Excuse me.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You make yourselves busy.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I'll catch up with you.
Mr. LaVangie / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Miranda.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Annie Connors OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Excuse me.
Mr. LaVangie / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Well, that's your name, right?
Mr. LaVangie / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): It's on your jacket.
Mr. LaVangie / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Fine, I'll just call you Bailey then.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You think you're charming, and that talented, neurotic, overly-moosed-hair sort of way good for you.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): But if you think I'm gonna stand back and watch while you favor her... I don't favor her.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): She's good.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): She is.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): You know, can I point out that technically, I'm your boss.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You don't scare me.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Look, I'm not gonna advertise your extracurricular activities with my intern.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): However, the next time I see you favoring Meredith Grey in any way, I'll make sure she doesn't see the inside of an O.R.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): for a month.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Just for the sake of balance.
Nurse or Surgical Tech / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): We're all set, doc.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): OK.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Annie Connors (PVM): Um, Annie, there's going to be a microphone in there for you in case you get scared or you want to get out.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Annie Connors OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): But, you know, try not to do that, because then we're going to have to start all over again.
Annie (the patient) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I'm fine.
Annie (the patient) / Annie Connors OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I'll be fine.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Annie Connors (PVM): I know you're going to be fine, because I'm going to be right over there behind that glass waiting for you.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Annie Connors (PVM): All right?
Annie (the patient) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): OK.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Annie Connors OR Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): You ready?
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Annie Connors OR Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Are you really ready?
Annie (the patient) / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Let's do this.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): See you.
Dr. Alex Karev / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Oh, hey, man, you got an extra battery.
Dr. Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Unbelievable.
Dr. George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, I know, right?
Dr. Cristina Yang / Annie Connors OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I've never seen anything like this.
Dr. Cristina Yang / Annie Connors OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): God.
Dr. Alex Karev / Annie Connors (PVM): What I don't understand is how a person lets it get like that.
Dr. Alex Karev / Annie Connors (PVM): I mean, man, that is a whole lot of nasty.
Dr. George O'Malley / Annie Connors (PVM): Maybe she's afraid of doctors.
Dr. George O'Malley / Annie Connors (PVM): Poor thing.
Unknown Female Relative / Annie Connors (PVM): Poor thing, please.
Unknown Family Member / Annie Connors (PVM): If you're afraid of doctors, you should take a pill.
Unknown Family Member / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): She's just sick, like warped, you know?
Unknown Family Member / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Seriously, I don't know how she lives with herself.
Annie's Mother / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Well, at first, we thought she was just putting on weight.
Annie's Mother / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): When we realized what was happening, I tried to get her to go to the doctor, but she was scared.
Annie's Mother / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): And the bigger it got, the less she wanted to go.
Annie's Mother / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): And she never really felt all that sick until last night.
Annie's Mother / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): She couldn't breathe.
Doctor / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Because the tumor was crushing her lungs.
Annie's Mother / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Yes, well, I called 911.
Annie's Mother / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): It just seemed like the right thing to do.
Doctor / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You know, the right thing to do would have been to call a year ago.
Annie's Mother / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Yes, thank you.
Doctor / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Okay, Mr. Levangie.
Nurse / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm gonna get you more comfortable, okay?
Mr. LaVangie: Uh-huh.
Nurse / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm gonna go downstairs, and I'll be back up shortly.
Mr. LaVangie: Okay.
Nurse / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Okay.
Unknown / Annie Connors OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Excuse me.
Unknown / Mr. LaVangie's Daughter OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm sorry, Dr. Gray.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): My dad seems to like you.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): He's always liked skinny blondes.
Intern 1 / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Is that rude?
Intern 2 / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm sorry.
Intern 2 / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm so tired.
Family Member (likely Annie's relative) / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Is there something?
Family Member (likely Annie's relative) / Mr. LaVangie's Daughter OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I was wondering if you would talk to him about brain surgery.
Family Member (likely Annie's relative) / Mr. LaVangie's Daughter (PVM): The doctor mentioned it, and I've read about it online.
Family Member (likely Annie's relative) / Mr. LaVangie's Daughter (PVM): If it worked, it could help with most of his symptoms, not just his pain.
Family Member (likely Annie's relative) / Mr. LaVangie's Daughter (PVM): Is he a candidate?
Intern 1 or Doctor / Mr. LaVangie's Daughter OR Annie Connors (PVM): I didn't... He is, but he's afraid of it.
Intern 1 or Doctor / Mr. LaVangie's Daughter (PVM): Surgery on his back, he can understand, but his brain... And there are risks, but his quality of life... There isn't any.
Intern 1 or Doctor / Mr. LaVangie's Daughter (PVM): And it keeps getting worse.
Family Member (likely Annie's relative) / Mr. LaVangie's Daughter (PVM): I'm getting married next month.
Family Member (likely Annie's relative) / Mr. LaVangie's Daughter (PVM): I already lost my mom.
Family Member (likely Annie's relative) / Mr. LaVangie's Daughter (PVM): And I want him to walk...
Family Member (likely Annie's relative) / Mr. LaVangie's Daughter (PVM): I want him with me.
Family Member (likely Annie's relative) / Mr. LaVangie's Daughter OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Maybe that's selfish, but you don't know what it's like having a parent.
Family Member (likely Annie's relative) / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Watching him.
Intern 1 or Doctor / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I do.
Intern 1 or Doctor / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I do know what it's like.
Intern 1 or Doctor / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I'll see what I can do.
Family Member (likely Annie's relative) / Mr. LaVangie's Daughter (PVM): Thanks.
Intern 1 or Doctor / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You're welcome.
Family Member (likely Annie's relative) / Unknown (PVM): Thank you.
Intern 1 / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): The right hemidiaphragm is so high that it's completely displacing her lung tissue.
Surgeon 1 / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): It's infiltrated her spinal canal in three places.
Surgeon 2 / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): We should start there.
Surgeon 1 / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): It's going to take three, four hours just to get around those nerves.
Surgeon 2 / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I'd prefer to start in front and then flip her.
Surgeon 1 / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You never know what kind of vessels are involved, how intertwined they are.
Surgeon 2 / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm going to need a good head start.
Surgeon 1 / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I should really go with the spine fresh.
Surgeon 1 / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I miss a step, she's paralyzed.
Surgeon 2 / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): If I don't relieve the pressure on her lungs, she'll be dead.
Surgeon 1 / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): So she won't mind if she can't walk.
Surgeon 2 / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You think she really wants to live?
Surgeon 1 / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Come on.
Surgeon 2 / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): She's been housebound.
Surgeon 2 / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): She's been living under this thing, just watching it grow for how long?
Surgeon 1 / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): She doesn't seem stupid.
Surgeon 1 / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Doesn't even seem all that scared.
Surgeon 2 / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Why would anyone wait this long unless they wanted to die?
Surgeon 1 / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): People do things every day that they know could kill them.
Surgeon 2 / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Doesn't mean they want to die.
Surgeon 1 / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): What are her chances of surviving the surgery?
Surgeon 2 / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Slightly better than if we do nothing.
Surgeon 1 / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): So is it worth it?
Surgeon 2 / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Hey, come on.
Surgeon 2 / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You were already thinking it.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm just saying.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): She's 43.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): It's worth a try.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Morning.
Hospital Intercom / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Dr. Moretti, 4672.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Dr. Shepherd.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Mr. LaVangie, the Parkinson's patient.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Is he a good candidate for DBS?
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Yes, but he's not interested.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): OK, but I think it's worth talking to him again, pushing him.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): We're talking about a brain surgery.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): It is performed while the patient is wide awake.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): There is a risk of paralysis, a risk of death, and the patient doesn't want it.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): It is not my job to push him into anything, and it's definitely not yours.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Okay.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Since you're clearly uncomfortable with my decision in this case, it's probably best you don't scrub in.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): But... It's a minor procedure.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): You won't be missed.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You know, they call you the Nazi.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): So I've heard.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Mr. LaVangie's Daughter (PVM): I won't lie to you.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): The surgery is going to be long and difficult.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Annie Connors (PVM): But we have an extremely capable surgical team, and I can't.
Annie Connors: Am I going to die?
Surgeon / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): There's always that risk.
Surgeon / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): But if we don't do the surgery.
Annie Connors: I'll definitely die.
Surgeon / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Yes.
Annie Connors: Soon?
Annie's Child / Annie Connors (PVM): Mom, the room's clean.
Annie / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Annie Connors (PVM): OK, Annie.
Annie's Child / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): OK.
Annie's Child / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Mom.
Annie's Mother / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): She'll have the surgery.
Annie / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): No.
Annie's Mother / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): No, Annie.
Annie's Mother / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): She will have the surgery.
Annie Connors: I guess I'll have the surgery.
Surgeon / Annie Connors OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I think that is a very wise decision.
Annie Connors: On one condition.
Annie Connors: I don't want him there.
Surgeon (the one Annie doesn't want) / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): I'm sorry, Annie.
Surgeon (the one Annie doesn't want) / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Did I upset you in some way?
Annie Connors: If he's in the surgery, I'm not having it.
Surgeon (the one Annie doesn't want) / Annie Connors (PVM): That's how I live with myself.
Dr. Karev / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): OK, Miss Connors.
Unidentified Speaker / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Dr. Karev.
Dr. Karev / Annie Connors OR Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): What the hell did you do?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Nothing.
Cristina Yang / Annie Connors OR Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): I don't know.
Dr. Karev / Annie Connors (PVM): Man, the mic must have been on.
Meredith Grey / Annie Connors OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I was talking to the tech guy.
Dr. Bailey / Annie Connors OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): If anything goes wrong, anything, you are 60% more likely to be sued if you've offended the patient.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): 60%.
Meredith Grey / Annie Connors OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I never would have said that stuff.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): The mic shouldn't have been on.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I didn't realize she could hear me.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Well, now you won't realize your chance to scrub in.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You're banned from the OR, mine or anyone else's, all week.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I got the history on the tumor.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): It's been growing for a year and a half.
Dr. Karev / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): A year and a half, and it's the first time she's even had it looked at.
Dr. Karev / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): It's like she's fatally lazy.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Why doesn't she get banned?
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Go prep Anna Connors for surgery.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You're scrubbing in with Christina.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Really?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I mean, thank you.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Um, OK.
Nurse or Intern (possibly Alex Karev) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): We just need to recheck your labs and get an EKG, so I just need to take a little blood.
Annie / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Dr. Burke is great, and Dr. Bailey.
Medical Professional (likely Alex Karev) / Annie Connors OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I know you're probably scared.
Annie's Mother / Annie Connors OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): That's OK, kitten.
Annie / Annie Connors (PVM): It can just do your job.
Annie Connors: You don't have to talk to the fat, nasty tumor lady.
Annie Connors: I mean, I let her get this bad, how much sympathy do I deserve?
Alex Karev / Mr. LaVangie OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Why did you let it get this bad?
Annie Connors: I'm the first person since I got here to ask me that.
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Well, I guess it's just like the elephant in the room.
Annie Connors: Elephant?
Annie Connors: I mean... It's more like a giant sow, don't you think?
Annie Connors: Every time I went to the hospital, someone died.
Annie Connors: All four of my grandparents, then my dad.
Annie Connors: My best friend's mom, my baby sister, they all went in, never came out.
Annie Connors: So I put it off.
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You know, you're not the only one to put things off.
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I mean, I never do anything to the last possible minute.
Annie Connors: Like what?
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Well... I've had this thing from my roommate since, like, day one, and I just...
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I can't tell her.
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You know, she probably wouldn't go out with me anyway, but how do I know that for sure if I don't ever ask?
Annie Connors: Seriously?
Annie Connors: You're equating your pathetic love life with my record-breaking tumor.
Cristina Yang / Annie Connors (PVM): Seriously.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): It's just that he blatantly favors me in front of her and then blatantly dismisses me.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): How do you know he was favoring you?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Look, you've got a brain.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You got into this program.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Just because Shepard likes to munch your cookies doesn't mean that you didn't deserve what you work for.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): But he's making me look bad.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I have to end it.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Right.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): It's over.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Uh-huh.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Is it true you get to scrub in on that tumor?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Don't sit here.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You get to scrub in?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): How psyched are you?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): On a scale of one to ecstatic?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Ecstatic?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): It's unbelievable.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): You know what I think?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I think Burke wants to get into your scrubs.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Why are you sitting here?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): to kick me off that surgery for the same crap you pull every day.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You know what?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): If I stuck this fork into his thigh, would I get in trouble?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Not if you make it look like an accident.
Alex Karev / Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Hey.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Hi.
George O'Malley / Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Hey.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Hello.
Dr. Alex Karev: Thank God, ma'am.
Dr. Alex Karev: I'm drowning in estrogen here.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Look, uh, is everything OK?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Shepard's a jackass.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Really?
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Annie Connors (PVM): I think he's kind of great.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You reamed her out when I bailed.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Why?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Annie Connors (PVM): Because he's a jackass.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Well, bad days are bad.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Maybe tonight, uh, if you, you know, if you drink alcohol.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I mean, we could, all of us, I mean, go out and drink alcohol.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It wouldn't be because of the bad day.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Here you go.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Dude.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Shut up.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): How's your back?
George O'Malley / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Still good.
Unknown (likely an intern or doctor) / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Good.
Unknown (likely an intern or doctor) / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): How are you?
Unknown (likely an intern) / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Can you leave the board for me?
Unknown (likely an intern) / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): I just want to check something.
Unknown (likely a doctor or intern performing an exam) / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Does that feel OK?
Unknown (likely a patient) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Yeah.
Unknown (likely a doctor or intern performing an exam) / Mr. LaVangie's Daughter (PVM): Right here?
Unknown (likely a doctor or intern) / Mr. LaVangie's Daughter (PVM): Did you, Paige?
Unknown (likely a doctor or intern) / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Mr. Navangi, have you given any more thought about the other surgical options we discussed this morning?
Mr. Navangi / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): What?
Mr. Navangi / Mr. LaVangie (PVM): Why would I?
Mr. Navangi / Mr. LaVangie (PVM): I already told you, no.
Mr. Navangi / Mr. LaVangie (PVM): I'm letting you cut into my back.
Mr. Navangi / Mr. LaVangie (PVM): But that's not enough for you.
Mr. Navangi / Mr. LaVangie OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): All you guys ever want to do is cut.
Unknown (likely Mr. Navangi's child or family member) / Mr. LaVangie OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Dad, just listen to what he has to say.
Mr. Navangi / Mr. LaVangie's Daughter OR Mr. LaVangie OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I already listened.
Unknown (likely a doctor or intern) / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Sir, there's a very small window of opportunity here.
Unknown (likely a doctor or intern) / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Mr. LaVangie (PVM): You know, once the Parkinson's progresses to a point of dementia, there's, you know, you're no longer a candidate for DBS.
Mr. Navangi / Mr. LaVangie (PVM): And when I'm no longer a candidate, is that when you people will leave me the hell alone?
Mr. Navangi / Mr. LaVangie (PVM): What, do I have to start drooling and forget my name to get a little peace and quiet?
Unknown (likely a doctor or intern) / Mr. LaVangie (PVM): I'll check back with you later.
Unknown (likely a doctor or intern) / Mr. LaVangie's Daughter OR Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Mr. LaVangie (PVM): Try to get some rest.
Mr. LaVangie's Daughter: Dad, you're being unreasonable.
Mr. LaVangie's Daughter: The doctors are only trying to help you.
Mr. LaVangie: It's my damn life, and it's my damn brain.
Mr. LaVangie: You want me to let them cut up my brain while I'm lying here awake?
Mr. LaVangie: For what?
Mr. LaVangie's Daughter: Dad.
Mr. LaVangie: I'll be at your wedding.
Mr. LaVangie: I will sit in the back.
Mr. LaVangie: Your uncle will walk you down the aisle.
Mr. LaVangie / Mr. LaVangie (PVM): I know it's not perfect, but it's life.
Mr. LaVangie / Mr. LaVangie (PVM): Life is messy sometimes.
Mr. LaVangie's Daughter / Mr. LaVangie (PVM): I know that.
Mr. LaVangie: If she knows, then what the hell are we still talking for, huh?
Mr. LaVangie: Why in hell can't she drop it?
Meredith / Mr. LaVangie's Daughter (PVM): It is your life.
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): But it's her life, too.
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): And you have a chance to get better here.
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): And all she's asking you to do is try.
Intern (possibly George or Izzie) / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Annie Connors OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): If they pull this off, I'm totally calling Oprah.
Attending Surgeon (possibly Derek or Burke) / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You two been working out?
Intern (possibly George or Izzie) / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Um, sometimes I jog, and I try to take the stairs whenever possible.
Attending Surgeon (possibly Derek or Burke) / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Why?
Attending Surgeon (possibly Derek or Burke) / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): See that large pile of tumor?
Attending Surgeon (possibly Derek or Burke) / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You're going to be retracting it for the next 14 hours.
Attending Surgeon / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm just saying, I hope you have strong backs.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Dr. Shepherd.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: Yes?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Mr. LaVange has agreed to DBS.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): If we do it today.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): If he leaves, he won't come back.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Don't worry, Dr. Shepard.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): It'll take hours before we get around to the spy.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I'll page you.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: All right, then.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Unknown (PVM): Let's do it.
Nurse / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Dr. Cartwright needs ICU.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Dr. Bailey.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I didn't know that he was my boss when I met him.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I didn't know.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I don't care.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Really?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): He sort of seemed to not be talking to me, so I... You see this, what's happening right here?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): This is the problem with you sleeping with my boss.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Not whether or not you knew him before, but how it affects my day.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): And me standing here talking to you about your sex life affects my day.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: And the longer this little fling goes on, the more favors you get over the others who are fighting tooth and nail just to make it through this program without any assistance.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: When those people start finding out what's going on, and they don't want to work with you, and talk to you, or look at you, and they start bitching and moaning at me, the more it affects my day.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: So no, Dr. Gray, I don't care what you knew or when you knew it.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): We understood.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Yes.
Miranda Bailey / Annie Connors OR Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Do it.
Meredith Grey / Annie Connors (PVM): This sucks.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Yeah, well, I'm not a real fan of yours either.
Meredith Grey / Annie Connors (PVM): Not you this.
George O'Malley / Annie Connors (PVM): Everyone else is scrubbed in somewhere.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Right side.
George O'Malley / Annie Connors OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): We have the room and the floor.
Cristina Yang / Annie Connors (PVM): Great.
Cristina Yang / Annie Connors (PVM): Want to do it in the stairwell?
George O'Malley / Annie Connors (PVM): I'm just saying, you never know what could happen.
Meredith Grey / Annie Connors (PVM): I'm changing.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): I'll pet you if I need you.
George O'Malley / Annie Connors OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You do that.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You're so my favorite person today.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): We need to hang another bag of un-egg.
Meredith Grey / Mr. LaVangie's Daughter OR Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm cauterizing the small bleeders to keep my visual field clean.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Alex Karev OR Mr. LaVangie's Daughter (PVM): God, is your bag killing you?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): George, shut up.
Unknown (likely an intern or nurse) / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Mr. LaVangie's Daughter (PVM): We're in here.
Unknown (possibly a doctor or nurse entering) / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Hold it right there.
Doctor (likely Izzie Stevens) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Mrs. Harker, let me show you these chest films.
Doctor (likely Izzie Stevens) / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): We were able to relieve the obstruction of his chest tube, so the buildup of fluids you see here should resolve itself soon.
Another intern (possibly George O'Malley) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Which translates as he should be home in no time.
Mrs. Harker / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He was making waffles.
Doctor (likely Izzie Stevens) / Annie Connors (PVM): I'm sorry?
Mrs. Harker / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): He was mixing the batter and...
Mrs. Harker / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): And then he was on the floor.
Nurse or Doctor (likely a nurse) / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Izzy, we need a central line run in 204.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Hey, Dr. Karev, will you?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He's not answering.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I'm so sorry.
Izzie Stevens / Annie Connors OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I'll be back.
Alex Karev / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Like what you see, right?
Surgical Nurse / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Neurosponge?
Doctor (possibly Derek Shepherd) / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): How you doing, Mr. LaVangie?
Mr. LaVangie: All right.
Surgical Nurse or Intern / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Drill bit's charged.
Alex Karev / Mr. LaVangie OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Where's Blondie?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm right here.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Can you see me?
George O'Malley / Mr. LaVangie (PVM): I'm shaky.
Miranda Bailey / Mr. LaVangie (PVM): I'm not blind.
Miranda Bailey / Mr. LaVangie (PVM): If anything goes wrong here, I'm blaming you.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, OK.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): In that case, I'll stay where you can see me.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Mr. LaVangie OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Now we just have to drill a hole and try to find the spot that controls the motor function.
George O'Malley / Mr. LaVangie (PVM): I can't see my brain from there.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Mr. LaVangie OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Aren't you supposed to be learning something?
George O'Malley / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I'm good right here.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): OK, Mr. LaVangie.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Just take a couple deep breaths.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Focus on the pretty girl.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): OK, this is going to sound really scary, but try and relax.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You shouldn't feel a thing.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Any pain here?
Mr. LaVangie / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): No.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Here?
Mr. LaVangie / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): OK.
A nurse / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Dr. Stevens, I need you to check the x-ray in 2103.
A nurse / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): 2118 needs post-op notes.
A nurse / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): And Jane's wondering if you want her to start feeding 2112.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm going on break.
A nurse / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Okay, yeah, um, before you do that, could you page Dr. Karev again?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I already paged him.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Yeah, again.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): A little more pressure.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): That's good.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Hold it right there.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Long and slow.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): I don't envy those two.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): They've been holding that thing for eight hours.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Their arms have to be ready to fall off.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Look at the size of this artery.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): My God.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): It's as thick as a thumb.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You ever seen a vessel this size?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): No.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): This thing is feeding on all our blood.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): We need more O negative.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I'll call the blood bank.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Damn it, O'Malley.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Do you want me to kill this patient?
Dr. George O'Malley: No, I'm sorry.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I mean, is the auto retracting just too much for you?
Dr. George O'Malley: No, I was, uh, uh, I had an itch.
Unknown Resident / Annie Connors (PVM): Way to go, George.
Izzie Stevens / Annie Connors (PVM): Nicely done.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Just keep trying, Mr. LaVangie.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Mimic my motions.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You can do it.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You're doing great, Mr. LaVangie.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Just a little longer.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Mr. LaVangie (PVM): Take a breath and try again.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): One more time, Mr. LaVangie.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): The probe is almost in.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You'll know it when we find the right spot.
Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Well, how about that?
Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): There it is.
Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Mr. LaVangie (PVM): I'll be a cinema bitch.
Alex Karev / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Bailey was on the warpath and was trying to protect you.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You trying to protect me is why she's on the warpath.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You can't do me favors.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You can't ask me to scrub in when I haven't earned it.
Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Okay.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Okay.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): And you can't treat me like crap when I haven't earned that either.
Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Okay.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I can take care of myself.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I got myself into this mess and I... And you'll get yourself out?
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I don't... know that yet.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Don't let me keep you.
Unknown / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): You did great work here today.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Dr. Shepard.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: Yeah.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Sorry I called you a jackass.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: You didn't.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I did.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Twice.
Unknown / Mr. LaVangie (PVM): Tell you what, Blondie.
Unknown / Mr. LaVangie (PVM): If you don't marry him, I will.
Unknown / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): No, no, no, Jimmy.
Unknown / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): No, no, Jimmy, no.
Unknown / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): We got pressure plummeted to 64 over 22, and he has runs of V-tech that aren't perfusing CVPs sky high.
Unknown / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Give him dopamine.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): 10 mics.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): He's already maxed out.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): The resident was here an hour ago, but I can't reach him now.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Of course.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Of course you can't.
Unknown / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): What is the matter with you?
Unknown / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Get her out of here.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): No.
Nurse / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Ma'am.
Nurse / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Mrs. Harper, you have to get out of here.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm thinking I have myocardial ischemia.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): No, it's a clot.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Pick one.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Page someone.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Page anyone.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): It's top or not.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You'll be dead.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You have to open him up right here, right now.
Mrs. Harper / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You said he was okay.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Get out of here now!
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You have to cut.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I can't.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I've never even seen it done.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I could kill him.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Do nothing.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You'll kill him faster.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): What's your glove size?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Six.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Oh, God.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Take a breath, Dr. Stevens.
Unknown (likely Cristina Yang or another surgeon) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): She has to move over there.
Unknown (likely Cristina Yang or another surgeon) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Walter, move out of the way.
Unknown (likely Dr. Shepherd or Cristina Yang) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Cut the stitches and then the staples.
Unknown (likely Dr. Shepherd or Cristina Yang) / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Don't let them fall into the chest cavity.
Unknown (likely Cristina Yang or Meredith Grey) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Wait.
Unknown (likely Cristina Yang or Meredith Grey) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I've never cracked a chest before.
Unknown (likely Cristina Yang or Meredith Grey) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Oh, god.
Unknown (likely Cristina Yang or Meredith Grey) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): No pulse.
Unknown (likely Dr. Shepherd or another surgeon) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Light complex rhythm.
Unknown (likely Cristina Yang or Meredith Grey) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I can't get this clot out.
Unknown (likely Cristina Yang or Meredith Grey) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I need more suction.
Unknown (likely Cristina Yang or Meredith Grey) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I need more.
Unknown (likely Dr. Shepherd or another surgeon) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He's brady and down.
Unknown (likely Dr. Shepherd or another surgeon) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You have to get the clot out.
Unknown (likely Cristina Yang or Meredith Grey) / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I can't get it.
Unknown (likely Cristina Yang or Meredith Grey) / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Screw it.
Unknown (likely Cristina Yang or Meredith Grey) / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): I'm using my hand.
Unknown (likely Dr. Shepherd or another surgeon) / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Mr. LaVangie's Daughter (PVM): The size of that heart.
Unknown (likely Dr. Shepherd or another surgeon) / Mr. LaVangie's Daughter (PVM): Anything?
Unknown (likely Cristina Yang or Meredith Grey) / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): No.
Unknown (likely Dr. Shepherd or another surgeon) / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Mr. LaVangie's Daughter OR Mr. LaVangie's Daughter OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You have to massage the heart, doctor.
Unknown (likely Dr. Shepherd or another surgeon) / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Come on.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Come on.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Come on, please.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Come on, Mr. Harper.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): We have a pulse.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): How's it going?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): It's more intertwined than the studies made it look.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm down ten units of blood, and I haven't even flipped it yet.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, wow.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Look at that.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Now, how am I supposed to get around that artery?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): We'll get...
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Uh, right then.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Uh, forceps.
Cristina Yang / Annie Connors OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): There you go.
Alex Karev / Annie Connors OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Excuse me.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): God, it's unbelievable.
Alex Karev / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Right?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): How did she live like that?
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Watch what you say.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): You never know who's listening.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Look at George.
Alex Karev / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Looks like he's about to fall in.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Are you really as shallow and callous as you seem?
Alex Karev / Annie Connors (PVM): Oh, you want to go out for a drink later and hear about my secret pain?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Does that line ever work for you?
Alex Karev / Annie Connors (PVM): Sometimes.
Meredith Grey / Annie Connors OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Must be because you look like that.
Alex Karev / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Like what?
Alex Karev / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): So is that a yes?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): No.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I can't.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm seeing someone.
Alex Karev / Annie Connors OR Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Look, you don't want to go out with me.
Alex Karev / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Just say so.
Alex Karev / Annie Connors (PVM): No need to lie.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I don't want to go out with you.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): But I think I really might be seeing someone.
Bailey / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): No, we're OK.
George O'Malley / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): We're still in the middle of surgery.
Bailey / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Mr. Harper, the post-op heart patient at 2114.
Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I had to open Mr. Anonymy bedside.
George O'Malley / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): What?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): What?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): What?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): What?
Bailey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): He had cardiac tamponade.
Doctor (likely attending or resident) / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): His chest films were clean this morning.
Doctor (possibly same as previous) / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): It's just it happened fast.
Doctor (possibly same as previous) / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): He was in PEA.
Doctor (possibly same as previous) / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): There was no time.
Surgical Assistant or Nurse / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Go ahead, I got it.
Surgical Nurse or Doctor / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): We're OK here.
Lead Surgeon / Annie Connors OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Book it.
Surgeon / Annie Connors OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Yeah, I need some retractions.
Surgeon / Annie Connors OR Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Pull back on the retractor.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Annie Connors (PVM): You opened a heart bedside and you couldn't even page me?
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Annie Connors (PVM): But needed all the glory for yourself, right?
Dr. Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Annie Connors (PVM): I paged you 50 times.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Do you have any idea what I've been through?
Dr. George O'Malley / Annie Connors (PVM): Oh, man.
Dr. George O'Malley / Annie Connors (PVM): The battery, I forgot to change it.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): You forgot?
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): You are hateful.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You are hateful, hateful, lazy, arrogant, hateful man.
Dr. Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Ever a dull moment here at Seattle Grants?
Dr. Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh!
Dr. Izzie Stevens / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, my God.
Dr. Izzie Stevens / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Oh, goodness.
Unknown (likely surgeon, possibly Dr. Burke or Dr. Bailey) / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Get right in there.
Unknown (likely surgeon, possibly Dr. Burke or Dr. Bailey) / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Get it close.
Unknown (likely surgeon, possibly Dr. Burke or Dr. Bailey) / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Give me a clamp.
Unknown (likely surgical assistant or nurse) / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): We need more blood.
Unknown (likely surgeon, possibly Dr. Burke or Dr. Bailey) / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Give me some suction here.
Unknown (likely surgeon, possibly Dr. Burke or Dr. Bailey) / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): I can't see what I'm doing.
Unknown (likely surgeon, possibly Dr. Burke or Dr. Bailey) / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Clamp, clamp, clamp, clamp, please.
Unknown (likely surgeon, possibly Dr. Burke or Dr. Bailey) / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Is there any blood in the rapid infuser?
Unknown (likely nurse or surgical tech) / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): We're waiting on two units.
Unknown (likely surgeon, possibly Dr. Burke or Dr. Bailey) / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): What do you mean you're waiting?
Unknown (likely nurse or surgical tech) / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Well, we didn't anticipate this much blood last night.
Unknown (likely nurse or surgical tech) / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): We prepped a double supply.
Unknown (likely nurse or surgical tech) / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): We've used it all.
Unknown (likely surgeon, possibly Dr. Burke or Dr. Bailey) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): What did you cut?
Unknown (likely nurse or surgical tech) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Nothing.
Unknown (likely nurse or surgical tech) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): It just blew.
Unknown (likely surgeon, possibly Dr. Burke or Dr. Bailey) / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): She came in with too much damage.
Unknown (likely surgeon, possibly Dr. Burke or Dr. Bailey) / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): The artery walls are too weak.
Unknown (likely nurse or surgical tech) / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): She's tested for 10 units of O negative.
Unknown (likely nurse or surgical tech) / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Here.
Unknown (possibly George O'Malley or another intern) / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Can I see?
Unknown (possibly surgeon or nurse) / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): What's this?
Unknown (likely surgeon, possibly Dr. Bailey or Dr. Burke) / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): George, give me your hand.
Preston Burke / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Push right down here.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Pull it towards you.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Suction.
Preston Burke / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Suction.
Surgical Nurse / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Pressure's dropping.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): She needs blood.
Preston Burke / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Where the hell is the blood?
Preston Burke / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Just squeeze it off right there.
Surgical Nurse / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Is that O negative for R1?
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Uh-huh.
Surgical Nurse / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): O R1.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): O R1, right?
Surgical Nurse / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Yeah.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): I got it.
Preston Burke / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Some suction, please.
Preston Burke / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): In here now.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Come on.
Surgical Nurse / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): We're losing her now.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Look at this.
Preston Burke / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Look at this.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Come on.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, come on.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Come on.
Doctor or Surgeon / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Time of death is 1142.
Meredith (voiceover) / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): The early bird catches the worm.
Meredith (voiceover) / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): A stitch in time saves nine.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Messy.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm sorry.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Don't be.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You saved this life.
Meredith (voiceover) / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Mr. LaVangie's Daughter (PVM): You found all the words you need.
Meredith (voiceover) / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Mr. LaVangie's Daughter (PVM): He who hesitates is lost.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I just grumble.
Meredith (voiceover) / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): We can't pretend we haven't been told.
Meredith (voiceover) / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): We've all heard the proverbs, heard the philosophers, heard our grandparents warning us about wasted time, heard the damn poets urging us to seize the day.
Meredith (voiceover) / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Still, sometimes, we have to see for ourselves.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Mr. LaVangie (PVM): I'm not doing you any more favors.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): This was it.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I have been holding up 50 pounds of tumor for the past 12 hours.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): My back's gonna need traction, and the patient died anyways.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You think you did me a favor?
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Look, I'm just... What is this?
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): that we're doing here.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): What is it?
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You need a definition?
Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You really want to be that guy.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): We have to make our own mistakes.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Lock the door.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): We have to learn our own lessons.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Have you seen Meredith?
Alex Karev / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Save yourself the misery, man.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): She's off the market.
George O'Malley / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): What?
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): No, that's not.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): We're just friends.
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Whatever.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): But she's not.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I mean, if she was seeing someone, I live with her.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I would know it.
Dr. Meredith Grey: We have to sweep today's possibility under tomorrow's rug until we can't anymore, until we finally understand for ourselves
Dr. Meredith Grey: what Benjamin Franklin meant.
Dr. Meredith Grey: That knowing is better than wondering.
Dr. Meredith Grey: That waking is better than sleeping.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I know this place where there's an amazing view of sunrise over the ferry boats.
Dr. Meredith Grey: I have a thing for fairy boats.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: I remember.
Dr. Meredith Grey: And that even the biggest failure, even the worst, most intractable mistake, beats the hell out of never trying.
Meredith Grey / Unknown (PVM): Thank you.