- Previously on Grey's
Anatomy: - He's gone.
It's over. So over.
Dr. Burke handed in his letter
of resignation two weeks ago.
- I was named chief resident.
- I would have made
an excellent chief.
- We're breaking up.
- It was a breakup kiss.
A breakup kiss.
I'm Lexie. Lexie
Grey. I'm your sister.
Why are you avoiding me?
I'm all alone in the forest.
All alone in the forest.
- Where are you?
- I love you too.
In the hospital, we
see addiction every day.
I feel this... this...
this exhilaration.
It's like I finally
figured it out.
You know, it's like when... It's
like I was sleeping and I woke up.
And it's just...
It's just amazing.
♪ From my heart to yours... ♪
It's shocking,
how many kinds
of addiction exist.
This is the best breakup ever.
I don't know why we
didn't a long time ago.
- What are you doing?
- Sleeping.
- No, no sleepovers.
- Yes, come on.
- It's three in the morning.
- No. Broken up people
don't sleep over.
Sex is the only part of
the relationship that works.
Why screw it up with
everything? Dinner. Conversations.
You're mocking my
severe emotional limitations.
I can live without conversation,
meals or sleepovers...
We shouldn't have
sleepovers. You snore.
But mockery, I don't
know. That's a deal breaker.
OK. Sex and mockery it is.
It would be too easy
if it was just drugs and
booze and cigarettes.
She said she loved
me and you know what?
My dad... Oh, God, he loved
her and... and, you know,
when he died, then... I...
I shouldn't have gotten married.
I think the hardest part of
kicking a habit is wanting to kick it.
I mean, we get addicted
for a reason, right?
♪ From my heart to yours ♪
I thought it was right,
but it wasn't. It's not.
- It's not.
- No.
Often, too often, things that start
out as just a normal part of your life,
at some point cross
the line to obsessive.
Compulsive. Out of control.
I... I got to tell her.
I have to tell her that the marriage
is over. It's the right thing to do.
♪ And there's no
denying our love is real... ♪
Did you see how I
walked out determined?
It made me proud.
♪ From my heart to yours ♪
It's the high we're chasing.
The high that makes
everything else...
fade away.
He loves me too.
What do you think of the board?
Good. Looks good.
You did a good job.
I didn't do it. I'm delegating.
I am being a delegator.
I'm doing it all different.
Making time for my wife.
Oh, yeah? She
talking to you yet?
Will when she
sees I'm a delegator.
- I should move
that surgery up there.
- Junkie.
Yeah, right, right.
It's good. It's fine.
I'm delegating.
Being a delegator.
- What's wrong
with the chief?
- He's a junkie.
Him? You're the one
who looks all strung out.
- I'm just tired.
- Let me guess.
You and Meredith are up all
night doing the horizontal salsa.
Mambo. Horizontal mambo.
Meredith and I, we're just friends.
- Sexy friends.
- You're the most juvenile
- human being I've met.
- The first step to recovery
is admitting you have a problem.
How many nurses you slept with?
That's not a problem,
man. That's an adventure.
- It is beautiful.
- It's the Belgian
Flip Round Pro.
- What do you want?
- What do you got?
Next projectile vomiter,
I lose your pager.
I know you better. Surgeries,
baby, preferably cardio.
Are these all wedding gifts?
She's giving them away.
Dibs on the Mixmaster.
I'm not giving
you the Mixmaster.
You're supposed to return them.
Burke registered for this crap.
Now I'm the one stuck dealing with it.
I'm using it for
professional gain.
You're ready to part with this?
She's not! I want it. I want it.
I am if I help on
the rhomboid flap
in your next Mohs defect repair.
Come to Daddy.
- You steal this?
- Make her
give me something.
- Give her something.
- Mixmaster!
Face it. You have
nothing I want.
Would you look at the residents.
Big, snazzy residents. Standing
around, playing with housewares.
Turn a blind eye, the
soup tureen's yours.
Four! Take this Mix... Hey!
Take the Mixmaster and all
this crap and put in my locker.
Carnage in the pit.
My day's improving.
Follow.
- We're not gonna round?
- Carnage trumps rounds.
Write that down.
Carnage trumps rounds.
- Callie.
- Oh, hey. I know, I know.
I never made it home. Got
swamped with paperwork
and fell asleep
in an on-call room.
I need to talk when
you have time.
I have no time.
This chief resident
thing is kicking my ass.
- Later then? Tonight when we're alone.
- Is it serious?
What do we got?
Uh, gas main blew in a
building. Five injured. Some badly.
Excellent. Horrible.
It's horrible. Sad.
Marla Kristler, 34-year-old female,
abdomen blown out, skull fracture,
third-degree burns over
40 percent of her body.
OK, I got this. Open OR Two.
Page Dr. Shepherd.
Torres, triage the rest.
Yes. Yang, you're
with the chief.
Thank you. One,
Four, come with me.
- What about us?
- Uh, go help Bailey
in the clinic.
My wife came in another
ambulance. Is she here?
- Straight to surgery. Are you injured?
- No. My son.
Eighteen months old.
Contusion, possible head injury.
BP and pulse are elevated.
- Everything's
going to be OK, baby.
- Karev!
- I'm supposed
to be on plastics.
- I'll take it.
- Karev. You're
with the Kristlers.
- What about me?
Were you up late last night?
You look tired. Perhaps
you should sit this out.
I'm fine. Not up late.
Went to bed early.
Early and alone.
- Hello, Mr...
- Roche. Archie Roche.
"Age 60, second, third-degree
burns, chest, upper abdomen,
facial contusions and fracture."
Reading the sports section, next
I'm looking up at a hole in the ceiling
- in Dave and Marla's apartment.
- Burns should be débrided.
We'll do a trauma series
and shoulder films. Stevens.
- Got it.
- Where's your pain?
Just promise me you'll take
care of Marla and the baby.
- Are they your family, sir?
- They might as well be.
How close to the
explosion was he?
We were in the living room.
His mom was in the kitchen and...
- Did the gas line blow?
- I think it was the stove.
Gonna run some
tests on the baby.
Karev, I'm going into surgery
with the chief. Keep me posted.
Marla and David are friends.
I was just leaving when
the kitchen blew up.
The blast knocked
me into a wall.
Have you seen this?
Grim. You guys look grim.
Clark, we need to get a CT
just to check for internal bleeding.
Internal bleeding? I
was on my way to work.
I need a resident to help me in
the clinic to oversee the new interns
- while I'm working
on this patient.
- I'm sorry. I can't help.
- You can't help?
- The clinic
is voluntary, Bailey.
I'm not gonna force residents
with this much going on.
You can have as many
interns as you need.
Tell Kent he's got to
find himself another OR.
- The chief's taking his.
- OK.
- Waffle maker.
- We covered this.
- But now I got
something you want.
- Yeah? What?
Hello. I'm Jane Burke.
Dr. Burke's mother.
Nice to see you.
I'm looking for a
Dr. Cristina Yang.
Yang, Yang. Let
me see. Dr. Yang...
I'll page her. But I
think she's in surgery.
I'll wait.
- Waffle maker?
- Fine.
- Hey. What's the 911?
- Mama is here.
I'm working with Callie.
Got to find George.
- Your mother? What?
- Not my mother. Mama is here.
- George? He's your intern.
- Burke's mom.
Make the synapses
fire more quickly.
I was with a patient.
I'd be happy to go back.
- No, help.
- I'll help.
For Mixmaster and
George's location.
Yang, you scrubbing in?
Yes, sir. Absolutely.
Just get rid of
her, OK? Politely.
- What?
- George!
Hey. Hey. It's OK. Brian,
I'm here. It's OK, sweetheart.
Brian, stop crying,
baby. I can't think.
- Why won't he stop crying?
- Hey there, Brian.
You're a big boy.
Do you work out?
You take care of yourself.
Dr. Karev. CT results.
Should I page Shepherd?
- He's in surgery. Let me take a look.
- What do you see?
- There's nothing acute.
- Nothing? So he's
going to be OK?
Yeah, I'm gonna... I need to
run a couple more tests, OK?
Schedule an MRI and have the
lab run a tox screen on Brian's blood.
- Why?
- I said so, Nancy Drew. Just do it.
Rooms one and seven are private
and should be used for
conversations with patients,
not for closed door socializing.
All carts are set up the same.
- Memorize where everything is.
- Will we do procedures
on our own?
No, you are interns. You
are in charge of nothing.
All procedures will be discussed
and overseen by an upper level,
all charts will be signed
out by an upper level,
and all patients will be looked
at by someone other than you!
And what if...? Ooh! I'm sorry.
I... Sorry. What if
we can't find anyone?
Mrs. Burke!
What a surprise to see you
here. Are you visiting someone?
- You're the maid of honor. Miss Grey.
- That's me.
When you stood up in front of
Preston's friends and loved ones
and you said, "It's over,
it's over, it's so over,"
were you trying to smash
the hopes of the best man
or were you just
trying to be funny?
- I...
- Because making light
of that situation
would be inappropriate.
And to use that moment
to send a message
to your boyfriend,
well, that's selfish.
So were you being inappropriate
or were you being selfish?
I... am...
I apologize for that,
Mrs. Mama. Ma'am.
I'm just gonna go. OK.
- Miss Grey?
- Yes, ma'am.
When you report
back to Cristina,
would you tell her, please,
that I am waiting for her?
And that I will
continue to wait for her.
Yes, ma'am.
- Oh! Sorry. Sorry.
- Any news on Marla?
My neighbor?
I promise as soon as I hear
something, I'll give you an update.
Crap! Sorry. I'm really
sorry. Really sorry.
Three-part proximal
humerus fracture.
Percutaneous reduction
and internal fixation.
That boy of theirs,
Brian. Gorgeous.
And sometimes
they're not. The kids.
Sometimes they're ugly.
You have any kids, doctor?
Not that I know of.
You're not married
either, are you?
I'm afraid I haven't found
anybody who will put up with me.
Well, get on the stick.
Don't do like I did.
Don't be a bachelor
your whole life.
You can only play
the field for so long.
Then, suddenly, one day,
your whole life passes you by.
Those parts aren't
working like they used to.
They have medicine for that.
They don't have medicine
for that all alone part, do they?
No, I suppose not.
You got some
pretty ones right here.
I'm off the market, Mr. Roche.
I'm very happily married.
I'm really sorry.
Sorry.
You can't tell her.
We decided. I was supposed
to tell her. I have to tell her.
No. I know. You can't.
You just... You can't, OK?
I'm working with
her. She's my boss.
- Damn it!
- Shh!
Maybe it'll just work itself out
if we wait. You'll grow apart.
- Izzie.
- She's working
long hours.
Maybe she's avoiding
you, having an affair.
- Izzie!
- Don't tell her.
How long would you suggest
I wait until I tell her about us?
I don't know.
At least until she's not in such
a bad mood. A week. A month.
I'm sorry.
But... Well, then,
you know... We can't...
I know.
Then you better walk away.
I better walk away.
Yeah, I really better walk away.
Hey. So George has Clark in line for his
CT and we're waiting on his blood work.
- Grey.
- Yes?
OK, I need you to
work in the clinic, Grey.
- Well...
- No.
Before you tell me the
reasons why you can't,
just let me say this.
I need this because
I have idiots.
You understand me, Grey?
Idiot interns are
down there in my clinic,
a clinic dripping with my
blood, sweat and tears.
And I am not convinced,
not at all convinced,
that they will not burn it
down with their ineptitude.
Look... No, I'm not telling.
Because I understand I do
not have the authority to tell.
So I'm asking. Nicely.
OK, I'm just saying, if I
ever did anything for you,
like, I don't know,
save your life...
If you ever felt you
owed me a debt of thanks,
now is when I'd like to collect.
Please.
Oh, no.
Hey. Are you working
down here today?
- I don't know. I...
- Great! No idea
what we're doing.
Plus, I was really hoping we'd
get a chance to speak, so, yay.
Yay.
I can't believe
this. This is surreal.
- You're claustrophobic?
- No.
I'm not claustrophobic, it's
just... I was on my way to work.
On my way to work and
stopped at a friend's house
and the next thing you know I'm
in a CAT scan machine. It's like...
How did this happen?
- Dr. Karev?
- Baby. It's OK.
Lab work?
- It's crazy, isn't it?
- Stay here.
Stay and do not leave. Do not
leave that man alone with that child.
Sweetie. Hey. Hey.
Dr. Yang, was that Dr. Burke's
mother I saw in the waiting room earlier?
- Mrs. Burke is here?
- I don't think...
- I wouldn't know.
- How we doing
up there, Shepherd?
Good. She's looks
good from my end.
It's the best part about the job.
Giving good people second chances.
Believe me, I know. I get it.
You know, it's life. It happens.
You're going down one path,
and all of a sudden then you realize,
"No, no, no.
This is the wrong
path. This is...
No, this isn't the path for me."
And it's good because you learn.
And you realize that you
can handle it. And you can.
You can handle this. You...
Clark?
Clark! Clark! Code blue!
We need a crash cart in here!
Chief.
The one-year-old? Brian
Kristler? He's strung out on meth.
- What?
- It was a meth lab
that blew up.
This woman and her husband
are running a meth lab.
- Oh...
- Clear!
Ah, yes, the joys of surgeondom.
Saving lives for those
who deserve it most.
Tell Dr. Torres to follow
exposure protocol for children.
- I'm counting on her
to take care of this.
- Got it.
Sure you don't want to page somebody
to take over so you can go handle that?
I'm trying to get
back with my wife.
In order to get back with
my wife, I have to learn to...
Delegate.
Dr. Torres can handle this.
- Shooting him up?
- They weren't.
When you cook meth, the
fumes coat the walls, the floors.
The baby crawls around,
puts its hands in its mouth.
- It gets in his bloodstream.
- God. OK.
Call the police
and social services.
What about the
dad? He's still in there.
Call the police. They
take care of the dad.
You take care of the baby.
Sloan! We got a situation.
You're doing a fine job.
You were acting awfully odd
before. Had me a little nervous.
Mr. Roche, I'm gonna
ask you a question.
I don't want you
to be offended by it,
but the answer could
affect your surgery.
- Fine. Fire away.
- Are you
a crystal meth user?
You're kidding,
right? He's, like, 60.
No judgment. I need
a yes or no answer.
- Crystal what?
- It's a drug, sir.
It's addictive and
very dangerous.
Unless you put it in my
blood pressure medicine,
I've never touched the stuff.
What's going on?
The Kristlers had a meth lab in their
apartment. It caused the explosion.
Marla and Dave had a
drug lab in their apartment?
No. Impossible. Absolutely not.
I've known those
two for five years.
We've gone on picnics, to
ball games. I baby-sit for them.
I baby-sit for drug dealers?
- O'Malley!
- What happened?
- He coded.
- He coded?
Coded. Out of nowhere.
Heart stopped, coded.
- Probably a drug addict.
- What?
I came to tell you.
That fire that he was in?
It was a meth lab explosion.
He could have cardiomyopathy.
- That would explain it.
- It's a miracle
I got him back.
- You ran the code? Where's Grey?
- She's covering in the clinic.
What is she doing in the
clinic? I told you to take interns.
I didn't want interns.
Sorry about that.
Some things, O'Malley, some
things just don't need to be told.
- How about here? Does it hurt here?
- Weird.
- It feels weird?
- No, that lady
is staring at me.
Or my fat.
Don't worry, she's
staring at me.
I'll be right back, OK?
- Well?
- How'd surgery go
on the mom?
She'll live. That's not the
mom I'm worried about.
I tried. I tried. Mama is not
budging. And she is very scary.
Yeah, obviously.
What does she want?
Did Burke send her?
I don't know. I
mean, you have to go.
You have to go deal with Mama.
Just go get it over with. Come
back and tell me all about it
because I could
use a pick-me-up.
Mama Showdown is
not for your enjoyment.
Besides, my patient is stable and
until I'm paged I'm gonna stay right here.
OK, she keeps staring
at us. Make her to stop.
- You.
- You're her sister.
I'm an only child.
You're her resident.
If you have time to stare, you have
time to get me coffee! So move, move!
Two, stay!
Hmm. Now see? If you
could just do that with Mama.
Dr. Dell to the NICU.
- Mrs. Burke!
- I don't think
I know you.
I'm George O'Malley! I'm a
friend of Burke's. I was Burke's guy.
Oh, hi, George O'Malley,
Burke's friend,
Burke's guy. Please sit.
I guess I have a minute.
One time he let me live on his
sofa when I had no place else to stay.
How is he? Is he OK?
He's Preston. He's a gentleman.
And so he doesn't
like to talk about it.
And I just really don't
know what to say to him.
Maybe, uh... I don't know.
You could tell him
that he dodged a bullet.
I mean, marriage is...
Once you're in, you're in.
Burke is smart, you know.
He didn't make a mistake.
Because a mistake
that, you know...
It's hard to take back. Which even
if you want to take back, you can't.
So you can tell him that.
"Once you're in, you're in."
Have that engraved
on your wedding ring
when you get married.
I'm already married.
You're already married?
George O'Malley,
Burke's friend, Burke's guy,
staying in a marriage
out of obligation?
That's no way to live.
It's no way to love.
But I think you know that.
I do.
Sometimes, I do.
Your timing could not be more
perfect. Where are we going?
- What do you mean?
- You paged me, right?
- I did.
- Good. So, on-call room?
I was thinking, maybe,
we could go to the cafeteria.
Thought you might be hungry.
Why are you looking
at me like that?
Derek, we agreed. S and M only.
- S and M?
- Sex and mockery.
- Right, S and M.
- So you're eating lunch?
I am.
- Want to come?
- No.
Meet me in the lobby at
8:00. And eat your dinner first.
Yeah. Great.
That's a big needle. Do you
have to use such a big needle?
His IV came out and
he needs to be hydrated.
OK. OK. Look, I'm...
Look, I'm just freaking
out a little bit here.
Can you give me an
update on my wife?
Your wife has a crater in her
abdomen. If she does survive surgery,
it's gonna be a long,
hard, painful recovery.
She's gonna be OK, right?
I mean, she's got to be OK.
My wife... Brian, sweetheart.
Look at me. Brian. Stop crying.
Brian, please.
Brian, stop crying!
He can't stop crying! OK?
He can't stop crying because
his nervous system is shot.
Because his brain and his
heart and his renal system
are all compromised. He can't stop
crying because he's in withdrawal
from crystal meth,
you son of a bitch.
No, no. That's impossible. He wasn't
in the room when we were making it!
It was all over your
apartment, OK?
I tested him because
I smelled it on his skin.
I love my son. OK.
We were broke.
I lost my job, but
I don't use drugs!
And I'm a good dad
and I love my family!
Well, now you can
love your family from jail.
It's all right. Come on.
I'm sorry.
- Dr. Torres.
- Yeah, chief?
"Yeah, chief"?
Is it that you don't know
what's going on in
my hospital, Dr. Torres,
or that you don't care?
Um, I'm sorry. I
guess I don't know.
I delegated the meth
lab situation to you.
And now one of your residents has
been attacked and a baby is missing.
- I don't understand...
- I don't want excuses.
Finish up here. You better
hope that baby shows up.
- I think you're a good chief resident.
- - What?
I know that you've been
having a hard time with it,
and this thing with the baby,
clearly, it's not an easy job
and I think you're
doing a good job at it.
- I can take it from here.
- What?
Get out of my OR, Stevens. Now!
So the happy little
family makes meth?
There's no such thing
as a happy family.
What's with her?
Well, Mama Burke is here
and we don't know why.
My guess is that she's
here to kill Cristina.
She's hovering again.
If you're done with the charts,
go fold something. Like sheets.
What are you looking
at? Don't look at her.
- Your sister, she's hot.
- I'm an only child.
Don't talk to me about Lexie.
Oh, the police
want to talk to me.
All I want to know is why she's
here. Is that too much to ask?
Hey.
Aah...
He's not returning my
phone calls anymore.
- He's doing his best.
- Mmm.
Do you think...?
Do you think she really
loved him? Cristina?
I think she loved him the
best that she knew how.
That would not have
been enough for you either?
No. No, it wouldn't have
been enough for me either.
So you would have ended it too?
Well, Burke and I
are built differently.
He's stronger than I am.
He was strong enough to...
And we're not built the same.
Honorable men are
all built the same.
- And you think
I'm an honorable man.
- Do you know when to walk away?
Do you know when not to
take less than you deserve?
If you do, then you're
an honorable man.
When you got injured in the
fire, the shock to your body,
combined with the
drugs and the damage,
your heart seized up and
you went into cardiac arrest.
You are also bleeding internally,
so you need to stay for observation.
Which means that you are
probably about to go into withdrawal.
But you can't leave because it is still
quite possible that you'll need surgery.
You got any good
news, Dr. O'Malley?
I wish I could say yes.
Come on. Come on,
come on, come on.
Where are you? Damn it!
- How's the surgery
on the old guy?
- Fine.
- Callie.
- Damn. Can't talk now.
- I have to find a baby.
- Are you OK?
A baby was lost on my watch.
I am chief resident.
I am responsible.
The chief gave this
to me and I blew it,
and now a baby's
missing, so no, I'm not OK!
No.
No, you are not OK.
Plus, I think...
I think my husband's
having an affair.
If that's true, he's an idiot.
If that's true, you
need to talk to him.
You know, as an alternative
to destroying your career.
Um... Dr. Grey.
I was wondering, do you know
where the thermometers are 'cause...?
Do you not know where
the thermometers are
or are you looking
for an excuse to talk?
- I...
- Simple question, Lexie.
Are you an idiot or a stalker?
OK. That was a
mean thing to say.
I'm aware of that because I'm
generally not a mean person.
But I'm a person who just
doesn't want to know you.
And you are a person who's
making that very difficult.
So please, just stop making it so
difficult for me to not know you, OK?
Oh, my God! Brian! Brian!
Please wake up, baby.
Please. Please wake up.
- Mr. Kristler.
- He won't wake up.
He was shaking and then
he just... He won't wake up.
- Let me take him,
Mr. Kristler.
- No. I love my baby.
- I don't want
to leave my baby.
- A seizure.
- Please.
- I don't want
to go to jail.
If you love him,
let me take him.
- It's going to be OK.
- I'm sorry.
- Nurse!
- Baby. Please.
He had a stroke. A one
year old with a stroke.
- You can yell, you know.
- Not my job anymore.
I'm just saying, you can
if you want. I deserve it.
You do deserve it. You
do deserve, Dr. Karev,
to be chastised for your
stunningly poor decision making.
You certainly earned a reprimand
for your unbelievably
destructive tactical error.
You got in the face
of a drug dealer?
You got in the face of a dealer
before the police had arrived?
You got in the face of a felon
while his one-year-old child
was in the room? Are you stupid?
Are you without intelligence?
You were taught better.
I taught you better
than that, Dr. Karev!
Getting in the face
of a drug dealer. Fool!
- Thank you.
- Oh, no, thank you.
I am a nice person. OK. I am.
And I don't know what
it is that I did to you,
but, you know, we
have the same dad.
So I was thinking a
simple conversation...
We don't have the
same dad, Lexie.
You and I? We do
not have the same dad.
My dad disappeared
when I was five years old
and I never saw him. Sound
like the daddy you grew up with?
I kicked a man out of my
bed in the middle of the night,
the world's most perfect man
who loves me. And I can't let him.
And it doesn't take a
shrink to figure out why.
Because our dad chose you.
So I'm sure you are
a very nice girl, Lexie.
But I hope you can understand,
you're not a girl I ever
wanted to have to know.
I never even tried
drugs until I was 30.
Stupid. So stupid.
I went to a party and there was
all this meth floating around and...
I just figured, what the
heck? Once won't kill you.
Then it's more than once.
It's all you think about.
Then you're outside your dealer's
house at 7:00 in the morning.
This isn't me. It isn't.
I'm not this guy. I'm not
this guy. I'm not this guy.
Clark!
Hello.
It took you long enough.
Yes. Well?
I came for Preston's key. I'd
like to pick up some of his things
and the necklace I
gave you for the wedding.
Of course.
Just, uh, leave it under
the mat when you're done.
OK. And I wanted
to say I'm sorry.
I... I've come to
know you, I think.
And what you love
even more than Preston
is being a surgeon.
You are planning to continue
with cardiothoracic surgery
- like my son, am I correct?
- Yes.
So I'm sorry you
lost the man you love.
But more than that, I'm
sorry you lost your teacher.
With him by your side,
you could've become
a brilliant heart surgeon.
- I see.
- You're a strong woman,
Cristina.
I respect that.
I wish I could have
been born at another time.
I might be more like you.
So I shall leave the
key under the mat.
Uh... Can you take the gifts?
There are all these
wedding gifts and I can't...
Can you please take them away?
Of course I can.
He's never coming back, is he?
Not even to say goodbye.
Remember, you're a strong woman.
His heart couldn't take it.
There was just too much damage.
He couldn't take it.
I'm not this guy. I
won't be this guy who...
I'm going to tell her.
- Chief, I...
- I've got paperwork,
Dr. Torres.
Kidnapped babies make
for a lot of paperwork.
I was planning on, maybe,
going to see my wife tonight,
- but instead
I get to do this.
- I could help.
- I mean, I could help.
- No. You've helped enough
for one day.
What?
How did I get...?
Well, you were cooking crystal
meth and the substances exploded.
Where's... Where's my...?
Your husband and your son
sustained only minor injuries.
Although it seems your son had been
passively ingesting methamphetamine.
He suffered a
stroke earlier today
and went into
surgery this afternoon.
I believe the surgery went smoothly.
Your husband was taken by the police
and I'm sure they'll be
wanting to speak to you as well.
Oh. OK. OK, you know
what? Just try to breathe.
Slowly. Slowly.
Breathe.
I'm sure it must feel
as though everything is coming
apart, but you can get through this.
Just breathe.
Breathe.
The thing about addiction
is, it never ends well.
Because eventually,
whatever it is that
was getting us high...
♪ When you look
to the future... ♪
stops feeling good...
and starts to hurt.
Want to grab a drink?
- I have a problem.
- What's up?
No. I'm just...
I'm admitting I...
I have a problem.
♪ Just add kerosene ♪
What's gonna happen
to them? And the baby?
Um...
His grandmother
is coming for him.
I think she's
gonna take custody.
They were it.
They were my family.
Can you imagine?
After 60 years on this planet,
my family is a couple of
drug dealers and their kid.
♪ The nights in the sand dunes ♪
Just because people
do horrible things,
doesn't mean they're
horrible people.
♪ It's the way we built you ♪
♪ That house just
won't come down... ♪
Still, they say you
don't kick the habit
until you hit rock bottom.
♪ My feeble ways ♪
But how do you know
when you're there?
So I take it you
still want to talk?
- Yeah. I do.
- No!
- No, I...
- No! You don't!
George, please. Just...
Please don't say anything.
Please. I'm asking you as your wife.
I am asking you
not to say anything.
I am asking you to just not.
Not tonight.
I am your wife.
Do this for me.
♪ Moon and sun... ♪
OK.
♪ We all move on ♪
Dr. Grey, I'm heading over to
Joe's, you want to grab a drink?
No, thanks. I'm meeting someone.
Yeah. Derek asked
me to track you down.
He's, uh, stuck with a patient.
He's not gonna be
able to meet you.
- He sends his apologies.
- OK.
So... Joe's?
I think I'm going home.
♪ 'Cause we always
felt so good together ♪
♪ But the days
just rolled on by... ♪
Meredith!
Because no matter how
badly a thing is hurting us...
♪ Moon and sun ♪
sometimes letting it
go hurts even worse.
♪ We all move on ♪