Previously on Grey's Anatomy:
You can't help her now.
You don't ask
a lot of personal questions.
And you're very hard to get to know.
Yes.
With your reputation,
Seattle Grace will become
one of the foremost neonatal hospitals.
Got a third trimester burn victim,
Dr. Bailey. I need help.
You show a real gift with my specialty.
I'll be staying in town for a while.
Goodbye, Derek.
Bye, Meredith.
Do you wanna buy me a drink?
When you were a kid,
it was Halloween candy.
You hid it from your parents
and ate it until you got sick.
So, this is where you live?
In college, it was the heady combo
of youth, tequila, and, well, you know.
As a surgeon, you take
as much of the good as you can get,
because it doesn't come around
nearly as often as it should.
Good things
aren't always what they seem.
That was amazing.
Yeah.
Too much of anything, even love,
is not always a good thing.
Did you...
Yeah. I did.
- There's a boy in my bed.
-  What's his name?
Um... Steve.
- Where'd you find him?
- Joe's.
- Guess where I am?
- Where?
Burke's apartment.
He went to the hospital.
He left me here alone.
You're going through his stuff,
aren't you?
There's no stuff to go through.
It's a freak show.
You can do surgery in here.
Oh...
He arranged his books
using the Dewey Decimal system.
- Mer, I'm scared.
- Get out. Get out of the house now.
Who you talking to?
Uh... I gotta go.
Uh... I have to go take a shower.
And when I get back, you won't be here.
So, um... goodbye, Steve.
Another sleepless night in Seattle.
Who was it this time? "Hairy Back Guy"?
You know who I miss?
"Inappropriate Facial Hair Guy."
You know, he did his own dishes.
"Tattooed Ass Guy" made coffee.
Yeah, he was a keeper.
What? What? Meredith?
- I am over her.
- OK.
- I am.
- Yeah, I can see that.
But, is she trying to set
some kind of record?
At least she has a goal.
Oh.
- He's new.
- And I shall name him: "Running Guy."
You know who I heard Alex
come home with last night?
- You.
- I don't want to talk about it.
I really do want to talk about it.
He doesn't want to talk about it because
there were technical difficulties.
- What?
- You know, he didn't... He...
- No.
- Stop it.
You can't say anything.
- George, stop it.
- I...
I'm gonna at least think about
making fun of him when I see him.
- He said it never happened before.
- That's what we all say.
And I mean, "they."
That's what "they" all say.
I don't know. Maybe this relationship
just isn't meant to be.
I mean, I just need some sex,
George, you know?
I need sex now! You know what I mean?
No matter how hard you beg,
I am not doing you.
- Nice to have you on board.
- Thank you, Patricia.
Your own service,
a state-of-the-art NICU,
and a salary that makes you one of the
highest-paid surgeons in the northwest.
- You better be worth it.
- Quintuplets, Richard.
- That's a go.
- Mother-to-be checked in today.
Nothing I like more
than a high-profile case.
Don't go calling the press in yet.
It's a high-risk pregnancy.
Three babies are surgical.
I'll need people from all departments.
You're my star. Whatever you need.
Is there meal service on this flight?
Robert Martin, 45, hit his head,
causing a small subdural hemorrhage.
Also, uncontrolled eye movement
and delirium.
Alcohol and tox screens were negative,
but sodium level is 112.
- A little too low for my taste.
-  Hey! Hey!
Mr. Martin, how are you doing in there?
I'm still waiting on that drink.
Are you the stewardess?
We're called flight attendants now.
Hey!
There it is. On his pituitary,
it's a Rathke's cleft cyst.
He's hyponatremic.
Thirst is a side effect.
- Water's screwing up his sodium levels.
- Causing his delirium.
How do you treat hyponatremia?
Three percent hypertonic saline solution
IV, 300 CCs over three hours.
Great. Call me when he stabilizes.
- Nicely done, Dr. Karev.
- Hey! When does the movie start?
Dorie, this is Dr. Stevens.
She'll be working with us.
- The more, the merrier.
- How far along are you?
- 32 weeks.
- How long is a normal gestation period?
40 weeks, but with twins
36 weeks is considered full term,
so with quints 34 weeks
is considered extremely successful.
Mom, give him some acetaminophen.
It's in the medicine cabinet.
I plan on going 36 weeks. No one's
leaving this uterus until I say so.
Power of positive thinking?
That, bed rest
and all your medical care.
We're with the doctors now.
So, I'll talk to you later.
OK, bye.
Adam's got a fever,
so soon they'll all have a fever.
Mom won't make it through lunch.
We have four-year-old boys.
Adam, Oliver, and Graham.
Triplets? You already have triplets?
When you take fertility pills,
you should read the fine print.
- Dr. Stevens...
- I'm sorry, I just... I meant...
It's OK. I'm used to it.
I just really wanted a girl.
- We just didn't bank on five girls.
- But think of all the clothes.
- And all that pink cuteness.
- That's your happy place, remember?
Oh, yeah.
Try not to say everything
that pops into your brain.
They always look so sad
when I kick them out.
Seriously, why do guys not understand
that when you pick them up in a bar
and take them home for sex, there are no
picket fences or kids in your future?
- Burke "keyed" you?
- I got freaking "keyed" before coffee.
- What is wrong with them?
- They're like these 1950s debutantes.
One dance, and there's
a shotgun to your head.
Meredith.
- You work here?
- What are you doing here, Steve?
- I'm having a little problem.
- "Steve," Steve?
Actually, I'm having a big problem.
- What?
- Steve, hi. Cristina.
Ever since you and I...
It won't go away.
- Cristina!
- What? It's right there, looking at me.
There are so many things
I could say right now.
Champ.
Do you think it's serious?
It hurts like it is.
You realize this is insane.
We have to stash him somewhere
until we figure this out.
- I can't have people finding out.
- I'm not going down for this.
- It's not my fault you broke his penis.
- You broke his what?
Don't make me chase you down.
I'm growing a person here.
I gotta check on some labs.
How's it look?
- Not bad.
- Not bad?
"Not bad" is good when you have
five babies in your uterus.
It's Kate. She kicks me so hard
it's like a belly burn every time.
You've named them already?
I know you think I'm crazy,
or maybe just a little bit stupid?
Mrs. Russell,
I'm sorry if I've offended you...
The only thing that will offend me
is if you pretend
you didn't judge me immediately.
We'll spend a lot of time together,
so we may as well be honest.
If you had reduced the fetuses
even by two,
the others could've been carried longer,
been more developed and healthier.
You're about the sixteenth doctor
who's told me that.
This one up here, this is Charlotte.
She's the stubborn one.
Lodged under my rib cage
and won't budge.
Over here, Lucy.
She's a badass.
She gets kicked, she kicks back.
Emily, she has the hiccups
almost every day.
And over here is Julie,
she's pretty mellow.
Every once in a while
she just turns over,
which brings us back to Kate.
- Who gives you belly burn.
- Every time she kicks.
We were just bringing him up here
because he's got this problem.
And he's a... a friend.
What did your friend take?
- Take?
- Which erectile dysfunction drug?
- You took...
- Absolutely not, I swear.
- It was all natural between us.
- Shut up.
Your condition is called priapism,
usually brought on
by the overuse of EDs.
I didn't take anything.
We'll have to take your word for it.
There's no test to see if you're lying.
We'll have to look for other causes.
There'll be lots of labs,
lots of procedures.
Painful procedures.
Procedures which might make you wish
you never had a penis.
- Sure you won't change your story?
- I swear I'm clean.
All right. Grey, start his workup.
Get some blood.
Get him some meperidine for his pain.
As of now, your friend is admitted.
Dorie Russell,
she's giving birth to quints.
Richard said we were on standby.
Which is no problem. It's not like
I have a neurosurgery department to run.
Yes. Apparently our departments
are at her disposal.
Do you have time to talk to the mom?
I want her to meet all her surgeons.
- Yes, no problem.
- I'll come by after I finish in the OR.
- Thank you, Dr. Burke.
- Sure!
I didn't hear you leave the hotel room
this morning.
I had an early surgery.
You're sure that's all? Nothing's wrong?
No, like I said, I had an early surgery.
OK.
I feel like a beached whale.
Dorie, this is Dr. Shepherd,
he's our head of neurosurgery.
- Another Dr. Shepherd?
- He's my husband, actually.
Seriously? Wow, look at you two.
Everybody must hate you.
You have no idea.
Anyway, Dorie, Dr. Shepherd wants to
talk to you about Baby "C."
- Lucy.
- Lucy has hydrocephalus.
It is a build-up of cerebrospinal fluid
on the brain.
OK, and that means...
The fluid puts pressure
on the baby's brain,
which could result in brain damage.
Here's the good news.
We caught it early.
We can take care of it quickly.
How?
I'll install a shunt to drain the fluid.
You're looking at a full recovery.
- No brain damage?
- No brain damage.
OK, really,
couldn't you have led with that?
Good point.
What the hell is this?
- It's a key.
- Why?
Why is it a key? Are we feeling
existential this morning?
If a key turns in a lock, and no one
asked for the key or even wanted it,
does it make a sound?
Hey.
Hi.
I'm going to take this opportunity
to be someplace else.
- Steve's labs came back clean.
- So?
So, someone needs
to induce vasoconstriction.
Nice try with the fancy word. He needs
an enema and the answer is "no."
I can't do it.
You let a guy you picked up in a bar
see you naked
- and you can't give him an enema?
- Uncalled for.
- Well, I'm keyed up and cranky.
- I'd do it for you.
Oh, really? You'd give Burke an enema?
- Yes.
- Uh-huh.
- Maybe.
- Mm-hm.
No. But that's not the point.
Oh, yeah. OK, here's how it goes.
I do this for you and you do every enema
I'm assigned to for a month.
Deal.
You really don't wanna do this.
- Have we heard from the seller's agent?
- I've been calling.
Mr. Martin, it's good to see you
back on solid ground. I'm Dr. Shepherd.
My assistant, Doyle,
says I passed out and hit my head.
This guy says it's some kind of cyst.
- I want you to say when I can leave.
- A Rathke's cleft cyst.
- Whatever.
- A congenital tumor on your pituitary.
- Is it treatable?
- You'll need surgery.
- I'm gonna use an endonasal approach.
- Endonasal?
You're going to pull it out
through my nose?
Look him up. Check his credentials.
It's minimally invasive
so there won't be scarring.
- Good. So, when?
- When we stabilize your sodium levels.
- That means no more water.
- I'm thirsty.
It's a side effect. We'll keep you
hydrated intravenously.
OK?
What the hell are you doing?
I'm just following the doctor's orders.
- I cannot believe this is happening.
- Try being me.
I mean, you meet someone in a bar,
you have a few drinks, a few laughs,
- you make out in the car...
- Roll over to your side.
Other side.
- Bring your knees up to your chest.
- You have a good time.
Spend the night,
wake up the next morning and...
- OK!
- Mm-hm.
- Still not talking to me?
- You gave me syphilis.
And I am talking to you.
I just don't have anything to say.
- How's George?
- O'Malley's a fetus.
He's all whiny and afraid of the light.
So you didn't tell him
you were doing me. Big deal.
Minimal disclosure, that's my policy.
Hey. I've been looking for you.
Hey.
- I'm on the quints case.
- Yeah, I heard.
They'll need multiple surgeries.
I put you on the pager list.
So you're in too.
Yeah, I kind of got my own cases
to worry about, so...
OK, Alex, was it me?
Because we seemed to be actually
having a normal time, a good time.
Yeah, we were having a good time.
Well, then, was it me?
Was it something I did?
It wasn't you, OK? It was just...
Look, I didn't feel like doing it.
I was tired, you know.
Well, do you feel like doing it tonight?
I'm on call, so...
OK. Well,
do you feel like doing it now?
Right now?
People have sex in this hospital
all the time.
- You hear about the quints?
- Yeah, I heard.
I gotta get in on that.
Yeah, well, that's Addison,
so I'm guessing I don't stand a chance.
So how do you break a guy's penis?
You know about Steve?
Why does every guy I meet
come with his own unique set
of nightmarish humiliations?
- Maybe it's a matter of volume.
- Volume? What's that supposed to mean?
I'm just... There's quality
and then there's quantity.
So, you think I'm sleeping with too many
guys? You think I'm some kind of slut?
I think you are taking some risks.
I think you'll find yourself
in some guy's basement
being ordered to do things
or you'll get the hose again.
- Come on.
- I'm talking.
So you're not over Derek.
You want to be, but you're not.
You're trying to find a replacement,
a way to feel better.
But it's not going to work because
a future of meaningless one-night stands
and problematic penises
is not what you want.
You want better, and you deserve better.
And not every guy is a nightmare.
- If it's me, just tell me it's me.
- It's not you.
Well, then is it a medical thing,
or a problem?
Because guys have problems sometimes.
I don't have a problem.
Get back down here.
We're gonna do this until we do it.
OK.
911. I'm sorry.
Damn it.
- Where have you been?
- I um... I... The nurse was here.
I've loaded her up with magnesium.
Start monitoring her for toxicity.
It's too soon. They can't come yet.
Mom says Graham started puking.
What is it? What's going on?
- She's having contractions.
- Vital signs are stable.
Your placenta is laying low.
We'll keep an eye on that.
We want them in there longer.
How, if she's already
having contractions?
They can stop them.
You're going to Trendelenburg me, right?
Yes, I am.
You've done your reading, Dorie.
I did it with the triplets.
Gravity, remember, Tom?
It worked fine then
and it'll be fine now.
Hang in there, Tom.
No time for second thoughts now.
We didn't think that we'd survive
a week with the boys, and we did.
We'll be the same with the girls.
We're ready.
That's all we can do for now.
Dr. Stevens, are you on call tonight?
- No.
- You are now.
- Enema didn't work.
- Enema didn't work?
Enema didn't work.
Huh.
- It was an excellent enema.
- So, what's the next step?
A needle aspiration.
A needle? My penis?
We have to drain the blood.
No way! No! Forget it!
Then you're looking at impotence,
penile infarction, or gangrene.
- So if you want it to fall off...
- No. No, I really don't want that.
Then let's get to it.
What goes up must come down.
I feel nauseous.
Just lie back, close your eyes,
and try to relax.
If I could relax, I wouldn't be here!
Doctor.
How is he?
- Surgery's scheduled for tomorrow.
- Anything I can do?
Don't let him drink any water.
Even if he begs.
Any family we should contact?
- No.
- Friends?
He doesn't get on with most people.
Not big on social skills.
- Sad guy.
- Well, he has me.
Three years as his assistant.
I guess I'm his friend.
Doyle!
What if I just give him back the key?
- He'll be hurt.
- What if I don't use it?
If you had no intention of using it,
you shouldn't have taken it.
Come on. Fishing a key out of a cup
isn't like some binding legal contract.
Your boyfriend gave you
a key to his place?
Why's he talking?
The guy put himself out. He's taking
the next step. You can't not use it.
Do you think you might not be
in the best position right now
to be handing out relationship advice?
Hey, he offered the key,
you took the key.
Just because I'm...
Look at that!
Congratulations.
You're flaccid.
Never thought
I'd be so happy to hear that.
Dr Jones to Radiology.
Dorie? Tom?
Hey, Dorie. Tom, this is Dr. Burke,
he's the head of cardiothoracic surgery,
and Dr. O'Malley,
who'll be assisting him.
Dr. Burke wanted to talk
about Emily's heart surgery.
- Heart surgery?
- Yes.
She has a condition
called hypoplastic left heart syndrome.
The surgery will be extensive,
and the odds are...
- We don't believe in odds.
- Good. Neither do I.
But it's important that you understand
medically what's going on.
After she's born, there won't be
much time to ask questions.
OK.
- We're listening.
- What's wrong with Emily's heart?
The left-side chambers
are underdeveloped.
And the mitral valve, which connects
these chambers, is abnormally narrow.
It's a key.
- Just a key?
- Just a key.
Good. Good. Good.
Or you could start thinking about
moving in with me.
Sorry.
Don't mind me.
- What's up with Doyle?
- I had to fire him.
Get me some water. I'm drying up.
Yeah, well, that's the tumor talking.
The IV is keeping you hydrated.
So why'd you fire Doyle?
He seemed like a good guy.
I could see it in his eyes.
He didn't respect me anymore.
He thought he was your friend.
- Friend? Doyle?
- Right. You don't have any friends.
If I did, I wouldn't let them
see me like this.
Illness is a sign of weakness.
Once they see it, they look at you
differently. You're a hotshot doctor.
I'm sure you don't let
the other hotshot doctors
- know about your problems.
- I'm a hotshot doctor.
I don't have any problems.
Probably don't have any friends either.
Oh, my Lord.
Oh, child.
- Don't tell me.
- The flag is flying once again.
Hey, nothing I did.
We've tried everything.
It must be neural.
- Neural?
- She already called for a consult.
A consult?
You called Neuro for a consult?
It's not my fault
you broke the boy's penis.
Hello, everybody, what's up?
Hm. So when did this problem begin?
Well, I had an erection last night
and woke up with one this morning.
Dr. Shepherd, if you don't need me,
the other Dr. Shepherd
needs a consult on one of the quints.
Yeah, no, we're fine.
So when did you last ejaculate?
I'm not sure. Meredith?
Oh, I'm...
I'm going to go with Dr. Bailey.
Meredith, what time did we, uh...
you know...
Yes, Meredith, what time did you two...
Here it is.
Right there, the omphalocele.
- Look at that.
- That's the scariest word yet.
All it means is some of the baby's
organs are in a sac outside its body.
- Cristina!
- "All it means"?
Her organs are growing outside of
her body? That's "all it means"?
- It's going to be OK.
- I'll remove the sac membrane
containing the organs, make
a small incision in the baby's abdomen
and put them back inside.
Julie.
She's the quiet one.
What makes you think... What makes
you think we can live together?
You don't know anything about me.
I know that you prefer an eleven blade
for your I and Ds.
I know you prefer to say "pick-ups"
instead of "forceps."
I know you like your coffee
from the cart by the front entrance
better than the coffee in the cafeteria.
I know you.
Those are little things. Just details.
You don't want to move.
But I can't always be the one
that takes the step.
Any more steps, and I'm walking away.
Mr. Martin! Mr. Martin, please!
Mr. Martin, please,
you heard what the doctors said.
- I don't need any doctors.
- Open the door, Martin.
I'm an island. A beautiful island
surrounded by water.
- What do you want to do?
- Shepherd gave me one job to do.
Keep this dude from drinking water.
- Do you want me to page him?
- No.
Get some restraints
and turn the water off to the floor.
Open the door!
Your CT shows a tumor
on your lower spine,
which is pressing against your cavernous
nerve, which is causing the erection.
A tumor? Right.
A tumor? So, I should be scared, right?
This is the time for "scared."
Um... It's going to be fine.
Um, Dr. Shepherd is
gonna schedule surgery.
I'll remove the tumor
and everything should return to normal.
"Normal" normal?
I have a urologist on his way up to talk
to you, but yes, "normal" normal.
Can you call my mom?
Her number is in my wallet.
Don't tell her about the tumor. I don't
want to scare her. She'll be flying.
Sure. OK.
- When did you start seeing each other?
- We're not... seeing each other.
We met last night at Joe's.
Joe's Bar?
Mm-hm.
I met a girl there once myself.
A very long time ago.
The water's off. We'll just have to wait
until he sobers up.
His sodium levels will drop too low.
No! No!
Leave me alone!
Let me go back. I need the water.
I need it!
- Martin, we're trying to help.
- I don't want your help.
I don't want people to look at me.
I'm pathetic.
Stop looking at me.
Stop looking at me!
Give him a three percent
hypertonic solution at 500cc's per hour
over the next four hours
to stabilize him.
You think you're such a hotshot doctor.
You're not. You're nothing.
I'll fire you too.
Go ahead. Fire me.
I used the key.
That's a step.
So you really wanna know me?
There's nothing you could reveal about
yourself that I wouldn't want to know.
This... is where I live.
My mother decorated it.
I don't do laundry. I buy new underwear.
And under that table?
Six months of magazines I know
I'll never read, but I won't throw out.
I don't wash dishes, vacuum,
or put the toilet paper on the holder.
I hired a maid once.
She ran away crying.
The only things in my fridge are water,
vodka, and diet soda, and I don't care.
But you do.
Still think living together
is a good idea?
Hey. Addison wants me
to put you guys on notice.
When the quints are born
we'll need everyone available.
Five babies and three surgeries, we're
gonna need all the hands we can get.
- OK.
- Fine.
So I'll just page you guys
when we need you?
- OK.
- Fine.
- OK, then.
- I was studying. What's your excuse?
I was staring at the ceiling
in abject horror.
My one-night stand
is a neurosurgical case.
I heard you broke his penis. Nice.
So I'm having a lot of sex.
What's wrong with that?
Nothing at all.
It gets problematic
when you start to care.
When you let your emotions
get in the way. You know?
Yeah. Right.
Damn it.
I'll just get the tea.
What is it? Why'd you page me?
He was acting all jittery
and started slurring his words.
Martin, can you hear me?
- He started seizing.
- How much sodium did you give him?
500cc over four hours.
Actually, you ordered 500cc's per hour
over four hours.
That's too fast. His brain is swelling.
- I thought I said...
- I gave you one thing to do.
- Will he be OK?
- He's currently impaired.
I can't operate on him like this.
I'm sorry.
I wasn't trying to get you in trouble,
but Dr. Shepherd needed to know.
- It doesn't mean you're a bad doctor.
- Lately, I'm crap.
Yeah, well, things have been
kind of crappy for me too lately.
Also my fault.
We both made mistakes.
Let me ask you something.
When we were together...
it was good, right?
You mean...
Yeah... it was good.
It was really good.
It was pretty great.
It was, wasn't it?
It was like, easy, simple.
You... better have a condom this time.
There it is.
It's on the S1 vertebra.
So removing it
should fix the problem?
Doesn't look like
there's nerve damage.
There shouldn't be
any long-term effect.
I'd wait a few weeks
before I tested it out, though.
Funny. You're a funny man.
I just didn't know you two were dating.
You knew it would happen eventually.
"Eventually" feels a lot different
than "actually."
Yeah, I guess it does.
Well, it's surprisingly painful.
It gets better.
Does it?
Well, I don't know,
but I'm determined to be optimistic.
So you officially signed your contract.
Congratulations.
- Time to move forward.
- Yeah, it is.
We're OK, right?
Yeah. We're OK.
It's Dorie.
- What's going on?
- There's fetal distress.
My contractions are really hurting.
And I think my water broke.
Her placenta's tearing.
OK, Dorie, we can't wait any longer.
The babies have to come out now.
It's OK. We're gonna take really good
care of you. Just keep breathing.
Dorie, the OR is prepped
and ready to go. Where's Tom?
- He's home with the boys.
- No, I called Tom. He's on his way.
Izzie, page everyone on Dorie's team.
The list is at the nurse's station.
Dorie, you're fine.
You're going to be fine.
Nothing about this is fine.
It's too early. They're too hurt.
Dorie, you've carried your girls
this far.
Now it's our turn. You have to
trust us to bring them into the world.
- Tom's on his way?
- Tom's on his way.
- Hey.
I'll just have to tell you
I'm happy to see you.
So Dr. Shepherd removed the tumor
without any complications.
So I just want to thank you.
For being there for me.
I mean, normally,
you don't expect your one-night stand
to stick by you through a tumor.
- Maybe when I get out, we could...
- I don't think so.
- Sure about that?
- Yeah.
You know, when I saw you at Joe's,
I was just... looking for a replacement.
Looking for something
to make me feel better.
You deserve better than that.
Dr. Bailey, Dr. Burke to
OR one. Dr. Bailey, Dr. Burke to OR one.
Sorry. I gotta go.
Quints.
- Everyone answered except Dr. Karev.
- Where is he?
- He was on call, he might be asleep.
- Go find him.
It's time for the quints. We need you.
How do you know
how much is too much?
Too much, too soon?
Too much information?
Too much fun?
Too much love?
Too much to ask?
And when is it all
just too much to bear?
www.tvsubtitles.net