Previously on "Grey's Anatomy"...
I raised you to be an
extraordinary human being.
Imagine my disappointment
when I wake up after 5 years
and discover that you're
no more than ordinary.
An hour ago, he was proposing.
Now he's going to the morgue.
You did good.
Do you believe in heaven ?
There are medical miracles.
Being worshippers
at the altar of science,
we don't like to believe miracles exist.
But they do.
Things happen.
We can't explain them,
we can't control them...
but they do happen.
Chief, I know the hypothermia is
protective to her vital organs but,
How much longer do you think
we can go on like this ?
I've seen people last
as long as 4 hours.
Yeah, but you...
No, this is not...
This is Ellis Grey's little girl.
This is my...
We're all on the same
side here, Chief.
Sir...
Her body temp is at 86 degrees. She's
not dead until she is warm and dead.
We need to warm her up to 98.6
and start her heart.
Yes, sir.
Let's do a gastric lavage
with warm fluids.
Addison.
- I have to go. I... it's my Jane Doe.
- Just... they're waiting...
for you. So...
Whatever you choose to say will...
Miracles do happen in medecine.
They happen every day.
Just not always when we
need them to happen.
Meredith ?
She's freaking out.
She's not freaking out.
People tend to freak out.
Trust me, she's fine.
Oh, okay, mr. I been dead longer,
knows everything.
You know what ? That's why
I don't like to be here with you,
because you don't assess the situation.
You just dive right in.
Oh, I'm not the one who got
himself all blown up.
All right, you wanna do this now
or you wanna do this later ?
- Oh, I... I wanna do this now.
- You wanna do this now ?
I will kick your ass anytime.
I'm the one with a fresh heart.
- Oh, yeah, you're gonna kick my...
- This is the brain thing.
This is the ketamine
neurotransmitter thing, right ?
- No.
'Cause you'd think if this were my brain
Doing this, the first person I'd want
to see, no offense,
Would be... Doc !
What a good boy.
Hi.
- Hi, Buddy.
- Meredith.
This is not your brain on drugs.
This is death. You are dead.
You're really freakin'dead.
You're dirt-nap dead.
- No more you dead.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa...
Way too harsh. Remember, we...
we're gonna take it easy.
That was not easy.
Meredith...
You drowned... in Elliott bay.
You remember that ?
Yeah, that sucked. Who's a good boy ?
- Who's the best dog ?
- Oh, this is gonna take a while.
- Who's such a good boy ?
- We don't have a while.
She's running out of time.
Who's the best dog ?
Tell me.
Her temp's still only 86.
There's still no heartbeat.
We're hoping once she warms up...
- I want to go in there.
- No.
There's a risk of brain damage.
- I need to go in there. I'm going in.
- Derek, you can't,
not for Meredith, not for anybody.
You're in no shape
- It's not good.
- Is she still cyanotic ?
What was her initial temp ?
- I mean, what is taking so long ?
- Dr. Yang...
It's not good.
They're doing everything they can.
I ...
You should maybe, um,
Prepare yourselves.
I have to go. Uh, my Jane Doe's awake.
I'm coming with you.
Iz, you'll let us know ?
Prepare ourselves ? That's...
That's what we tell the families
before we call time of death.
She's gonna be okay.
Sometimes you're wrong.
Unh-unh.
No.
- Cristina...
- I am not doing this.
Cristina.
She's gonna survive this.
She's gonna survive this. She's gonna
survive this. She's gonna survive...
Meredith.
I don't know if you remember me.
I was your mother's scrub nurse.
- I died from...
- Liver cancer.
Bonnie ?
She remembers me.
You remember.
You were a very important
patient for her.
What are all of you doing here ?
- Is this...
- It's not heaven.
We're here because
you called us here.
I didn't. Did I ?
Tell us about the water, Meredith.
You do not have the authority
to speak to me in that way.
You are a bug.
- You understand ?
- I need you to hold still !
Go ahead.
- Burke usually writes for lorazepam
when she's like this,
- This amateurs !
- But I don't want to bother him.
- Let me out of this bed.
Do it. Give it to her.
Who do you think you are ?
This is a day she should
sleep through.
Do you even know what you're doing ?
Get me Richard !
I'm Dr. Montgomery. You need this
oxygen. I need you to lie back.
No. I'm not...
- I'm not supposed to be here.
- This wasn't in your plan today.
I get that. But we're trying
to take care of your baby.
Now I need you to calm down.
Just... just tell her you're gonna take
me home. Just just talk to my husband.
Th...  This is Dr. Karev. He's my intern.
- What ? You're not ?
- You lost your I.D.
We don't know where
your family is yet.
But I... I know you.
- You're my...
- No, I found you on the dock
after the accident.
What dock ? What accident ?
What happened ?
You were on the ferry.
You don't remember ?
No.
What about your name ?
My name ?
- Shh.
- I don't know.
- I'm having a baby.
- Shh.
I should know my own name.
I'm having a baby. I should know
my own name.
She can't remember anything
from before the accident.
It could be head trauma.
It could be psychological
from the shock.
I mean, retrograde amnesia...
it could be just transient, right ?
Well, that's the hope, but, you know,
I'm worried about her lungs, too.
- Get a chest x-ray and an A.B.G.
- Okay.
Hey, are you okay ? You want
to be with your friends ?
- No, I'm... I'm on this.
- You sure ?
Yeah, It's just, I don't know,
Meredith always makes me think...
I don't know, screwed up people
have a chance.
I'm in.
Start the warm fluids. Hold C.P.R.
Anything ?
Her heart is still.
No movement,
No fibrillation.
Nothing ?
Nothing.
Restarting C.P.R.
- Stevens, get out of here.
- I just...
Oh, my god.
Go back outside and wait
with Yang and O'malley.
Cr... Cristina isn't, um,
She left.
She left in the middle of her shift ?
Where did she go ?
Meredith, I need you to understand.
This is important.
- You can't screw around.
- Doc ?
There's no time for that. You don't have
the time, and we don't have the time.
I drowned. That's all.
- I drowned.
- Meredith, please listen to us.
You have to listen to us. You have to !
Oh, no.
I can't find the source
of this bleeding !
I need gloves and surgical towels.
It happens with Bonnie, baby.
You just gotta ride it.
I can save her.
- I can start an I.V.
- There's no point.
Go to the O.R. and get me
sterilized surgical instruments.
Go.
Go !
Meredith...
Are  you ready to talk about this now,
or you wanna waste some more time ?
It's been over an hour.
There's a ch...
We need to prepare for
the possibility that she may...
Look, she is young, she is healthy,
Her temp's going up, and it's gonna keep
going up and her heart will start again.
That's the only possibility
I'm prepared for.
Mm.
Do you use moisturizer ?
Here. Take this.
Keep it behind the bar.
Wow. What is this ? It smells like
something burning.
It's gingerbread.
Yeah.
You're not getting this, are you ?
Okay, this is 99 cents.
Okay ? You can buy anything
for 99 cents.
Oh !
Oh.
It's small.
It's, um,
A tiny size. It has, uh,
cat-type creatures on it.
But it is a chair.
For 99 cents, you can buy furniture.
That is America, Man.
That's Taiwan, Man.
You know, this ferry thing's pretty bad.
- Don't you think you should be...
- I am coping.
Okay ?
I'm coping. So, uh, shut up
and, uh, look at all my crap !
Uh,  Callie, I'm putting you
in charge of my interns.
Put'em to work anywhere but here.
Dr. Bailey, please let us stay here.
- No, we can't go anywhere. We have to
- You're concerned.
I understand.
There's been a disaster
and there's work to be done.
Go, now.
All right, they need bodies down
in the clinic. Let's go down there.
Hey, Bailey's right.
We can't help Meredith.
All we can do is sit around
and go crazy.
I... I can't.
- I need to be here.
- Izzie,
We're all freaked. We just need
to stay out of the way. Got it ?
Let's go.
Do you or your immediate family
have a history of cancer ?
Um, I don't know.
How about heart disease
or high blood pressure ?
How about alcohol or drug use ?
You don't know any of this, do you ?
I don't even know the sex
of my baby or if I'm married.
I mean, I...
I have a ring line, but
I don't have the ring.
So what does that make me ?
I...  I don't know.
Is it really bad ?
You look... I mean, am I gonna...
No. No, no, no, no, no. It's, uh...
It's a friend.
She was in the accident, too.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Yeah. Well...
Things are tough all over.
I have no new information about
your loved ones. I'm sorry.
But we are facing
a serious blood shortage.
So anyone eligible to donate
blood should see me.
If you're not sure, see me.
These need to go to the blood bank
for testing. Thanks.
What are those for ?
Meredith is AB.
She's been down a long time,
but, you know, she's strong.
- We shouldn't give up.
- I wasn't planning to, but thanks.
Okay.
Is this stress related, or am I doing
something specific to piss you off ?
Because believe me,
we need to pull together.
Not "we".
What ?
You keep going on about how "we" need
to do this for Meredith
and how strong Meredith is,
like you know her.
- I do know her.
- No, George, Cristina and me,
we know her.
We're her family.
We were here long before you and
George started fooling around.
Hey, he is my husband.
Stop saying that like it means
something. It's a piece of paper
You act like it gives you history
or weight.
Okay, enough !
Enough.
I will not be run off. I am here.
George wants me here.
And if you can accept that,
That... that I love him, too, then maybe
we could be, I don't know, friends ?
Or you can keep on the way you are
and be that person that
George used to know.
You don't get to decide that.
- George decides.
- Oh, I know what he'll decide.
And if I were you, I would think about
it long and hard, because you
cannot afford to lose another friend,
not when people around you keep...
Keep...
Dropping like flies.
Is that what you were about to say ?
So all of you just disappear at will ?
- What happened ?
- I drowned.
That's it.
Really ?
Then why are we here ?
Again.
I can't do this if you're gonna
keep saying you drowned.
Do you have any idea
how much that hurt ?
You know, when you came into the E.R.,
You were so brave,
- So strong.
- I was in shock !
And you guys doped me up.
And you know what ?
In retrospect, what happened
to me really sucked.
I was young and beautiful and in love.
I was getting married in four months,
and then I was dying.
And here you are, all happy
and perky to be dead.
You think I want to be here ?
I swam. I fought hard.
- The water was cold.
- All right, but that thing in the tub,
What was that ?
It wasn't anything. It was...
You see me in the tub ?
I do not see women in the bathtub.
I wish I saw w...
- We know things.
- You had to think about it.
- No daughter of Ellis Grey could...
- This is so not an Ellis Grey thing.
- Ah, it's a Derek thing.
- I would never...
- You would.
I know crappy things
have happened to you,
But how can you be a surgeon and have
so little respect for life ? How...
Oh, come on.
Who are you here for ?
What ?
I'm waiting on my wife.
Car hit her.
Can you believe that, on the ferry ?
She was run over on the ferry.
They haven't said much.
Hard as hell to get any of
these people to talk to you.
Yeah, I'm, uh...
My girlfriend was there, too.
And I don't know...
I don't know what's gonna happen.
It's out of our hands.
It's up to the Doctors now.
Yeah.
yeah.
What's her name ?
Meredith.
I'll put her in my prayers.
Thanks.
I need to get in there and find
the source of this bleeding.
Honestly, Mer, It's...
It's just gonna happen again.
Where is something
to wipe up this blood ?
Fool me once...
Oh, good, yeah. Show up now,
be a smart-ass.
We have a job to do. Where are you ?
You know, It's a waste of time.
She's either gonna get it
- or she's not.
- Get what ?
The way I see it, it doesn't
matter how you got here.
You're either in this thing
or you're not.
There is no in between.
And cowboy here can get pissed off,
because for all his tough talk,
He's no different from Bonnie.
- He's stuck.
- And you're not ?
- No.
- Oh, please.
- Stop.
I had a good life.
I helped when I could.
And when that shell went off in my
hands, I completed my task.
I saved you.
What about another epi ?
We've been pushing epi for
an hour and a half now.
Check another lead.
Asystole on three leads, sir.
- What about her temp ?
- Down to 86 degrees.
86 ?
- It's 86 now ? It was 89.
- Afterdrop phenomenon.
Water. Get me some water.
You broke her.
You call her ordinary.
You taught her time and time again
that nothing she does,
Ever, is good enough.
Every good thing Meredith is...
H appened
Despite you.
She may not survive this,
And that's on you.
- That is on you.
- Derek.
The woman is just...
She's a black hole,
there's no question.
But she can't help herself, and she
certainly can't fix Meredith.
It's my fault.
Don't.
See, I knew what was going on,
and I wasn't there for her.
You were human.
She was pulling away from me,
and I just... I...
I just...
Y... you think that she went
in the water on purpose ?
She knows how to swim.
She's a good swimmer.
Derek, you don't know that she's...
No, you do not get to break down.
You do not get to fall apart,
Not when there's still a chance, and
there still is a chance, Derek. Okay ?
Okay.
What are you looking for ?
Something strong.
The next time Bonnie decides
to bleed out,
- I'm gonna dope her to high heaven and
- Why are we still talking about her ?
- If I can find the source...
- She can't be saved.
This isn't fair. I could save her.
If you'd just give me a chance,
I could save her.
What happened in that water ?
- I swam. I fought.
- No, you didn't.
- And you can't stay here, Meredith.
- I don't want to !
Yeah, you do.
It's easier.
But you can't, because
George's dad died,
Because Izzie lost me.
And Cristina ?
When she was 9, she was in a
car accident with her father,
And he bled out right in front of her
while they waited for
an ambulance to arrive.
- And Alex...
- Stop.
They are barely breathing.
This will break them.
And none of them deserves that.
And this...
This is the big one...
So you pay attention.
Do you know what kind of miracle it is
That Derek is who he is ?
Do you know how rare it is that
someone like him even exists ?
He's still an optimist.
He still believes in
true love and magic and...
Soul mates.
He's waiting for you,
And if you don't come back from this,
You will change who he is.
Oh, god.
Oh.
Code blue.
What about a cardiopulmonary bypass ?
Come on. We could do it here.
Page Burke and the surgical team.
Get him here now.
You know, this is... this is
quality suku, Joe. This is, like,
- $2 worth of sudoku.
- Good to know.
No change.
- I thought you should know.
- No kidding.
Well, some do, you know,
come back from this.
You know what ? I am not a civilian.
I know the science here.
- It's drinking time.
- Not yet.
You have a responsibility to Meredith.
Unh-unh.
I don't do this stuff.
I mean, you should know.
I go to great lengths.
You were there when I needed you.
After.
After I knew you were gonna make it.
Okay, I'm not proud.
Okay ? I just...
I can't.
I can't go back there. I can't...
I can't go back there and watch her...
Listen to me.
This is about you and the woman
you call your "person."
And you do know the science here.
And if she dies, and you are sitting
here when that happens,
I can't see you coming back from that.
Come and say good-bye to your friend.
I was swimming.
I was fighting.
And then I thought...
Just for a second...
I thought...
What's the point ?
And I let go.
I stopped fighting.
Don't tell anybody.
What ?
Izzie.
You can see her ?
No.
But sometimes...
We'll be in the same place
At exactly the same time.
And...
Oh, I can almost hear her voice.
It's like I'm touching her.
I like to believe she knows I'm there.
That's all you get,
That's it,
Moments with the people you love.
And they'll move on.
And you'll want them to move on.
But still, Meredith,
That is all you get, moments.
Is this really happening ?
I don't know.
This is your afterlife, not mine.
Any change ?
No.
George, come on.
- We can't do this today, not today.
- What the hell did you say to my wife ?
- I didn't say anything. We both said
things. She was...
- I saw her face. I saw her face.
She didn't say anything, but why ? Why
would you pick now to throw down ?
I didn't.
I...
- I can't lie about how I feel.
- Actually, you can.
You can. People lie all the time.
They hold their tongues and they wait.
You should hold your tongue because
if I'm not making a mistake,
You're gonna look like a jerk, and if
I am, I'm gonna need you.
I need you,
And you... you keep taking that away.
Place the C02 monitor.
Did you page Dr. Burke ?
He's in trauma doing
cardiopulmonary bypass.
On Meredith Grey ?
Yes, sir.
All right. Okay, push 1 of atropine.
Billy, what's her temp ?
We're up to 96.
That's good. Good.
All right.
Now we just have to get
her heart beating.
Okay, draw an A.B.G. Push 1 of epi,
a gram of mag and an amp of calcium.
I don't want to be here.
I want to go back.
We were told there
wasn't a lot of time.
I'm out of time ?
- Well, we're not sure, baby.
- Oh, god.
I can't...
I w... oh. I... I... I
- I had intimacy issues.
- Yeah.
Do you know how stupid that seems now ?
- Yeah, I do.
- It's not enough.
It's not enough, just a whiff of Derek
or just... or Cristina.
I need to go back. Please.
I can't... I can't...
This is not gonna happen,
not today.
You're not gonna die on me
today, not today.
v-fib.
Give me the paddles.
Clear
- How many epis is that ?
- Six.
What's the external pacer ?
It's not catching.
- Billy, what's her body temp ?
- 98.
So she's warm ?
Yes.
and dead.
V-fib.
That looks like v-fib.
Shock her at 300.
- Charged.
- Clear.
You cannot give up. You understand me ?
Do you know how much time
and effort and energy and... and...
and resources and drugs...
You cannot give up.
Turning the pacer up to max.
If there was any ounce of activity,
the pacer would've picked it up.
she's been on bypass for...
almost an hour.
Cristina.
I can't breathe.
- This will pass.
- It wontT.
It feels like...
Mom ?
Go.
Go, Meredith.
Try again.
Try again !
Okay, one more round
of A.C.L.S. Drugs ?
One more.
Still v-fib. Okay charge to 300.
Clear.
You shouldn't be here.
Neither should you.
Just keep going.
Don't be a damn...
You are...
You are anything but ordinary, Meredith.
Now run.
Run.
- Is the lidocaine in ?
- Yes.
Okay, holding compressions.
Come on.
Come on, Ellis. Come on.
- Sinus brady.
- Okay
We got a heartbeat ?
We got it.
She's breathing on her own ?
She is.
She's been down a long time.
Do we know the brain function yet ?
We don't know.
- Derek, does, um...
- I haven't paged him yet. I wanted to
I'm giving her more time.
Did you say something ?
Did you just speak ?
Oh.
Mer, I don't understand you.
Okay ? Try...
Try again. Try again...
Try again for me, okay ?
What ? I,
I can't...
Please, please don't be...
Your brain works.
Okay ? So all you need
to do is form a word.
Please.
Ouch.
Oh, god.
Hi.
I'm getting married to Burke.
Not that that should be anywhere
on your list of thoughts right now,
but just in case you slip
in the hall later or...
You are the one person I wanted to tell.
Thank you for not dying.
Hey.
Meredith...
My mother's dead, isn't she ?
Yes.
It's okay...
I think.
I think it's okay.
So she's okay ?
Yeah.
We never had that.
He never...
felt that way about me.
I did.
You know, sometimes I think what a waste
it is to throw away all that history.
I'm flawed.
I'm a
a wreck.
But you...
it wasn't a game.
60 days.
Go 60 days with no sex, no other women.
60 days cold turky, then maybe
I'll believe you.
- So I only have sex with you.
- No.
No sex with anyone.
Grow up, mark.
- Find another way to scratch the itch.
- Say I do.
You'll give us a try,
a real try ? The couple thing...
no sneaking around, no booty calls ?
If you make it, yes.
Okay.
We're on.
Oh, and, Addison ? If I'm not having
sex, neither are you.
Who would I possibly
be having sex with ?
How you doing ?
I hurt all over.
- How's your friend ?
- Well, she pulled through.
Good. That's great.
- And... nobody's...
- Claimed you ? No
No, nothing yet.
So we still don't know anything ?
Oh, oh, no,
not so. We, uh, learned a lot
about you today.
Well, we know that
your heart is healthy.
We know that your blood type
is b-positive.
you probably eat pretty
healthy, because
your cholesterol level is excellent
and you're not diabetic.
Your lungs don't look like
smoker's lungs,
and you don't drink alcohol
on ferries in the morning.
And you're about, uh,
32 years old.
And your baby is a girl.
Really ? A girl ?
Yeah.
- and I think I am married.
I feel married.
- Yeah ?
Yeah.
See, now I know more about you
than some of my closest friends.
That's pathetic.
Held it down.
Thanks.
What you did today
with Meredith...
everybody's talking.
Chief resident talk.
Okay, I'm talking...
to myself... But...
you're gonna give me
a run for my money.
Yeah, I am.
I let you down.
And I get it if you
don't trust me right now. Bur...
please, George.
It's me.
It's us.
Please.
At the end of a day like this,
a day when so many prayers are answered
and so many aren't...
you've been gone a long time.
I know you think you died
when the Alzheimer's started.
I know it's a relief to you.
I know.
But it doesn't feel like a relief to me.
I'm not relieved.
I miss the sound of your voice.
I miss talking to you.
I miss you.
I dyed my hair...
for the ladies.
We take our miracles where we find them.
We reach across the gap...
and sometimes...
against all odds...
against all logic
we touch.
Izzie.
Transcript : Raceman
Synchro : ChipounetteF et Mickeyte
Pour
www.forom.com et
http ://experts.heberg-forum.net/