- Previously on Grey's
Anatomy: - I'm Sydney.
Dr. Sydney Heron.
Big fan of your work.
- What's the matter?
- Have to start dating.
The sex. With Izzie. It's
like she's trying too hard.
- I got fired.
- The problem with you
and your sister?
- Not my sister.
- Same dad.
You killed my wife!
You took her from me.
- What do you need? Scotch, vodka, gin?
- Don't tell Meredith.
There comes a point in your
life when you're officially an adult.
Suddenly, you're old
enough to vote, drink,
and engage in
other adult activities.
So why the brain? Why
biology's crown jewel?
Why did I go into neurosurgery?
Something must have
stirred you as a youngster.
Come on. Share.
Share with Sydney.
It was the headset, with the magnifying
glasses that tipped the scale for me.
And the man has a sense
of humor. I like that. Yes, I do.
Suddenly, people expect
you to be responsible.
Serious. A grown-up.
- Oh.
- Oh?
- Work stuff.
- OK.
As if you didn't
know. I'll just be a sec.
Oh.
I think they're on a date.
That's definitely a date, right?
- Maybe she's dying.
- Is she dying? Is that why?
Grow up. She's nice. Asked me out.
You said I should see other people.
Want me to fake a heart
attack? I do a great heart attack.
- Here she comes.
- Carry on.
- Oh, it's Sydney.
- In the movies,
when the handsome, but
sensitive, football player
kisses the awkward, freaky girl in
front of the school, that girl is her.
You are very awkward and freaky.
We get taller...
We get older...
But do we ever really grow up?
You know what kind
of batteries these take?
- Double A.
- Is it really? Do you have one?
I have some in my locker. Yeah.
- We're avoiding 'em. It's come to that.
- Why are you avoiding Izzie?
Like we're not us anymore.
Everything used to be so easy.
Talking, at least, used to be easy.
Now we can't even talk anymore.
And you?
Derek went on a date with
Sydney Heron last night.
Probably a fake date to make me
think he's healthy and moving on.
Do you think he is?
- Can we take the stairs?
- OK.
Dr. Fletcher to Pediatrics.
Bailey. I, uh... just
wanted to congratulate you
on getting picked
for Chief Resident.
- I'm sorry if things got...
- You deserved the job.
Does she ever! Come here,
new Chief Resident, huh?
- Someone deserves a big hug.
- Oh, come on. Sydney.
Well, I admit I'm
a wee bit jealous.
The Chief has made his
decision, and I will abide by it.
Oh, Callie. I'm,
uh... I'm so sorry.
Don't be. I'm...
I'm fine with it.
Oh, good. We're
being a brave soldier.
No, I really. I'm fine with it.
Let's not spoil this
moment for Miranda, OK?
All right, listen up.
I have nothing but respect
for the job done by Dr. Torres,
but things are gonna be
different from here on in.
Things are weird between George
and me. We can't hold a conversation...
This will be a
professional environment.
So your love lives,
your hopes and dreams,
the little joys and tragedies
that make you who you are
have no place in my hospital.
He's acting like a stranger,
like I don't even know him.
The locker room is for
changing, not for crying.
The on-call room is for napping,
not for anything that
requires a locked door.
And, my God, don't even
get me started on the sex.
- It is tragic. It's like...
- Did you hear a word I said?
Grow up, I believe, is my point.
Dr. Bailey? Can you make sure I
stay on Dr. Hahn's cardio service?
Already done. But if you
piss her off or mess up
or in any way embarrass
me, that's it. No more chances.
Thank you. I'll be the
best resident she's had.
No, Yang, I will be the
best resident she's ever had.
Yes. Right. Second to you.
Chief... Resident.
His incision is healing nicely. No
erythema or purulent discharge.
He'll be monitored, we'll wean him
off the drip once meds are maximized.
After discharge, we expect
him to follow up in the clinic.
There are four other people.
How about letting them talk?
Uh...
Mr. Talbot's cardiomyopathy is
unusually complicated, that's all.
You could take a
cue from Dr. Stevens.
She knows what's going on
with patients and she's inclusive.
- What do we got?
- High school bus crash.
Bunch of kids just came
in. We got more on the way.
Tricia Hale, 17,
vital signs stable.
Sustained a large facial laceration,
trauma to the buttock area,
open fracture to
the lower right leg.
- Trauma Room Two.
- Still bleeding.
- My face is bleeding.
- We'll get to that in a minute.
We? No, try the head
of plastic surgery.
No one is touching my face until
I've spoken to the head. No one.
Thirty-four-year-old
passenger, Marcus King.
No complaints except
deep cuts on his left arm.
- Stable en route.
- OK.
- I'm fine. Help the kids.
- They're being taken care of.
What happened?
Bus slid down an embankment.
One, two, three.
Mandi?
Mandi!
Marcus?
Mandi?
You're from Stockton?
Mr. King was taking us juniors
on a tour of the colleges up here.
Which means that our parents
are at least six or seven hours away.
Yeah.
Just wonderful.
This the eye?
- What's your name?
- Danny.
OK, Danny, I'm going to take
this off so I can have a look. OK?
Man, high school
really does suck.
It was that asshat Sully
and his stupid friends!
Driver kept telling
them to shut up.
I'm drawing a logo, and
suddenly I'm upside down.
Pencil went all the
way in Danny's eye.
- I see that.
- Does it hurt?
No, it feels like a
soothing bubble bath.
- What do you think?!
- I think it hurts.
Look straight ahead for
me. Try not to move your eye.
- Should I call his parents?
- Why don't you let us?
Those jerks should be in jail.
Call the police, not parents.
Don't think about them. You'll be
out soon and never have to see them.
- Still got to finish.
- Need to calm down.
When you raise
your voice, get upset,
your blood pressure shoots
up, could lose your eye.
- I need you to stay calm.
- OK. I'll try.
Listen, I really can't
feel what you're doing,
but I hope you're not
leaving a big old scar.
No! No, no, no.
Just a few little stitches.
Just... I do stitches all the time.
You want me to
take over, Dr. Bailey?
No. I do stitches all
the time, O'Malley.
I thought with all the serious
injuries, you'd want me to take over.
I'm fine here. You're
not the boss of me.
Interns.
Actually, I'm the boss of
him, if you'd want to know.
I'm the Chief Resident.
- What?
- Yeah.
Oh, Mandi. You know
something? I'm not surprised.
- Know that we went
to high school together?
- Really?
Yeah, and this girl
here, she is a genius.
- Used to help me
with my homework.
- Just a few papers, that's all.
Oh. Oops.
- Dr. Bailey?
- I do stitches all the time.
You might want to take a listen.
- Something wrong with
my ticker?
- OK.
Um, part of your heart
may be working overtime.
So, I will get his
EKG and page Hahn.
- Will you finish the sutures?
- You can't finish this?
I guess... I can do it.
Sure, I'll do it.
- OK.
- You better be able
to fix my face.
I have pom
statewides in a month.
Which is...?
It's a competition. Poms.
Pom routines.
- You're a cheerleader?
- I'm a pom.
Cheerleaders just jump
around. Poms are dancers.
I was on the football team.
Not sure you're doing any
dancing in the next month.
- You better be lying.
- Not lying.
You have serious knee and leg
fractures. Not to mention a cracked coccyx.
What the hell is that?
- The bone at the bottom
of your spine.
- Huh?
- The bottom of your bottom.
- My ass? I broke my ass?
- That's one way to look at it.
- Don't look at it.
You're going to need surgery,
but we'll put you under so that
we can fix the bones and
Dr. Sloan can fix your face
- all at the same time.
- You better be good.
I am, but there may
still be a little scarring.
Scarring? On my face?
Call my mother right now.
I'm finding somebody else.
Baby, you're not going to
find anybody better than me.
Oh, my God. Hot cheerleader ass.
"Take a cue from Stevens."
From Izzie Stevens. Seriously?
So many insults running
in my head, I can't pick one.
Need to cut Izzie slack. Her
and George are having problems.
Already? Only been a week.
That point you don't talk.
- All you do is have sex.
- Doesn't mean you can't
have problems.
Derek and I are having sex,
and he's dating other people.
- You didn't hear any of this.
- Oh, please.
- Don't even think about it.
- We were in an accident.
We're traumatized.
Fine. Whatever.
Paged me because you
couldn't handle stitches on a wino?
Hollering for Dr. Grey. Wasn't sure
if I should get her or call the cops.
That's not Dr. Grey.
Dr. Grey's a girl!
I want my daughter! Alex Karev!
Stay here. Make
sure he doesn't leave.
- Did you page... page her?
- Karev.
Keep Meredith
out of it. Get Lexie.
- Yes, sir.
- G-R-E-Y!
- Come on!
- I need to talk
to you about your dad.
Know what? I don't
want to talk about my dad.
We're never gonna talk about him again.
You helped me out once. Now it's over.
I can't believe I got
to fill out all this stuff.
I mean, a kid gets
a bump on the head
and you've practically
got to write a novel?
I know you're really busy,
but if there's any chance at all
you could help
me out with this...
Patient fill those
out. Not the doctor.
You be quiet. Don't
worry about it, Marcus.
- We'll figure out something.
- Good old Mandi.
- You always got my back, huh?
- You hush now.
I hate to interrupt the reminiscing,
but I am trying to listen here.
You do have atrial fibrillation.
You're not symptomatic,
that's a good sign.
We'll start you on blood thinners
and do an outpatient workup.
A treatment plan you could
have made yourself, Dr. Bailey,
if you weren't acting
like such a blithering idiot.
Oh, teacher's pet's in trouble!
Oh, come on, now.
Hush now, Marcus King.
Hey, you paged me.
- Yeah, your dad's here.
- What?
He's drunk, noisy, and you
need to take him off my hands.
I have a broken
ass to get back to.
- Call Lexie.
- I called Lexie,
she's not coming.
Next person I'm calling
is the cops because
the guy's ready to get out,
and there's no way he can drive.
Get out! Leave
me alone! Meredith!
Gosh, it's good to see you.
See, that's her! Meredith Grey!
- I'm sorry. I really, really am.
- I'm sure you are.
Not just for this.
The last time I was here, I
said some terrible things to you.
Telling you not to come to
Susan's funeral? It wasn't your fault.
What happened to her, I know that.
I know you did everything you could.
You're a good doctor.
You're a fine person.
What I said to you...
I'll regret it until
the day I die.
And the drinking...
It's unacceptable.
I... I don't.
Very... very rarely.
But today...
Today is Susan's
birthday, and I...
- Should I go get Lexie?
- No. Just you.
I just want you.
I never knew what to say to
them. In high school, kids like him.
I always felt so sorry for them.
They were always so...
separate from the rest of us.
Alone. Wasn't like that for me.
I was prom queen
and class valedictorian.
Yeah, I wouldn't broadcast that.
Even beyond that, I had a
great group of friends, you know?
- Not really.
- Hey. Let me see
what we got here.
See that, Dr. Stevens?
Yeah. Looks like the pencil lifted
up one of the branches of the ACA.
- Is that a bleed?
- It is. It's a little one.
We need to get that pencil
out before it gets any bigger.
I'll book an OR.
I am not a blithering idiot.
Hahn had no right to speak
to me that way. No right at all.
Marcus isn't a...
Well, he's just not an
old friend, is he? Is he?
He was, maybe, a boyfriend or...
You know, high school sweetheart or...
I was his tutor. OK?
He was a track star, didn't
have a lot of time for homework.
So I helped him with his math.
And reading.
And French. Chemistry.
And he was just a friend?
Really?
OK, there was some talk.
The possibility of us going
to the homecoming together,
but it didn't work out,
and I was fine with that.
Certainly not a
blithering idiot.
Today nor any
other day in my life.
That, that and that. Thank you.
Is it me or are there
teenyboppers staring at you?
I get that a lot.
It started when I was their
age. It never really went away.
Is that so?
Come on. Let's go over
there. Come on! Come on!
- What can I do for you ladies?
- Tell him.
- No. It's embarrassing.
- You can tell me.
You look like
exactly like her dad.
Swing and a miss!
I'm crazy with this Hahn thing.
Every time I try and impress her,
she hates me even more.
Not worth getting hung up on.
Why? Did something happen?
Apparently, they're not even
talking to each other at this point.
But I didn't say anything.
I know it's wrong, but
that makes me feel better.
Oh, thanks.
You're not going to sit?
Um, I was going to, but I need
to cram. I got a big surgery today.
We're operating on the kid
with the pencil. I'll see you.
- OK, see you around.
- OK.
- OK, got that.
- She be able to sit
on her butt,
or carry around one of those
toilet seats for the rest of her life?
She'll have use of
her butt in a few weeks.
I am so honored to be
filling in for you as captain.
You're filling in
for me as captain?
Well, somebody's got to. I prayed on
it. God seems to think it's the right move.
- Oh, OK.
- And I don't want you to worry.
Called Randy. I
might've convinced him
to take you to homecoming, even
though your face and butt's messed up.
Bet he'll take you.
He's classy that way.
OK, so now that we've established
that Randy's a classy guy,
- visiting time is over.
- Bye, sweetie.
- I hope they don't ruin
your face.
- Go!
Kind of sucks, huh?
When they turn on you?
Little manicured vultures.
My life is over.
My life is over!
Mom?
I'll be fine.
It'll be fine.
I know.
I love you, too.
Will you... Will you tell Dad...
Hello? Hello?
Thanks to your piece of crap
phone, my mom's going to think I died.
Oh...
- This is where...
- Yeah. But we'll keep you updated.
Hey.
You better not end up blind and go
to some blind kid's school because,
if I have to go back to
junior year without you,
you're going to be dead meat.
- Later, freak.
- You're the freak.
- You are.
♪ This is the last one ♪
- How's the bleeding?
- Slight. Very controllable.
Promised life gets better after
high school. Deserves to see that.
Got a good friend. That's something.
That girl's been by his bedside all day.
Even so, those
cliques are miserable.
He needs to know
it passes, eventually.
Sorry, Dr. Shepherd.
Didn't mean to interrupt.
What's so funny?
I'm not sure we've come as far
as you'd like to think. Clique-wise.
- We?
- The hospital.
- Think the hospital's cliquey?
- You don't?
Oh, damn it. The artery's burst.
The pericallosal artery. Brain is
swelling. Cutting off the blood supply.
OK, push 80 grams of
mannitol. OK, let's go!
How do I tell his best friend
that he's going to be in a coma
- for the rest of his life?
- You can't tell her yet, Derek.
The family has to know first.
They're still on a plane.
- I understand that, but...
- Danny's doctor.
Oh, thank God. Only been
a few hours without Danny,
I'm already
starting to freak out.
I mean, look what I have to
put up with. They're crying.
Like real tears because
they're so worried about Danny,
which would be fine if
they knew who Danny was.
Whatever. Can I see him?
He hasn't woken up yet.
He's OK?
Soon as I know
something, I'll let you know.
OK.
- Think she'll recover
full function?
- Hope so. If she doesn't
get back on the pom-pom
brigade, her life is totally over.
Is that what she said?
After the band of harpies she thought
were her friends picked over her carcass.
You'd think, way they treat her,
she'd be ready to ditch
the whole thing, but no.
She's not going to walk away from
that. It's her life. It's her identity.
Only way she understands
herself in the world.
Mm-hm. Heard one of the sweet young
things told Mark he looked like her dad.
Harsh.
What does that have
to do with anything?
You seem really
empathetic to her plight.
You know, loss of identity?
Shattered self-image?
You seem happy about
what happened to her.
Torres is just happy because
Stevens and O'Malley hit the skids.
Didn't I tell you
not to tell anybody?
I pulled the X-rays for
tomorrow's scheduled surgeries.
And what am I supposed
to do with them?
Thought I could put them in
the OR if you needed me to.
Well, I don't.
- Back off.
- What?
- You're being a brownnoser.
- I am not a brownnoser.
I'm helping her.
Annoying her. Got a chance to show
what you can do, you're blowing it.
Trust me, these kind of chances
do not come around all the time.
So, you know, just back off.
Back off...
I'm sorry I didn't know you
when you were in high school.
I've regretted it every
day, not knowing you.
Not being there.
Sometimes I still
worry about you.
Other times I think, you know,
maybe it's what made you so strong.
Not an excuse, not at all.
You are so strong.
You're stronger than Lexie.
- I don't know her that well.
- Well, true.
You're a very impressive
person, Meredith.
I'm so proud of you.
I'm a lifetime's worth of proud.
Anyway...
Anyway, old man's rambling.
Thank you.
Hey. How was your
date with Sydney?
Wondering when you
were going to bring that up.
- My dad's in the ER.
- Really?
He cut himself.
He's not bad company, actually.
He's quite funny and charming.
Drunk.
Is it weird that I like my drunk
dad better than my regular dad?
A little.
- Are you OK?
- Yeah, um...
My patient's in a coma and he's
never going to wake up again.
His best friend is
in the waiting area.
Poor thing thinks he's...
She thinks he's going
to wake up any second.
I don't know.
I don't believe
it. Who told you?
Henry. He was observing
in Sloan's surgery,
and he said that Sloan
announced it to the whole OR.
- Wow. O'Malley
and Stevens are done.
- Yeah.
- They didn't even last a week.
- I know.
Tragic.
Can I have the key
back, to my house?
Hey. What?
Key. To my house? I want
it back. I heard we broke up.
- Can I have it?
- Don't have any idea
- what you're talking about.
- Everyone's talking about
the fact we broke up.
Who you been talking to?
Nobody. I mean, to Meredith.
I knew it! What exactly
did you say to her?
Nothing I... What do you mean
you knew it? You been talking to her?
Yeah. But only after
you were talking to her.
So I'm not the only one
who talked to her, then.
You talked to her first!
What is my dad doing here?
Your dad came in
drunk this morning.
That's what I was trying to
tell you when you blew me off.
So you run to Meredith?
The one person that I
asked you not to tell?
- I was trying to help, OK?
- Right.
And what about Linda Russell,
do you have her contact info?
You know you haven't
changed? I mean, not even one bit.
You get this very intense look on your
face when you're serious, you know?
It's your serious
homework doing face.
- Hasn't changed.
- Dr. Bailey.
Is that a patient form
I see in your hand?
Yes, I suppose it is.
You're not supposed
to fill out patient forms.
Patients are
supposed to fill forms.
You have work to
do. Your own work.
- Yes, sir.
- Mandi?
- Mandi, I'm not...
- I'm not feeling so...
- Marcus? Marcus!
- Pulse ox is dropping.
- Pressure's 82 over 48.
Tell Radiology we need a stat
spiral CT, and page Dr. Hahn.
- Dr. Shepherd?
- Marissa.
Is he awake yet?
No, not yet.
I know Danny's parents aren't going
to be here for a couple more hours,
but could I at least
see him? Please?
All right, come on.
Let's go sit down.
The...
When I removed the
pencil, the artery burst.
When the brain swells that
much, it has nowhere to go.
The hem...
Hey.
I would like to announce that I
am getting two cups of coffee.
Two. One for me, one
for my dad. He's here.
It's not horrible.
What's wrong with you?
At this exact moment in OR Two,
Dr. Hahn is performing a
pulmonary embolectomy.
- A pulmonary embolectomy. Meredith.
- So what's the problem?
- You're on her service. Go.
- No, I can't.
That'd make me a brownnoser,
and everybody hates brownnosers.
I cannot be a brownnoser.
OK. There'll be other embolectomies.
You can let this one slide.
No, no, no! No, I can't!
I don't know how to just let a
pulmonary embolectomy slide!
Sure you can. It's
like cutting a class.
- You never cut a class.
- Never. Not once.
Ha.
That was a pretty
big VSD on the echo.
Going to have to do an additional
arteriotomy of the right PA.
- It should never
have come to this.
- I'm sorry?
You should've taken the situation
seriously, ordered further tests.
Maybe I should have.
Maybe you should have.
And if you weren't so busy flirting with
the patient like a lovestruck teenager,
maybe you would have.
Forceps, please.
This is so sad. I used to
walk by his house every day.
He was in my
algebra class, I think.
Marissa.
I know that this seems impossible
right now, but you will get through this.
- Danny would've wanted you to.
- Don't know what he would've
wanted.
You're just like them.
You're a prom queen and you're trying
to act like you know what it's like for me.
You have no idea what it's like.
I wasn't a prom queen.
I was the girl in the cheap clothes
from the trailer park who got pregnant,
and got thrown in the
pregnant girls' class.
I lost all my friends.
None of the mothers would
let their kids hang out with me.
But I got through it.
You will get through this.
I'm going to write a
letter to his mom and dad.
That's really beautiful.
- Get out.
- What?
You're not supposed
to be in here.
- She's here.
- She's his friend. His best friend.
Go away. Go!
- I'm sorry. I didn't mean to...
- It's OK.
You just lost your best friend.
It's the worst thing in the world.
- I won't repeat a word.
- Thank you.
- Dr. Shepherd?
- Yes.
I'm sorry. About Danny Metcalf.
It looked like it was hard on you.
Which is good. If I had
a son going through that,
I'd want the surgeon to be
fully invested, like you were.
You have no idea
who I am, do you?
Course I do.
Bye, Dr. Shepherd.
You're the nurse in OR Two.
The one that talked about cliques?
Yeah, right?
♪ ...make myself feel bad
There's a chance I'll start ♪
♪ To wonder if this
was the thing to do ♪
Once we get your knee moving,
we can get you out of bed,
and then you can start
putting some weight on it.
But I won't be able
to dance for a year?
Probably not.
Sometimes...
when things don't work out the
way you planned, there's gifts...
You're gonna give me some
stupid speech about silver linings?
I am never going
to be captain again.
I was fired from a
job recently, and...
You were fired from being a
doctor, and they let you cut my ass?
OK, shut your trap for eight
seconds and let me finish.
I didn't get fired from being a
doctor. I got fired from being, like...
Well, our version
of squad captain.
Which is mostly
about organizing crap.
- Not about surgery.
- So?
So... I got to go back
to the part that I like.
Which... It's kind of a gift.
Hahn. Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
- ♪ Call ♪
- ♪ Break ♪
- ♪ It ♪
- ♪ Off ♪
- ♪ Call ♪
- ♪ Break ♪
- ♪ My own heart ♪
- ♪ Heart ♪
♪ Maybe I would have been
something you'd be good at ♪
♪ Maybe you would have
been something I'd be good at ♪
You paged, Dr. Hahn?
Apparently when you ask for
copies of the CT angio around here,
people think it's all right to just give
you the slices that contain the clot.
Can you please bring
me the entire CT?
Absolutely. Yes, absolutely.
I'll do that right now.
♪ ...to wonder if this
was the thing to do ♪
♪ I'll start to wonder if
this was the thing to do ♪
- Your dad was in the ER today.
- I know.
You know he was drunk and he
put his hand through a window?
- Yeah. Anything else?
- I know it was Susan's
birthday,
and I'm sure it was a very
hard day for the both of you.
And he wasn't
actually a problem.
He was kind of charming,
but he seemed very sad,
and I'd hate to see
it happen again.
So, maybe, you should think
about keeping a better eye on him.
Every day is my
mother's birthday.
My mother was born
in March. He lied.
He's a liar. And I'm glad.
Really, I'm glad that
you found him charming.
I'm sure he was delightful.
He's a blast after five drinks.
Not so much after nine, though.
He gets a little weepy and mean.
He's a drunk, Meredith.
He probably came in and
told you how wonderful you are.
How sad he is that he doesn't
get to spend more time with you.
You know, yesterday he said
that I was his favorite daughter.
The day before, I was
an ungrateful bitch.
The week before, he wrote
me a check for 20,000 dollars
because he said I deserved
everything life had to offer.
Because he was so proud of
me. A lifetime's worth of proud.
So you can't listen to anything
he says because it's not about you.
It's about a pint and
a half of Dewar's.
So thank you for letting me know
that I need to keep a
better eye on him. Thanks.
Meredith, you want to come
in for a minute and sit down?
Meredith?
- I'm sorry about all this.
- Meredith, please.
You have nothing to
apologize for. Nothing at all.
I'm keeping you
from doing your job.
This is my job.
At least part of it.
Think of it as the
principal's office.
Only I'm the nice principal.
Anyway, I promised your
mom I'd take care of you.
I told you, you
don't have to do that.
I know. I know
I don't. But I do.
- Hey, you.
I guess I'm still alive
and kicking, huh?
You had a clot that traveled to
your lungs, but we got to it in time.
So you're going to be kicking for a
good long time now, Marcus King.
Mandi.
You have always been my angel.
Always have been. I just...
I never would've made it
through high school without you.
through this day without you.
- Come on now.
- Mandi, I mean it.
Thank you. I thank you.
My mama thanks you.
And you know my
daddy thanks you.
You tell your mama and daddy
that I said they're welcome.
Oh, hey, I was...
I was wondering if you got a
chance to finish up that paperwork.
I wouldn't ask, but, you know,
I think a lot of it was
kind of important.
No, I didn't. I
was planning on...
Just got to, you know...
finish it right now.
Thanks. You're the best.
♪ Oh, oh, 'cause I'm
scared I'm growing old ♪
♪ Oh oh oh ♪
♪ Don't return the love I gave ♪
Come here. With all due respect,
this has reached critical mass.
You saved his life, and
he's taking you for granted.
Know what he deserves? A long
speech. You need to go right back in there,
and you need to give
him a long, long speech.
♪ Troubles don't turn
upside-down, ohh ♪
♪ They shit on
the last bit of fun ♪
♪ There's sin all around ♪
♪ Lovers cannot let down ♪
♪ And the winter
wears and tears ♪
♪ Our bones ♪
I don't do secrets.
I don't do any of
that 15-year-old,
"Oh, I'm going to tell you,
but don't tell anyone else."
I don't do that crap.
We're not talking about who made
out with who at the Halloween dance.
OK, this was a
private family issue.
Your dad's a drunk. He
comes in and screams
at the top of his
lungs in the ER.
It couldn't be less private.
I had to start cleaning up
my dad when I was seven.
That's when I turned
into the grown-up.
So you got to wait until
you were 24. Good for you.
♪ He sweats it out
all the night through ♪
Night, Bailey.
- Sit down.
- What?
Sit down!
- You OK?
- What do you care?
With your hair products
and your perfect little face,
perfect little life. What
do you care how I am?
Perfect life? Have you
been paying attention?
Yeah, I pay attention.
I pay attention.
I pay attention to people
in all walks of life. All types!
I notice people. I see people.
It's guys like you who
don't see people like me.
I don't see you?
Clearly, I'm not talking
about you, Shepherd.
Just...
Guys like you who
don't see girls like me.
We don't exist for you. We
exist to do your homework.
We exist to build your ego up.
I am a successful,
married mother.
I am Chief Resident!
I am Chief Resident of a
major metropolitan hospital!
I am a surgeon who
saved his life today!
And he still doesn't see me.
I may as well still be
that high school girl
with the mushroom haircut
and the Coke bottle
glasses, and the band uniform.
The girl who didn't get to go
to homecoming dance because
it didn't even occur
to him to ask me.
All those late nights tutoring him,
and it didn't even occur to him to ask.
Hmm.
Band uniform. Really?
Do I look like I'm going to
be mocked by you right now?
No, you don't. I'm just
going to say one thing.
In high school, I was a 110 pounds
and I hadn't yet figured out hair product.
I had a big Afro and had acne.
And I, too, wore a band uniform.
Sax.
Oboe.
I would have been honored to
take a girl like you to homecoming.
In some ways we grow up.
We have families.
We get married...
Divorced.
I was trying to think
of a long speech.
You know, like Bailey with
her long speeches, and just...
Just everything I
wanted to say to you.
The gist is, I can't talk to you.
That's why I talk to Meredith.
I just... I don't know why.
It used to be...
It use to be...
that I was the only person you could
talk to. And you were the only person
- I could talk to.
- I know.
I need to be
able to talk to you.
I'm in love with this incredible
guy, and we're having problems.
And my best friend, he would
know what to say to me about it.
I need to be able to
talk to my best friend.
I cannot get through this
without my best friend.
Why isn't this easier?
I don't know.
Well, I want my
best friend back.
Me, too.
But, for the most part, we
still have the same problems
that we did when we were 15.
Hey, Rose. Rose!
- You know my name.
- I had to ask around,
but now I know.
- Good for you. Good night.
- Hang on.
I should have recognized
you from the OR today.
We worked together for three
hours and... It's thoughtless.
I've worked on 36
of your surgeries,
and today was the first
time you made eye contact.
Like I said, hospital's no
better than high school.
Good night, Dr. Shepherd.
Someone figured out how
to get back on the horse.
What? No. Was just
talking about work.
Could've fooled me.
Hey, Dad, want to get a drink?
♪ Here's to all
the pretty words ♪
Doctors S and S. How
are we this evening?
Hiya, Sydney.
Derek, you think I just could
talk to you for one quick minute?
Yeah. Have a seat.
Remember, heart attack.
♪ Is there trouble on the line ♪
- Derek.
- Sydney.
I want you to know that I really
enjoyed our date last night. I really did.
- I don't think
we should do it again.
- You don't?
I'm a lot of woman. OK?
I bring home the bacon.
Fry it up in a pan, serve it
with eggs or on a sandwich,
- or crumbled up
in a Cobb salad.
- You do a lot with bacon.
Not just bacon.
But, Derek, I bring a
lot of things to the table.
And I'm looking for a
man who can do the same,
a man who can meet my needs.
All my needs.
I just don't think you're ready.
Hmm.
Well, you might be right.
I won't let this affect
our work if you won't.
I won't.
♪ Betrayal is a thorny
crown You wear it well ♪
♪ Just like a king ♪
No matter how
much we grow taller...
Grow older...
Apparently, I'm not
good at meeting needs.
And I don't bring
that much to the table.
I'm awkward and freaky.
We are still forever stumbling.
- Do you want
to get out of here?
- I do.
♪ Ooh it feels good to be free ♪
♪ Ooh it feels good... ♪
Forever wondering...
Forever... young.
♪ Ooh it feels good to be free ♪