Previously on "Grey's anatomy"...
George's dad got admitted last night.
I met a sister I never knew I had.
Can you imagine...
Your whole family you know nothing about ?
I'm just asking about your dad.
Why do you care ?
You broke up with me, remember ?
Mr. O'Malley has elected to have Dr. Hahn
perform his valve replacement.
- I can clear you for surgery.
- You're sure ?
Yeah, absolutely.
I need you to tell me why you
didn't want me in on your surgery.
I'm afraid I just couldn't use you.
I can't see your mother anymore.
It's time for you to retire, Richard.
I'm going to be chief.
I had a tremor and I didn't
say anything about it.
- We crossed the line.
- You dragged me across the line.
He's with her.
He's with that woman... His wife.
I don't think he is, not anymore.
He is. I mean, why would he do that ?
He loves me.
I mean, why would he go back to her?
I gave up everything for him.
Mom.
Mom, look at me.
This happened... a very long time ago.
This is not happening now.
It's because I have a daughter, isn't it ?
He always said he didn't want kids.
I should never have had a kid.
What's gonna happen to them ?
- What?
- Dr. Burke and dr. Yang...
What are you gonna do to them,
their punishment ?
- Dr. Bailey...
- There's a need for justice here.
Justice ?
Justice has no definition within the
four walls of a hospital, Dr. Bailey.
- This isn't a court of law.
- I just wannna know what's gonna be done.
Legally and technically, they've done
nothing wrong. Nobody died,
there was no malpractice.
I haven't made a decision.
Excuse me.
- He...
- He what ?
Nothin'.
Dr. Yang, you'll go back on the floor
with Dr. Bailey.
- Sir...
- Dr. Bailey, am I not understanding this ?
Does this situation directly
harm you in some way?
No, Sir.
I am fine.
Then get back to work.
Burke, you and Shepherd need to come
together on this tremor
as soon as possible.
- He doesn't want my help.
- Derek...
I don't want his help.
That hand is worth $2 million.
I want it fixed,
and I want it fixed yesterday.
Figure it out.
Listen, your brothers are good boys,
but they're not that responsible.
It's a standard procedure.
It's just that,
- if things go wrong...
- Dad...
- If
things go wrong,
the life insurance papers are in the
second drawer in my nightstand...
and my... magazines are in the garage
- with the truck manuals.
- Your magazines ?
Get'em outta there
so your ma doesn't see them.
Your magazines ?
Good morning, Mr. O'Malley.
Just wanted to stop by before the surgery
and see how that collarbone was healing.
George... You're not gonna say hello
to Dr. Torres ?
I'm gonna see you for rounds, Dad.
If you had you told me that you were
developing a tremor, I could've run some tests.
The likelihood is that there's just some
compression of the structures around the injury.
- I can go in there...
- I don't want another surgery.
- It could be a small clot. I just go in--
- Shepherd,
I don't want another surgery.
The first one caused enough damage.
I can do this.
That's what you said the last time.
Now I have a tremor.
Maybe she'll be on "look but don't touch"
patrol, too. At least I'd have some company.
Whatever she gets, I hope it's bad,
Really bad.
She made a mistake.
- A mistake ?
- We all...
She was gonna let Burke... Burke with
the shaky hand operate on my father.
Could you stop looking at me like that ?
It's creepy, and it makes me feel
like you haven't been fed.
- How's it going ?
- How's what going ?
You and Burke, are you okay ?
We're existing in total silence.
- He's not talking to you ?
- I'm not talking to him either.
I'm sorry. Are you okay?
Stop  asking me that.
- I'm making an effort here.
- Please don't.
Rounds started 30 seconds ago.
The chief may be confused about
punishment for you, but I'm not.
You're late again, you will find
another resident.
Dr. Bailey, can I have Grey ?
You can have'em all.
Something you needed, Dr. Montgomery ?
This is none of my business, but I just
thought you might want to be warned.
I'm sorry. I don't know...
Your sister Molly's just been admitted
for an emergency c-section.
Molly's not my sister.
Okay, but technically, she is,
you have the same father.
- And, uh, Susan--
- Susan Grey is definitely not my mother.
I appreciate you're trying to be nice
and everything, but I really don't
even need to know this,
- So...
- Actually you do.
- Hello, Meredith.
Hi, mom.
Honey. Oh.
I put out some breakfast in case you
kids haven't eaten yet.
- Score.
- Karev.
Hey, ready for the big day, pops ?
Mm, food.
All right, let's make this fast,
people. I have a day.
- Which one of the interns is mine ?
- It's mine.
He's family, and she's a candy striper.
- I'm ready.
- What if you did pick me ?
What if you picked me?
Pick me !
Guys, this is serious.
Yang.
- What ?
Dr. Hahn, Cristina is very good with cardio.
I'm sure you can use her for the day.
What are you waiting for, Yang ?
Present the case.
Harold O'Malley, 63, diagnosed with
esophageal cancer and severe aortic regurge,
he is scheduled for aortic valve
replacement this afternoon.
Dude, I wanted that surgery,
and she hands it to Yang.
- I haven't had a cardiac case in ages.
- It's not a case. It's my father.
I guess there's a double standard now.
Yang does something wrong, and
she gets rewarded. That's fair.
Yeah.
If you thumb suckers don't stop whining,
I swear I won't show you what's behind this door,
and trust me, you want to see
what's behind this door.
Excuse me, Doctors, you're gonna have
to wait a few minutes. He's gotta pee.
Every five minutes, he's gotta pee.
I've always had a small bladder.
I can't live like this any longer.
You  ? I'm the one who has to
put up with your whining.
Like the whining you're doing right now ?
Okay, you know what ?
If you don't move, it's gonna go all over your leg
So what else is new ?
Now which one of you thinks
that Yang got the better case ?
That's what I thought.
Jake and Peter Weitzman,
35-year-old pygopagus
conjoined twins attached at
the lumbosacral junction.
But not for long, right, Dr. Webber ?
The Weitzmans came about six months ago
for a separation procedure.
They opted out because of the risk.
Pete chickened out.
Well, forgive me for wanting to live
longer, even if it meant living with you.
Yeah ? Well, you wasted
six months of our lives...
Oh, come on.
- Thank you very much.
- Stop it.
You guys came back at the right time.
We just scored New York's
top plastic surgeon.
Mark Sloan, plastics, and you remember
Dr. Shepherd, your neurosurgeon.
- We, uh, we used to work
as a team, actually.
We worked together.
We were never actually a team.
I hear ya.
- Mr. Weitzman ?
- Call me Jake.
- Call me Pete.
Jake, Pete, um, why...
do you mind me asking why now
when you thought the procedure
was too risky six months ago ?
- Well...
- Guys.
Whoa.
That's a lot of doctors. I'm...
I'm just gonna come back later.
No, no, no, no, no.
Elena, come in, come in.
You wanted to know why now.
This is why...
The love of my life... Elena.
Jake, don't...
I told him not to do this, not for me
anyway,'cause that's just crazy.
'Cause Pete said that
they could end up paralyzed.
They could end up dead.
What do you tell her
things like that for ?
I wasn't telling her. I was telling you.
She just happens to be
the only one who listens to me.
She happens to be right.
Do you know what it's like to have to
be stuck to the same person...
Here we go.
Every... That's right.
Do you know what it's like to have to be
with the same person every minute of every day,
To not have anything that's just yours,
not be able to do anything on your own ?
Well, nobody should have to
live like that.
What do you think, Pete ?
I think, why would I want to be attached
to someone who doesn't want to be
attached to me ?
I'm calling it. It's mine
I have two brothers.
I feel their pain.
I would be great at watching this.
- Zip it, all of you.
- We're on the case, right ?
- Right.
- Yes !
Awesome.
Stevens, you are to...
Look and not touch or speak or breathe.
I got it.
So this is the crack team, huh ?
Feel  free to take one.
How about I take the one that doesn't
touch or speak or breathe ?
Right.
Damn it.
Thank you... for picking me.
Even just observing.
I thought you might be fun
to look at while I work.
Will you be working on both the
nerve graft and the skin reconstruction ?
Yes, and I think I'll handle them a whole
lot better with a little caffeine in my system.
Get me a blueberry scone, a bone dry cappuccino
and a little something for yourself.
There's a cafeteria on the second floor
and a coffee cart in the lobby.
Feisty. Cappuccino.
You can kick me back to Bailey
if you want. I don't do coffee.
So how will you be handling the nerve
graft and the skin reconstruction ?
Conjoined twins, Derek.
I know, Chief.
Conjoined adult twins.
I mean, it's rare enough to separate
conjoined infants. But conjoined adults ?
Mm-hmm.
Can you imagine the press,
what a surgery like this
could do for this hospital ?
I know, which is why
I don't think we should do it.
Their spines are fused together
from the l4 down.
Their blood flow
is intricately connected.
They could end up paralyzed,
or even dead.
Your patients want this operation, Derek.
Why are you backing out ?
This isn't like you.
Unless there's incontrovertible evidence
that this surgery can't be done,
we're moving forward.
Your  father's not here.
Thatcher's at Harvard med visiting Lexie.
We thought we had a lot of time.
I mean, Molly's only 36 weeks, and Dr.
Montgomery's been trying to stop the contractions,
but I guess the baby
is ready to come out.
Well, do you need anything else or...
Yeah, actually, I could use an intern for this.
Can you ask Dr. Bailey for someone ?
Uh... I'll do it.
Are you sure ?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Okay.
It'll be so nice to have a familiar face
in the operating room.
Thank you
for being here.
It's my job to be here, so...
Uh, does Molly know who I am ?
She doesn't.
I wanted to tell her, but your father...
- He just... He...
- No,
It's better. It's better that she
not know. It's good.
So I think, uh, Molly should be ready
in the O.R. Susan, you'll need scrubs
and a cap.
I'm about to be a grandmother.
Yes, in about a half an hour,
you will be a grandmother.
Oh,  my. Okay.
- Here we go.
Here we go.
We're going to be replacing your aortic
valve with a porcine valve.
Well, Georgie says it's gonna be okay.
He says they know what they're doing.
Besides, if you die,
I'll kill you.
Well, it's a good thing
we're doing this today.
Well, it's a good thing we're doing this today.
We noticed you had a lot
of irregular heart rhythms
this morning.
We noticed you had a lot of irregular
heart rhythms this morning.
Did you check his dig level ?
Excuse me.
What are you doing ?
This morning his potassium
was a borderline low.
All right, we've got a handle
on things here.
Oh, I'm sure you do.
Uh, george, I think maybe
you should step outside.
You don't talk to me like that.
Oh, she's waking up the baby.
Ronny, shut up.
Be careful, Dr. Hahn,
- He might start crying.
- I said shut up.
All right, you are out of here.
No, I'm not.
- Georgie.
- No, uh, she can't kick me out.
She has no right. I hired her.
I'm staying.
How you doing there, Molly ?
Okay.
I'm just excited to see my girl.
Well, you're gonna get to take a look
at her in just a couple of minutes.
Dr. Grey, can you give me
a little more traction ?
Vitals are holding steady.
Can you see her yet ?
No. I'm not gonna look
until the blood's all gone.
You want to cut the cord, Dr. Grey ?
The warmer is ready when you need it,
Dr. Montgomery.
Dr. Grey, will you follow me ?
Dr. Knox, will you close for me, please ?
Bag valve mask.
We have to stabilize this baby
and get it into surgery.
- Get her on the monitor.
- What's happening ?
What's wrong with her ?
Susan, I need you to stand back
and stay with molly, please.
What's wrong with her ?
- No response to stimulation.
- Grey, you want to talk her through this ?
Let's try suction.
Grey, I need your help here.
The baby is not breathing.
What ?
What did she say ?
You left me hanging in there, Grey.
I'm sorry. I was...
I'm sorry.
Do you need me to scrub in on the baby ?
No. I want you to keep
molly and her mother
apprised of the baby's condition
while I operate.
I'm sure they'd rather talk to you.
The baby's got jejunal atresia.
She may die.
I got consent, but I don't
have time for updates.
I think I would really learn a lot
from observing this procedure.
No, it was a mistake to let you in the O.R.
with your family in the first place.
It's not gonna happen again.
Check in with me every hour.
How many valve replacements have you
performed in your life, Dr. O'Malley ?
- None.
And how many valve replacements
do you think Dr. Hahn has performed ?
That is my father!
And you are in that room as his son.
You interns think you can do
whatever you want to do.
Well, not anymore, not with me,
which is why you are going to stay away,
50 feet away to be precise.
You are going to remain 50 feet away
from your father at all times today,
and, Dr. O'Malley, do not make me
tell you again.
Everything okay with the O'Malleys ?
The kid's a pain in the ass.
But Dr. Yang here is proving to be
an extremely capable asset.
I hear she studied under you.
You trained her well.
Yes.
Well, she's very...
professional.
What do you know about Dr. Levine ?
Pretty good.
Better or worse than Dr. Korsikov ?
Wait...
why are you researching neurosurgeons
when you and I both know that Derek's
better than anybody ?
I don't want Shepherd.
You blaming this on him ?
You know, up until now,
I have not yelled.
I have not yelled because you were
a guy in trouble,
and I was supporting you.
But now...
- I am yelling !
- Chief.
I am yelling very loudly !
I want to retire, Burke!
I want my wife back !
And I passed the torch to you !
I passed the torch to you,
and you blew it out !
Look, I know I let you down.
Burke...
I'm tired.
I'm tired of you men acting like boys.
You let me down.
And if you don't let Derek fix that hand,
you're letting yourself down.
22 surgeons...
it takes 22 surgeons to do this.
So where are we ?
I've gotten to the cauda equina.
I'll be working on the musculature
of the perineal floor.
I'll be harvesting
the sural nerve for transfer.
Now once I resect this artery,
we're gonna have less than two minutes
before all sensation to these nerves are gone.
I'm pretty sure we'll have enough nerve
to transfer and cover the deficits.
We can definitely do this.
Oh, damn it.
It's gonna be a lot more
fragile in the body.
It's one thing if this is a life-or-deh
situation
and this is all we can do to save them.
These guys are fine.
This isn't worth the risk.
How is our baby ?
She has an intestinal obstruction,
which is why she couldn't breathe.
Dr. Montgomery is operating
on her right now.
I can't do this.
- I can't do it.
- Yes, you can. Yes, you can.
I am right here, baby,
and dad's on the way.
I have to call Eric.
O kay.
I don't know what to tell him.
That's her husband. He's in Iraq.
I can't tell him this.
He's gonna want to name her,
and I don't wanna name her'cause I don't
know how long she's gonna be ours.
Oh, now... Shh.
We'll call him together.
He's just gonna be happy
to hear your voice.
The baby's gonna be okay.
You hear me ?
I thought you were sloan's right hand.
- Yeah, well, Sloan can kiss my--
- Ow...
I haven't even put the needle in yet.
Sorry.
I'm just not a big fan of pain.
Well, you're about to have a fairly
extensive and painful surgery.
You think this is an elective procedure ?
That we're just coming in here because
we're getting on each other's nerves ?
Please,
- You want to know the real reason ?
- Come on, Jake.
- She doesn't want...
- It's because...
We have rules.
Rules ?
Yeah, like say one of us
is on a dinner date,
According to the rules, the other one's
supposed to sit there quietly,
eat his falafe
and shut the hell up.
I try.
It's just the way you talk
to her sometimes--
It's none of your business.
How is it none of my busins ?
He sticks up for me, and I
think that that's kinda nice.
Okay, you don't talk to him anymore.
What ? Oh, we can't even
be friends now ?
- We have other rules, too.
- Oh.
Like for when we're with someone.
- Got it.
- Sort of. No looking, no talking, no touching.
It was an accident.
Oh, this is gonna end badly.
Baby, I told you,
I'm completely fine with it.
How are you okay with the fact that he's
touching you while you're naked ?
Uh... be... cause it wasn't a big deal.
And it was kinda sweet and...
It just... It wasn't a big deal.
Wait, you... You liked it.
You enjoyed it.
I'm completely in love with you. That's
not even that you're... You're a great guy.
And...
You know, when we make love,
The... It's... It's great.
It's... It's really great.
And I've never had that before and...
It's just that when you fall asleep,
That, uh, Pete and I just... We talk.
And, um...
- I really love that, too.
- Elena.
- No
No. No, you have to choose.
- What ?
- Him or me ?
We're gonna have this surgery,
and you can't have us both.
So choose...
Him or me ?
See, this is the part where you're
supposed to say, "you, Jake. I choose you."
I'm so sorry, Jake. I'm so sorry.
Elena...
Oh, God !
- No, no, no !
- I swear to God...
Jake, it's...
- I am gonna kill you !
- Ow ! Get him off !
I think it's romantic... Two brothers
fighting... Over the same woman.
You know what's freaky ? The whole
conjoined twin having sex in front of
the other one thing.
How do you do that?
Family is complicated.
You're here.
You haven't been kicked out
of the program yet.
- Alex.
- No, not yet. I'm still here.
How'd you do it ?
I mean, did you have some kind of signal
in surgery so that the nurses wouldn't know,
- or did you--
- Alex--
What ?
I mean, I'm just wondering
how to get ahead around here.
Me ? I get coffee for sloan.
Yang. She gets surgeries
none of us would get.
Got a head count on how many patients
you two lied to the past month ?
George.
Leave her alone. Her patients lived
so she gets to scrub in.
Izzie.
Meredith, please, can you
just stop defending me ?
Ah.
No, no, no, no. I'll, uh, I'll go.
No, wait, wait.
Georgie, you should make nice with her.
- Look, dad...
- No, really, Mr. O'Malley, it's fine.
It's not fine.
George, you're so angry.
No, I'm not.
- You've been picking fights every chance
you get, and that's not like you.
- Dad...
You don't know what's been going on.
Okay, then tell me.
Why are you so mad at Dr. Torres ?
- I should go. I have patients to see.
- No, you know what ?
I'm gonna go.
No ! Everybody stays.
You're angry, Georgie...
at Callie, at your brothers,
at Dr. Hahn, at Dr. Bailey,
at Dr. Yang, at Dr. Burke.
That's a long list of
people to be angry at.
Especially when the person
you're really angry at... is me.
Dad ?
I drink and I smoke
and I don't exercise and I eat
all the wrong things, and now
I have cancer.
And you have to take care of everything.
You have to take care of me.
I don't mind.
You do.
You're mad at me, and that's okay
because
I'm mad at me, too. You think I want
to die and leave my boy in charge ?
You are not gonna die.
What's going on ?
You're not supposed to be
in here, Georgie.
Yeah, you're gonna get in trouble,
Georgie.
Georgie doesn't work here !
In this hospital, my name is
Dr. O'Malley !
Dad?
- Honey !
- Dad ?
Get Dr. Hahn.
I... I can't...
Dad, dad, don't try to talk.
He's having a heart attack, Georgie !
Why don't you pump his chest ?
Pump his chest?
Get the paddles !
They always use the paddles !
He's not having a heart attack.
Dad. Dad, stop !
I'm trying to help.
Your heart's going too fast.
Recycle his B.P.
Uh, pull, uh, verapamil, 5 milligrams.
Dad. Dad !
Stop fighting the mask.
O'Malley, what's going on ?
- You should've paged Hahn.
- I paged anyone from cardiothoracics.
He's got a-fib with rapid ventricle
response. I've ordered verapamil.
He's in v-tach. The verapamil is gonna
cause more problems than it solves.
100 lidocaine.
Uh, put on his 0-2 mask.
All right, what happened ?
He went into v-tach. O'Malley
is giving him lidocaine.
- It's already put him back in normal sinus.
- All right, I need everyone out of here.
- I got your page.
- I need another cappuccino.
Did you think I was kidding before ?
I am your attending, and if you want in
on my surgeries,
you're gonna learn how to fetch
and stay and heel.
Fine.
- Don't fetch angry.
- If you think this means I respect you,
if you want me to respect you, you have
to do something worth respecting.
all of these cables of nerves... ah...
I can't do this surgery, Miranda.
I started to think I shouldn't be
operating after the Duquette M&M.
All the whispers and the talk...
- I let that in.
- Mm.
I started to question myself.
I believed it when I was told, uh,
I was no longer of use in the O.R.
Oh, so when you said you wanted justice,
you were talking about...
I'm a surgeon.
There are lives in my hands.
To make me question that...
No, that's to put a life at stake
every time I hold a scalpel.
Well, I told Burke I could fix his hand,
and then...
Well, you did.
Yeah.
He is not paralyzed or...
Or disabled in any way.
He has a tremor.
And if he had been honest about that,
well, there's no telling what you could
have done to prevent it.
Mm-hmm.
We can do this.
Hold on to my wedding ring,
honey. Hospital rules.
Georgie, are you gonna
be there in the operation ?
They don't allow family in,
but you'll be fine.
I'll be fine.
We'll take good care of you.
What am I gonna do ?
What am I gonna do if he dies ?
- I changed my mind.
- Oh, no, you didn't.
Dr. Bailey, I'd like to be excused from
the twins if that's all right with you.
I'd like to be with my mom.
That's the right call, O'Malley. Go.
Promise me something...
when you separate us, can you make
sure his ass is bigger than mine ?
I can hear you.
You're still here. I went to N.I.C.U.
I thought you'd be done.
I'm having trouble with this anastomosis,
and I still have to take a look
at the distal bowel.
- What should I tell Molly ?
- I don't know.
Tell her I'm doing the best I can.
I don't know.
Dr. Bailey,
I'd like my intern to observe
from a better vantage point.
Dr. Stevens ?
Yes.
She's my intern today, and I'd like her
nearby during surgery, not up in the
gallery, if that's okay with you.
No problem.
Dr. Bailey, Stevens is without privileges.
Oh, 'cause she messed up ?
Dr. Yang messed up, and she's
over in O.R. Two right now.
Will you hit that for me ?
Stevens,
I take it you remember how to scrub in.
Come on.
This vessel's even more fragile
than in the biomodel.
Let's do a microvascular bypass graft.
I could harvest the saphenous
vein while I'm down here.
I don't know. I don't know
if that's a good idea.
Gentlemen,
we need to make a decision,
and we need to make it now.
Derek, it's your call.
Do you or don't you want to proceed ?
- Give me a 10-blade.
- Let's get some suction in here, please.
I'm not supposed to be here.
Me either.
- How's it going ?
- They just started.
Allright, the skin incision
is done. Let's go.
she's... Through the sternum.
There's a bit of bleeding.
She's stopping it with bone wax.
Inserting the retractor...
she's opening the pericardial sac.
Taking a look at the echo,
she's nodding.
Looks good.
They're looking at your dad's heart now.
She's preparing to put in the stay sutures.
- Is the saphenous vein graft in place ?
- Yeah. Yeah, I'm ready.
Dr. Bailey?
- I'm good.
- Chief ?
Ready when you are.
All right,
the moment of truth.
Removing the clamps.
Dr. Bailey check the nerve stimulator.
S.S.E.P. are falling.
All right, pump up the blood pressure.
We need as much blood through
the area as possible.
I'm going up to 2 milliamps.
Up to 3.
wait a minute. Uh, I see something.
A flicker on the hamstring of twin "A."
Anything on twin "b"?
Pump it up some more.
Okay, up to 4.
A twitch. I got a twitch
on twin b's gastroc.
Yeah, it's small, but it's there.
We have a signal.
Congratulations, ladies and gentlem.
We have four functioning legs.
Good job, everybody.
Ladies and gentlemen, on three.
One...
Two...
Three.
It'd be nice if every love triangle
could be fixed with a scalpel.
If they could, you'd have stabbed me
with a 10-blade a long time ago.
How is she ?
Please tell me good news
because I have to go in
and tell molly,
and I don't want to tell her
anything bad.
because I have to go in and tell Molly,
and I don't want to tell her anything bad.
Dr. Montmery is on her way,
and she will explain everything.
But the baby...
Laura. Molly named her Laura.
Oh, Laura... Will need some recovery time,
but she should be just fine.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, I was so scared.
Oh, thank you. Oh, God.
She's gonna be so happy to hear this.
Hey, this is your niece you know ?
I'm sorry.
You're very nice. You both seem...
so nice.
But I don't know you.
And you are not my family.
I'm closing the aortotomy.
What's next ?
Place the needle in the ascending aorta
to remove air and then release
the aortic valve clamp.
You remind me of myself
when I was an intern.
I do ?
Focused, intense...
cold...
and I don't mean that as a bad thing.
Cold is good.
The dating, the friends, the family...
If you ask me, it's all overrated.
all right, tubes are out.
Oh, the ascending aorta
is looking dilated.
There's too much bleeding
around the aortic suture line.
B.P. Is 68 over 42.
God...
he's bradying down.
Get me another T.E.E.
And an echocardiogram, stat.
Let's move it, people.
This doesn't look good.
We gotta get control of this bleeding.
All right, let's get him back on bypass.
I could put the aortic cannula
into his right atrium.
- By yourself ?
- Yes.
All right, do it.
Replace it with a 2-stage
venous cannula.
Why is she doing that ?
- Wh-why is Hahn letting her do that ?
- No, it's okay.
She's doing a running whip stitch.
She's done it before.
There you go.
Ah that's beautiful work, Dr. Yang.
Dr. Hahn's work was impeccable, O'Malley.
I wouldn't have done
anything different myself.
It's just, uh...
You can never tell how the body
is going to respond.
Every surgery...
Every body is different.
You just...
never know.
But it's okay now.
They're in the home stretch.
Thank you, Dr. Burke.
It undermines everything for my interns
to see Yang go without punishment,
For me to see Burke
go without punishment.
Take a step back.
Try and get some perspective.
So there will be no consequences,
for either of them.
What would you have me do,
Fire the both of them,
End their careers ?
They made a terrible judgment call.
- Which is what happened with Denny Duquette.
- And they didn't kill anybody.
- And I did.
- You didn't kill Duquette, and I won't
have you saying you did.
I was responsiblefor Izzie Stevens.
I was responsible.
And I'm responsible for Cristina Yang.
I...
am the common thread here.
lost them. Cristina, Izzie...
Are not the same.
Miranda...
You raise them... You raise them like...
Like children...
And some of them make mistakes
and some of them disappoint you.
Some of them...
Do you know what kind of strength
it must have taken Yang to come to me,
to report on an attending,
on her boyfriend ?
Do you see how much she's grown?
You raise them...
like children...
and some of them turn out
exactly like you, Dr. Bailey.
Finally alone.
Yeah.
Pete ?
It's been a long day.
Okay.
Well, you get a good night's sleep,
and, uh, I'll, um, come back in the morning.
At the end of the day,
when it comes down to it,
all we really want
is to be close to somebody...
couldn't stay away ?
So this thing where we all
keep our distance
and pretend not to care
about each other...
It's usually a lot of bull.
Did you want to come in ?
No. Uh, I just, uh...
She's okay ?
She's beautiful.
We could be your family
if you want us.
You have a mother, I know.
I'm not saying... I'm just saying that
we could be your family, too.
So we pick and choose
who we want to remain close to.
I can't take this anymore.
What ?
Let her off the hook. Let Cristina off
the freakin'hook.
- Meredith...
- Izzie, you cut the lvad wire.
She stuck by you and did Denny's echo.
You cheated on Izzie with syph nurse,
and she helped you study for your boards.
And, George, when everybody
was calling you 007
She was calling me 007.
Just let her off the hook.
It's okay.
Sorry.
Why can't you mind your own business ?
You know, what is your problem ?
You're my sister. You're my family.
You're all I've got.
And once we've chosen those people...
I'm so tired.
I know. Me, too.
We tend to stick close by...
Uh, I was... I just... I wanted to check
on your dad and see how he was doing.
Good. He's resting, but he's good.
Okay.
No matter how much we hurt them.
- Hey.
- Hi there.
I'm gonna go back upstairs
with dr. Burke.
He wants me to take
a look at his shoulder.
I'm gonna be a while.
Don't wait up, okay ?
Okay.
The people that are still with you
at the end of the day...
those are the ones worth keeping.
And sure, sometimes close
can be too close...
I couldn't stay with that man.
I don't care that he...
that he's Meredith's father,
I. I just couldn't take it,
and then Richard...
and he...
No...
Meredith.
Mommy ?
But sometimes that invasion
of personal space...
It can be exactly what you need.
Transcript : Raceman - Synchro : ChipounetteF
Traduction : Chryssie, Tbdb - Relecture : Cookie
www.forom.com