Surgeons are all messed
up. We're butchers.
Messed up, knife-happy butchers.
♪ There's a piece of
me you can't have ♪
♪ And I know it's
driving you mad ♪
Sir? Would you like a cot
set up for you in her room?
We cut people up. We move on.
Patients die on our
watch. We move on.
No. I'm a doctor here.
We cause trauma.
We suffer trauma.
♪ Leave it to be taken
upon the breeze ♪
Oh, wait.
And here it comes.
♪ Pieces falling from me ♪
♪ You can have them for free ♪
♪ Never felt so complete ♪
We don't have time to worry about
how blood and death makes us feel.
This is how you unwind?
By watching two hours straight
of advanced carotid
endarterectomy?
Cristina?
♪ Last piece of the jigsaw ♪
♪ While the others are
scattered across the floor ♪
♪ So you try to
get them all up ♪
♪ Leave it to be taken
upon the breeze ♪
♪ Wind is always blowing ♪
♪ Though you try your
best you never find ♪
♪ There are pieces
that are left behind ♪
Everything OK?
Cristina? Owen!
What...? What?
It's three in the morning,
Cristina. This better be...
Callie?
What? He what?
It's me. Cristina!
What's going on?
Owen's out there upset,
- Callie was screaming...
- No changes in visual acuity.
No petechiae. I'm fine.
Oh, my God! Your
neck! I will kill him!
No, no, no. He had a nightmare.
Cristina, please.
Is she all right? I just need
to know that she's all right.
No, no, no. Cristina, no.
I am so sorry.
I don't know what happened.
- I'm sorry.
- Look at me.
I'm fine. See? It's
OK. You were asleep.
It's OK. OK? It's OK. It's OK.
- I'm sorry.
- It's OK. I know.
It's OK. You were asleep.
It's OK. OK? It's OK.
It's OK. It's OK.
There's coffee.
No. Not like this.
Today's your first day
back at the hospital.
Today's about Izzie.
You have to operate on
her brain. You have a gift.
And you can do this.
I'm gonna shower before I go in.
You're wearing a
turtleneck under your scrubs.
It's ugly.
Not as ugly as the fact
that you hugged him.
- You hugged him...
- I get it. I hear you. Move on.
Turtlenecks aren't OK. You're
not OK. Your boyfriend is not OK.
- Is your boyfriend OK?
- What?
To be cutting into brains
today. Is he OK to be back?
Yes. Of course. Derek is fine.
I was there for his carnage
in the OR, remember?
This isn't just any
patient. This is Izzie.
George, hey. I'm
surprised you're not...
Isn't there a presentation
happening with Izzie?
I didn't know she was sick.
Bailey told me after Cristina told her.
Izzie trusted Cristina. I
was the very last to know.
- I'm sure Izzie
wasn't trying...
- I don't want to talk about it.
I want to work. Do you have
any room on your service?
- Yeah. Three
hip replacements...
- Thank you.
You three. I understand why
you're here. You want to help.
I will be the
resident on her case.
I will be prepping
her for surgery.
If you're going into that hospital
room, you will do so as her friends.
Izzie needs her
people around her
to tell her everything
will be fine.
She needs you to hold her hand. She
needs you, not more doctors. Understood?
Great. Let's get started.
As you know, you have
stage-four metastatic melanoma.
We have surgeries and procedures
lined up for you over
the next few weeks.
We've seen mets on your
liver, so one of those surgeries,
Dr. Bailey and I will resect them.
We also lined up Dr. Parker from OB
to harvest as many
healthy eggs as she can
before you undergo
any radiation.
- Right. Babies.
- Leaving the option open,
- if you want it.
- But our priority
is to address
mets in your brain.
I'm surprised
we didn't catch it.
It causes headaches,
seizures, hallucinations.
Hopefully the lesion has clear
margins and I can remove it.
Are you people done?
Over the next four weeks,
you're slated for
three major surgeries,
seven outpatient procedures,
just for mets we've found.
In all likelihood,
we will find more.
We may have to
cut into you more.
You may as well get
used to the idea now.
I'll be administering your radiation,
chemotherapy and immunotherapy.
The treatment will be aggressive,
it will be harsh. Prepare yourself.
I'll be overseeing
procedures, including today's,
which means every surgeon
in this room now answers to me.
Welcome to the
cancer wing, folks.
See you in the OR.
Thanks.
Seriously, don't just
stand there staring at me.
It's making me nervous.
- Get out of here. Go save lives.
- Yeah, we have rounds.
- Yeah.
- OK. See you later.
Karev, I just reviewed
Izzie's most recent MRI.
Doesn't look like the tumor
has grown since her last scans.
Do you have concerns you'd like to
discuss with me before we brief Izzie?
Just try keeping her frontal
lobe inside her skull this time.
Good morning, Izzie.
- You coming?
- No. I'm on
this old lady, so...
- This'll only take a minute.
- I gotta go, really.
Hi, Dr. Sloan. These are
Aunt Joyce's nephews,
my brothers Tobin and Luke.
They flew in early this morning.
Dr. Sloan did the surgery.
I'm sorry. Your
aunt is very sick.
There's not much more we can do.
Probably time to
say your goodbyes.
Do you mean say our goodbyes now
or sometime in
the next 24 hours?
I mean, what kind of time
frame are we talking about?
- Twenty-four hours
seems unlikely.
- You sure?
Because I have a flight
to catch in the morning,
and if I wait past
noon, I can't change it.
I need to be on a plane
tonight. Board meeting tomorrow.
So do you think she'll
die before tomorrow?
You really think Shepherd's the
guy for Steven's surgery today?
- Someone else in mind?
- Shepherd wouldn't
be my choice,
given his recent history, but it's
not my brain he'll be manhandling.
- No.
- Damn. She's HLA type B3.
Have to hit her with the DTIC
and high dose IL-2 instead.
- IL-2? That's pretty toxic.
- It's about as bad as it gets.
- You're gonna
tell Izzie this now?
- I am her oncologist.
Studies show giving patients
bad news before surgery
can drastically increase
their chances of complications.
Today or tomorrow,
the news is the same.
Right now, I have time.
You coming?
I believe Izzie is
down in radiology now.
Fine. We can wait an hour.
- Chief, you paged me?
- Karev. Yes, I did.
Um...
As you know, we're
gonna be harvesting eggs.
From Stevens.
Who, I believe, is someone
you're having relations with.
- Chief.
- Frozen eggs have a better
survival rate when
they're... fertilized.
- Fertilized.
- I know this
is a lot to digest.
So take some
time, think about it.
If you decide this is
something you might consider...
- Give me the cup.
- Karev. Speak to Stevens.
Just give me the cup!
- Is she doing OK?
- Yeah. Well, she says she is.
- Do you believe her?
- No. Not really.
Oh. Heads up.
- What do you hear?
- Motorcycle lost control. No helmet,
massive head trauma,
lost vital signs en route.
- Good to have
you back, Shepherd.
- Thanks.
Get back inside. He's DOA.
Hunt? Did you hear me?
Owen.
Swender has no vision.
He wrapped his hands
around your throat,
you're pretending
nothing happened.
Focus on Izzie.
Hunt literally tried to kill you.
He's barely back from Iraq.
It's obvious he has issues. That
doesn't mean you have to stand by...
If he had a heart attack
or a stroke or lost a leg,
would you walk away?
How is it acceptable I walk
away from this? He's wounded.
He has war wounds, Meredith.
It's not cut and dried. And
it's not as bad as you think it is.
Clear.
- This might be it.
- From your lips to God's ears.
Charge to 360. Clear.
- Oh, for the love of God.
- Hey.
You know how many people
are in this hospital waiting,
hoping loved ones might
live? You're a bunch of vultures.
- But we're not.
- Aunt Joyce was
given a month to live
three years ago.
And we were crushed.
And we held her hand
at her bedside for weeks,
and we said our tearful
goodbyes. And then...
she stabilized.
She's been in and out of
the hospital once a month.
Each time we jump on a plane, sit by
her bed, say our goodbyes all over again.
And each time, she
winds up getting better.
We want to be here when
she goes. We really do.
But... it's a lot of flying
around the country.
She's ready. We're
all ready. It's time.
And I've got a board
meeting tomorrow.
Big one.
They're doing tests that show altered
brain anatomy in patients with PTSD.
Close to understanding the
physical side of psychological trauma.
- Amazing what you can
see with an MRI.
- What did Meredith tell you?
Post-traumatic stress
is a real injury, Owen.
It can be healed. There are
resources, vet centers, therapy.
You shouldn't try and
handle this on your own.
I came back in one
piece, both arms, both legs.
Lots of guys came
back with real injuries.
The worst I have is nightmares
or freezing for a moment...
Is that what
happened last night?
You had a freezing moment?
If you want, I can help.
Oh, yeah? I'm not the
one who needs help.
I'm not the one who cut out
half a brain and ran off to hide.
I'm not the one half the
hospital is talking about.
You should spend less time worrying
about me and take a look in the mirror.
Karev? Just checking in.
To see how you're com...
- See how you're doing.
- I'd be doing better
if you weren't on the other
side of the door listening.
Uh... Right, right. Sorry.
I said go away.
You left the door
unlocked. That's bold.
- The chief send you in here?
- No. I offered to come in
- in case you need to talk.
- You think talking will help?
A Dixie cup full of my swimmers
will make everything
OK? It's crap.
This is crap!
You can't go messing with
people's heads like that.
Even if she freezes the embryos,
you think we'll get a
chance to use them?
You think she'll still be here?
You think she'll survive
all this? You think...
I think... She told me...
She told me she was
seeing a ghost, OK?
And I'm so used to all the crazy
chicks in my life that I didn't even...
I'm a doctor. A doctor!
And I didn't even think to...
And now she's... This is...
This is wrong. This isn't
how it's supposed to happen.
- I know.
- It's crap!
- I hate this.
I know.
This isn't...
♪ I'm not ready ♪
This isn't how we were... This
isn't how I wanted to do this.
This isn't how Izzie and I
were supposed to make a baby.
♪ For the weight of us ♪
- ♪ For the weight of us ♪
- I haven't seen you all day.
What if I hadn't woken up?
I can't even remember what
happened. I have no memory, no way to...
I would never hurt you, ever.
But I did. My hands just...
How could my own
two hands be capable...?
- I can't do this, Cristina.
- But you did wake up.
- Stop blaming yourself.
- We have to stop
seeing each other.
Why?
- Cristina, I almost...
- Almost what?
I told you, I know my limits.
Let me decide what I can handle.
♪ For the weight of us ♪
♪ Oooh... ♪
Good. Stand right
there. Let me see.
I never know how
long to make these.
I like the color.
Who's it for, Karev?
Haven't seen much of him today.
He's working.
They're all working.
I told them to go work.
Their patients shouldn't suffer
because I have things
growing on my organs.
I have got a colectomy
this afternoon.
If you were the
resident assisting me,
and I were to say to you, "Divide
the cecum," what would you use?
I'm not assisting you.
You're not gonna ask
me to divide the cecum.
But you're not going to get rusty.
In a year, you need to do this stuff.
You need to teach residents.
- Think I'm gonna
be here in a year?
- Yes, I do.
So I have exposed
the right lower quadrant,
and you are dividing
the cecum with...
Forceps.
Lift free from the arachnoid.
Tacking sutures.
Patties.
Suction.
Starting over.
Here's your cup, all filled up.
- I'm eating here, Karev.
- It's fine, I washed my hands.
Did you talk to
Izzie about this yet?
Considering you
two are basically
conceiving a child together,
think you should talk with her?
Look, you said she
needed my... contribution.
Here's my
contribution. Whatever.
- Hi. How's Izzie?
- I don't know.
- How's Izzie?
- Why?
- Have you been to see her?
- No, I've been working all day.
- What?
- Have you been to see Izzie?
No. Haven't you?
- You finished
that thing in one day?
- Had some free time.
- Had a lot of free time.
- Nobody came up to visit?
It's OK. If I were them, I wouldn't
want to step foot in this room either.
- You don't have
to keep checking on me.
- I do have to.
I have to start you on
this before your surgery.
Right. Surgery.
And I wanted to tell you how
my surgery went this afternoon.
- Colon guy?
- The colectomy went great,
but I was in there,
and I see a mass.
You're kidding.
Was it a big mass?
Big enough. The size of a fist.
This is going to
burn a little at first,
but just for a few seconds.
So we had to mobilize the SMA
before we could resect the
thing and reconnect the bowel.
I wished Izzie
Stevens would die.
I wished her dead. Every
day, for I don't know how long.
I woke up every morning
wishing Izzie Stevens would die.
And now...
What kind of person
wishes someone would die?
What kind of doctor wishes...?
Knowing how things happen, what...?
What kind of...? What
kind of doctor wishes...?
Are you in here, right
now, praying for Izzie to die?
No. I'm praying for her to live.
- Clear!
- You know what?
- Wait outside!
- Will you let us know...?
Yeah. I'll let you know.
- Bastards.
- Push one of epi.
Charge to 360. Clear!
Come on, Joyce, you old bag,
don't give 'em the satisfaction.
- Charge again.
- Charged.
Clear!
Hey. I'm Dr. Karev.
You're a fighter, you know
that? You worked hard today.
She needs some rest.
Make sure the family doesn't come
in. Give her a break from all the love.
No. They're impatient.
It's been a long time.
But they always come.
They're my people.
People keep you going.
People are better
than no people.
Uh... It's not a good
time, he's still scrubbing in.
I know, it's just...
he should wear this.
It's his ferryboat scrub
cap. He loves ferryboats.
- Meredith.
- What are you doing?
You're gonna have to re-scrub.
- I'm not ready.
- Yes, you are.
I need to know that
at least I have you.
No matter what happens in
there, I need you to say yes.
- I need to know...
- I can't say yes.
Not if agreeing to
be with you forever
will make it OK if Izzie dies.
I can't say yes. I love
you, and you can do this.
You can do this. I know you can.
Iz!
♪ Where the doors are moaning ♪
♪ All day long ♪
♪ Where the stairs are leaning ♪
♪ Dusk 'till dawn ♪
♪ Where the windows ♪
See you soon, Dr. Stevens.
- Hope so.
- Know so.
- Dr. Bailey,
if something goes wrong...
- It won't.
The scarf.
I made it for you.
♪ This is a place
where I don't feel alone ♪
Beautiful night to save lives.
Let's get started.
♪ This is a place ♪
♪ That I call my home ♪
I get why I haven't been camped out
at Izzie's bedside holding her hand...
- I'm not talking about this.
- Why not?
Maybe it's the fact
that I asked Izzie
a hundred times what was
wrong, and she just ignored me.
Then there's the fact that
when she actually needed help,
she trusted
Cristina, of all people!
And there's the fact that
she's your best friend,
and she might die on you.
There's also that.
Come on. We are
going to go wait for Izzie.
George, you were my
husband and you slept with her.
You are the reason I wished
her dead. You owe me this.
You can lie to
yourself all you want,
but I know you.
I loved you once.
And I know you care
if she lives or dies.
Surgery started.
- Hey, have they
started surgery yet?
- Yeah.
Dr. Grey? We were wondering,
did Dr. Stevens'
surgery start or...?
Keep it moving. No
loitering. That's the rule.
If they wanna
stay, let 'em stay.
People are better
than no people.
Clamp.
I am ready to... No.
Yes. OK. I'm ready to buzz
the superficial temporal artery.
- Tenting sutures.
- There's no rush. Take your time.
- Everyone is on your side.
- You sure that's gonna hold,
- with all the
friable scar tissue?
- Dr. Swender?
Actually, I saw Dr. Shepherd
do three different
craniotomies last month,
each with easily double
the amount of friable tissue.
They held just fine.
Next tenting suture, please.
Clear!
Push another epi. Charge again.
Come on, Mrs. Wallington. Clear!
I'm so sorry. She's
not responding.
We've done everything,
so she's gone.
Thank you. You
did a wonderful job.
- Are you kidding me?!
- Oh, God, this is
never gonna end!
No... No, she's gone.
She's really gone.
It's really gone.
It's her pacemaker.
It's still firing. Makes it
seem like there's a heartbeat.
She's gone. Just
with a heartbeat.
- Are you sure she's dead,
young lady?
- I'm an intern.
I'm not authorized to call time
of death in a situation like this.
So I'm gonna get my superior.
Excuse me. I'll be
right back. Excuse me.
- I'm worried about you.
- - Meredith...
- Choking.
- Stop.
- It's unacceptable.
- Back off.
- Hands around the neck.
- Ring thrown in your face.
This'll shut the pacemaker down.
Time of death, 2240.
There you go. She's officially
dead. You can catch your plane.
Get to your board
meeting. You can leave.
♪ What's in your heart? ♪
♪ What's in your head? ♪
♪ It's one of the
other these days ♪
♪ The quick or the dead ♪
♪ Sometimes we gotta fight ♪
Actually, could we
stay a little while longer?
♪ So don't you complain ♪
♪ 'Cause I never promised
this would be easy, babe ♪
♪ You and me ♪
♪ Are gonna rise up ♪
♪ And they will
be surprised, yep ♪
What are you all doing out here?
Waiting for Izzie,
sir. We're waiting.
♪ And everything's weird ♪
You're scared.
♪ But soon they'll be gone ♪
I'm scared too.
♪ 'Cause our whispered words ♪
♪ Are louder then bombs ♪
♪ so don't you lose faith ♪
Damn it. Some of
the Sylvian vessels
are wrapped around
the tumor capsule.
- Penfield four, please.
- Really?
Instead of the arachnoid knife?
Yes, instead of
the arachnoid knife.
Because the Penfield four will let
me slide the arteries around the met.
I need to dissect it free
so I can de-bulk the tumor,
avoiding unnecessary
trauma to my patient.
- Yes, Penfield four, please.
- ♪ You and me
are gonna rise up ♪
- Vitals stable the entire time?
- Spikes or intracranial
pressure?
- Was there residual tumor?
- Shepherd resected
all of the tumor.
She'll be in the PACU
for an hour. She's fine.
♪ 'Cause we're gonna rise up ♪
Your friend is just fine.
No thanks to any of you.
Tomorrow, do better.
- The surgery went well today.
- Mmm.
Shouldn't you and Meredith
be out celebrating or something?
She turned me down twice.
She said she understands, she forgives
me for what happened in the woods.
So you showed
her your dark side.
Meredith never struck me as a
woman who's afraid of the dark.
I don't know.
Do you know it was
Meredith's idea to ask Izzie
if she wanted to
harvest her eggs?
So Izzie could have a chance
at the future she wanted.
The future, Derek.
She was confident
you'd succeed today.
Meredith believes in you.
♪ Oh, the ones I
often dreamt of ♪
- I'm here, Iz.
- ♪ With the notes in my ears ♪
I'm right here.
♪ And the ones I
often mimicked ♪
♪ With the notes on my fingers ♪
- Izzie's surgery went well.
- Good. That's good.
I wish things were...
That they could be...
- That we could be...
- Me too.
♪ Oh, the ones I
often dreamt of ♪
♪ With the notes in my ears ♪
Could I hold you?
♪ And the ones I
often mimicked ♪
♪ With the notes on my fingers ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh... ♪
♪ And my bed is on the floor ♪
♪ Yes, my bed is on the floor ♪
♪ Of one of the ones
I often dreamt of ♪
♪ With the notes in my ears ♪
♪ And that's why I
know that I can say ♪
♪ I'm lucky today ♪
♪ And that's how I know ♪
♪ That it's time to be brave ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Ooh... ♪
- Wait! No. You can't take that one.
- Why not?
I said don't take it.
I will take the
elevator I want to take.
Well, go on.
- ♪ I saw what I wanted to ♪
- Hey. Come on in.
♪ You did what you needed to ♪
This is a CT for Katie Bryce.
16-year-old female,
subarachnoid aneurysm.
From a fall during
gymnastics. I remember.
It was the first surgery we ever
scrubbed in together on. Our first save.
Right here is a cerebral
cyst. Tough save, but we did it.
I kissed you in the
stairwell after this surgery.
This is where Dr. Bailey
kicked you out of the surgery
because she caught us
in your driveway in my car.
And right here, this was
a seven-hour craniotomy.
You held a clamp the entire
time and never flinched.
That's when I knew you were
gonna be an incredible surgeon.
Beth Monroe,
who made our clinical
trial a success by surviving.
You talked me into
putting her under.
That's when I knew I needed you.
And this is today. Post-op
head CT of Izzie Stevens.
See that?
Right there. Tumor-free.
Because of you. You
got me into the OR.
If there is a crisis,
you don't freeze.
You move forward.
You get the rest of
us to move forward
because you've seen worse,
you've survived worse. And
you know we'll survive too.
You say you're
all dark and twisty.
That's not a flaw.
It's a strength.
It makes you who you are.
I am not gonna get
down on one knee.
I am not gonna ask a question.
I love you, Meredith Grey.
And I want to spend the
rest of my life... with you.
♪ In love ♪
And I want to spend the
rest of my life with you.
♪ In love ♪
I don't think...
I can't handle this after all.
What...? What do you mean?
- Are you saying...?
- I'm sorry.
I am so, so sorry.
But I'm lying here
in your arms...
and I'm afraid to fall asleep.
Doesn't matter how tough we are.
I want to apologize for earlier.
What I said was...
It was out of line.
- It's already forgotten.
- Thank you for doing this.
♪ In love In love ♪
Trauma always leaves a scar.
♪ In love ♪
- ♪ In love ♪
- I'm engaged.
♪ In love ♪
- I broke up with Owen.
- ♪ In love ♪
♪ In love ♪
It follows us home.
♪ In love In love ♪
It changes our lives.
Hey.
I snooched into a
cup for you today.
Thank you?
Trauma messes everybody
up, but maybe that's the point.
All the pain and the
fear and the crap...
Maybe going through all of that
is what keeps us moving forward.
It's what pushes us.
Maybe we have to
get a little messed up
before we can step up.