♪ I see the world
Through brand new eyes ♪
- Chicken!
- Good chicken.
It's chicken.
I know it's chicken.
I want to know
what it tastes like.
Tastes like chicken.
- I'm having surgery today.
- Maybe. If the mets
have shrunk.
I am maybe having surgery and as
such I cannot taste the chicken for myself.
So I really need you guys
to tell me what it tastes like.
I need to announce it on Meredith
and Derek's wedding website.
- There's a website?
- Can you please be
more articulate
than just "chicken?"
Yay! Oh!
That's the one!
Very dapper, Dr. Shepherd.
You're serious about this?
It's not some cruel joke?
And you look fantastic.
He looks fantastic, right?
- Yeah.
- Whatever.
Remember when we were
little and we'd accidentally
bite a kid on the playground?
- Good luck.
- Good chicken.
So?
Pork!
Our teachers would
go, "Say you're sorry."
Oh! Fine, I'll
taste the chicken.
We would say it, but
we wouldn't mean it.
Because the stupid kid
we bit... totally deserved it.
Sorry. I'm sorry.
Take care now.
Hey. So, I can't afford rent.
- Owen just told me
to "Take care now."
- Nice. Three words.
More than she's getting
from any of her family.
My mom, silent. My
aunts, silent. My sister Aria?
I know, I know how much power
my father wields. But seriously?
What am I, invisible? Dead
to them? To my mother?
You just have to give them time.
Why can't you just tell them you
broke up? It's no one's business, right?
And I will leave
you to ponder that.
But as we get older, making
amends isn't so simple.
- You really think I should lie?
- I think you should pay rent.
But, you know,
whatever. Take care now.
After the playground days
are over, you can't just say it.
- You have to mean it.
- I got you a present.
You can't give me money. Even
if you are a fancy plastic surgeon.
I'm not your charity case. Not your
mistress. I am your friend. Your equal.
It's not money.
Really? I was just doing the
"poor but proud" thing for show.
Better than money. Wait.
Of course, when you become a
doctor, "sorry" is not a happy word.
It either means, "You're
dying and I can't help"...
She fell out of a tree
and broke all her limbs.
Ooh! That is better.
Or it means, "This
is really gonna hurt."
How many days?
- Twenty-nine.
- Fresh from rehab?
I could tell you some
good meetings in the area.
Thanks, they gave
me a whole list.
One more thing
we have in common.
Have you... talked to Meredith?
To Lexie?
Ow!
OK, Willow, I'm afraid your
cheekbone looks broken, too.
I'll need to wait a few weeks until
the swelling goes down to repair that.
In a few weeks, I'm
gonna be up a tree in Utah.
Those corporate bastards,
the same ones who just
bulldozed me out of Kaili?
They wanna clear-cut acres to
build another ski condo complex.
Sons of bitches.
There is so much about that
sentence I do not understand.
You were "bulldozed"
out of something?
Kaili. She was the tree that I
was living in for the past six weeks.
She was a beautiful
200-year-old oak
in a grove full of beautiful
200-year-old oaks.
You named a tree "Kaili?"
Kaili is Hawaiian for
"divine beauty and wisdom."
And she was all of those things.
She was all of those
things and now she's gone.
They're all gone. And
for what? Yuppie housing?
Those corporate bastards.
I'm sorry, but you're not gonna be
climbing any trees for a long while.
How does one
exactly live in a tree?
I mean, how exactly does
one, say, eliminate waste?
He's asking where your poo goes, which
may not be the most sensitive question
while she's mourning
the death of her...
tree friend.
Excuse me, doctor?
Oh! Excuse me, young
and yummy doctor.
- Can I help you?
- I don't know, can you?
Are you looking for
someone, ma'am?
Oh, gosh, I'm gonna pretend
you didn't just call me ma'am,
because I have this image of you
and me in my head playing doctor
and that just kinda ruined it.
OK. I'm gonna go back to work
now. But good luck with... whatever.
Well, I am looking for a doctor.
Gosh, I guess she's a
patient now. Isobel Stevens?
I'm, uh...
I'm an old friend.
- After you.
- Oh, a doctor
and a gentleman.
Now, that's a double yummy.
Oh, my God, who's getting married?
- Oh, my God. Mom. What are you doing here?
- Mom?
Shh! Cricket, you don't want
that hot doctor to think I'm old.
Hey. You got paged, too?
Yeah. "Report to the
chief's office, stat."
What do you think? Why?
Why would he page us stat?
I don't know. We kill anyone
lately and don't remember?
Your father's here.
He's 29 days sober,
just out of rehab.
He's taking it seriously.
He's working his steps.
The ninth step is to make
amends wherever possible.
It's the key to an
alcoholic's recovery.
To take responsibility for
the wreckage of his past.
I paged you here to ask
you to please hear him out.
As a favor to me, to
please hear him out.
- Uh, I'm covering
the pit, chief...
- I'll cover it.
- But there's a trauma...
- I've got it, Meredith.
Please.
What are you doing?
The chief asked me
to cover Mer in the pit.
- I'm on Hunt's service
all month.
- O'Malley! Hey there, now.
O'Malley, update me.
Two ambulances. Three patients,
one critical. Multiple gunshot wounds.
Mike Carlson, 35, multiple GSWs.
Last BP, 88 systolic
after two boluses of LR.
Where was he shot?
Chest, abdomen,
back, legs, shoulder...
- Someone meant business.
- Not so sure about that.
She didn't mean it, it was
an accident. She really didn't.
She's sorry. Maddy,
tell them you're sorry.
She's the shooter?
Somebody page the chief.
- Breath sounds are better.
- Three to
the thoracoabdominal area.
What's that bring the count to?
Three plus seven to the
legs... Two on the side.
Could be through. Put a swab
through, see where it goes.
- Do we roll him now?
- Finish his catheter.
- Does it enter and exit?
- Hold on.
Yeah, that makes 11.
- What can we infer from these?
- Blood in the urine. Guessing kidney.
O'Malley, let's roll
him. On your count.
One, two, three.
- Yeah, more wounds here.
- Yang, page Shepherd.
Let's get an accurate count
while we have him positioned.
Maddy, how's this feel?
Does it hurt when I do this?
Good.
What about this cut?
Can you tell me how you
got this big cut on your face?
She's scared.
Scared she did a bad thing
and you're gonna take her away.
The police will want to talk to both
of you about how Maddy got the gun.
We called social services
and they'll be here soon.
They'll give you the support
you need to come back from this.
And nobody's gonna take you
away from your mom, OK, Maddy?
It hit her in the face.
The gun, the kickback.
Huh...
- 'Cause this doesn't
look like...
- That's how she got the cut.
Her daddy shoots
targets in the backyard.
He put the gun down for a
minute. It was really stupid.
She never meant to hurt him.
OK. You'll tell the
police that and it'll be OK.
Everything'll be OK.
And I'm so deeply sorry...
for every time that I ever
hurt you or disappointed you,
or let you down.
I don't deserve your
forgiveness, but I hope...
I so hope that you'll give
me the opportunity to earn it.
Thank you. Congratulations on...
You seem well.
Good luck.
And you remember
Jade, from 114? Well...
She had a spot of cancer
last year. It was breast cancer.
That was such a shame, I
thought. She had such a great rack.
Remember what a
great rack she had?
You used to do all those exercises
to try to get yours to grow like hers.
Anyway.
My point is, Jade,
she had 'em cut off.
Both, just to be
on the safe side.
They look even
better now. For real.
Life gave her lemons
and she made cantaloupes!
So, maybe, honey, there's an
upside in this for you, too. Right?
Um... Mom. Just,
uh, just listen, OK?
I... I don't have breast cancer.
OK. I have skin cancer, or
what started out as skin cancer...
Hang on. Skin cancer?
Oh, God, Isobel Stevens, oh,
you scared the hell out of me.
And you made me come all the way up
here to Seattle for some ugly old mole?
- Sweetheart.
- No, I didn't.
I didn't make you
come up here. I, uh...
I didn't even call you. I'm really...
I'm curious. Who did? Who called?
Who called her?
Seriously. Who called her?
You OK? Are you crying?
- My dad's here.
- OK...
He's here and he's sober, and
I'd really like for you to meet him.
Oh...
Oh.
Umm... Oh.
How about dinner
tonight? Camparo's at 8?
Lexie, uh...
dads historically
do not love me.
And by that, I mean that
when I was a teenager...
dads did not love me,
and then that's the last time
I had to meet anyone's dad.
I'm crazy about you.
I know that my dad will be, too.
You have nothing to worry about.
That's what you said when
you told me to tell Derek.
Lexie, I'm closer to your
dad's age than yours.
So I'm thinking he may
not love me so much.
You know, what
we have is fantastic.
Why don't we
just keep it for us?
Excuse me, I'm looking for
my sister, Karen Zelmann?
We have a Willow
Zelmann in there.
- Her name is Karen.
- My name is Willow!
I told you this would happen. I told
you to come out of the damn tree.
How'd it go?
Dr. Grey, Maddy could use a little
cleaning and repair. I'm being paged.
- Absolutely.
- Meredith.
- You OK?
- I'm great.
Thanks.
Hey, Maddy, I'm Dr. Grey.
Mind if I take a look at
that cut on your face?
She's so sorry. She's so sorry.
Is my daddy gonna die?
I don't know. I hope not.
Five bullets still inside.
How many gunshots total?
Twenty-five wounds total,
five are lodged inside,
two graze wounds,
nine through and
through, so about 17.
Seventeen? Thought this
was an accidental shooting.
- How come?
- How come what?
How come he don't die?
I shot him lots of times.
She's just a
little girl, a baby.
She wasn't really trying
to kill him, she was...
She doesn't even
understand what that means.
She was just trying to stop him,
she was only trying to stop him.
So that cut on her face
didn't come from the gun?
He was hitting her.
He loves us.
Daddy loves us, Maddy.
Sometimes he just gets mad.
And he's been working on it.
He's been working on it so hard.
But she was just
trying to stop him.
She wasn't trying to kill him.
Please understand.
She's just a little girl.
Uh-huh. Oh. Really?
Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Really?
Oh... Yeah, that's great,
that's great. Oh, thank you.
Yeah, thank you, hon.
Thanks a million. Oh!
Oh, that's great news, Cricket!
You're gonna be just fine!
Oh, yeah?
Let me guess. Your
psychic told you that?
It's not just any old psychic. He's
the best that I've ever heard of.
Anyway, he said that skin cancer
is highly curable if caught early.
Oh, that's so great. A
psychic with Internet access.
Let me guess how much that call
cost you, mother. $19.99 a minute?
When you have a
sick child, Cricket,
money's not really the
first thing on your mind.
You seem like a very
capable doctor, Dr. Bailey.
Can I trust that you caught
my daughter's skin cancer early?
- Um, well, Mrs. Stevens...
- Oh, no. Call me Robbie, hon.
No, Mom, don't call her
"hon." Don't call Bailey "hon."
You know, if you have
questions, you can just ask me.
She's very busy and this thing
I have... It's complicated, so...
I know it's complicated,
Isobel. I'm not a complete idiot.
Now, I saw this
thing on Tyra's show...
There was this woman who
had a mole on her private parts.
The dermatologist did not check
'cause she thought the gynie
would've done it. The gynie didn't do it...
Maybe she didn't even go to
the gynie... Anyway, it was bad.
She was bald and everything.
She did not have a mole
on her private parts, did she?
No, ma'am. No, she did not.
Good.
We need to take him in now.
GSWs to the abdomen, hematuria,
vital signs are unstable. Ma'am,
he has major internal injuries.
We're rushing
him to surgery now.
Wait! Maddy needs to tell her
daddy she's sorry before he goes.
Baby, you need to tell
your daddy you're sorry.
Maddy, people die in surgery.
You don't want your daddy to die
without telling him how sorry you are.
Come on, let's go
tell him we love him.
- You know? No. No.
- What?
Maddy, stay right here, OK?
- Dr. Grey...
- No.
She will not go
apologize to him.
You should be
apologizing to her.
I understand you're a victim,
but there's no room for you to be
when your six-year-old is on the line.
She's stronger than you. Your
six-year-old is stronger than you.
At least she did something.
She stood up for the two of you,
which is more
than you did for her.
No, she won't apologize to him.
Thank you so much.
All right, I'll call you back.
Listen, I have great news.
I have a contact at
Schuster and Werner.
More like Dirtbag and Felon.
They've agreed to pay your medical
bills and to not sue you for trespassing
if you sign a contract
saying you won't sue them
and you won't trespass on
their properties ever again.
Do you know how many acres of forest
they have single-handedly destroyed?
How many ecosystems
will never be restored?
The bees are dying, Julie.
The temperature is rising!
I'm sorry. Is it possible I could
have a moment alone with my sister?
- You'll sign this deal, Karen.
- My name is Willow!
Can't say I'm sorry
I never had siblings.
- They're yelling
'cause they care.
- That how it works?
Yeah, it is, in
some families. It is.
I expected them to yell, you
know? I didn't expect silence.
Call them and claim
temporary insanity.
You don't have to end it with
Roller-girl. Just say you did.
Yang said the same thing.
That's because it's
none of their business.
There's no reason you
should have to hurt this much.
I can see that
you're angry with me,
and maybe angry
with your mother...
Don't do that. I'm not your
friend, and I'm not your family.
You don't get to call me into
your office on personal business,
and you don't get to speak
to me this way right now.
It's an abuse of power. I'm
a resident. I work for you.
You have to speak to me like
I'm a resident. And for the record?
Someone had to stand up for that
girl. I make no apologies for that.
You want to just be a resident?
Fine. All right then.
That woman is a victim
of domestic violence.
This hospital is supposed to be a
safe place for her to come tell her story.
As her doctors, it is
our job to help her.
You did not do your job.
You further battered
a battered woman.
- What about...
- Dr. Grey!
You will stay away
from that child.
from that family.
You will not come
within 100 feet of them.
If you do, you will be
suspended from this hospital,
pending re-evaluation of your
emotional and mental fitness for residency.
The IVC and the aorta are nicked.
O'Malley, get in there with some clips.
Gonna need the
angled vascular clamp.
Nothing's stopping.
Still bleeding out.
Don't move, Yang! Need
some more suction in there.
- I know Webber
is your friend.
- Not about Richard.
It is. It is about him.
I have to deal with him on a
professional basis every day.
I've tried to draw a line with
him and he won't respect it.
He uses his
relationship with you...
- Richard doesn't...
- Stop defending him.
Be on my side. I need
you to be on my side.
- OK.
- He's not your best friend.
He's not your Cristina. Which
is why I feel OK to say to you
he is not invited to our
wedding. I swear, Derek,
if he's there, I won't be.
I'm the bride, so I have to be.
So I'm begging you.
He's not invited. OK?
- OK.
- Thank you.
Mm-hmm.
If you don't make this deal, who's
gonna pay your bills? Take care of you?
They tried to kill me,
just like they killed Kaili,
just like they kill all
those defenseless trees,
all of the creatures
that live in those trees.
You are not a defenseless
tree-living creature.
You are an adult woman who
made a decision to trespass.
It was unbelievably stupid, naive,
just unbelievably irresponsible.
- What about
unbelievably brave?
- Excuse me?
Trees may not
be my thing, but...
even if it was
stupid, it was brave.
She slept in a 200-year-old
tree and watched as a bulldozer
knocked her off. She was
standing for what she believed.
You have to admit, she's brave.
How can trees not be your thing?
Karen? Karen?
Damn it. Pulse is
weak. Start her on O2.
See if you can get
a femoral pulse.
She's bleeding out.
We need her stabilized.
- What's happening to my sister?
- Julie, you need to clear out.
- Get her out of here.
- Karen? Karen?
Get her ready for transport and
tell the OR we're on our way, now!
Damn it. Too many bleeders.
Hang another bag of O neg
and get me some fibrin sealant.
- Can I help?
- You are helping.
You've got more bleeders
than you have hands.
- Sorry.
- No, that's it.
You get in there and take over.
- Yang, run to my truck!
- What?
Run to my truck. It's
where I always park it.
Run fast. In the glove
box, there's a green bag.
- Pull harder
on that retractor.
- I am a surgeon...
I'm trying to save
a life, Yang. Run!
Oh... The Lovers card.
Do you know what this means?
Yes. No. Yes... Mom,
can you please shut up?
Meat. Definitely
some kind of meat.
You're killing me,
you know that?
It means the sex is hot.
I bet that little mole
didn't get in the way, right?
Honey, hey. Listen.
Isn't it time for my scan? Isn't
it time for my scan right now?
I'll go check.
- See if I can
get things moving.
- Thank you.
Tell me about Dr. Hottie. How
long have you been together?
Mom? It's not just a mole.
I have stage IV melanoma.
It's in my organs.
It's not just a mole.
You don't have skin
on your organs, hon.
Doesn't make a
whole lotta sense.
Don't just sigh at me, Isobel.
Just, you know... just explain.
OK, um...
You remember when Grammy
had that tumor on her thyroid?
Grammy died.
She died. She...
Really soon after
that, she died.
Why are you...
telling me...
You have a mole.
I don't understand...
OK. I'm sorry. I'm sorry,
that was a bad comparison.
What I have is nothing
like what Grammy had.
- No. No...
- OK. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Just breathe. It's OK.
I'm OK. Just breathe. OK?
It's OK. It's OK. I'm
OK. Just breathe.
I've got a good
feeling about this.
I think those mets
are shrunk way down,
and I think I'm gonna go
right in and take the rest out.
Really? You think that?
Did your psychic tell you so?
This scan has to be
good. It has to be good.
Listen, if it's not, it's not the end of
the world. There are other therapies...
She'll never leave.
If this scan isn't good? If I
can't give her good news...
She won't leave.
I love my mom. I don't
mean to sound... ungrateful...
I just...
It was me. I called her.
I really...
I thought it was
Alex. Or George.
It was me. Because...
I'd want to know
if my kid was sick.
And if I was sick, I
would want my mom.
I thought you were
being too proud,
or you were trying
to protect her.
Now I get that you were
trying to protect yourself.
She's not a bad person.
She was a great mom.
She's just... limited. She's...
limited.
This scan has to be good.
It has to be good.
Hang more blood.
Come on, Willow.
Come on. You lived in a tree. You
crapped in a bucket, for God's sake.
- You can do this.
- She crapped in a bucket?
- What're you doing here?
- Saw it on the board.
Never seen an intermedullary
rod put into a femur.
So... bucket?
Yeah. Bucket on a pulley.
She's up in the tree. She
lowers a crap bucket to her friend,
every day, who empties it, cleans it,
puts food in it and sends it back up.
- That's friendship.
- Yeah.
They teach us in med school
how not to care so much.
We drape the patients,
so we don't see faces.
We do a thousand
things to care a little less.
But you care like
crazy and I love that.
And I'll keep loving that,
even if you decide
to lie to your family.
Nice work, Yang. Open the bag.
See the bottle
with the blue label?
Open it, pour it in a sterile
basin and give it to O'Malley.
Shake it onto the wound. Right
over the bleeders. A lot of it.
What is this stuff?
Use it in the field all the time.
It's not FDA-approved, but...
it's saved a lot of lives. When you
don't have time to stitch a guy up,
pour some of this on, and it
holds things till you get to an OR.
Look, it's locking up the wound.
Replicates the clotting process.
Not a permanent solution,
but it buys us some time.
BP's going up. He's stabilizing.
Magical.
I think it's gonna be fine.
I think those mats are
gonna be teeny tiny.
It's, uh, "mets," Mom. Mets.
- Mets. Like baseball?
- Yeah. Like baseball.
Good news. Great news.
The cancer's practically gone.
Looks like your psychic
was right, Mrs. Stevens.
Looks like we
caught it early after all.
Oh, thank you, God.
Thank you! Oh, my baby.
Jesus, Mary and
Joseph. Thank you!
Thank you! Thank you!
Thank you, thank you. Mm!
But I knew it. Didn't I?
I knew it. I knew.
Because you're my Cricket.
Nothing can happen to you.
- I love you, Mom.
- Oh, I love you, too,
my baby girl.
I love you so, so much.
God, look at me,
I must be a mess.
I'm gonna go clean
up. And then, uh...
And then I'm gonna
call Jade and Ms. Norris.
I got them all so worried.
♪ Scarecrows know
their own defeat ♪
♪ Envy and the heart
that it consumes ♪
Just tell me.
The mets have shrunk some.
But there are new mets, too.
Several new mets.
In the small bowel.
- No surgery, then.
- Oh, I'm gonna operate.
I'm gonna take out
absolutely everything I can,
be as aggressive as I
can. We'll take it from there.
- OK.
You just have to give her
room. You two have history...
- I apologized.
- I know and it's loaded.
She keeps yelling at me that
I'm not her father. Well, I'm not.
I fell in love with her
mother. That's all I did.
Her mother never got
over you, and she...
That's not my
fault! I was young.
Lots of people have affairs.
They have affairs
and they don't...
What Ellis did after
I left, that's on Ellis.
And I'm trying to
run a hospital here.
- She's doing
the best she can.
- Her best isn't good enough.
If any other resident pulled
the crap she did today...?
She is still here because
of my history with you.
That's it. That's
the only reason.
Keep saying you're not her
father, but... Since we're talking...
You're the most professional
guy. The most level-headed.
Except when it comes to
Meredith. You gave me hell.
You weren't gonna give me Chief
because I was dating Meredith.
You told her about the ring,
sent her to bring me back.
That's not running a hospital.
You paged her to try on dresses.
You paged her
today for Thatcher.
You have history with her. You
keep saying you're not her father.
But the way you act,
you consider her family.
For what it's worth.
♪ I have yet to meet another ♪
♪ Who burns bright... ♪
- What happened?
- Hunt is incredible.
The guy shouldn't be alive. 17 bullets?
He has one lung, one kidney left...
- Dr. Grey!
- Meredith?
I'm sorry for the way
I spoke to you earlier.
- Dr. Grey!
- Don't.
I know I was out of line.
I know I can't possibly imagine
what you've been through.
But I also know that this can
not be your daughter's story.
That she shot her dad 17
times to protect her mom
and you went back to him.
You have to change her story
while you still have a chance.
For both of you.
But for her, for
your little girl...
You have to change her story.
♪ I wouldn't sink like a stone ♪
I'll pack my stuff.
She lost a lot of blood,
but she's stable now.
They weighed the cost.
I'm sorry?
They weighed the
cost of killing her
over letting her stay up there.
And then they got a bulldozer
and knocked her out of a tree.
They knocked my
baby sister out of a tree.
Jules?
I'm here.
Hey, I'm here.
I filed a lawsuit, against
Schuster and Werner,
a ten million dollar lawsuit.
We're gonna make those
bastards pay for this, you hear me?
I'm gonna make them pay.
We can plant so many
trees with ten million dollars.
And when we win? The
check will be made out to Karen.
My tree girl made it through?
I can't lie.
Even if they think I'm wrong,
even if they don't understand,
even if they think I'm crazy...
I'm me. They're
supposed to accept me.
They're supposed to support me.
They're supposed to love me, you know?
I can't lie.
Great.
Is this another heart to heart?
I know you don't like me.
You have every
right not to like me.
I have abused my power,
but now I'm here on your turf.
What I need to say...
What I need to say is, I saw
what your mother was doing.
I saw how neglected you were.
I saw her drive your father off.
I spent a lot of time
beating myself up about that.
But what does that do
for you? Nothing. Nothing.
I wasn't your advocate.
I didn't fight for you. I
never stood up for you.
I let myself off the hook.
I told myself I was young and didn't
know better. But I did know better.
And I wasn't much
younger than you are now.
I should've fought
for you, Meredith,
like you fought
for that child today.
I told myself I
wasn't your father,
that it wasn't
my responsibility,
that I was right not to butt in.
I let myself off the hook.
You were helpless.
You were a baby.
A beautiful, smart,
funny little girl.
And no one stood up for you.
I'm so sorry.
♪ We are calling
in all the ships ♪
I'm so sorry.
As doctors, we can't
undo our mistakes
and we rarely forgive
ourselves for them.
But it's a hazard of the trade.
But as human beings, we
can always try to do better,
to be better, to right a wrong,
even when it feels irreversible.
You sure you don't
want me to stay?
I'm sure. I'm OK.
I'll be OK.
If you're not, you
know where to find me.
I love you, Mom. I
love you so much.
But we do better loving
each other from a distance.
You were always too
good for that trailer park.
That I knew.
I might not know that much and I
might not be quite as smart as you, but...
I always knew that.
♪ Break every
lock to every door ♪
♪ Return every gun
to every drawer ♪
Of course, "I'm sorry"
doesn't always cut it.
Maybe because we use
it so many different ways.
As a weapon, as an excuse...
Nice work today.
"Nice work today?" Seriously?
- I'm sorry?
- "Run to my truck?"
You got O'Malley clipping bleeders
and you tell me to run to your truck?
You know what my truck
looks like. O'Malley doesn't.
And that run saved a guy's life.
All day you were teaching
O'Malley and ignored me.
O'Malley wants to be a trauma
surgeon. You declared cardio.
I didn't do anything wrong today. I
treated you like I would anyone else.
I am not like anyone else.
"Take care now?" What is that?
What, are you, like,
happy now? What are you?
Just a "choke 'em and
forget 'em" kind of guy?
"Hey there, now. Take care, now.
Nice work, Yang." What is this?
My shrink gave me these sentences.
We came up with them together.
They're three-word sentences,
so I'd have something to say
instead of the three
words that are...
that are killing me.
The three words that you
know I feel, but I can't say them,
because it would be cruel to say
them, because I am no good for you.
I don't want to torture you. I
don't want to look at you longingly
when I know I can't be
with you. So I'm smiling,
and I'm saying,
"Take care, now."
I'm letting you off the hook.
I'm trying so hard to
let you off the hook.
I'm trying to make it
right what I did to you.
Can't you see that?
I'm trying to make it right.
♪ Every traveler
please come home ♪
♪ And tell us all
that you have seen ♪
Take care, now.
♪ Break every
lock to every door ♪
♪ Return every gun
to every drawer ♪
♪ So we can turn ♪
♪ And turn again ♪
But when we are really sorry...
When we use it right?
When we mean it?
We're leaving. For
good, we're leaving.
As I understand, you'll be
too weak to follow us soon,
so I'm sure you won't
be able to follow us later.
So... We're here to say goodbye.
Say goodbye to Daddy. This is
the last you'll be seeing of him.
Bye, Daddy. Feel better.
- Bye, Dr. Grey.
- Bye, Maddy.
♪ I'm stuck here waiting
for me to get to you ♪
When our actions say
what words never can...
Sorry I'm late.
Um... Dad, this is Mark
Sloan. Dr. Mark Sloan.
- He's my...
- Teacher?
No. He's my...
He's Mark.
Nice to meet you,
Mr. Grey. I'm...
So nice to meet you.
Vice versa.
Please, grab a chair.
♪ I'm gonna take you up
We will dance and sing ♪
♪ I'm gonna show you ♪
♪ That I'm so much more
than I've been in the past ♪
OK. It tastes like shrimp.
Alex...
But listen, the
shrimp kinda tastes...
sweet and spicy.
Like our first date.
The good part. The part before
I didn't kiss you on the porch.
OK. Nice.
The chicken tastes like...
a drive to the beach with the
windows down and the dog hanging out.
Like when you're a kid.
Salty... Tastes good. But...
I vote for the shrimp,
if we have to choose.
There's one more.
OK, yeah, that tastes like crap.
OK, the OR's prepped
and ready. How about you?
Yeah, I'm ready.
Now I taste like crap.
♪ I'm gonna find a ring,
one I can give to you ♪
♪ When I do... ♪
When we get it right,
"I'm sorry" is perfect.
♪ I'm gonna take you out
and we will dance and sing ♪
We have to move the
wedding up for Izzie. She's...
OK.
Packing up your mom's journals?
Yeah, there's nothing
in these for me.
I keep thinking... I don't
want to throw them away.
So I was gonna
give them to the chief.
And... he can come
to the wedding.
If you want. He can come.
OK.
When we get it right,
"I'm sorry" is redemption.
♪ I'm gonna buy you a ring ♪