Previously on "grey's anatomy"...
- O'Malley.
- what ?
George's dad got admitted last night.
It's just a valve replacement, George.
Burke will do it, and you will clear
his schedule.
If someone is gonna operate on my
dad's heart, I want it to be Burke.
Dr. Hahn here graduated second.
Ask her who graduated first.
Adele and I...
she wants me to stop down as chief, retire.
We're starting fresh.
And starting fresh means no sex because ?
Because we started with sex last time,
and it didn't go very well.
You decannulated a heart this morning.
- I didn't decannulate--
- Yes, you did.
And when Burke and I were fishing,
I noticed something weird with his hand.
I slept with another guy.
Do I tell george ?
Callie slept with sloan.
I spent the entire day worrying
about Burke.
Burke is fine.
- Your dad will be fine.
- You're lying.
Burke is hiding something,
and you're helping him.
George knows.
Cirstina : As doctors...
we know everybody's secrets--
their medical histories...
sexual histories...
confidential information
that is as essential to a surgeon
as a 10-blade...
and every bit as dangerous.
we keep secrets.
We have to.
but not all secrets can be kept.
6-letter word for pinnacle.
- Zenith.
- Oh, this is good.
No sex, crossword puzzles,
current events--
when's the knitting start ?
shut up.
Good things come to those who wait.
Yeah ? I want sex.
- there will be no sex.
- Am I interrupting sex ?
No.
- Good. Get out.
- What ? You can't ask me to leave.
Meredith.
give us a sec.
When I get back,
there'd better be some sex.
- Why are you all sweaty and ick ?
- I jogged here.
We don't jog. You jog.
- Cristina--
- what if derek robbed a bank ?
What ?
Say Derek was robbing a bank,
and while he was in there,
you were waiting outside because it was
your job to drive the getaway car.
- Why would Derek rob a bank ?
- Just go with me, please.
- Okay, Derek's robbing a bank.
- And he gets caught.
But no one knows you were involved
'cause you were driving the car.
Okay, Derek's in jail, I'm in the
mystery car. What's the question ?
Would you turn yourself in,
or would you stay quiet and let
Derek go down for a robbery in which
you were a complicit participant ?
Or would you, you know, stand by him ?
Well... whose id was it to rob the bank ?
I don't know. I don't know.
His, but... you helped.
I mean, could you live with yourself
if you just walked away and let
the man you love take the fall ?
If you tell me, maybe I can help.
- If you tell me--
- No, I'll see-- I'll see you at work.
Cristina, you don't jog.
We don't jog.
- Has George said anything to you ?
- About what ?
I jog sometimes...
without you.
- How's your dad ?
- His surgery is today.
- You have nothing to worry about.
- I'm not worried, not anymore.
- What do you mean by that ?
- Hey.
So are you and Meredith having one of your
"we're best friends, we're so cool"
secret time things ?
Sorry, I'm cranky.
Candy striping makes me so cranky.
- Cristina's leaving.
- Ah, so I can have my girlfriend back.
What's wrong with her ?
- Why are you acting like the sky is falling ?
- The sky isn't falling. It already fell.
- George knows.
- I was in surgery for 14 hours yesterday,
- and no tremor.
- Yeah, with me by your side, ready to jump in.
- I haven't had a tremor in a week.
- George knows.
And this is not any surgery.
You are operating on his father today.
-  I am aware of that, and I am fine.
- Well, he's gonna do something.
- I know him. He's not gonna just
stand by and say nothing.
- There's nothing to say.
I had a tremor. Now I don'T.
We need a strategy. We have to figure out
our story and come up with a plan.
Oh, Cristina,
you're too intense.
I am too intense ?
I have been working my ass off
making sure nobody here knows,
running your board,
- Learning surgical procedures I shouldn't
have to know until my fif year covering you.
- Covering me ?
- And I haven't been covering you ?
- Excuse me ?
I'm just saying...
we're a team...
- Okay.
- A strong team, and I wouldn't be in that
O.R. If I didn't know I could do it,
- and you just have to trust me on that.
- Don't let this O'Malley thing break you down.
- No, I'm not.
- Cristina--
- I gotta--I gotta go.
- what happened ?
- Driver lost control of his car,
plowed through the fish market at the warf.
At least a dozen injuries.
- I need all hands on deck.
- All hands ?
Does that mean "all hands,"
or just all hands ?
Stevens, uh, you shouldn't
have been paged.
You can go and take over on mr. O'malley.
He's having his surgery today with dr. Burke.
- Uh, that's my case. I'm with burke.
You have traumas rolling into the pit.
She can take over for you.
So I get to scrub in ?
- Thanks.
- But--
- Stevens, you will not scrub in.
You will not handle any instruments.
You will not move or talk or do anything
other than breathe and watch.
Candy striping again. No problem.
- Where is george ? Why isn't he here ?
- I don't know. He switched shifts with me.
Dr. Bailey...
um, I just wanted to say,
Dr. Burke requested me on the O'Malley
case, so if I have to go...
I mean, Izzie can't even scrub in, so
- if and when my attending asks for me--
- well, if and when your attending asks for you,
then you have to go, don't you ?
Grey, trauma room one. Yang,
man that stretcher. Karev, come with me.
All right, talk to me.
Larry shane dickerson, 86,
G.C.S. 8, B.P. Of 100 over palp,
- pulse in the 120s.
- Obvious deformities to the right tib/fib.
Get x-rays. Let me know
if there's anything surgical.
Looks like he's got a lot worse
problems than a broken leg.
Honey, let me hear your voice.
- That car, that car--
it just about killed him.
- The car hit him ?
No, he was driving. Hit his head on the
windshield, chest hit the steering column.
Old car, no airbags.
He was driving the car that
crashed into the fish market ?
He wasn't driving it.
That's what I'm telling you.
It  was driving him. He didn't
do all this. It was the car.
He couldn't stop it.
Okay. Left pupil is sluggish.
Mrs. Dickerson,
Dr. Yang is gonna take
your husband over to radiology.
And, mrs. Dickerson,
there are two police officers
You see, he dropped me off, he went
to park like he always does.
Larry is a good driver.
Please, I want to be with my husband.
- Yes, mrs. Dickerson, but just give the statement
- Not now !
please.
Okay, uh... all--all right,
I'll--I'll ask them to come back later
- He's crashing.
- I need suction here.
should we shock him again ?
Shocking is not gonna help
a heart with no blood to pump.
- Damn it.
- There are clots everywhere.
If I could just get better
visualization...
so you said you were inside of
the fish market when this happened ?
Okay, I need you to get her...
Ma'am ?
- Call it, Grey.
- Time of death--7 :53 A.M.
Ma'am ?
Preston burke... back from the dead.
- Can't say the same for your patient.
- Ma'am ?!
Ma-- I need a stretcher over here.
- I think I might be parked in a red zone.
- Oh ! I need a stretcher, please !
- Awesome cuts.
- I flew through a window.
- I flew.
- Karev.
Stop manhandling my intern.
That's my job.
- Can you tell me your name ?
- Janelle duco.
Janelle, what do you do for a living ?
- I sell vegetables at the fish market.
- Janelle
honey, can I get you anything ?
Some food maybe ?
Mrs. Dickerson, is that you ?
Mrs. Dickerson, I'm sorry.
You can't be here right now.
Larry is a good driver.
The car went crazy.
Janelle, if--if you need anything,
I'll be right over here.
She's my best customer.
She collapsed in my arms.
I just want to make sure she's okay.
- You got it from here ?
They don't call me "doctor" for nothing.
Mr. Dickerson is such a nice man.
I hope he didn't kill my baby.
Addison ! She's pregnant.
I need an ultrasound.
How far along are you ?
Ten weeks.
Ow !
- Sorry.
- There's glass in there, karev.
Try a lighter tough.
The doctors... hot men.
They're all really hot.
They are, aren't they ?
- It's not just 'cause I'm wearing
a plate-glass window ?
- No
- they're man-candy.
- Good.
okay, that is nasty.
Her sats are in the 80s.
I've got to get her oxygen.
And I'm gonna need a portable chest,
stat.
I love the bossing.
Boss more.
- hey, Izzie.
Honey, this is Izzie.
- Hi.
- Oh, yes.
One  of the girls who lives with georgie
- in some kind of setup there.
- It's not some kind of setup.
It's like what they do these days.
Men and women live together
without being... you know
men and women.
It's like a neutral thing, huh ?
- So nothing sexual ?
- Mom !
No. Nothing sexual.
Where are the other O'Malley men today ?
I told 'em to get back to work.
They were climbing the walls in here.
Well, I'm here to prep you for surgery.
As you know, dr. Burke is your surgeon.
Dr. Burke--right.
Georgie's always saying
"dr. Burke this, dr. Burke that."
Yeah, he's pretty incredible.
he's one of the best cardiothoracic
guys in the world.
yeah.
Um, I have to go.
I'm gonna be right back.
You're not even working today.
Why are you getting paged ?
I have to go.
You're pretty.
There's nothing sexual between
you and Georgie,
- not even a little bit ?
- Louise !
What ?
I just want Georgie to be happy.
Okay.
Let's just prep you for surgery.
Anything you would've
done different, dr. Hahn ?
Given the size of the wound,
I would've given up sooner.
So how have you been, Preston ?
Last time I saw you, you stole my patient's heart.
Then  you got shot.
Karma rocks.
What brings you all the way from
Seattle presbyterian to Seattle grace ?
A consult,
and knowing how much
my being here would annoy you.
Oh, on the contrary,
it's always a pleasure,
but not as much as when you leave.
Hey, do you think I could
get in on erica hahn's surgery ?
- I've heard she's amazing.
- Who ?
Dr. Hahn.
She's doing a consult.
I wonder who the V.I.P. Patient is.
Um, get him-- get him to C. T
Maria, may I have my father's chart ?
Dr. Hahn...
I was pleasantly surprised
to hear you were joining us today.
Oh, well, I'm always ready
to lend a hand, dr. Webber.
George.
Hey, how's your dad ?
Uh, here is his chart. He's in room 3975.
It's down the hall, third door on the right.
- I'll be there in a minute.
- Okay.
I'll escort you,
and you can tell me what it would take to
steal you away from seattle presbyterian.
We  could use an extra hand around here.
- Callie.
- Hey.
We broke up. You broke up with me.
Unless I'm missing something ?
That doesn't mean...
- I'm just asking about your dad.
- Why ?
Why do you care ?
Because I care about you.
Right. Well, I guess that's why
you slept with Mark Sloan, huh ?
That makes sense.
Did dr. Bailey see the chest x-ray ?
No, but with the decreased breath sounds
and the low pulse ox,
she suspects janelle will need a chest tube.
I'm dabbing out freakin' glass splinters,
and she gets to do a chest tube ?
- You signed on for this.
- This is not a good day for me.
- This is not a good day for me at all.
- The baby looks good, janelle.
Heartbeat's strong.
- Do you want me to call the father ?
- You could do that,
but that would require me speaking
to him, which I no longer do.
Plus, hearing he's a daddy from some
random doctor might not go over real well.
- So the baby's father doesn't know.
- No,
and he's never going to.
Grey, can I speak with you ?
Um, I'm setting up a chest tube.
- I need to talk to you when you're done.
- I'll come find you.
You know, I can suture.
I've done it before.
When you can do a z-plasty and
barely see the scar, give me a call.
Till then, dab and clean,
dab and clean.
How's plastics, karev ?
Everything you've ever dreamed of ?
Uh, we're not doing
a chest tube, dr. Grey.
- What's going on ?
- Ms. Duco,
there's a shard of glass
going into your heart.
- Hey.
- Hey. Have you seen dr. Torres ?
- No.
- Quite a morning, huh ? 14 injured, 2 dead.
- I know. There's a lot of blood...
- yeah.
- And blood.
You know, there's a girl who literally
has a shard of glass in her chest.
Come here.
Larry dickerson-- the guy that crashed
into the fish market.
it's a subdural hematoma along with air
in his mediastinum. Now look at this,
look at his spine right here.
- Spinal stenosis.
- Yep.
Narring of the spine,
most often a result of aging.
Causes numbness in the legs and feet.
His case is so far advanced,
I doubt he could even feel his feet,
- which means--
- oh, he shouldn't have been driving.
You paged me ?
Patient has air in the mediastinum.
Wanted you to take a look.
- Oh, this guy shouldn't have been driving.
- I know.
It looks like he has a tracheal injury.
You going into the O.R.
For the subdural ?
Yeah, as soon as one becomes available.
What's going on with Cristina ?
What do you mean ?
Well, first she kicks me out of bed
at 5 :00 this morning so she can have
girl talk with meredith,
and now I can't find her.
She was supposed to be my intern.
I had to get my own C.T. What's goin' on ?
Nothing. Cristina's fine.
She's just working really hard.
I'm sure I don't have any idea.
don't mention Cristina to Burke, okay ?
It's just not a good idea.
Yeah ? What did you talk
about this morning ?
Bank robberies...
which isn't really the point,
okay ?
She was jogging, and well...
just cut her some slack today, okay ?
- Not that I should interfere--
- but you're going to anyway.
I'm just gonna ask once, very nicely.
Please.
- Please.
- You know what says "thank you"
like nothing else ?
I'm leaving now.
hey, uh, Derek's looking for you.
He said you left a patient in the C.T.--
- Shh, shh, shh. I'm trying to hear.
- What's going on ?
- Dr. Yang.
- Yes, sir.
When you see dr. Burke, tell him
I need to speak with him.
Of course, sir.
Uh, is that, uh, dr. Hahn from
presbyterian talking to George's dad ?
Mr. O'malley has elected to have
dr. Hahn perform his valve replacement.
- Um, but what about dr. Burke ?
- Dr. Burke's been replaced.
***************** Dr. Hahn ?
I'm no longer on his father's surgery.
That's a good thing if it means
you stop obsessing.
George didn't just replace you.
He told the chief.
The chief knows.
I mean, for all we know, Erica Hahn's
being considered the new head of cardio.
And the chief asked me to tell you that he
has something important to talk to you about.
Oh, okay.
So we need to align our stories.
This is why I feel like
I'm covering for you.
I don't line up stories.
That's not me.
Oh, I'm sorry. You think it's me ?
- That's not fair.
- You know, it's done.
The chief wants to talk to me,
so I will talk to him.
I am not telling him a story, Cristina.
I'm gonna tell him the truth.
Burke. Burke.
Still getting a heartbeat there ?
Happy to say. And it'll get stronger
once you've had your surgery.
Do you mind me asking why you guys
switched from dr. Burke to dr. Hahn ?
No, we didn't. Georgie did.
- Did he say why ?
- Not really, no.
Did Georgie and dr. Burke
maybe have a falling out ?
Not that I know of.
Then is there something going on
with George and dr. Hahn ?
Ah, here we go again.
No, there's nothing going on
with George and dr. Hahn.
I already told her. Dr. Torres
is the one who loves George.
Well, then why did dr. Torres
break up with him ?
Why did dr. Torres break up with him,
I mean, between us ?
Well... how much did George tell you ?
Everything, I'm his mother.
Okay, well, then you know
that callie is a little bit out there.
I mean, I have seen more of that
girl's body than I have of my own.
It's just a little bit too much
information for me.
I mean, nobody needs to be
naked that often.
He didn't tell you that ?
Um... I don't know why they broke up.
George seemed to really like her,
and he kind of needed her.
I mean, you remember the whole
George and Meredith thing.
- Wait, George and Meredith ?
- I knew it.
George didn't tell you that either.
First Meredith, then dr. Torres
and now this dr. Hahn...
O'Malley men are studs.
He isn't a stud, he's just very handsome.
Okay, people, focus. George
is not dating Erica Hahn.
Then why would he want her to perform his
father's surgery instead of dr. Burke ?
Is she better than dr. Burke ?
She's good, really good.
Nobody's better than burke.
Then  why can't I have dr. Burke ?
- I don't know.
- Do me a favor...Could you find out ?
- Hey, have you seen george ?
- No.
- He is acting so weird.
- So is cristina.
What is wrong with everyone today ?
Hey, Callie. I was gonna come and find you.
What did you want toalk to me about ?
Panties.
Uh, Callie, what you up to ?
I'm gonna kick Meredith's ass right now.
Get off me !
kept your secrets, I was discreet,
I was a really good friend to you,
and I didn't have to be,
- and then you go and do this ?
- Do what ?!
Hey, Callie, use your words !
Use your words, Callie
Panties, Meredith. I'm talkin'about
the mcfreakin'-cone-of-silence
pair of panties I pulled off
the bulletin board,
not to mention the adulterous
mcsex I witnessed.
You remember that ?
Hey Hey, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, but she's
very little, and you're hurting her.
You told George. My night with mcsteamy
was not yours to share.
That's what this is about,
your sex with mcsteamy ?
- You told Izzie.
- No. No, no !
- Callie !
You told me you slept with someone.
You never said it was Sloan.
George told me it was Sloan.
George ?
George told you ?
Who told george ?
- Maybe perhaps the guy you slept with ?
- Um...
George thinks I betrayed him,
and I didn't.
- I didn't. We were broken up.
- Well, go tell george.
- Dude, she went all cage fighter on you.
- I know.
How's my dad doing ?
George, your ex is hard-core--
passionate, but hard-core.
Yeah, I don't--
how is he doing ?
He's fine, George.
And my mom, is she driving you crazy ?
Has she offered to iron your scrubs ?
She does that. She offers to iron
things, weird things.
- They're fine. They're just, um...
- what ?
Confused. You know, suddenly a stranger
is operating on your dad's heart,
and they both want to know why,
and I have no idea what to tell them, so...
Cristina, tell Izzie why dr. Hahn is
doing my dad's surgery instead of burke.
Go on.
Look... dr. Hahn is an incredible
surgeon. Your father is in great hands.
- Nothing else matters.
- You're wrong.
There's a lot of people with fathers
in this hospital, and it does matter
to them who their doctor is.
George, I... I-I know this is scary.
I understand that.
But burke... I didn't come back until
I was ready. Preston burke is ready.
Look, I...
I just can't talk to you about this. This
is none of your business, and just please,
please stay out of this.
- What do I do about your parents ?
- You don't do anything about my parents.
Your job is to watch, remember ?
I was just... sorry.
You might consider leaving that alone
until she goes into the O.R.
Yeah, about that--
when's that gonna happen ?
There's a large shard of glass
in my heart, you know ?
You'd be suprised how long people can
live with stuff inside their bodies--
glass, shrapnel, bullets.
I saw a guy once with half
a chair leg in his chest.
That was one hell of a splinter.
Can we focus here ?
Well...
it looks like we'll, uh, have the O.R.
In a few hours.
So if I get hit by a car,
thrown through a window,
have a big shard of glass in my chest
and my baby survives,
that's pretty much a sign
I should have this baby, right,
even without a father ?
- Everyone has a father.
- Not if she doesn't tell him.
You think I should tell him.
Everyone says I'm wrong.
He's scum, and now I'm the bad guy 'cause
I don't want him in my kid's life, right ?
- That's what you're thinking ?
- Janelle...
my thing is, what about the kid ?
I mean, what happens when he's 6 or 7
and he wants to meet his dad ?
Karev, this is none of
your business, okay ?
She asked, okay ?
He cheated on me.
Makes him an ass. Doesn't
mean you have to be one.
ms. Duco ?
B.P.'S 80 over 60.
J.V.D. And muffled heart sounds.
She's officially unstable.
The O.R. Can't wait.
Alex, find burke and bolus a liter
of saline, hang a unit of blood.
We've got to get her ready
for transport, people, now !
- I'm sorry. Spinal what ?
- stenosis.
- And he got this in the accident ?
I think it may have caused
the accident.
Spinal stenosis is common
in older people.
No, no.
Larry didn't have anything wrong with
him before the accident.
So there were no symptoms
that either of you noticed ?
No, Larry was fine.
We're old, but we've both
been in good health.
Larry was fine.
We're gonna need to operate
on your husband.
He has a subdural hematoma,
which is bleeding in the brain.
And we need to bring in a cardiothoracic
surgeon to repair the hole in his
trachea, which is his windpipe.
That--that--so that means
that you need to operate on his...
- chest and his head ?
- Yes.
We just wanted to go to the market.
It'll be okay, whatever happens.
- Cristina--
- No, he can't punish you.
Every surgery we've done
has been textbook,
- and we haven't lost a single patient.
We're flawless, and he can't--
- Cristina.
You were right.
The chief does want dr. Hahn to replace
me as head of cardiothoracic surgery.
Richard's planning to retire.
And he's recommending that the board
name me... the next chief of surgery.
This is good. It's good, right ?
It means George didn't say anything.
- I'm going to be chief.
- And you didn't tell him anything
about your tremor, right ?
I'm going to be chief...
of surgery at Seattle grace hospital.
- Why do you sound like that ?
- Because I'm going to be chief of surgery
at Seattle grace hospital.
This is what you've worked for.
This is what you wanted.
And I can work harder. I--
I can learn more procedures,
I will do whatever you need.
- What ?
- Right now
nobody knows. I-I mean, yes, okay,
the fact that George hasn't told the chief
yet doesn't mean that he won't,
but we can deal with that.
I mean, I'll--I'll talk to him,
or you talk to him.
And once you're chief, it won't matter.
I mean, you'll be chief. Okay, this is--
- this is good. Nobody will ever know.
- I'll know.
I can't be chief, not now,
not like this.
Do you know how long I wanted this ?
My entire career.
And when I finally get it...
there's blood on it. I had a tremor,
and I didn't say anything about it.
It's unimaginable.
It's unethical...
dishonorable.
- I've crossed a line.
- We crossed the line
- Together. I crossed the line with you.
- You dragged me across the line.
You made us a team,
you told shepherd I was fine,
you said, "nobody has to know."
I was out there on my own.
You made us a team.
I did what you needed me to do.
You were standing there looking at me,
telling me your whole life was your hands,
if you couldn't operate,
if you couldn't be Preston Burke--
- That was your concern, not mine.
- Oh, no, no, no, no.
No, you put that on me.
When you got shot, I walked away,
and you cannot let that go, can you ?
Well, I'm sticking now.
Okay ? I'm sticking.
You know how tired I am ?
Do you know how scared I am
every time we go into surgery ?
But I do it, for you.
Do you know how scared I am
when we go into surgery ?
I don't have to just worry
about my career now.
I have to put yours on my back, too.
- We are a team.
- Oh, there is no team.
There is no team.
There is only me, once again, making
allowances for your emotional shortcomings.
we shouldn't say anymore.
No...
we shouldn't.
Oh, look who's here.
Oh, look how wrinkled he is.
Thank god I brought the travel iron.
Mom. M, what's going on ?
They paged me to your room. Are you okay ?
Fine.
It's just that...
- What ?
- Want me to ?
No, I'll do it.
Here's the thing,
we appreciate everything
you've done for us.
All the strings you pulled
with dr. Burke and dr. Hahn--
the last thing we want to do
is cause trouble
'cause we heard how much stress
you been under.
First with you and Meredith,
then with you and Callie--
- Izzie !
- I thought they knew.
And we hope you won't be mad, but we
rescheduled the surgery for tomorrow
- because--
- we're sticking with dr. Burke.
What did you say to them ?
- We asked her--
- I asked you to stay outta this.
- I just told them what I thought, that doc--
- get out.
W-what ?
Georgie...
- you don't talk like that to anyone.
- Dad...
did dr. Stevens tell you that she's on probation
because the last time she was allowed to
interact with patients, someone died ?
It was really nice to see both of you.
you know the guy
who caused the accident ?
An O.R. Just cleared up.
You available to scrub in with me ?
- Shepherd...
- Burke.
What's going on ?
dr. Burke, we got a pregnant woman in the pit
with a traumatic cardiac tamponade
from a piece of glass
piercing her heart.
- Addison asked for you.
- Well, you can't do two surgeries at once.
No, I can't.
Well, she's bleeding like crazy.
What do you want to do ?
Burke, my guy can't wait much longer.
Well, dr. Hahn is here.
Invite her to scrub in with you, dr. Shepherd.
I'll take the glass piercing the heart.
Okay.
- Uh, Karev.
- Yes, sir.
Make sure that dr. Yang
scrubs in with me.
Everybody gets a surgery but me.
We were broken up,
as in not together.
- I can't do this now.
- I-I slept with mark to get over you,
and guess what, it didn't work.
It was a mistake,
but I did not betray you, George.
I wouldn't-- I would never do that.
I can't do this now.
Oh, where are you taking her ?
- She's having an operation.
- Oh, no.
What--what-- what's wrong with her ?
She has some bleeding in her chest,
and they need to operate.
I'm sorry, janelle.
I'm so, so sorry.
It's okay, mrs. D.
- I'm gonna be okay.
- All right.
Mrs. Dickerson, you should go back to your
husband's room and wait there, okay ?
He's having surgery, too.
Everyone is having surgery.
Uh, go on and take her up.
The surgical team is waiting.
Ma'am.
What did I do ?
- How could I have done this ?
- Done what ? Done what ?
I knew
that he had trouble, my husband,
with his feet.
My daughter came to town,
she took away his keys.
She took away his keys.
You gave'em back to him.
If I'd sided with my daughter,
oh, larry would have felt so betrayed.
He loves to drive.
He--he--he didn't mean to hurt anyone.
Oh, god.
I didn't mean to hurt anyone.
I'm so sorry.
Um... listen, come with me.
- What ?
- I know that you didn't mean to hurt anyone...
but we need to tell the police.
Just trust me, okay ?
it entered the right ventricle
and went right through the septum.
I'm going to need to place
a pericardial patch.
Shall I do a running whip stitch ?
- No, I've got it.
- I can do a mcgoon.
I've been practicing.
Dr. Yang, move to
the other side of the table.
Dr. Burke, I apologize. I--
move... to the other side
of the table. Thank you.
can I get some more lap pads ?
How's it going down there, dr. Hahn ?
Oh, just groovy.
They're all gonna be so jealous
back at Seattle presbyterian.
Why is that ?
Scrubbing in with Derek Shepherd,
the genius who saved Preston Burke
when he almost got his a shot off ?
Major jealousy.
Did you hear that ?
I'm a genius.
Of course you are.
- No, she was serious.
- Mm-hmm.
Damn it. I'm seeing
a partial tear in his aorta.
You okay ?
I'm gonna have to enlarge
the incision to get to the aorta.
We're gonna have to turn him
on his back and redress.
his pressure's bottomed out.
Can you get control down there ?
I know, I know, he's crashing, and this
leration's getting bigger by the second.
All right, you need help ?
I need four hands,
and I need everyone in here
to help me turn him.
- Page thompson.
- He's out.
Is burke available ?
He's in O.R. Three.
Run in there and see if
they can spare him a second.
Okay, I need everyone to help
me turn him.
On your count derek.
We've got about half an hour
move it.
before this patient dies...
Take it off. Let's go.
That is it.
Start rewarming.
Pledgeted 5-0 prolene.
It's gonna take about ten minutes
before the body warms up,
then we'll take her off bypass.
Nice work, dr. Burke.
Thank you.
Dr. Burke,
dr. Hahn was repairing the trachea
and found an aortic transection.
Patient's crashing.
She really needs your help.
What are you doing ?
The heart can't come off of bypass for
a while yet. I'll be right back.
Um, shall I come ?
No, stay here.
Mer. Mer.
Is it bad ?
What does she need him to do ?
The guy's chest is a mess.
She's juggling the tracheal and the aortic injuries,
and she just needs another pair of hands.
He just repaired a hole in her heart.
I'm sure he can handle it.
Cristina.
hey, hey, hey.
What do you think you're doing ?
Get back in there.
What, do you think Burke
can't operate without you ?
Oh, my god,
- Cristina.
- Shut up.
He can't operate without you.
If you ever gave a crap about me
in any way you will shut your mouth
and get back into that O.R.
There's a beat.
It's beating.
- She's ready to come off bypass, right ?
- She is.
Dr. Burke asked me to tell you
he's gonna be longer than he thought.
"Longer than he thought"?
What else did he say ?
She could stroke out
if she stays on any longer.
What did he say ?
He said you shouldn't worry.
He'll be right back.
Well, let's unclamp
and see what we've got.
Brain's not interesting
enough for you, dr. Grey ?
I've still got a lot of bleeding.
I'll place a partial occluding clamp.
4-0 prolene.
- There.
- Excellent, Burke. Thank you.
It should hold once you get
a few more in there.
Focus, dr. Grey.
Focus.
everything okay, dr. Burke ?
Everything's fine.
Dr. Grey ?
It's been too long.
She needs to come off bypass.
She should come off soon, dr. Yang.
How do you want to proceed ?
I'm not having this girl
die of a stroke after all this.
Page someone, anyone who can
help take her off bypass.
- What happened in there ?
- He's going to live.
Dr. Burke, you were gone too long.
She could stroke out any second from--
Gather yourself, dr. Yang.
Let's take her off bypass.
Good. Good rhythm.
Temperature is up.
Okay, let's take her off bypass
*** off bypass.
start protamine.
Give her more volume.
Arterial line is out.
nice. Keep going.
Come on.
There it is.
Heartbeat's still strong.
Nicely done, dr. Burke.
Uh, so we just check everything
and close.
- We'll close--
- Wait.
Ugh ! She blew a stitch.
She ould have a tear in her heart.
Give me he pledgeted 4-0 prolene.
Put up two fresh units of blood.
- What can I do ? Burke ?
- Hold pressure.
I need to repair the heart wall.
Should I put on a clamp ?
- One moment.
- We don't have a moment.
Hold on !
I need to put the cannulas back in
so we can empty out the heart again.
She needs to go back on bypass.
Reheparinize and give me the tubes.
her atrium is extremely friable.
It can't hold a stitch.
- What about a horizontal mattress ?
I can do it.
- Dr. Yang,
I don't need you for this.
this is a known complication
of the surgery. It happens.
It happens.
- Restart bypass.
- Restarting bypass
I was paged. Can I help ?
I'm repairing the heart wall.
I could use your help for a
second attempt to come off bypass.
I'll scrub in.
Load more 4-0 prolene
and a new pericardial patch.
come in.
Chief, we need to talk.
Yes, dr. Burke,
I think we do.
You're lucky, you know ?
- Pardon ?
- To study under Burke.
If your little intern brain can retain
any of what he teaches you,
Maybe you'll become half the surgeon he is,
And that's pretty damn good.
If you tell him i told you this...
ah, he'll never believe you.
- Karev.
- Dr. Montgomery,
- How's she doing ?
- She made it through the surgery.
So did the baby, which is, uh...
well, it's like i said,
the kid's a fighter.
You think she'll call the guy, the dad ?
No. It takes more than a, uh, well
meaning speech
To get a girl to make a
commitment like that.
Yeah.
I appreciated it, though, your take. Uh,
it was surprising.
"Surprising"?
Well, for a mark sloan protg.
Lackey. I dabbed blood all day.
You're a decent guy, Alex.
I'd hate to see sloan beat
that out of you.
- Anyway...
- Yeah,
- Thanks.
- All right, then.
- Okay.
I would've helped you if you'd told me.
Burke ?
I cannot.
It's... been a long day...
and i just cannot.
- I thought you were my friend.
- I thought you were my surgeon.
In some ways, betrayal is inevitable.
When our bodies betray us,
Surgery is often the key to recovery.
When we betray each other...
when we betray each other,
The path to recovery is less clear.
It was both our idea to rob the bank.
- It was both of us.
- I know.
I just--Oh, i couldn't do it anymore.
It wasn't--
You did the right thing.
Yeah ?
Then how come i walked across the parking
lot And realized i can't go home ?
But where am i supposed to go ?
- Hey.
- So dr. Hahn...
- Yeah.
He's my dad... and
i'm scared
you of all people know what it's like
To have someone you love in the hospital--
No. You do not get to bring up denny
to me ever again. Do you understand ?
I'm sorry.
Don't try to apologize, not now,
not yet.
Okay.
- Maybe tomorrow.
- Okay.
You watched his hands all through
surgery.
You knew.
I can't say anything.
There are things cristina told me.
She's my friend. I can't say anything.
No.
No, that is not how this works.
How could you know what you know
Or suspect it and not even tell me ?
You cleared him for surgery, Derek.
How did you not know ?
You can't be angry with me.
She's my best friend,
And right or wrong, she...
What ?
She was there when you weren't.
We do whatever it takes
To rebuild the trust that was lost.
And then there are some wounds,
Some betrayals that are so deep,
So profound...
That there's no way to repair what was lost.
And when that happens...
There's nothing left to do but wait.