Previously on Grey's Anatomy:
- Patient's name!
- How many times...
- Ellis Grey.
- Meredith's mother.
It's not that Burke broke up with me,
it's how he broke up with me.
Have you even told Burke about the baby?
Cristina!
It's an extrauterine pregnancy.
Stop talking to me like you're
my boyfriend! Stop talking to me at all.
If you came here to try to win me back,
forget about it.
I just know I still love you.
Hating you is the most exhausting.
The key to surviving
a surgical internship is denial.
We deny that we're tired,
we deny that we're scared,
we deny how badly
we want to succeed,
and most importantly,
we deny that we're in denial.
When I left, Cristina said she was OK.
Nobody goes through what she did
and is totally over it by now.
- Cristina can.
- She's fine.
Too fine. She's cold.
No, she's hardcore.
She's got ice in her veins.
- She does what she has to do to.
- She lost a baby.
And a fallopian tube.
She acts like she doesn't care.
She's all "Hello, I'm totally fine."
She's my friend too but she's acting
like she has no emotions or warmth,
like she's missing a soul.
- God, she's gonna make a great surgeon.
- George!
It's true. You show no weakness,
you make it to the top.
Some people just keep their feelings
to themselves.
We only see what we want to see
and believe what we want to believe.
And it works.
We lie to ourselves so much that,
after a while,
the lies start to seem like the truth.
Meredith kissed me. Addison kissed me.
My wife and my girlfriend kissed me
on the same day.
Joe, do I look friendly to you?
Oh. Yeah, you're a tiny little kitten
of joy and love.
- What? He saved my life.
- His first mistake.
McDreamy, go sit by someone who cares.
We deny so much
that we can't recognize the truth,
right in front of our faces.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Addison'll go back to New York.
Meredith and I will start over,
everything's gonna be fine. Right?
You so damn stupid.
I want everyone focused.
With Cristina out, we're short an intern
and I feel it will be one of those days.
- And, Karev, see the chief today.
- What for?
Do I look psychic to you?
He's the chief. He asked. You go.
- What did he do now?
- Maybe he gave the chief syphilis.
So we're in the middle of
the Belizian jungle and this jaguarondi
jumps out and bites one of the guides.
They all look at me. They're yelling,
"You're a doctor, help him!"
This is one time a Ph. D. does no good.
I'm sorry, did I miss the bell
for social hour?
- Missionary tales.
- You're a missionary?
No, my parents.
We traveled a lot. They still do.
Wow. This stuff is great.
Um, this is Dr. Burke's patient,
Kalpana Vera...
"Kull-punnah."
Named by villagers in Nepal.
Presents with multiple syncopal
episodes and ventricular arrhythmias.
- So you've been passing out?
- And having palpitations.
History of rheumatic heart disease
with mitral valve stenosis.
They had to ship me
from Zambia to the States
for three months of treatment when I was
eight. Rheumatic fever almost killed me.
Dr. Stevens. What are the primary causes
of ventricular arrhythmias?
Valvular disease, mitral valve prolapse,
stimulants, drugs,
and metabolic abnormalities.
Scrub nurse to OR Six.
- What?
- Out.
- I'm fine.
- Out!
You better be in your room
by the time we round on you.
- And when will that be?
- In fifteen seconds.
Fourteen, thirteen, twelve, eleven...
Nice panties, Yang.
In your dreams, Evil Spawn.
Cristina Yang. Post-op day three
from a unilateral salpingectomy.
- And ready to get back to work.
- Is she?
I'm taking solids and my pain
is controlled with oral meds. I'm ready.
Didn't the nurse say this morning
you had a fever?
- Mother.
- Cristina, did you have a fever?
Temp spiked to 101 last night.
Big deal.
She worked two shifts
with a 102 degree flu.
Yes. Exactly, George. Thank you.
And we appreciate your dedication,
but you stay in bed until it normalizes.
I keep telling her there's more to life
than surgery and career.
Go upholster something.
Look, I need you to relax, shut up,
and get better.
You're a patient this week
so you can be a doctor next week.
Mer. You cannot leave me alone with her.
I am flying over the cuckoo's nest here.
Save me.
- You need time to heal.
- I'm healed. I'm healed!
Oh, God.
OK, Dr. O'Malley, you're presenting.
OK, Dr. Grey is post-op day three
from a tumor resection.
Wrong, wrong, wrong.
He's got it all wrong.
It's not asthma, it's GERD.
He needs a Nissen fundoplication.
- I don't want her in the room.
- Mom!
She's a child
and I won't have her on my team.
We'll meet you outside, Dr. Grey.
Dr. Marash to Cardiology.
- Skipping rounds?
- Avoiding mother.
Meredith...
- You've got a wife.
- Yes.
- Your life is complicated.
I don't need complicated.
I have complicated all on my own.
- Yes.
- Stop saying yes.
I'm trying not to make
any sudden movements.
- You think this is funny?
- Addison's leaving.
She doesn't have
any more patients here.
- There's no reason for her to be here.
- No reason?
None whatsoever.
Well now, isn't this cozy?
Can I join in
or are you not into threesomes?
Dr. Shannon, 1436.
- I have to go.
- Meredith...
You really are Satan.
You realize that, right?
If Satan were to take physical form,
he'd be you.
- Everywhere, all the time.
- I am so not Satan.
Why haven't you gotten
on your broomstick and left?
- Stop being petty.
- Stop being an adulterous bitch.
You are going to forgive me eventually?
You can't just...
There was a time you thought of me
as your best friend?
There was a time when I thought
you were the love of my life.
Things change.
Divorce papers.
Your lawyer said they're OK.
I haven't signed them yet.
The ball's in your court.
If you sign, I'll sign.
I'll sign and be on
the first plane out of here.
I'll sign them immediately.
I want you out of here soon.
Derek, have you ever thought that, even
if I am Satan and an adulterous bitch,
that I still might be
the love of your life?
It's my chart.
You're the patient. Not the doctor.
Act like one.
- It's been tough finding you alone.
- Yeah? Well...
- How are you doing?
- You have my chart. You tell me.
How are you doing?
I'm fine. Perfectly OK.
- I had a right to know.
- Well, now you do.
- Cristina...
- Look. Now you know. It's over.
There's nothing for you to deal with.
So what else is there left to say?
- Plenty. For starters...
- Oh, look. It's my mother.
Dr. Preston Burke.
Nice to meet you, Mrs. Yang.
Actually it's Rubenstein.
Dr. Saul Rubenstein of Beverly Hills?
The oral surgeon?
I'm remarried. Been remarried since
Cristina was, what? About three?
Mom, that's too much information,
he has other things to do.
You're good-Iooking. He's good-Iooking.
Why don't you ever bring home
a man as good-Iooking as him?
- Stop.
- What?
- Stop talking.
- Cristina. Forgive her.
I don't know what I ever did
to raise such an unpleasant girl.
- Oh, me? I'm unpleasant?
- Excuse me.
- Do you know who that was?
- Who?
- That was my boss!
- I only said nice things.
Why'd you call me unpleasant
in front of my boss?
Lighten up, please.
OK, I was thinking that maybe
we might want to... you might...
- OK, we both have tonight off so...
- You are so into me.
- Shut up.
- It's sad. The worship. The adoration.
And I'm so handsome,
I intoxicate you.
OK, you know what? Forget it.
Izzie, would you like to go out
with me tonight?
On a date? And you wear
something gorgeous, I pay for food...
- Are you making fun of me?
- I'm not making fun of you.
OK, then.
- Good.
I said I never wanted to see you again.
'Cause you're too lazy
to learn anything more.
Dr. Meredith Grey, Jeremiah Tate.
Thinks he knows so much
because he was my first intern patient.
I knew as much as her. She was clueless
about how to treat cystic fibrosis.
A cholecystectomy
turned into a month-Iong stay.
Better not be alleging malpractice.
Guy raises about 100,000 grand a year
for cystic fibrosis, running triathlons.
- Thinks he's a big shot.
- You run triathlons?
- Why not?
- Pain for one.
- Finally admitting to feeling a little?
- A little.
How little? Truth.
Enough to keep me awake at night.
Had some seizures.
Too weak to work out.
Anyone been through here
with your CT results?
No. It's probably just my pancreatitis
kicking up again.
All right then. We'll be back.
With your results and a plan.
Where do your parents
think you are this time?
New Jersey.
What about his parents?
He doesn't like to bother them until
he's well or about to get discharged.
He understands his reality.
He just chooses to ignore it.
Denial works for him, Grey.
"Abdominal pain."
"Perirectal abscess."
"Gunshot wound to the head."
Where the hell's this GSW to the head?
Why wasn't the trauma team called?
Hello? Are you people insane?
There's your gunshot victim.
Him?
I'm redoing the living room
in beige silks, I'm thinking.
And modern. Very mid-century.
- And the dining room...
- Mother, give me back my toes.
OK. I change the subject.
- Who's the father?
- Mid-century, did you say?
Someone you work with, right?
Was it just for sex?
You make such a point
of not forming attachments.
20 minutes. All I want is 20 minutes
of peace and quiet.
The daughter I raised
would appreciate her mother's help.
The daughter you raised
is begging for you to go. Now.
I didn't have to come here.
You know I'm very busy.
Yeah, I know.
Redecorating your house.
Well, can you get me
a mocha latte, please?
A non-fat one.
No. A fat one!
You're walking, you're talking,
there's no exit wound.
- This mark here looks more like a burn.
- I'm telling you, I shot myself.
Pulled the trigger cleaning my.22.
I thought the clip was out.
If you're thinking suicide, don't.
People make mistakes. I made a mistake.
And now I'm paying for it.
But I did shoot myself.
- Where's your IV?
- I'm taking solids. I Hep-Locked it.
- On whose orders?
- Mine.
OK. Yang.
How about this order: "Bed rest, out
of bed to chair, bathroom privileges."
Nothing about stealing charts.
OK, you know what.
Hey. Give me that.
There. Satisfied?
I'm "out of bed to chair."
- I'm telling your intern on you.
- Meredith?
- Yep.
- Oh, I'm so scared.
- Dr. Grey, how are you doing?
- You're here. Good.
I need the results of the
barium esophagram or the EGD.
And you have neither. OK, no worries.
I'll be here when you get back.
So today you're her intern. Well,
that's better than being her husband.
- That's a matter of opinion.
- Good morning, Ellis.
Richard, good to see you.
I need those labs immediately.
Chief?
She's not a surgical patient anymore.
And I'd really like
to get back to the OR.
So, do you think I could hand her off
to someone else?
O'Malley, Alzheimer's causes her reality
to shift depending on situation or mood.
She needs stability right now.
That's why I'm depending on you
to keep a special eye on her.
Yes, I know, sir.
But, you know,
it just doesn't seem fair to me.
I need those studies yesterday.
You heard the doctor.
Get moving.
I saw that. I saw you take that pill.
Oh, it's my pill.
You know, the pill.
It's not in your chart. You're supposed
to tell us all the meds you're on.
You're not my doctor.
You shouldn't even be here.
- She's right. You shouldn't be here.
- She took unauthorized medication.
I'm on the pill and I had
grapefruit juice this morning.
Since the juice inhibits enzymes
involved in the metabolism of OCPs,
I avoided the interaction
by taking it two hours after food.
She has a doctorate
in neuropharmacology.
- I don't see oral contraceptives.
- Guys.
Now you will. Go back to bed
and stop poaching my patients?
This is ridiculous! Go back to bed
and stop poaching my patients!
- She's in V-fib!
- Call the code!
Code blue, second floor.
- You got the code equipment?
- It's all ready to go.
- No code?
- Not anymore.
- Can you help us get her back in bed?
- I'll help.
Would you just go back to bed? Go!
Oh, God. You know, Izzie, if she's
on OCPs, can we mark it down, OK?
Yeah.
Jeremiah's got a mass
in his midepigastrium.
Diffused enlargement of the pancreas.
That, with his hypoglycemic seizures...
He's gonna need
an exploratory laparotomy.
But, despite his triathlons,
his lungs still make me hesitant to cut.
What are we going to do?
- I don't know that yet.
- Doctors.
- Dr. Montgomery-Shepherd.
- How old is he?
- He's 26.
- A survivor, huh?
And then some.
My patient for at least five years.
- I'm not gonna lose him now.
- You planning a laparotomy?
Yeah, but his lungs.
You know,
I think I could help you with this.
I've seen one case like this
in a nine-year-old.
We had to do a total pancreatectomy.
I'd be honored to take any help
you can give me.
You're a neonatal specialist.
What...
This isn't your area.
I'm just saying. I...
I did genetics research
in cystic fibrosis.
- I've pretty much seen it all.
- Oh.
Dr. Ramirez, please call extension 543.
Just because she offered her services
doesn't mean she intends to stay.
- Well, what does it mean?
- It means that she's a good doctor.
- Why are you suddenly defending her?
- I'm not.
Meredith, she gave me divorce papers.
She filed.
Oh. Well, that's good.
All I have to do is sign, and I'm free.
We're free.
Is there anything to think about?
No, of course not.
I read through them, sign, then
Addison's on the next plane out of here.
- You say he got shot in the head?
- He says he got shot in the head.
I say he's a mental defect.
- Hi.
- Ma'am, you can't be in here.
I'm looking for Samuel Linden, he...
Oh, my God. Samuel.
Well, how bad is it?
- Are you his wife?
- For 21 years. Just tell me how he is.
Fine, for a man who says
he shot himself.
He shot himself. He was cleaning his
gun. What is wrong with you people?
We'll know when we finish his CT.
- This is a restricted area, ma'am.
- My husband has a bullet in his head!
Then we'll find it. Wait outside,
I'll be with you as soon as
we know something, I promise.
Of all the fine doctors in the city, you
accept a consult from Addison Shepherd?
- Montgomery-Shepherd, isn't it?
- She should be on her way home.
You're trying to drive me crazy,
aren't you?
Hey, don't...
You think this has
something to do with you?
You think I'm even thinking about
your romantic problems?
I'm trying to help a patient
very near and dear to my heart.
And if consulting with your wife,
your ex, your mistress,
whatever she becomes, if that's
what's needed to save my patient,
- then I'm damned well going to do it.
- I understand that.
I deserved that. It's...
Look, you have put yourself
between two very fine women
and you're looking for an easy way out.
You want to use me, the hospital,
somebody to make the decision
for you, and it's not gonna happen!
- Could I just say a couple of things?
- Just...
You scared us a little there.
How's her work-up coming?
Electrolytes are within normal limits,
urine tox was negative and EKG's fine.
Tilt test is scheduled for noon.
Oh, and she's on contraceptives.
- So?
- That's what I said.
That other doctor
made such a big deal of it.
She didn't tell us before.
So I documented it in her med list.
- What other doctor?
- Cristina. She was wandering the halls.
Fine. Take her down for an echo.
An echo?
What about cardioversion or ablation?
Won't I need a pacemaker
or a permanent internal defibrillator?
Although it would be unusual
for rheumatic heart disease
to cause ventricular dysrhythmias,
we've still got to check your valves.
I thought your doctorate was
in neuropharmacology, not medicine.
It is.
Addison gave Derek divorce papers,
which is good.
I mean, she's still here, being Addison,
but it's not like I'm jealous.
- That's odd.
- It's odd that I'm not jealous?
No, you have every right to be jealous.
It's your territory and she's peeing all
over it. What's odd is Burke's patient.
Four other hospitals this year.
Something's not right.
- Why the interest in Burke's patient?
- This has nothing to do with Burke.
You lost a fallopian tube, a baby,
and a boyfriend all in one day.
You have the right to be upset.
You're losing McDreamy to his wife.
You have a right to be jealous.
I did not lose McDreamy. Divorce papers,
remember? And I'm not jealous.
- And I'm not upset.
- You really should be in your room.
If this was reversed, would you
want to spend time with your mother
in a confined room with one window?
Do you think we're like them?
Our mothers?
Uh, where's your mom?
Exactly. Where is my mother?
- Where's your mother?
- Funny you should ask.
Oh, crap.
Oh, man,
you are not going to believe this.
No. It can't be. The guy was reading
a freaking magazine.
It's definitely a bullet.
Tracked clear through his head.
Now are you people just going
to sit here or get him into surgery?
Here's the missile track. As you can see
it doesn't even cross the midline.
He's lucky. This guy may have even
been sitting there talking to you.
He'll need debridement of the
entrance wound and repair the dura,
but we won't need to remove the bullet.
That's an excellent diagnosis, Dr. Grey.
I'm Dr. Shepherd,
I'm your neuro consult.
Dr. Grey, they need you upstairs.
- You'll book the OR and staff?
- I'm on it.
- Unbelievable.
- O'Malley.
Can you not handle this, doctor?
I can handle a lot of things.
Wheelchairs. Come on, Dr. Grey.
We won't know for sure
until we go in there,
but it looks like I'm gonna have
to take out your pancreas
and re-route your intestines.
Did you tell her my lungs
don't do well with anesthesia?
Don't I always have your back?
Your kidney function is decreasing
and I'm afraid
you'll go into multi-system
organ failure if we don't operate.
- If I say no?
- There's no guarantees, Jeremiah.
It's going to be a long, hard surgery,
and put a lot of stress on your body.
Yeah, but I'm me.
- But you're you.
- So if we don't operate, I die.
And if we do operate, I may die.
Basically, yes.
Well, I like those odds.
And 26 years with this disease
is awesome. And that's the reality.
So if I get lucky, great.
If I don't...
it's been sweet.
It's gonna stay sweet.
We'll need to do a psych evaluation.
How many times do we have to tell you?
He wasn't trying to kill himself.
- It was an accident.
- They're just doing their job, hon.
- Their job is to make you better.
- Where were you at the time?
I was in the next room.
And I heard the shot. And it was awful.
- It's over now.
- Why didn't you call 911?
Because he was only unconscious
for a moment.
And then he was walking,
and talking and...
You'll have to give a report
to the police.
- Police?
- Why do we need to talk to the police?
We have to report any gunshot wounds
to the police. It's the law.
You're officially AWOL, you know.
I'm working. Trying to figure out what's
going on with the crazy woman on four.
You are the crazy woman on four.
I made a break for freedom.
Hand me that dictionary.
You have a better patient than
me and you don't even have a patient.
Meredith's got a CF case.
Alex's got the gunshot wound.
Izzie's got the mystery arrhythmias.
I'm not a nanny.
I am a surgeon. A cutter.
But no, I'm getting fake labs for a fake
patient so she can do a fake surgery.
- She's faking it.
- It's real to her. It's Alzheimer's.
The missionary. Kalpana...
God! Thank you!
Ow!
Uncalled for!
- Izzie. How have her studies been?
- I've been looking for that everywhere.
Negative, right?
Oh! The echo test showed mild mitral
stenosis, the tilt test was negative.
We're doing EP studies.
I know what's wrong without
sticking electrodes in her heart.
- Really. Just by the chart?
- No, from the pill she took.
They were contraceptives. Why are you so
obsessed with this? Just go back to bed.
- She's doing this to herself.
- Inducing ventricular arrhythmias?
- She'd have to be crazy.
- No, she'd have to have Munchausen's.
Wait. You think she's secretly ingesting
something to produce real symptoms?
- Seriously?
- Yep. Just run it by Burke.
- Tell me what he thinks.
- Tell him yourself. He's behind you.
- Where are we?
- OR Two in 30 minutes.
He's prepped, transpo's on the way.
Do you understand that?
21 years!
- What's that all about?
- I haven't got a clue.
I love you. I forgive you.
You cheated on me. You cheated on me.
- You do not get to play the martyr.
- I got a bullet in my head.
- And that doesn't make us even.
- You shot me!
I think we need to get the police
up here right now.
She obviously loves the patient role.
She practically lives in hospitals.
And we're like an imaginary family
to her
because her real family blows her off
to go take care of other people.
- And I saw her take something.
- That's not enough.
We have to rule out everything else.
She lied about her job.
She's a pharmacy tech, not a Ph. D.
So she's a liar.
I've been lied to before.
- We're not talking about us here.
- Maybe we should be.
- I didn't lie.
- You withheld the truth.
OK, you know what? I remember you
breaking things off with me.
You didn't seem so upset about it.
This? This is not a relationship.
- This is not real.
- Cristina!
OK, and so what's with
the big fake display of hurt and drama?
- Cristina!
- I'm supposed to be in bed.
Cristina!
Officers, thanks for coming.
Ma'am, why don't you have a seat?
We need to ask you a few questions.
Uh, of course.
Well, nothing like a domestic dispute
to liven up a pre-op, huh?
- Where do I sign?
- Here, for consent.
And here for DNR
and no extraordinary measures.
Good. OK, lift up for me.
You should probably call my parents.
Call them yourself
when you walk out of here.
Dr. Grey, I have those labs...
Oh, no you didn't.
You lost her again? Again?
I am a surgeon. A surgeon!
Yeah, well.
You won't be when Dr. Webber
finds out you lost Ellis Grey again.
We're using three different catheters.
Why are we doing that, Dr. Stevens?
Programmed electrical stimulation
maps the heart's electrical system
- to find the focus of the irregular...
- Doctors? Sorry to interrupt.
- Yes?
- Her urine's blue.
What?
Why is her urine blue?
She says she has a surgery scheduled
with Dr. Shepherd?
- I turned my back for...
- Why did you turn your back?
I told you to take care of her!
Just get out of here.
You want to find a hot surgery,
then find one.
You're free.
I'll take care of her.
This is one sick bastard. We
should flip him over, give him a spine.
Pull back on the retractor, Dr. Karev.
A little suction.
Covering for his wife
after she shot him?
- He did cheat on her.
- And that's worth a bullet in the head?
Relationships are built on sacrifice.
- Not that kind of sacrifice.
- I don't know.
Sometimes a bullet's worth it.
Richard, I thought you'd never get here.
Look, the OR's empty,
I have a little time before my surgery.
I don't think I'm supposed to be here.
No.
No, you're not.
Come on,
I'll take you back to your room.
I need more traction. Dr. Grey?
Here, give me some suction there.
Grey, retract the duodenum. Good.
How's he doing?
- Hard to ventilate and no urine output.
- He's shutting down.
- Did you increase peak pressures?
- Any higher, I blow his lungs.
Bradycardia. Pushing one of atropine.
Try ventilating him manually,
see if he starts coming back up.
- Did we miss any bleeders?
- Surgical field is clear.
- Agonal rhythm.
- Any pulse with that?
- No carotid.
- Starting CPR. Push one of epi.
No extraordinary measures, Dr. Bailey.
He's DNR.
No, this is just good medicine.
Blue urine?
A second drug screen was positive
for amitriptyline,
which, I'm sure you know,
causes ventricular arrhythmias.
You knew it wouldn't show
on a drug screen,
but I'm guessing
you didn't realize it turns urine blue.
I didn't do this to myself.
You have to believe me. I'm sick.
- I have something...
- No. You're just deceiving yourself.
Manufacturing things that really aren't
there, seeing only what you want to see.
Wasting our time, our resources,
and throwing away your own life.
Your illness is in your head, Kalpana.
We will be transferring you to Psych.
Come on.
Come on, don't give up. Come on.
You're getting tired.
Let me take over, Dr. Bailey.
Dr. Bailey, his intestines are
cyanotic. There's no blood circulating.
It's been shunted to his brain where he
needs it. You call those compressions?
Fight it. Come on!
Why isn't anyone moving?
Who's recording?
It's been ten minutes
since we had a perfusing rhythm.
It's your call, Dr. Bailey.
One, two, three...
Asystole.
Time of death: 19:26.
It's hard to accept the end
when you're too close.
Look, I don't want someone
who doesn't want me, Meredith.
But if there's the slightest chance
that he does, I'm not leaving Seattle.
What did she tell them?
That you cheated on her,
that she was drunk,
and you were cleaning your guns
in the kitchen.
- I'm not gonna press charges.
- It doesn't matter, she confessed.
- Assault in the first degree.
- They arrested her?
Man, you should be grateful.
You know what I am?
I'm stupid.
Nothing is more stupid
than cheating on the woman you love.
You don't know what you're missing.
Your latte's by your bed,
and I'm pretty sure it's cold.
- I don't need it.
- You should be in bed.
Stop it. I'm fine, OK? My brain is fine.
My body is fine. I'm fine.
- I don't know why I came.
- Then why did you?
You know, I... Just stop it. I don't...
I'm sorry I'm not that person. I'm sorry
I don't need you here taking care of me.
Well?
You were right. Kalpana definitely
suffers from Munchausen's.
See. I was right.
I was right.
I was right. I was...
Oh, I'm...
I'm right...
I'm right... I'm...
You took the Clinical Skills section of
your medical exams after most interns,
so the results are only now coming out.
I got a call from USMLE this morning.
Oh.
So you're saying...
Karev, you're still an MD.
You still get to practice medicine.
The hospital grants you four months
to retake the exam.
You study it, you pass it,
you put it behind you.
One misstep doesn't affect your career.
Right, thanks. Thanks.
What happens if I take the exam
for a second time and I don't pass?
You will no longer be
a surgical resident at Seattle Grace.
Failing again is not an option.
- What's going on?
- I can't stop. I can't... I can't stop.
Crying. She can't stop crying.
I can see that. What did you do to her?
Nothing.
She's going to dehydrate.
Cristina, do you want some water?
No. No.
No!
I already tried that.
It just made it worse.
I knew she'd break sooner or later.
Just a matter of time.
I will kill her!
I am her mother.
We don't do well with mothers here.
Why don't you leave and come back later?
Cristina.
Make it stop. Make it stop.
Somebody sedate me!
Sometimes reality has a way
of sneaking up and biting us in the ass.
And when the dam bursts
all you can do is swim.
The world of pretend is a cage,
not a cocoon.
We can only lie to ourselves
for so long.
We are tired. We are scared.
Denying it doesn't change the truth.
Hi, Mrs. Tate?
It's Miranda. Miranda Bailey.
I'm calling about Jeremiah.
I'm so sorry.
She doesn't want to be touched.
Sooner or later,
we have to put aside our denial
and face the world head-on,
guns blazing.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- You look great.
- Thanks.
- Are you OK?
- Yeah, you ready to go?
Yeah, you just...
You don't seem like yourself.
No. Look, we got dinner reservations.
We should go so, let's go.
OK.
Denial. It's not just a river
in Egypt. It's a freaking ocean.
I'm glad we're doing this.
Me too. Want a drink?
- Yes. Oh...
- That's OK, I got it.
I'll get it.
So how do you
keep from drowning in it?
www.tvsubtitles.net