Previously on "Grey's Anatomy"...
You're shot?
Cristina?
- You're throwing me out?
- Got no choice.
What's with the suitcase?
Yes.
My answer is yes.
An hour ago, he was proposing.
I thought I was a surgeon, but I am not.
I stopped teaching when you needed a teacher the most.
Our marriage is over.
There's this thing that allows for the considering of options.
In the olden days, they called it dating.
You bowing out?
No.
You?
I don't think so.
Surgeons usually fantasize about wild and improbable surgeries--
someone collapses in a restaurant,
we slice them open with a butter knife,
replace a valve with a hollowed-out stick of carrot.
But every now and then,
some other kind of fantasy slips in.
Good morning.
- Good morning.
- It is a good morning.
- Hi.
Did you get any sleep last night?
Not really.
You want to get some now?
Most of our fantasies dissolve when we wake,
banished to the back of our mind.
But sometimes, we're sure...
If we try hard enough...
We can live the dream.
Damn it!
Stupid--
I was having a really good dream, and you ruined it.
Sorry.
It's,uh,the,uh,these boxes.
All these boxes.
Callie said she was bringing her stuff over,and,uh...
it's all here.
It's okay,george.
I don't mind.
I don't mind either.
No.
Don't mind a bit.
Kick her out.
What?
I can't kick her out.
You were the one who told her she could move in.
I said she could stay for a couple of days--
a couple of days.
It's been over a week.
Now there are boxes,and she's using my computer.
And she's here all the time.
Would you kick her out? And kick her out now.
Hey,you guys might want to wait a little while.
There's no more hot water.
do it.
Why do you hate me? Just do it.
Hey.
Can I get a ride with you guys to the hospital?
You're going to the hospital?
Yeah,I'm--
I'm gonna go in,talk to the chief,see about coming back.
Anyway,just let me know when you're leaving.
that's great.
Izzie is coming back. That'S...
great,right?
That's my towel.
Sorry.
boy,he is really moody in the mornings.
Yeah.
He's,uh...
- yeah.
- Yeah.
You know I don't have to leave today.
I could change my flight.
No.
No,you can't.
Because I'M...
sober now,and,uh,there's work to get to and--
and planes to be caught and real lives to be led.
Thank you,truly,mark,for all of the...
sex.
I-I really,I feel much better now.
I do.
And I'm-- I'm--
well,now I have to go,and so do you.
So,uh,do you,uh,want me to call you...
a cab to the airport?
Why don't you try your bad hand?
That's what the ball's for,right,fixing your bad hand?
Works.
There's coffee on the floor.
Fine. I'll--
you know what? I'll clean it up.
Whatever.
Leave it.
It doesn't matter.
So I was thinking,since your shift ends after mine,
and I don't want to have to wait around,
maybe I should get a copy of the house key.
No.
I like leaving together.
You don't need a key.
Izzie?
I'll see you guys in there.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Bailey is on your side.
And the chief is...
he is gonna put on his angry face,
but he's on your side,too.
Everybody wants you back in that building.
I know.
You guys go ahead.
I'll be fine.
I'm just gonna take a minute,practice my speech.
Okay.
I didn't ask you to convince her to come in.
But I di I d cod.
Ince her.
There is a whole series of disciplinary and rehabilitative
steps that izzie stevens will have to take
- before we can--
- you can explain them to her.
- I never agreed to that.
- She didn't commit a crime.
She's an intern--
my intern.
You--
you want to blame someone,blame me.
Look,but that girl is coming in hertoday,and--
and--
and you are going to talk to her.
And you're gonna remember all the other surgeons you've known
who've ever had a lapse in judgment that led to someone dying
or someone's arm falling off.
Most importantly,you're gonna remember all the mistakes
that you made when you were young and stupid.
And you're gonna be filled with patience and compassion.
- That's what I'm gonna do?
- Yes!
- Because I'm the boss.
- I'M...
look,I didn't mean any disrespect,sir.
I apologize.
This is really important to you personally.
Very personally,sir,yes.
Being the boss isn't as gratifying as it used to be.
No,sir.
Get outta here.
I'm on my knees in a puddle of coffee,
and he's lying on the couch playing with himself.
You know,and not in a good way.
T he's recovering from surgery,and you've read
the studies on recovery and depression in surgical patients.
Well,he's not a patient.
He's preston burke.
He's just milking it.
You know,he's got me fetching his food
and the paper and his slippers like I'm a dog.
- Hey.
- Hi.
I had a dream about you last night.
- You did?
- Mm-hmm.
What was I doing,bringing you coffee?
You were definitely not bringing me coffee.
But coffee's good.
I'm told dating starts with a casual invitation over a cup of coffee.
Does it?
So,meredith,would you like to go out to dinner with me tonight?
How was that? Was that casual enough?
That was good,right?
- So we're dating.
- We're dating.
Pick you up at 8:00.
- hey.
- I was in the neighborhood.
Actually,I wasn't.
But I decided you were worth a detour.
I had a dream about you last night.
- Was it a good dream?
- It was.
- And what was I doing?
- Yes,mer,what was he doing?
- What's that?
- It's for you. It's coffee cake--
best in the northwest.
Figure I better soften you up so that when
I ask you to dinner tonight,you have to say yes.
Uh,dinner tonight?
How about that?
Are you free tonight,meredith?
Actually,uh,I'm not free tonight.
Well,how about lunch?
I could come here.
You're volunteering to eat hospital food?
I love crappy food.
- 1:00?
- I'll be here.
Okay.
You had a dream about the both of them?
A threesome?
Nice.
Just when I think you're boring,you rise.
I'm dating.
And...
it comes with snacks.
- Hey,iz.
- Hey.
- I'm going in to see the chief.
- Excellent.
Back in the game,stepping up to the plate.
Look,I'm-- I'm running late.
Um,I'll catch you later?
Yeah,later.
Izzie's back.
That's good.
Ooh,coffee cake.
I'm dating.
Touch that piece,lose a hand.
Morning,people.
Grey,we're clearing the decks.
I need you writing discharge forms.
Yang,you're with Dr. Shepherd.
Karev,as usual,you're with Dr. Montgomery-
shepherd in O.B.-G.Y.N.
O'malley,Dr. Torres has requested you today in ortho.
- Was she smiling?
- Izzie's back.
"Dr. Torres has requested you."
Just tell her,george.
Tell her you're not ready to move in together.
And then try dating.
Dating is fun.
Karev,we ready?
- Isn't this getting old for you?
- nope.
Makes my whole day,actually.
hello.
Hello.
Are you okay?
No.
Uh,ye--
n-no,I can't.
I gotta--
five minutes.
- Go find something to do in the pit.
- Personal problem?
go.
fourth visit in three months.
I'm Dr. Karev.
And you are...
megan clover.
And it's not as bad as it looks.
She fell on the playground,
and there was a lot of blood,and it looked deep.
We know how this looks.
Just so you know,we know how this looks,and it's not that.
She just...
plays rough.
You know?
This is her file,all right?
And it goes back since way before we got her.
Before you got her?
We're her foster parents.
She's such a great kid,but she plays really--
- she plays rough.
- Yeah.
Right.
Uh...
why don't you guys go up to the nurses' station
and let them make a copy of her file for you?
And,uh,I'll take a look at megan's leg.
Okay.
We'll be right back,honey.
You all right?
- Yeah.
- okay.
You got some mean looking bruises,you know that?
What,did you hurt your arm,too?
Nothing big.
I fell off my bike.
Are those staples?
What the hell?
- Did they do this to you?
- No!
- Who did this to you?
I did.
I didn't want to go to the doctor again,so I just stapled it.
It's no biggie.
You stapled your own arm?
Can you please just stitch up my leg so we can get out of here?
You're not going anywhere with those people,megan.
They're never gonna lay a hand on you again.
They didn't do anything. Please.
They're my best parents I've ever had.
- Megan.
- They don't hurt me.
I can't be hurt.
You don't believe me?
Punch me in the stomach right now.
The staples are in there pretty deep.
I'm gonna have to give you a shot to numb the pain.
I don't need a shot.
Trust me. You want a shot.
It's swollen. It's gonna hurt like A...
there.
Can I go now?
That didn't even hurt?
I have superpowers,okay?
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:YTET-gagegao
Greys Anatomy
Season 03 Episode 03
Mrtreslt'savseing a corpus callosotomy.
What's that gonna look like?
We'll be severing some of the fibers that connect
the rightnd left hemisphere of his brain...
To prevent the spread of seizure activity from
one half of his brain to the other.
Good.
Right.
Daddy's letting them chop his brain in half
because daddy's a big dummy.
Yes,he is.
They're not chopping my brain in half,leanne.
Chop!
Right down the middle.
Taylor should function much like he does right now.
Really?
- I'm having five seizures a day,leanne.
- I know that.
You don't leave me in a room alone with the baby.
You think I don't notice?
You ask your mother to come by every time you need to take a shower.
- That's not the reason.
- It's because you think I'm a danger to the baby.
And I am.
Look,if you're not sure,for any reason,we can wait.
I want to be able to take care of our baby.
Please,leanne,we already agreed.
Please.
I got this kid in the pit.
She's psycho and her foster parents are beating the crap out of her.
She tell you that or you figure it out yourself?
Well,she's covered in bruises.
She's got a 10-centimeter lac on her arm with three staples in it,
like from a staple gun in your garage.
- Her parents did that?
- Well,she saysshe d it herself.
She's got this whole bit about being a superhero
and how she can take the pain.
- You call social services?
- They're on their way down.
Okay,well,ha them speak to the parents while you
run a cold pressure test on the girl.
A what?
Ice water.
Test her response to pain.
At the very least,it'll keep her distracted
while the parents are questioned.
You requested me?
Yeah,I did.
- You were weird this morning.
- I wasn't weird...
any more than I normally am in the morning.
It's a weird time of day for a lot of people.
It's bright...
and crowded at our house in the morning.
There's just a lot of people running around.
Good.
We have a radical case today.
You're gonna be glad you're with me.
Thanks.
Mr. Jasper hobie.
- Dr. T.
- Hey!
You missed me.
More than words can say.
This is Dr. O'malley.
He's gonna be helping out.
Hi.How you doin'?
June 12th,baby.
2.4-mile swim,112 miles on the bike and then a marathon.
- That is rockin'.
- Am I gonna be ready?
You bet your sculpted ass you are.
I love this woman.
you had three surgeries last year.
Yeah,two rotator cuffs and an A.C.L.
All with Dr. T.
And now you're having an ankle replacement?
We waited over a year for a match.
We're gonna replace his ankle with an ankle joint from a cadaver.
- Who's my guy?
- Your donor?
Well,he hasn't been dead long,right?
Um,about a week.
And he's downstairs.
No way.
Can I meet him,pay my respects?
I don't think you two are gonna have much to talk about.
Dr. O'malley's gonna handle your labs.
have you met my guy?
Hey,superkid.
Where are my parents?
They're talking to some grown-ups.
I'm not a moron.
They're talking to a social worker.
Megan...
these bruises,these cuts all over you,this isn't normal.
I t in fights a lot,okay?
Because I'm stronger than some of the other kids,
so I end up defending the ones who are wimpy or small or whatever.
You know you're scrawny,right?
I mean,you're not one of the big kids.
Yeah,but I can take them in a fight.
All right.
Put your hands in here.
Why?
Because...
we're gonna test your superpowers.
You don't believe me?
Punch me in the stomach right here. Come on.
- Punch me in the stomach.
- Let's just stick to the water.
Just put your hand in here.
And I'll-- I'll race you.
You can race me.
What?
Come on.
What are you afraid of,uh,you afraid of a little ice?
You afraid I'm gonna beat you?
Come on.
On the count of three.
One,two,three.
Pull your hand out when it starts to hurt,please.
What are you,deaf?
It won't start to hurt.
Just think about it,okay?
Superheroes are all kids with dead parents,like me.
And they all figured out when they were around my age
they could do things that nobody else could,like me.
You missed your plane?
Grounded on account of bad weather.
It's a cloudless sky.
That happens like,twice a year in seattle.
Yeah,but there's a typhoon in new york.
Sit down.
Have a drink with me.
No,I'm not having a drink with you.
I am working.
At work,not here.
So coffee,right?
- Mark--
- joe,can we get the doctor a coffee?
And they think it's weird that they can do all this stuff,
but they don't tell anybody because people would freak out like you d.
What's wrong with you?
Son of a--
Take your hand outta there before it falls off.
You need to relax.
You didn't feel anything?
Nothing?
No.
Nobody ever believes me.
Like yesterday in school,this kid said I was full of it.
I had to letim punch me in the stomach
25 times before he believed me,
and once with a baseball bat.
What?
We'll have cardiology check this,and then you'll be good to go.
All done.
There's my guy.
Jake...
we're almost all done with this whole thing.
we're not almost done.
You still have brain surgery and god knows
how many weeks of recovery ahead of you.
She's right.
It's good to know what you're getting yourself into.
Thank you.
I appreciate that.
Yeah.
Recovery's hell on the spouse.
It's gonna be harder for you than on him.
My mom's staying with us for a week.
Maybe she should stay longerer.
You know,it's--
it's brutal being the caretaker.
You'll be fetching the paper and then cleaning the carpet...
honey.
And oh-- oh,he wants ice in a cup,not a mug.
It's like-- it never stops.
It's the caretakers that are the silent victims.
You know,and when do you ever hear about them?
- Honey,take the baby.
- Never.
I never hear anything about them.
It's always,you know,"the patient this,the patient that."
Silent victims.
Honey,take the baby.
Taylor!
Can someone help here,please?
his seizure lasted about a minute,
and he was post-ictal for five.
- Is the baby okay?
- He's fine.
It shouldn't interfere with his surgery,assuming we're still going forward.
Honey?
Yeah.
I guess we don't have any other choice.
All right,leanne,I'm gonna do everything I can,okay?
It's not gonna be a walk in the park,but I'm gonna take care of him.
okay.
Hey,izzie.
You done with the chief?
Not yet.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
- What are you guys doing?
- Uh,she's dating everyone with a pulse,and,uh,
I'm trying to get burke out of the beljar.
Crap.I'm late for finn.
Gotta go.
- You're sure you're okay?
- Yeah.
she's playing the field,and I've got a wife.
Point to the justice.
Here's the thing--
we've both really enjoyed each other,
b-before and now again,and--
and I think that's a healthy release.
I mean,I-I think it's--
it's healthy,I mean,for everybody involved.
And,um--
but I do think that just because I made
what can only be considered a transcontinental...
booty call...
doesn't mean that we should be trying to make something out of this.
I mean,we-- we--
stop doing that!
- Why?
- Because I can't think.
- We're good together.
- We aren't. You have to go home.
- Come back with me.
- You're insane.
I'm not going back--
I'm not going back to new york.
'Cause it was just about sex?
Okay.
Uh,well...
- good-bye.
- Good-bye.
Stevens was supposed to bein my office at 9:30.
Didn't show.
Did you two change your minds?
No,she said she was coming in.
I'm sure she'll track you down.
We nto run a C.T.
On this kid's abdomen.
This superhero stuff's way out of hand.
It's all right if she thinks she's a superhero.
I believed in santa claus till I was 11.
Really?
Did santa ever hit you in the gut with a basebalbat?
Hey,lab's good?
Yeah,they're all clear.
so why does a guy have four ortho surgeries in one year?
Because he's a serious athlete.
His body takes a beating.
Maybe his body can't handle it.
Do you know how many triathlons the guy's done?
Right,he's 55.
Do you think an ankle replacement and 26 miles a day is still a good idea?
Um,what,do you think we should fit him for a walker?
He's pounding the crap out of his joints,
and he's asking you to clean it up.
Do you know how many hips I replace because people
can't be bothered to walk around the block once a month?
Sometimes,we can make dreams come true.
It's not all the often.
When we can,we should.
Don't you think?
Yeah,yeah.
George,don't worry about it.
Hey,I was gonna go home for lunch.
You wanna come?
Callie just called my house "home."
- Where does she get that?
- Shh.
It is not her home.
What are you doing?
Meredith and finn.
50 dn on whether shepherd shows up to challenge finn to a duel.
Oh,can I be,uh,with 5?
That's not a bet.
That's milk money,dude.
oh,and she's laughing because he made
a joke which probably wasn't funny.
"oh,you funny vet."
I left the rest of my cash at home,
which I can call it because I live there.
I'm not a visitor.
Hey,you're a loser.
You like comic books,right?
No.
I got this kid,this patient.
She thinks she's a superhero.
- What's up with that?
- Superhero?
Well,superheroes look like anyone,like you or me.
Maybe they're not someone that people necessarily
notice as extraordinary,maybe in their daily life,
they get walked on,but then there's a moment--
they get hit by a cosmic ray or bitten by a radioactive spider,
and then suddenly,something that has been inside them all this time,
lying dormant,comes raging out--
dude,forget I asked.
Oh,here we go.
Here we go.Okay.
Come on,come on,come on.
takes it like a man...
and walks away.
- Thank you.43...
- he's comin' back.
Oh,yeah.
Oh,yes,he is.
Give me my money,mary jane.
Let it go.
Oh,god.
I'm so sorry about this.
- What?
- Hi.
- You're having lunch?
- In fact,we are.
Oh,it looks good.You know,I'm sorry to interrupt,
but I'm doing a corpus callosotomy.
- Thought you might like to scrub in.
- Are you serious?
- When?
- I'm gonna guess now.
Look,if you're busy,don't bother,but,you know,
it's not something that happens every day.
He's cutting a man's brain in half.
I'm sorry.
I'm an intern and...
I have a lot to learn.
Apparent so do I.
It's okay.
Oh,shoot.
- I'll call you tonight.
- Oh,you're busy tonight.She has a date.
- I'm sorry,finn.
- It's okay.Go.
Take care.
- I think I owe you another 50.
- Yeah,I think you do.
Coming or going?
I don't know.
Me neither.
That was brilliant,really.
I thought so,yes.
It wasn't because now I owe finn another date.
That's okay.
He needs all the help he can get.
This isn't gonna be easy for him.
Oh,you think he can't take the heat?
I think he's out of his league.
But you gotta hand it to the guy for trying.
This is Mr. Tresselt.
Prep him.
I thought you said we were operating.
We orate at 4:00.
I'm not just gon slide you into the O.R.
You gotta work a little,too,right?
How much is this gonna cost my parents?
That's not something you need to be worrying about.
But this is so stupid.
I'm fine.
Hey,pun me in the stomach,right here.
Stop telling people to punch you in the stomach.
You need to lie down and not move.
Which of the superfriends can do that?
Hi,miranda.
You needed a consult?
Yeah.
Just waiting for a picture.
haven't seen you since you were sucking down martinis at joe'S.
Oh,yeah. That was just--
well,I'm-- I'm over that.
Good.
- We talked about,uh--
- a lot of things.
- And I remember--
- none of them.
- Is that for the best?
- I think so.
She came in for sutures,but she's a walking accident
and has got an off-the-charts pain threshold.
- I'm thinking--
- chronic insensitivity to pain,yeah.
I've seen it in babies.
It's usually diagnosed young.
But...
if she's been bounced around in the foster care system--
Dr. Bailey,what the hell is that?
Dr. Burke.
- Oh,o'malley,how are you?
- Good.How's your arm?
Good,good.
Slow.
P.T.,You know.
Yeah.
Well,uh,we all miss you around here.
You're missed.
Hey,o'malley.
Stevens is standing outside the hospital.
I am retracting the right hemisphere.
What do we want to avoid?
Grey?
We want to avoid retractors on the sagittal sinus.
That's right.
Why?
To prevent sinus thrombosis.
Excellent.
Saw Dr. Burke today.
He looked good.
Yeah,he looks great.
He was meeting with the chief.
- Working out the leave?
- The what?
His leave of absence.
His what?
you've been standing out here for a while.
For a while,I stood over there.
- Maybe u should sit down.
- I don't want to sit down.
- Maybe you should sit down anyway.
- Go inside,george.
Izzie,seriously this is--
I hate the bride thing.
I hate the pictures in the magazines of the girl with the veil
and the flowers that she's sniffing like it
never occurred to her to stick her nose in there
until there was a camera pointed at her.
I hate the idea of bridesmaids and the colors and
"does the bustle make my ass look bigger or smaller?"
I hate the whole thing,and i never wanted to be that girl.
That girl is stupid and shallow.
Why the hell is that girl's thoughts running through my head?
Izzie...
I'm going to do it,george.
I'm going to walk through those doors.
I just need to make sure that when I'm standing in front of the chief of surgery,
I am not thinking about my wedding dress.
And that's gonna take another minute.
And with surgery of this kind,
there's always risk of an infection if the bone is compromised--
blah,blah,blah,I could die on the table.
Where do I sign?
I think we should talk through the rest of this consent form first.
Fourth surgery in a year--
I know the routine.
When I come back in for my hip,you can give me the speech in french.
- You're having hip surgery?
- In the fall,after patagonia.
Do you still want to meet your guy?
Megan's bleeding internally.
what?
It appears there's some severe trauma to her abdomen.
If you're trying to ask us if we hit her,
we've said ten times and in ten different ways--
social services cleared you,
and I'm sorry that we suggested you were mistreating her.
But she's hurt pretty badly,so we're gonna need to operate.
Oh,my god.
megan may have a chromosomal condition that
causes her to not feel any pain when she's injured.
It would explain why she gets hurt so often.
We need to do some genetic testing before we can be sure,
but let's assume she'll need to be monitored very closely from now on.
We got O.R. Three.
So surgery is the only option?
I think it is.
I-I know you've been put through the wringer already today,
but I need to ask you to trust me on this one.
Where is she?
Where's megan?
She's over...
hey,a leave of absence?
Yeah,I'm on my way home.
I was just making some notes for the chief
so he can reassign my open cases.
Because you're taking a leave of absence?
Okay,that's,like,what,a week?
As long as it takes.
Well,it's not gonna take that long.
You're already three weeks into P.T.
Already,so--
come on,recovery from brachial plexus surgery
is measured in months,cristina,years,not weeks.
The surgery's considered a success when the patient can flex the elbow.
Some patients never move their shoulder again.
Some don't recover sensation,
they don't recover dexterity,they simply don't recover.
Yes,but you are not one of those.
Really?
Says who?
Thanks,carl.
That's my guy?
No,that's not him.
That's someone else we lost last night.
He came in for lipo.
He died on the table.
Complications.
Didn't know they did liposuction on men.
People do a lot of stuff they don't need.
And,uh,the older you get,it's,uh...
here he is.
That's your guy.
That can't be my guy.
He's really old.
His bones are probably brittle.
What are they doing using a guy that old as my donor?
He's two years younger than you are.
What the hell happened to my ankle allograft?
I had O.R. 2 at 3:00.
Anybody wanna tell me ere it went?
It was canceled.
The guy went home.
Why the hell would he do that?
- Hey!
- O'malley!
We've lost supergirl,and she's bleeding into her abdomen.
Start looking in cners.
Do you think you cut enough of the fibers out
or are you gonna have to go back in?
We'll see if the seizures are under control.
If not,we'll go back in for the last third.
Well,do I get to scrub in on that,too,or only
if I'm in the middle of a date with somebody else?
I wodn't consider a meal in the cafeteria a date.
Don't denigrate the competition.
I have nothing but respect for Dr. Dandridge.
It shows courage to woo a woman with a tuna salad.
Keep an eye on taylor.
If there's a problem,page me.
I'll see you in the lobby at 8:00.
Hey,grey,I lost a kid.
Help me look for her before she bleeds out in one of our bathrooms.
- What's her name?
- Megan!
It's not easy.
If you think you're a superhero,
you're not gonna let someone come at you with a knife.
There's no way to tell what it can do to your powers.
I mean,if you take away green lantern's ring,
hal jordan is still a hero,but it creates a crisis of confidence...
- come on,megan.
- When you've worked hard to hone your strength.
Hey,just look at,uh,batman.
Robin just marches into the batcave,
and he says,you know,
"here I am.I'm gonna live here,too.
Give me some tights,and I'm taking your towel."
I mean,batman,he fought for his powers,you know?
He honed his strength.
Dude,if you don't stop this,
I'm gonna punch you in the face.
O'malley.
Good luck with that.
I arrange for you to see an incredibly cool surgery,
and you talk my patient out of it?
- No,I didn't--
- you asked me what I thought,
you didn't like what I said,so you went behind my back.
Jasper's gone.He canceled the surgery.
I expressed an opinion.I suggested that,you know,
not everything has to go at warp speed.
It is all warp speed with you.
It is all,"oh,your ankle hurts? Let's cut if off."
You intimidated my patient.
You got a problem,you bring it to me.
I'm not ready for us to move in together.
And if you weren't toddler,if you could use your words,
then maybe you could've said that the first four times I asked you.
And then I would've said,"oh,that's funny,me neither.
I'm looking for a place.I'll be out in a week."
Really?
- Because remember,you--
- george,save it.I'll be--
I'll be out in an hour.
Megan.
Hi.
Weren't you just up on three?
I was.
We lost a patient,a little girl,and I was just--
look,why don't you pick a floor and stay on it,
and I'll pick a floor on stay on that?
Because I really need a moment or two without you.
Your face shows up in my head,your...
panties show up in my husband's pocket--
really,you're everywhere--
and I need a moment or two without you.
I get that.
Thanks.
megan.
Come on.
Enough already.
We got half the hospital looking for you.
Your powers of invisibility are well intact.
Get up.
You're a hosebag,you know that?
- And you have a potty mouth.
- Nobody's cutting me open.
Hey,it's surgery.
We do it all the time.
In fact,it's all we do.
You can't keep telling my foster parents I'm defective.
They can't afford surgery.
It's too expensive.
They can handle it.
They'll send me back.
Dude,that's stupid.
They got their own personal superhero.
Nobody sends back a superhero.
I thought you said I didn't have superpowers?
Yeah,well,you don't.
But take away green lantern's ring,
the guy's still a hero,right?
Okay.
Close your eyes.
Squeeze 'em tight.
Good. Okay.
Can you squeeze my fingers?
Fantastic.
Let's wiggle your toes for me,please.
Very good,vy good.
Flying colors.
He's always tested well.
I kicked ass on the,uh...
what--
what's it called?
The S.A.T.S.
Now can you tell me,whatthis?
Honey?
Take your time.
Honey,what's that called?
It's right in front of you.
Can you see this here?
I can see it.
I-I just can't think of the...
that's all right.
It's okay. Take your time.
See,sometimes the names of things are tough.
So try again.
What's my name?
I can't...
wh-what's his name?
I-I know what it is.
I-I-I just...
- what's his name?
- Leanne,let's just give him a moment.
It...
what's his name?
I...
he named the baby. He named him after his father.
How do you not know the name of your own baby?
Well,he knows who the baby is.
See,the right side of the brain senses emotional connection to the baby.
It just can't communicate with the left brain where the words are formed.
The pathway to the two sides has been compromised.
He needs to make new pathways.
How long is that gonna take?
Well,he'll get there.
Recovery is hardork.
It's a learning process.
You need to be patient.
You need to help him.
he can't do this without your support.
man,she wasn't kidding about the baseball bat.
I need more lap pads.
Just keep 'em coming.
Are you gonna resect the liver?
I need to try and do a debridement.
Look at this.
Everybody wants a life without pain,d what does it get you?
She needs to be on a poster somewhere
to remind people pain's there for a reason.
Megan's stable.
I ordered a repeat h&h in two hours.
She been outhere all day?
Dinner was good.
Dinner was excellent.
- Are you coming in?
- I don't know.
Am I?
Well,you could come in for a drink or a-a coffee.
I owe you one from this morning.
Yeah,you do.
hi.
Finn.
I didn't think you guys would be here.
I just wantedto drop this off.
It's strawberry ice cream.
A patient made it for me.
Patient's owner.
It's made from scratch.
Real strawberries.
I love strawberry ice cream.
- And he remembered.
- I did.
I just thought I'd leave it by the door.
- Oh,you didn't think it would melt?
- No,you take your chances.
- Worked out for you.
- What exactly is going on here?
- He's crashing our date.
- Where do you think I got that idea?
I didn't crash your date.
It was professional.
- You can't operate without her?
- I certainly operate well with her.
Enough.
This is not dating.
I want moonlight and flowers and candy
and people trying to feel me up.
Nobody is trying to feel me up.
Nobody is even looking at m I'm an intern.
Do the two of you have any idea
how much effort it takes to do all this?
I'm waxed and plucked,and I have a clean top on.
And the two of you are looking at each other.
- Meredith,it's--
- no!
- My fantasy is not two men looking at each other.
- We didn't--
no talking until one of you figures out how to put on a date.
I want heat,I want romance.
Damn it,I wanna feel like a freakin' lady!
The fantasy is simple...
pleasure is good...
I'm in room 22-something--
2214.
- If anyone calls,I'm not here.
- Yes,ma'am.
And twice as much pleasure is better...
hi.
Checking in,please.
certainly.
Room for...
one.
That pain is bad...
room 1817.
Any messages?
And no pain is better.
Checking in,please.
Room for one.
Something on the 22nd floor if you've got it.
I'll take a look.
Dr. Sloan?
Dr. Webber.
What are you doing in seattle?
I don't know.
I have a thing for ferry boats.
But the reality is different.
- Are you cooking for me?
- I am not.
You can take a leave of absence if you want to,
but you're not gonna sit on your ass all day.
You're gonna work hard and you're gonna get
every bit of your strength and dexterity back.
Really?
How?
Put it back together.
The reality is that pain is there to tell us something.
- Iz.
- I'll do it.
- Izzie.
- I can do it,alex.
I know I can.
does it hurt?
Yeah.
Where does it hurt?
Everywhere.
Maybe it hurts for a reason.
Come on.
Let's go.
And there's only so much pleasure we can take
without getting a stomachache.
And maybe that's okay.
Hey.
I didn't go in today.
Maybe tomorrow.
Hey,george.
Callie moved out,which is a relief.
Oh,I am so relieved.
Strawberry.
It's good.
You left spit on the spoon.
- No,I didn't.
- You did,a little.
Maybe some fantasies are only supposed to live in our dreams.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:YTET-gagegao
Greys Anatomy
Season 03 Episode 03