Gratitude.
Appreciation.
Giving thanks.
No matter what words you use,
it all means the same thing.
Happy.
We're supposed to be happy.
Grateful for friends, family,
happy to just be alive...
Hey!
... whether we like it or not.
What are you doing?
Answering the door.
- You're going to the hospital?
- Yes, but...
Everyone is supposed to
help me make dinner. It's Thanksgiving!
I'm really not in the mood.
- But it's like a family...
- Doorbell.
- This where Georgie lives?
- Georgie?
- O'Malley. Where is he, upstairs?
- Oh. George. Yeah.
O'Malley!
O- Mal-ley! O-Mal-ley!
- Should I call the police?
- O'Malley!
Meredith! I'm serious! You need to be
back here for dinner at 6:00! I mean it!
Five... four... three... two...
Happy Thanksgiving!
Hey, you.
I saw you from the window and...
Looked like you could use
a wake up call.
I thought you moved to a hotel
closer to the hospital.
You still at Bainbridge?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah,
I had a thing for ferryboats.
Always with the mocking.
So, I was thinking that we could...
have sex tonight.
Yeah.
Look, I know we're both
going to feel weird about it.
- And it's the first time...
- Since Mark?
And Meredith.
I have the day off.
Do you have the day off?
Just stop by the hospital,
I have patients I need to check on.
If you have the day off,
what are you doing here?
Was thinking we could have sex tonight.
I made a reservation at noon,
I figure we can do Thanksgiving,
and then, I don't know,
just rip the stitches, get it over with.
No anesthesia?
Right. What do you think?
Remember med school?
We spent Thanksgiving studying
and eating really bad Chinese food
instead of turkey.
Too busy and too tired
to even think about cooking.
We never had to schedule sex.
Not once.
Derek, I want get through this. I do.
I want things to be normal again.
So will you meet me at noon?
Yeah, OK. I'll see you at noon.
Grey. We're working with
a temp attending today, Dr. Kent.
He's subbing in from Mercy West.
We need to get him oriented.
Thank you for volunteering to come in.
Saved me from having to choose
an intern to torture.
Happy to be tortured.
Not a fan of Thanksgiving?
Not a whole hell of a lot
to be thankful for.
I like Thanksgiving. It's a day
people spend with their families.
Too much family time
triggers depression,
repressed childhood rage,
bitter disputes over the remote
and way too much alcohol.
People get stupid,
people get violent, people get hurt.
- And that's a good thing because...
- Surgeries, Grey.
- Lots and lots of surgeries.
- I never thought of that.
The stupidity of the human race, Grey.
Be thankful for that.
- You're supposed to be at home.
- So are you.
Best maze procedure I've ever done.
- Under an hour.
- I thought you had the day off.
I did. I do. I'm leaving.
I simply like to start my day cutting,
gives me a rush.
Admit it. You can't function
ten feet away from the hospital.
- I notice you're both here.
- Well, I'm here for an hour.
- I'm on my way home.
- Ah. Say it like you mean it.
I know how to have a life
outside this hospital.
Damn right you do.
- Dr. Kent?
- Yes?
I'm the surgical resident
assisting you today.
I know you're subbing in from Mercy
West, so if there's anything I can do...
I'm here one day.
I don't need my ass kissed.
I'll just tell you what to do,
and you do it. I don't like mistakes.
- I don't make mistakes.
- Whatever.
There's only one resident I want in
my OR. Guy they call the Nazi. Know him?
The Nazi?
Gets great word of mouth. Stellar rep.
Balls the size of Texas.
That big?
Sounds like an
impressively talented man, this Nazi.
- Do you know him or not?
- Never heard of him.
- But I'll keep an eye out.
- For now, work on smaller cases.
A guy just came in to curtain three.
Page me if you get confused.
I'll be sure to do that.
Like I said,
the stupidity of the human race.
Hurry up, Georgie. There's a turkey
out there with your name on it.
Whoa! Hey!
Hey, where are you going?
Where are you going?
Every year, my father, my brothers and I
hunt, shoot and kill a helpless turkey.
Isn't that great?
- O'Malley!
- What about dinner?
We'll have him back
as soon as he kills his first bird.
This is the year Georgie
becomes a man. Right, Georgie?
I can't make dinner myself.
Who's going to help me?
Holden McKee.
Brought in from Mayfield Nursing Home.
Mayfield? He's in the garden?
- Garden?
- Vegetable.
His chart says he fell into a persistent
vegetative state 16 years ago.
He was a firefighter injured
by falling debris in the line of duty.
What brings him here?
Fell from his bed
while being turned by orderlies.
Insurance says
he has to be checked out.
Temporoparietal scalp lac
with associated hematoma.
What's your plan?
Irrigate and explore the wound.
Repair the lac.
A CT to rule out intra-cerebral
hemorrhage, contusion or cerebral edema.
Go to it. If anybody asks,
I'm off looking for the Nazi.
OK.
It's just me and you.
I'd give anything
for your kind of serenity.
Great. Now I'm jealous of vegetables.
You just look so peaceful.
Dr. Bailey.
This guy's got third-degree burns
over half his body.
Tried to deep-fry a turkey.
Course, he got drunk first.
Gonna be good. You want in?
My PVS case? He opened his eyes.
And I think he was looking at me.
- He wasn't looking at you.
- No, he was.
- Anything good?
- Uh...
Nothing you want to waste time on.
There are 13 patients that need sutures.
She's the intern.
She can do the sutures.
Actually, she's on her way to CT
with a VIP patient.
- On orders from the Nazi.
- Tell him I'm looking for him.
The burn unit is waiting for him.
I'll meet in the OR.
Grey, get a CT, have neuro consult.
But trust me, he wasn't looking at you.
Don't mention Shepherd.
Or Montgomery-Shepherd.
Or the fact that Shepherd
is with Montgomery-Shepherd.
- OK.
- Or anything to do with syphilis.
- I've been in social situations before.
- Yeah, well, not with me.
Well, why are we here?
Just be nice or something.
It's half-past ten. You're late.
I've had to try to do all this...
Oh. Hi, Dr. Burke. Hello.
Oh.
What was I supposed to do?
Blow off my boyfriend for Thanksgiving?
I tried to.
He wouldn't blow.
He's like something sticky
that won't blow off.
OK, he's going to ruin Thanksgiving.
What can I talk to Dr. Burke about?
People who are shocked when
I show up uninvited call me Preston.
- Nobody calls you Preston.
- You don't call me Preston.
- Nice house.
- Yeah.
Izzie, why is it so quiet in here?
Meredith went to the hospital and
George is off shooting with his family.
So it's just me, you and Preston?
- And Alex. When he shows up.
- Oh, great!
Hey, Alex? It's me.
Where are you? OK, call me back.
- Is something burning?
- Oh! God, yes!
- Hey, Chief!
- I'm on my way home.
Yeah, me too. I was supposed
to meet Addison 20 minutes ago.
Dr. Shepherd. You're leaving?
- I'm also going home.
- Then go home.
Adele's sister's in town.
I hate that woman.
The OR Board needs
to be checked one more time.
It does, doesn't it? Excuse me.
I didn't think you'd be here today.
Yeah, well, I need a neuro consult.
Holden McKee. PVS 16 years.
There's no bleed,
there's no mass, no fracture.
He can be discharged.
Well, he opened his eyes
when I was examining him.
- He opened his eyes.
- Certain reflexes are preserved.
- There's arousal but no awareness.
- He was looking at me.
- He wasn't looking at you.
- He was.
The CT report says he wasn't.
- Do you want to argue with what I saw?
- No.
I don't want to argue with you anymore.
I gotta go, I'm late.
He was looking at you?
So, how are you?
I'm fine. How are you?
- Fine.
- Good.
Me and you are in this weird limbo.
This is gonna go on forever, isn't it?
I hope not, but I think so.
- Yeah, me too.
- Yeah.
I moved Holden to a room on 4, so...
- You lead, I'll follow.
- OK.
Sixty-five GTO.
Fifty-seven Bel Air convertible.
Two door.
The GT 500. That was a car.
- It was.
- Georgie! Pick a car. Come on!
You do realize that you can buy a turkey
at the market.
They got hundreds of them. You know,
all wrapped. They're ready to go.
No ammo required.
You'll shoot the turkey today,
I can feel it.
That's the thing.
I don't want to shoot the turkey.
You say that every year.
Well, and every year
I don't shoot the turkey.
- What is that?
- It was supposed to be my marinade.
Alex? It's me, again.
Just wondering where you're at?
You've never made
a Thanksgiving dinner before.
You can't cook? Izzie.
Well, I'm a baker. I bake. I've seen
my grandmother cook a million times.
If there's no food, I'm going home.
Cristina. I have this.
What is your reference text?
The Joy of Cooking. I also printed
some recipes from the Internet
but they contradict one another.
I can't figure out which side is the top
and which is the bottom.
OK. OK.
Um...
I'm going to need a basting brush,
a bowl, a clove of garlic, and...
- Do you have any fennel?
- Um... Yeah, right here.
OK. Well, let's get this turkey
up and running, Stevens.
- Garlic.
I'm going to need liquor.
Lots and lots of liquor.
There's no sustained visual pursuit.
You might have just seen him respond
to some sort of external stimuli.
He wasn't looking at you, I'm sorry.
I was sure he was.
Look, he just did it again.
Mr. McKee. Can you follow the light?
Can you hold up two fingers?
OK, well, I know
you're late for something, so...
- Keep talking.
- What?
Walk over here.
Just keep walking. Talk.
Holden? Holden?
Holden, can you hear me?
Holden?
It's you he's tracking,
he was following your voice.
Well, that's why there's no mention
of brain atrophy in the CT report.
- Because there isn't any.
- None? He's been PVS for 16 years.
Well, he's not PVS.
He's minimally conscious.
He's minimally conscious
and no one noticed?
Even in a state-of-the-art neural
facility they'd have tested him but...
- The regular nursing home just...
- Missed it.
He's been frozen, sleeping,
for 16 years, and they missed it.
That sucks.
There's one thing to be thankful for.
- What?
- We might be able to wake him up.
Alex? It's Izzie. If you're not coming,
you could at least call and tell me.
- I'm in hell.
-  I'm the one in hell.
Burke's going all Iron Chef.
Get your ass back here and save me.
I'm in the woods.
With shotguns and car talk.
- It's like Deliverance.
- Let's break!
- One-two-three chug!
- At least you have liquor.
- Where does Meredith keep the booze?
- I don't think she has any.
How is that possible? She's a WASP.
Liquor is like oxygen to a WASP.
Which is why we're out of liquor.
Can you come and get me?
OK, how am I supposed to get through
the holidays without liquor?
Just come and get me.
Hell... Cristi...
"You can't handle the truth!"
Selfish!
Derek, it's me.
Where are you?
- Which one do you think she is?
- Holden's wife?
Yeah.
It's her.
How do you know?
Mrs. McKee?
It's Mrs. Leonard now.
What do you mean "wake him up"?
Over the years your husband's brain
has been slowly trying to heal itself.
And we've given him
a course of amphetamine
that should give his brain
a push toward consciousness.
When? How long does it take?
If we're right, your father
will be awake in a few hours.
Is he going to realize what happened?
Most patients in this situation have
no idea how much time has passed.
- Oh, my God.
- I'm going to be sick.
- I know it's a difficult situation...
- I just got married.
We're having a baby in December
and Coby turned 17 on Thursday.
- Difficult? This is unimaginable.
- Perhaps you should sit...
I can't be here when he wakes up.
He can't see me like this. Or Coby.
Coby, baby, we're leaving.
We'll be in the car.
Mrs. Leonard.
Holden is going to wake up
and find out we didn't wait for him.
He's a good person.
How could you do this to him?
You should get her back.
I'll try, but I don't know.
Took her a long time to move on.
We did the right thing.
Medically, Holden's our patient
and we treated him.
I'm sure he'll thank us later.
Meredith, it's...
Did you see that kid's face?
Holden is a complete stranger to him.
- Cases like this are...
- It's not cases like this.
It's this one case.
You don't get it.
You have a life.
You go to sleep, you wake up
and that life doesn't exist anymore?
That man has no one.
Everyone's moved on.
Except for him.
It's not an easy thing.
I'm sorry.
I know.
What are you doing up here?
Go to the pit. We're backed up.
No can do, sir.
The Nazi has me on this surgery.
We've got a line out the door
for sutures.
Everybody's an amateur chef
until they use a knife.
Knives can be tricky.
Your wife know you're working today?
I'm going home.
I just wanted to watch a bit.
Well, don't stay here too long.
You could end up like him.
Wife stabbed him.
Said she didn't like the way
he was carving the turkey.
Ouch.
- Happy Thanksgiving!
- Joe! Thank God.
Hey, this is my boyfriend, Walter.
- Whatever. Tell me you brought liquor.
- I brought pie. Pumpkin.
You're a bartender.
Did you bring scalpels?
- Come on. Pick a car.
- I don't want to pick a car.
- He doesn't know jack about cars.
- I do. I just don't want to pick one.
Georgie's tired. They working you
too hard at the hospital?
You know, he works 48-hour shifts.
- 48 hours and you enjoy it?
- Yeah, I enjoy it.
- Like, what do you do?
- You know, medical stuff.
- Come on.
- They're not going to get it.
Make your brothers jealous. Tell them
what it's like to be a big-time surgeon.
Come on!
OK. Last night, this was pretty cool.
- I assisted on a truncal vagotomy and...
- Assisted?
- Well, what do you mean?
- I helped a surgeon.
- Anyway, we inflated...
- Wait, I thought you were the surgeon.
I'm a surgical intern. The resident or
the attending, they perform the surgery.
So you don't actually cut anybody open.
I mean, by yourself?
No.
Do you hand the surgeon
stuff that he needs?
Scalpels?
That's a scrub nurse.
Georgie does that thing with
the gas that puts the patient to sleep.
That's an anesthesiologist.
Do you like take the patient to surgery?
Um... orderly.
No, like, the point of being an intern
is that you're learning.
We watch the surgeries.
The attending asks us questions.
And we have to answer them.
It's not easy.
I have to be on top of my game 100%%
of the time. It's incredibly difficult.
So you don't actually do anything.
- Yes, I do.
- You just stand there.
- I assist...
- Watching the real doctors.
- I am a real doctor! Dad!
- You said you don't do anything.
No, I didn't!
You said I didn't do anything.
Real doctors save lives.
If you're just standing there...
Oh, for God...
What?
I want to go home.
Just as soon as you shoot your turkey.
- What are you doing here?
- Waiting for my patient to wake.
Why aren't you at the Thanksgiving?
Why aren't you at Thanksgiving?
What?
I tell you something,
you tell me something.
OK.
I feel like one of those people
who's so freaking miserable
they can't be around normal people.
Like I'll infect the happy people.
Like I'm some miserable, diseased,
dirty ex-mistress.
Your turn.
I failed the medical boards.
If I tell Izzie, she'll be nice
about it, all supportive and optimistic.
She might as well rip my nads off
and turn 'em into earrings.
Alex, you should go to Thanksgiving.
I mean, don't tell her
if you don't want to.
But you should go.
Otherwise you're just... me.
A miserable, diseased,
dirty ex-mistress?
That's hot. That's really hot.
- I feel better already.
- See?
Happy Thanksgiving.
Hello? Is somebody there?
Somebody?
Yes. Somebody's here.
Your muscles have suffered deterioration
and your joints will be painful,
which is to be expected.
The fact that your communication skills
are still intact is remarkable.
Did you reach my wife yet?
I mean, is she coming?
I mean, have you told her
or do you wait until she gets here?
Because this is going to be
quite a shock.
How long have I been out?
- A year?
- Would you excuse us?
Yes, doctor.
No, you tell me. Please.
You found me. You tell me.
I'm only an intern.
I've never really done this before.
Me either.
You'll do it quickly.
Rip off the bandage.
Mm. No anesthesia.
Exactly.
Mm.
I'll be right outside if you need me.
Truth time.
How bad is this truth gonna be?
It's bad, Holden.
You have to cut the celery
into finer pieces, Stevens.
Like that?
- It'll do. Put them in with the onions.
- OK.
Now, what should you be
concerned about?
Um...
The turkey, Stevens.
I expect you to know that.
Right. I need to check the turkey
to make sure it's cooking
at the correct temperature.
- And how do we do that?
- Meat thermometer.
Ten bucks says she dries out the turkey.
- 20 says she pulls it off.
- 75 says I don't care.
OK, Stevens.
Let's see what you can do.
All right. More pressure.
Turkey has a tough shell. Dig in.
- I'm in.
- Damn. She got it in.
- Told you she'll pull it off.
- Not bad.
All you have to do now is get the
thermometer deep enough in the bird.
- But be careful not to...
- Oh!
You hit the bone.
The pan is filling with juice and you're
losing moisture. What do you do?
- Think!
- That's it. I'm out of here.
- What's the problem?
- You're operating on a turkey.
And... And you're making friends
with my friends.
Shh. You told me to be nice.
It will be nice.
I'm just going to go to the store
and get some liquor.
Can I have the keys, please?
I'll be back.
- Dr. Burke!
- Suction! Use the baster and suction!
The GT 500 was a Shelby.
He also made the Viper, you know that?
- Yes. We do know.
- Shelby 500. A good car.
Yeah.
- And the other car he made is...
- Turkey.
Turkey.
Jerry. We came out here
so I could shoot a turkey.
Dad said we're not leaving
until I shoot a turkey.
I am shooting this turkey.
When you're sure
you've got it, squeeze.
No fair. I called turkey.
Don't worry, he's going to chicken out.
Yahoo!
- You got it!
- I got it?
You got it, Georgie!
Let's go home!
What's he like? My son.
You know, I didn't really get
a chance to speak with him.
But he seemed nice.
He's tall like you.
And he's got your eyes.
That...
That's good.
- Holden, we're ready to begin.
- What does the MRI do?
Just gives us a better picture
of your brain, really.
You're one for the books, you know.
That's nice.
If you're ready.
When I went down into that fire...
we were going on vacation the next day.
Taking the baby to see my mom.
She was so excited.
I tried to call my mom today.
But, um...
She's dead now.
My mother's been dead for eight years.
I'm ready.
OK.
- How's he doing?
- As well as we could expect.
Damn it.
An epidural hematoma.
When you fell out of your bed
this morning, you hit your temple. Hard.
The CT didn't catch it, but the MRI did.
- And you can fix it?
- Won't be easy.
Sometimes it's impossible to find
the vessel and complications can arise,
but, yes, I can operate.
Well, so there is a risk?
Very large risk, yes.
And what happens if you don't operate?
The best-case scenario
is that the bleeding resolves itself.
Or it can continue to bleed
and cause the brain to swell.
Which means what?
Most likely,
without the operation, you'll die.
But the operation could kill me, too.
Right?
There are equal risks both ways.
What do I do?
What would you do?
I can't answer this for you.
Can I have that spatula, please?
Thank you.
You want the butter to melt,
not to boil.
Dr. Burke, how did you
learn to cook like this?
My mother owns a restaurant in Alabama.
- Seriously?
- Seriously.
Does Cristina know that?
No. Actually, she doesn't.
She doesn't ask
a lot of personal questions.
- She's kind of hard to get to know.
- Yes. She is.
- Karev didn't show?
- No. He didn't.
Is that OK?
No. It's not.
Do you know that there's
absolutely no liquor in this house?
- Yeah, Cristina went to get some.
- Over an hour ago. Where is she?
Dr. Yang?
Um... Yes?
Have you seen my husband?
No, I have not.
Do you know where he is?
No, I do not.
He was supposed to meet me hours ago.
- I'm not here.
- Neither am I.
Any available IV nurse to the ER.
- Levi Johnson!
- Yes.
- You swallowed a wishbone?
Excellent.
We'll have to take some films.
Maybe you ruptured your esophagus.
That means surgery.
I don't believe this.
Car's loaded! Guys! Coolers, come on.
Get up.
Dad! Come on.
Hold on, Georgie. We got to blood you.
Oh, no.
Now there you go.
Now you're officially an O'Malley man.
O'Malley!
I left my hat.
Guys! Get in... Just get in the car.
- O'Malley!
- Twenty-one gun salute for Georgie!
That's not the best idea, guys.
I'm serious. Don't!
Ow!
You shot Dad in the ass!
Are you happy now?
It's like laser tag.
- Not in the eyes.
- Guys! This is the trauma room.
What are you doing?
Put it down.
Dad, I'm going to inject you
to numb the area.
I'm fine. I don't need anything.
It doesn't even hurt that bad.
Dad. You have birdshot
embedded in your gluteus maximus.
When I start removing it, believe me,
it's going to hurt very bad.
Hey, '65 GTO.
That's a V8 tweaker.
You don't want that.
You want the Bel Air.
- But it's gotta be the two-tone. Right?
- Nice.
- Pick a car, Georgie.
- No, thanks.
Come on, pick a car.
He doesn't know jack about
cars. He doesn't know jack about jack.
Jerry, first you say the GTO.
Ronny counters with the Bel Air, which
never fails to make Dad say the GT 500.
The Cobra, the Chieftan,
then a German car,
which then starts
the American-versus-foreign debate
that ends when one of you
brings up the DeVille.
And that always, always leads
to the unbelievably long discussion
on the merits of the '57 Thunderbird.
So how about I jump to the end
and name the Thunderbird now
so once in our lives we can stop
picking cars! And my name is George!
What do you know. The kid came back.
No, he didn't.
He says we have the same eyes.
Yeah.
I don't see it.
He said that he couldn't stay.
Because of the holiday.
But he said he'll come back
some time soon.
Good.
Yeah.
He said she's happy.
That this guy, Hal,
is really good for her.
She loves him.
So I've decided to
go ahead with the surgery.
They've moved on. I should too.
Now get this thing out of my head
and let me get on with my life.
Right.
I'll tell Dr. Shepherd.
- Dr. Grey.
- Yeah?
Do you think he really will come back?
I hope so.
Joe and Walter have got the table set up
in the living room. How's our bird?
He needs a few more hours.
Why did you plan this big dinner
if you knew you couldn't cook?
I just like Thanksgiving, Dr. Burke.
Preston.
You just like Thanksgiving?
Doctor-patient confidentiality?
- Doctor-patient confidentiality.
- OK.
We work 18 hours a day, six days a week,
50 weeks a year.
We don't really have any time
for our families.
We don't have friends
that aren't doctors.
But we have this one day
where we don't have to cut anyone open.
One day where we get to be
like everybody else.
One day to be normal.
A day where nobody lives
and nobody dies on our watch.
It's like a gift.
So I just thought
we should appreciate it, that's all.
I gotta set the table.
A day without surgery.
Who swallows a wishbone whole?
Dr. Bailey,
why are you working on Thanksgiving?
You work the extra shifts
and get the extra practice.
I'm trying to get in
all the practice I can...
before the baby comes
and I have to take time off.
My husband isn't thrilled
I'm working Thanksgiving,
but he isn't a surgeon
so he doesn't get it.
Oh.
You and Dr. Burke?
Yeah.
He would have made a good father.
They said the Nazi was in here.
He was, but he left.
I think he went down to the pit.
Don't ask.
Hey.
- You coming?
- Not enough interns.
I got to cover the floor.
What would you have done if you
were him? Would you have the surgery?
You would have the surgery.
I would want the future.
Or to be asleep again.
One or the other.
Nothing in between.
I honestly don't know what I'd want.
I know you don't.
If you get a chance,
you can scrub in later.
I'm going to be at this a while.
- Thought you'd forgotten about me.
- No. Where are Ronny and Jerry?
A nurse told them
that the cafeteria was open.
Oh.
- You didn't have fun today.
- It's not that...
No.
No, I didn't have fun.
- You hurt your brothers' feelings.
- Dad!
- You did.
- They talk to me like I'm stupid.
They call me Georgie. They've never
treated me like I'm one of them.
George, Jerry is a dry cleaner,
Ronny works in a post office,
I drive a truck.
You're a surgeon. You're not one of us.
I know it. And they know it.
You make sure we know it.
- Dad...
- I'm not blaming you.
It makes me proud you're so smart.
Like I did something right.
It's just...
We try.
We try to include you.
But you don't like the stuff
that we like
and we don't know how to talk about
the stuff you wanna talk about.
You're not one of us.
But damn it,
we don't treat you like you're stupid.
You treat us like we're stupid.
And maybe we are, but we're your family.
Give us an inch, Georgie.
Every once in a while, pick a car.
I saved a guy's life
on an elevator last month.
I performed open-heart surgery
on him right there.
By yourself?
By myself.
Just like a real doctor.
Hm! That's something.
That's really something.
I'll take care of it.
What are you doing here?
Oh. This is beyond bad.
Sorry, Izzie, it's after eight.
Got to get to the bar.
- On Thanksgiving?
- It's one of our busiest days.
People need a haven from the bitterness,
Ioneliness, quality family time.
I'm their port in the storm.
See you later?
- Yeah.
- OK. Night, doc.
- Night, Joe.
- Bye, Walter, thanks for coming.
You can leave too if you want.
I'm not leaving the table
until the hostess does.
- They're not coming.
- Even so.
Today I committed bird murder
and I was forced to touch my Dad's ass.
I get extra points
for showing up at all.
I brought booze.
Let's just eat.
You know today in the waiting room.
How did you know Cheryl
was Holden's wife?
Waiting rooms are full of people
hoping for good news.
She was the only one who looked like
she'd completely given up.
Yeah.
Do you love her?
I don't know.
It's good that you're trying.
You wouldn't be you
if you weren't the kind of person
who's trying to make it work.
- You think so?
- Yeah.
It means I wasn't wrong about you.
Thanks.
Goodbye, Derek.
Bye, Meredith.
Maybe we're not supposed to be happy.
Maybe gratitude...
has nothing to do with joy.
Hey!
Hey.
You going inside?
- No. You go ahead.
- You sure?
Yeah. Go make her happy.
Yeah.
Maybe being grateful means recognizing
what you have for what it is.
Hi.
You're a surgical junkie. Go home.
Adele's already mad.
I'm in trouble no matter what.
And there's a Whipple happening
in OR two.
Go home right now!
This kind of treatment
is why they call you the Nazi.
- Appreciating small victories.
- Happy Thanksgiving.
I was nice.
Yeah. I noticed.
You don't ask
a lot of personal questions.
And you're very hard to get to know.
Yes.
My mother owns a restaurant in Alabama.
I scrubbed in on a foreign body removal
this afternoon.
A guy swallowed a wishbone whole.
Admiring the struggle it takes
simply to be human.
You didn't show.
So, um...
I bought Chinese food.
And I waited.
It was good.
Now it's lukewarm and old.
Which makes it just like the food
we used to have in medical school.
So...
Derek, are you done?
Hurting me back, I mean.
Because I need to know,
because if not...
I gotta special order a thicker skin.
Or something.
Maybe we're thankful
for the familiar things we know.
No anesthesia in sight.
Here we go.
And maybe we're thankful
for the things we'll never know.
Is this seat taken?
- Do you work at the hospital?
- No.
You're not a brain surgeon
or a doctor of any kind?
No.
Then this seat isn't taken.
At the end of the day, the fact that we
have the courage to still be standing...
Do you wanna buy me a drink?
Actually, I do.
... is reason enough to celebrate.
www.tvsubtitles.net