Previously on "Grey's anatomy"...
You're watching me sleep again?
It's just that
you snore a little.
Harold O'Malley, 63,
Scheduled for a transhiatal
esophagectomy tomorrow morning at 9:00.
I want you to take the tumor out.
As things progress with my dad, it would
help me if you were straight with me.
Okay.
So that's it?
We're closing him back up?
No.
- But I thought...
- The patient asked us to proceed.
You want to watch the kidneys
because if the kidneys fail, that's a sign
that everything else is starting to go.
130 ccs of shiny, yellow urine!
That is fantastic!
Heather Douglas, 17, past medical
history of vater syndrome.
I think I could significantly
help with the spinal curvature.
I get to scrub in.
Not till I say so.
I deposited the damn check.
Insurance bastards.
The surgery's
too experimental.
Looks like there won't be
a surgery to scrub in on.
Sorry, Stevens.
You don't get the high horse
this week, Addison.
Not this week.
Dr. Burke's hand...
has he had any tremors?
- Talk to him.
- No. 'Cause then he wins.
My father's here.
The one I don't talk to
and barely know?
He's here.
If you want to go back to plastics...
Nah.
All right!
Just shut it off, please!
Could you not snap at me?
I didn't sleep much.
Maybe that's because you were too busy
shoving me every five minutes.
I wasn't shoving you.
I was nudging you to stop the very loud
sawing of wood
I wore the nose strip.
Oh, it's cute, but it doesn't work.
Ow.
- What?
- You need to shave.
Izzie, uh...
The--the--the--the...
The check. The--it's not, uh,
It's--it's not--
Did you--did you-- did you drop here?
Here. Move, move, move. Did you--
not--it--it's not here.
Izzie, it's not here.
I deposited it, okay?
You didn't deposit it in the garbage
disposal or something like that, did you?
It's at the bank,
okay, George?
Now just shut up about it already.
It's at--it's at the bank?
It's--
- It's earning interest?
Did I not just say,
"shut up about it already"?
Izzie...
It's real now.
That money, it could--
The money could travel.
It could--it could buy things.
It could buy many, many things.
That's a--
- That's a lot of money, Izzie.
- Shut up about it, George.
I'm just saying--
I'm just saying,
life is short.
You know, it's like,
cancer happens and surgery happens,
and I--
You know, it's just... it's just...
"gather ye rosebuds"...
You know, you have
8.7 million rosebuds, Izzie.
You gotta spend some rosebuds.
That's what I'm saying.
You made me burn my french toast.
You can buy new french toast.
Oh.
Hey. Uh, I was, uh--
yeah, I was just, uh,
-  Just...
- The baby's doing...
Good. Yeah, she's good.
- Good. That's... That's good.
- Yeah.
- Doctors.
- Yes.
- What?
I was wondering, the baby looks...
Good.
- Yeah, she's good.
- She looks good.
- She is. She's, uh...
- She's good? She's out of the woods?
- She's good.
She is out of the woods. Her vitals are
strong. She made it through the night,
and she's, uh...
She's a fighter.
So I can tell my wife and my daughter?
You can.
And you should.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you both so much.
Yeah. No, she's out of the woods.
How am I related to that man?
What do you mean?
Look at him. He's a mess.
Yeah?
I mean, he's a disaster...
He's a stammering, mumbling,
clumsy disaster
with whom I have absolutely
nothing in common,
Not one thing.
I hate to break this to you...
What?
Well, you know, you do your own
share of stammering yourself.
Yeah, that nervous talking thing you do?
It's actually a lot like him.
mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
yeah, that's why I'm so happy.
- No, it's not.
- Plus that messy thing.
Oh, totally.
You're the messy one.
No,
my apartment's messy, my locker's messy,
but I am not messy.
Sometimes you have, like,
food and stuff in your hair.
Yeah, food.
Band-aids on your face.
I can still kinda see that indentation from
the nose strip you were wearing last night.
You... are in a relationship
with no words.
And you are a millionaire in $20 shoes.
Whatever.
Oh, my god...
She's just like him. Right?
Dr.  Bailey, you paged me?
Yes, I did.
We're going to proceed with
Heather's surgery, as scheduled.
The insurance company
changed their mind?
No. Better.
It seems an anonymous donor has
offered to foot Heather's entire bill.
Wow.
That is incredible.
You're a very lucky girl.
Hey, that's the first time anyone's ever
said that sentence to me in my entire life.
I like it.
You spent 300 grand so you could
scrub in on this surgery?
- No.
- No?
I... I spent the 3...
Have you seen that girl?
Her life is miserable.
She's desperate.
She... She'll never have a date,
She'll never wear high heels,
she'll never feel normal.
I... I spent 300 grand because it--
It's a good thing.
I was hoping you would tell me you spent
the money so you could scrub in.
But I...
You need to decide whether
or not you're a surgeon.
Because this thing you did...
this is lovely and generous, and I'm not
trying to take away from any of that, but
You are, once again, overly involved.
Once again, you are personally involved,
so...
no, I'm sorry. You cannot scrub in.
George kissed me.
Yesterday.
One minute he's holding a urine bag,
the next minute, he's kissing me.
You think he's just freaking
out about his dad?
Yeah, you're right, you're right.
He's probably just freaking out.
I shouldn't hold him to it.
- Oh, man.
- What?
Did you not just hear a word I said?
I'm pouring my heart out here.
Jeez.
It's all about you, isn't it? It's all
about a... Everything's about Addison.
I aborted Mark's baby.
It is all about you.
Floor is all yours.
About eight months ago.
I...peed on a stick,
and I wasn't even, uh...
gonna tell him, but then I did...
tell him. And, uh,
he went out and he bought this...
insane yankees onesie
and a calendar
and marked the due date,
which, I should mention, was today.
- You didn't want a baby?
- I wanted Derek.
I wanted to have a baby with Derek.
I never thought I'd end up alone.
Hey, you have not "ended up" anywhere.
Yeah, you're right, I know.
It's just that, um...
Sometimes it feels that way, you know?
This is one of those weeks
it feels that way.
Drill.
Another screw, please.
Hey, how's your old man?
His  urine output's holding steady.
Mostly it's steady today,
- which is good.
- Have you seen burke today?
Even if I did like you,
I still wouldn't tell you that.
How can you be okay
with Burke but not Cristina?
Her career wasn't on the line
when she lied to me.
Why don't you just ask Burke
about the hand yourself?
I am not talking to him.
He owes me.
What?
Oh, I don't know.
So you're together, but you
don't talk to each other?
I wish I could find that in a woman.
Hey, how's it going with Addison?
What?
Why... why why would you... what... What
what do you... What do you mean by that?
Laura Grey, tiny baby.
Laura. The baby. Right.
She's, uh, she's, um, doing fine.
She's doing well.
I gotta get out of gynie, though.
I gotta get back to sloan.
What are you plotting,
and can I get in on it?
Shut up.
Oh.
Ah! This is my surgery.
I should be down there.
No.
Excuse me.
Mr. O'malley.
9-1-1?
Yeah.
- Sucks.
- Yeah.
Give  me the retractor.
Um, dr. Shepherd, can you proceed
without me?
Are you kidding me?
This is your surgery, Torres,
this is your find,
and you want to leave?
I, um, I don't,
but, uh, yes, I'm sorry.
But if it's all right, I need to leave.
Give me some sponges,
Okay, I called the family in
because I need to perform a procedure,
uh, on your father to help him breathe.
So--so you're saying he can't breathe?
With the extensive surgery,
uh, your father is not
breathing on his own,
which is why we still
have him intubated.
Intubated?
The tube in dad's mouth.
It's breathing for him.
And right now that tube has a kink in
it, which is straining his breathing.
- How did it get a kink in it?
-
It just happens.
We don't always know why.
- How did it get a kink in it?
- It just happens we don't always know why.
But... But he's doing good today.
I mean, he made...He made plenty of pee,
still,  we need to replace the tube.
So why don't you just do it?
I mean, what are we waiting for?
okay,
with the damage
to your father's esophagus
and the swelling in his throat
from being intubated all this time...
you might not be able to get it in,
the new tube?
Under these circumstances...
it can be a complicated procedure.
If I'm not successful...
I'm saying, uh,
you need to prepare yourselves.
What is that?
It's Jerry.
I'm sorry. I'm nervous.
Oh.
- Oh, god.
- Oh!
- Oh, my god.
- God, stop it, Jerry!
- I'm nervous!
Oh! For god's sake, take some
charcoal or something, son.
That's disgusting.
- Tyler.
- Yeah.
Could you let dr. Burke know that
Mr. O'malley is having some kind of medical crisis right now
and I thought he would like to know.
He's awake, you know?
Yeah, I know.
You want to handle this, chief?
Dr. Bailey, you have a lot more hands-on
hours these days than I do.
I'll be standing by to help,
but this is all yours.
- Grey, let me have an 8.0 E.T. tube.
- Dr. Bailey...
This is a patient,
like any other patient.
There's no room for error,
which means there's no room for nerves,
so shake it off.
All right, let's do this.
Great. 8.0.
- I can't, uh...
- Is it too tight?
I can't get past the vocal chords.
Damn it.
Pulse ox down 88.
- Damn it.
- 86. Come on, let's go, let's go, let's go
Let me have a 7 1/2.
Hurry.
Good.
- Let me get a...
- Okay, I got it.
Beautil job. Beautiful job.
Oh, can I go tell George?
Dr. Bailey, you all right?
My son... is named after his son.
I just need a minute.
There's a surgery, you know?
It's a minor laser thing.
Supposed to really help.
We could look into it.
Sure, and while we're at it,
let's look at halitosis cures for you.
Not to mention stubble cures,
because it's now become
physically impossible
for me to kiss your face.
I am too tired to shave!
Sloan!
Dr. Sloan.
Bone dry cappuccino.
And I watched 'em make it this time
so no mistakes.
Hey, I noticed you had a reconstructive
rhinoplasty on the board today, and I'd
I'd really like
to scrub in if at all possible.
You been working with Addison this week?
Yes, sir, working.
Working... a lot.
Working hard.
Just...
Working.
Is she miserable?
I'm sorry?
It's just...
I need to know if she's... at least
miserable this week. Did she seem...
Is she miserable?
Oh, dude, she's awful.
She's torturing me.
I seriously have to get
away from that woman.
I mean, she is completely
and utterly, 100% miserable.
Good.
- So can I scrub in?
- No.
Are you sleeping?
I should be. I haven't slept in days.
Me neither.
I can't sleep alone anymore. I used
to sleep just fine, and then he...
God, he gets me all strung out on him,
and then he disappears?
He didn't disappear.
He's in the hospital.
I just want to know how he's doing.
You could just ask him.
Uh, he could just tell me.
George's dad is going into
renal failure.
I heard.
My dad's here,
everywhere, every day. He's perfectly
healthy, and I have nothing to say to him.
If George's dad dies...
I know.
If Thatcher died, my life
wouldn't be any different.
Is it weird that I'm
a little jealous of George?
Yes.
Bailey re-intubated him, but, um...
He was without oxygen for,
I don't know, a few minutes.
O'Malley...
there's no blame here.
Your father's body is diseased
and has undergone tremendous trauma.
Now his organs are shutting down.
There's no blame here.
Do people come back from this?
His B.U.N. and creatinine are high.
I get that.
I was just wondering,
in--in your experience,
can people come back from this?
I don't have any statistics.
I don't have any more medicine for you.
Now it's about faith.
We're men of science.
In my experience, science is not enough,
O'Malley.
But if you want me
to hope with you...
if you'd like me to send up a prayer,
that is a thing I'd be happy to do.
You have family here?
Yeah, a daughter.
She's 17.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Yeah.
She had surgery on her spine.
And they said it went well.
But then she has trouble
with her kidneys and...
well, she hasn't woken up.
My husband either.
It was a dangerous surgery.
They told us that.
My  husband's, too.
He has... cancer, so...
I was surprised when they
went through with it.
I thought I'd be taking him home.
Excuse me, mrs. Douglas.
Heather is asking for you.
She woke up?
She did.
And she looks great.
Congratulations.
That's wonderful.
Good luck.
I'll...
Thanks.
Why did you do it?
Dr. O'Malley.
Why did you do the surgery once
you saw the cancer had spread?
George...
He asked you, right?
He asked you to do it no matter what?
We have to honor our patient's wishes.
You said you would be straight with me.
He... he could've lived for weeks...
or... or months.
We could've had months with him.
My mom...
she could've had months with him!
he wanted to fight the cancer, George.
- It was his choice.
- He didn't know any better!
You knew better!
You shouldn't have done it.
You shouldn't have done it!
Oh, my God. Look at you.
I'm miserable.
It's the rain...
the constant dampness in the air.
It takes the body a while to adjust.
I don't want to adjust.
Then go home.
If you'd had the baby,
we'd be together in New York right now.
It wouldn't be raining,
and even if it was, we wouldn't care
because we'd be together.
We'd be together,
and I'd have a family instead of walking
pneumonia and an ex-best friend who hates me.
You didn't want to raise a child, Mark.
You wanted to trump Derek.
You wanted to win.
Don't make this my fault.
You didn't want a baby.
No, i did
want a baby, Mark.
That last woman you slept with
before I left New-York Charlene
the peds nurse?
Did you think that she was
the only one I knew about?
You're rewriting history, Mark.
We wouldn't still be together.
We weren't a great couple.
And you would've made...
a terrible father, Mark.
I did want a baby.
I did. I just...
I just didn't want one with you.
What?
- Is that his lunch?
I've been looking everywhere for that.
- Oh, no. He can't have that.
- What?
- He's, uh, restricted from food.
- No, he's not.
- No, I'm his doctor.
- You are not.
- I just want to know how he is.
And with holding food gets her that how?
Fine.
Feed him. Whatever.
You want me to call security?
Hey.
Haven't seen you
the last couple of days.
Yeah, I was covering the pit,
and, uh, I got pulled into
an emergency appy
and a ruptured spleen.
It's been pretty chaotic.
Look, Karev, I'm your attending.
I'm sorry about what happened.
It's been a...
a weird week for me.
so I normally...
anyway, I apologize.
The baby's, uh, bowels functioning yet?
Uh, yeah, actually, um...
she had her first dipper change today
That's good.
Yeah, it is.
That neighbor kid,
Mike Wilden?
I did hit him in the face with a stick.
And... when his dad came over
and he was yelling and...
and... and you asked me if it was true.
I lied.
And you thought I never lied
so you took my side.
And you and his dad
got in that big fight,
and then his kids egged our house
and then Ronnie and Jerry
went over and...
blew up his lawn mower.
Anyway...
I did it.
He was teasing me...
and he was bigger than me...
so I needed the stick to reach his face.
And I lied to you, dad.
So...
I'm saying I'm sorry.
Dad...
if you have any more fight in you...
if you could fight thithing just...
just a little harder,
that would be good.
That'd be good right now.
Where's derek?
He slept at his place.
Do I really snore?
Well, I grew up next to a freeway,
so it doesn't really bother me,
but, yeah, you do.
Did you get any sleep last night?
No.
No, I stayed up baking
and cleaning the bathroom floor
in case George wants to lay down on it.
It's weird.
I have all this money.
I... I have all this money,
and I would spend every penny of it
to save George from what he's
about to go through, but
I... can't.
It's useless.
So I made cobbler.
Well, cobbler's good.
Yeah.
She told you.
Uh...
yeah.
U think I'd be a terrible father?
Oh, I don't--
I don't... Are you...
Okay, do you like kids?
I don't know.
Depends on how loud they are.
Okay. Do you like your family?
I mean, are you a family kind of guy?
I don't really have a family.
Derek...
was my family.
Okay.
Well, what about, uh,
birthdays and anniversaries?
Do you remember those sorts of things?
No.
I don't know.
Sometimes.
Isn't it the same with... with all men?
No.
Some men just like kids. To, uh,
To some men, family is everything.
Right.
And you know these men?
I do.
I know one.
I would' made a terrible father.
You're saying...
You're saying it's not getting better.
You're saying he's not gonna wake up.
Mrs. O'Malley...
All of his organs are shutting down.
His liver and his kidneys
are no longer supporting him,
and he is entirely dependant
upon his life support machines.
We're saying he's not going to wake up.
You can keep him on life support
and wait for nature to take its course.
That could take days or weeks.
Or you can...
take him off life support.
Unplug him?
Yes, ma'am.
Georgie.
Yeah?
What do you think?
Dad's in pain.
His organs are shutting down.
He can't breathe on his own.
It's painful.
And he's on medication, but...
medication can only do so much.
You think...
you're saying you think it's time...
to let him go?
We can't tell you
what to do here, George.
He's not dad like this.
And he's not
gonna wake up, mom.
Is there a drawer
of unopened cards somewhere?
I'm sorry, what?
I just...
wanted to know.
I've only ever heard my mother's version
of the story of why you left.
And I was just wondering if maybe
you have a side that I haven't heard.
Your mother moved to boston, and, u..
I wanted to...
but she told me not...
to call or come around, and, uh...
She... She was, uh, um...
Eventually, I remarried.
And I...
I'm s... I'm sorry.
Do you snore?
What?
It appears that I snore.
My mother never did, so I was just...
Forget it.
I snore.
I snore like a trucker.
You get that from me.
The wax earplugs work pretty good.
Thanks.
hey.
Derek.
I was waiting on an update
on mr. O'Malley.
I didn't want to intrude, but, uh...
do you have an update?
They're letting him go.
Haven't had any more tremors.
Not one all week.
How about that?
Yeah.
I'm both.
What?
I'm a surgeon,
and I am a person who becomes
emotionally involved.
And I will never again
cross a line like I did with Denny.
I have learned my lesson.
But I'm still both.
And I'm not gonna give up
either part of me.
And I'm not gonna apologize for it.
There's a club--
The dead dad's club...
And you can be in it until you're in it.
You can try and understand, you can
sympathize, but until you feel that loss.
My dad died when I was 9.
George... I'm really sorry
you had to join the club.
I...
I don't know how to exist in a world
where my dad doesn't.
Yeah, that never really changes.
Beer, Joe, please.
George's dad?
Hey.
You got a dad?
Not really.
Not anymore.
Transcript : Raceman - Synchro : ChipounetteF
Traduction : Chryssie, Tbdb - Relecture : Cookie
www.forom.com