Previously on Grey's Anatomy:
- How did your test go?
- Good, but I won't know for a few days.
- We're pulling for you.
- We are?
You cannot kick me
while I'm doing my job.
I thought you could give me
an answer to my question.
About you... moving in.
I have a dog.
That's not a dog.
It's a hyena dressed in dog clothing.
I love dogs.
As doctors
we're trained to be skeptical...
because our patients
lie to us all the time.
The rule is: every patient is a liar
until proven honest.
Why aren't you prepping for rounds
and stealing the good cases?
- No reason.
- No reason?
Lying is bad. Or so we're told.
Constantly, from birth.
"Honesty is the best policy."
"The truth shall set you free."
"I chopped down the cherry tree."
Whatever.
- I'm waiting for McDreamy.
- I'm avoiding Burke.
- Why are you avoiding Burke?
- He thinks I moved in with him.
- Why are you...
- McDreamy's doing me a favor.
- Thinks you moved in with him?
- You're calling him "McDreamy?"
The fact is, lying is a necessity.
Thank you for this,
with the needles and blood.
They won't accept her
without a family history.
I'm happy to get your mom
into the clinical trial.
Even with the needles and blood.
All done. How's that feel?
We lie to ourselves because the truth...
The truth freaking hurts.
It feels good.
- Burke thinks you moved in with him?
- It's not important.
- You're calling Derek "McDreamy" again?
- It's nothing.
- All right, what are you doing?
- What are you doing?
- Stop repeating what I say.
- Stop asking me questions.
Cujo has to go!
He peed on my bed. My bed, Meredith.
- He's our dog.
- No, he's not my dog.
You two bought him
without even asking me.
We rescued him from certain death.
Come on, you guys.
I'm putting my foot down.
Either the dog moves out or I do.
Foot. Down. Now.
Me or the dog. Which is it?
- You hesitated. She hesitated.
- You hesitated?
I didn't hesitate. I was thinking.
You have to think about it? Fine.
I'm moving out right now.
Later. I'm moving out later.
Because right now, I have rounds.
- Tell me that is not a dog.
- It's not a dog.
- Let's go.
- Rick Freeark, 29.
Severed three fingers on his left hand.
Controlled the bleeding.
Vitals stable.
Gave him five of morphine.
- Fingers?
- Had trouble retrieving them,
so we took off. Rig behind us found 'em.
They're iced and ready.
- Ten minutes out.
- Continue with IV fluids
and start a course of antibiotics.
Yang, wait outside for the fingers.
Can you sew them on?
They sewed that guy's penis back
on after his wife chopped it off.
Penises and fingers
are like apples and oranges.
- How did it happen?
- I was loading my gear on to the truck
for a gig and they got caught.
- You're a musician?
- I play the guitar.
You can sew them back on, right?
This is not that big a deal, right?
Oh, dude,
I better not be out of the band.
The cuts look clean. That's good.
Clean severed makes reattachment easier.
I'm not going to lie to you.
If the surgery is successful,
we're looking at a long recovery
with lots of physical therapy.
- You smoke?
- Why?
Cigarettes constrict blood vessels. I've
seen grafts fail over a few cigarettes.
So what are you saying?
I smoke a cigarette after my operation
and boom! My fingers fall off?
No. First they turn black and necrotic
and then they fall off.
Well... I don't smoke, so...
Really? Because judging by
the nicotine stains, your fingers do.
Anybody out there?
Hello?
Don't look at me.
She had hip replacement surgery a
month ago and was discharged last week.
Then why is she still here?
Because I am not a bouncer
and this is not a nightclub.
I am doing what I can, with extremely
limited staff and resources
and if you have a problem with that,
take it up with the chief.
~ Don't know why
~ There's no sun up in the sky...
- Mrs. Larson's got to go.
- If she refuses to go, what can I do?
She's 78 and non-ambulatory.
You have the upper hand here. Use it.
Karev, can I talk to you for a second?
- Results of your Medical Board exams.
- Thanks.
- Aren't you going to open it?
- Yeah, I'll open it.
~ I'm weary all the time ~
- Oh, thank you. Thank you.
- Mrs. Larson, I'm Dr. O'Malley.
Oh! An Irishman. I love the Irish.
They have a sparkle.
You can see it in the eye.
And the swagger.
Come on, Dr. O'Malley.
Show me the swagger.
The eyes are right,
but you'll have to work on the swagger.
- Mrs. Larson...
- Call me Sophie.
Now, be a doll and bring me a remote.
This one's busted.
Sophie.
I can't bring you one because you're
no longer a patient at this hospital.
According to your chart, you have
a room at the Sugar Maple Nursing Home.
I'm staying
until my daughter's house is ready.
She's converting her den
into my bedroom.
She's doing it in a shade of pink.
Now... bring me a remote, Irish.
I'm going to sing... until you get back.
~ Can't go on
~ Everything I have is gone
~ Stormy weather...
Coming right up.
Yumi Miyazaki, 22. Presented this
morning with persistent hiccups.
She was given 50 chlorpromazine which
stopped them, but then they returned,
so she needs a surgical consult
to rule out esophageal perforation.
- When did your hiccups start?
- A few days ago.
- She doesn't speak English.
- You her boyfriend?
Her coach.
- She's an athlete?
- Yumi is a competitive eater.
Eating is a sport?
Miyazaki. Yeah, yeah.
She's like a rock star in Japan.
Again, eating is a sport?
Tell her I saw her on TV. Tell her
I'm an athlete too. I'm a wrestler...
She wonders how a wrestler
got smart enough to be a doctor.
Most wrestlers she knows are dumb.
Tell her she hasn't been hanging out
at the right gyms.
How about instead you tell her
that a persistent hiccup
could be an indication
of something much more serious?
Schedule an esophagogram.
She's competing this afternoon
at the Taste of Seattle.
Can't you give her
a stronger dose of that drug? It worked.
Did the hiccups come back?
- Yes, but...
- Then it didn't work.
- Dr. Bailey?
- Be quiet.
Dr. Bailey, are you OK?
All right,
somebody page Addison Shepherd.
There he is. Heartbeat's strong.
Since there's no dilation or effacement,
it looks like nothing more
than Braxton Hicks.
Except?
I know the mild-concerned tone.
I've used it myself from time to time.
Sometimes false labor
is the body's way of saying "slow down."
I'm a surgeon.
I understand the realities of your job
but you need to understand the realities
of your pregnancy. Take it easy.
- Is there anything I can do to help?
- You can help me get up off this table.
Dr. Bailey?
The GI lab has a couple of questions
about Miss Miyazaki's esophagogram.
All right. Let's go.
Dr. Stevens.
Keep an eye on her. Watch for painful
contractions, more than five an hour.
Anything that could indicate
preterm labor.
The favor's not for me, Stevens.
You know that.
Naomi Cline, 43.
Had her tricuspid valve replaced
three years ago with a porcine valve.
Oh, Naomi.
I'm surprised to see you
back again so soon.
Pig valves usually hold up 10-15 years.
Yours is degenerating
too quickly for my comfort.
Oh, heart-valve, schmart-valve.
I got married, Dr. Burke.
I found him. My true love.
My "you jump, I jump."
Look. Isn't it beautiful?
And look...
Iook at that beautiful, beautiful man.
- We met in the grocery store.
- Oh, honey.
Congratulations.
It's good to see you so happy.
Yeah.
So, Naomi's heart valve?
What does this mean?
There's a cause for your wife's valve
failure that remains undiagnosed.
Theories, Grey?
Rheumatic fever,
chronic use of migraine meds...
...or IV narcotics
could all cause valve disease, sir.
Oh, I don't use drugs. Don't need 'em.
I've got Tom.
He's my drug. Aren't you, baby?
- She's high, Dr. Burke.
- She's in love. She's happy.
Nobody is that happy. She's on drugs.
Run a tox screen.
But Naomi doesn't strike me as a liar.
If she says no drugs,
then it's no drugs.
- You develop a sixth sense about this.
- Everybody's a liar.
Dr. Grey, is that a dog?
No.
We need to keep this elevated, OK?
I'm gonna check in on you
in a little bit.
Yang.
You were a little harsh in there.
He was lying. Your "harsh"
is another man's "refreshing."
Well, he's in shock. He lost his fingers
and his only remaining habit in one day.
We need to be compassionate.
- Compassionate?
- It's an emotion.
- Have you ever heard of it?
- Have you?
Barely back on her feet and you've
got her calling you McDreamy again.
I was telling the patient the truth.
You might want to try it sometime.
Remotes.
- More remotes.
- O'Malley?
I'm getting a remote for Mrs. Larson.
What happened to the upper hand?
Have you met Mrs. Larson, sir?
Why do you think she's been here
this long? In a private room.
She handled you, too?
Well, she sang for the troops, you know?
Can't we just keep her here until her
room at her daughter's house is ready?
No, we can't.
Not on surgical service, anyway.
Oh. OK.
- But... some other service?
- I'm the Chief, O'Malley.
I can't condone turfing patients
onto other services.
You hear me, O'Malley?
Any available IC nurse to OR 2.
I'm missing my program, Irish.
And I don't see a remote
in that hot little hand.
Your urine output has increased slightly
since yesterday.
I'm going to have to
take you to gynecology
to make sure
you don't have a prolapsed uterus.
Honey, my uterus
hasn't been an issue for 30 years.
I know. But it might be an issue now.
You know, one that could
keep you here in the hospital for tests.
You drive. I'll ride shotgun.
- You're not moving out, George.
- Oh, yes, I am.
I gave an ultimatum. Threw down the
gauntlet. I drew my line in the sand.
Well, un-give, un-throw, un-draw.
A man does not give an ultimatum
and then back down.
Meredith had a choice
and she chose the dog.
A girl chose a dog over you?
- Yes.
- No.
- Are we going to do this or what?
- Yeah. Let's go.
- Don't start without me.
- We won't start if Izzie doesn't focus.
- Come on.
- What should I put?
- I don't know.
- Destructive hell-dog available.
- Not helping.
- Fine.
Playful, protective puppy
needs loving home.
Good.
- Hey, George.
- Don't talk to me.
You'll mess up my game,
and I'm in the zone.
OK. What are you doing?
- It's a flyer...
- Izzie, come on.
OK. Keep your panties on.
- All right.
- No touching!
Go.
Advertising for a home for Doc?
I said I'd do it.
And you haven't. And you won't.
And I don't want George to leave.
Say he's not house-broken.
- What? It's the truth.
- So you want me to put the truth? Fine.
Vicious, hyper devil-mutt
is available and will pee on your bed.
He's yours too. We got him together.
We got him together, but he's not
my dog. He's not your dog either.
He doesn't even know us. We're not
home enough for him to know us.
Ha-ha!
- You cheated.
- I kicked your asses.
~ You wanna be me, but you can't be me
~ You wanna be me, but you...
- Uh-oh.
- She's gonna blow.
"The surgical floor is a dumping ground
for patients who aren't even surgical."
"We are overworked and exhausted.
This makes..."
The nurses again?
Can't you do something?
You used to be one of them.
Don't you speak "nurse?"
That's why you don't
get any respect from the nurses.
- Surgical arrogance.
- I'm not arrogant.
You're killing them with that workload.
Look at the board.
What? That's a beautiful board.
It's a crowded board.
We need more nurses.
Mr. Kamaji? This is probably
what's causing her hiccups.
- A tear in the lining of her esophagus.
- Can you fix it?
Yes, surgically. Sooner the better.
After today,
her schedule is clear until March.
No, her schedule is clear now.
She can't compete today.
And if she enjoys
the taste of solid food,
I recommend giving up the sport
for something a little less aggressive.
Say, boxing.
I see.
Could you give us some privacy please?
Karev, get the translator up here.
Let's make sure
she's getting the whole truth.
- You know?
- Yeah.
- Busted.
- Put that out.
Sorry.
I've gotta prep you for surgery.
Can you ask your friends to leave?
Love you.
I wasn't gonna light 'em.
I was just holding them.
OK.
- Seriously. Take them. Throw them out.
- You hang on to them.
- Seriously, I wasn't gonna smoke.
- I don't care. Do what you want.
You don't think
I'm gonna be able to quit, do you?
No. I don't.
~ I'm lonely all the time...
Oh, no.
Oh, yeah.
Irish.
That nice lady doctor in gynecology
said that,
since I had a hysterectomy back in '74,
I don't have a uterus to prolapse.
- Damn it.
- I've been feeling a bit feverish.
A woman my age with a fever
could be an indication of...
any number of awful diseases.
They took your temperature an hour ago.
It was normal.
I am sorry, Sophie, but I am
going to have to call your daughter.
I'm telling you, I'm warm.
That must be one hell of a dog.
Excuse me?
With those eyes...
and those nice firm hands.
A girl who chooses a dog over you...
It must be one hell of a dog.
Mrs. Cline's tox screen and titer
both came back negative.
I was sure I was right about that.
Gonna have to adjust your world view.
- There are people who don't lie.
- Maybe.
Although, frankly, the drug use
would have explained the valve failure.
- So how do we proceed?
- Schedule Mrs. Cline for a surgery.
OK.
Do you want to come over for dinner?
- What?
- Dinner.
- Our place. Mine and Cristina's.
- Why?
You're Cristina's friend. I want her to
feel welcome to have our friends round.
- So she moved in with you?
- Yes. Didn't she tell you?
Of course she told me.
Why wouldn't she tell me?
She's in, right?
- Which, you know, I think is great.
- Right.
Thank you.
I just came from Mr. Freeark's room.
He's convinced he won't be able
to quit smoking. Says you agree.
He asked my opinion.
- Want me to apologize?
- Tell him you're wrong.
You're having a bad day.
Your favorite uncle died of lung cancer.
Say whatever you need to. Get him to
believe this is about you, not him.
If he thinks he can't quit, he won't.
- Then we shouldn't do the surgery.
- Fine.
- What is your problem? I'm your boss...
- You're not right now.
We're in an elevator,
your specialty for McDreamy moments.
- Dr. Yang...
- For a moment I'm not Dr. Yang,
you're not Dr. Shepherd.
You're the guy who screwed up my friend.
The guy who drove her to get a dog
because her boyfriend lied...
I never lied to her.
I know a liar when I see one
because I'm a liar.
Want me to lie to the patient?
Fine, I'll lie.
Yumi?
Hey. The translator's here.
Where's the patient Miyazaki?
She left with her friend 20 minutes ago.
- She wasn't discharged.
- Sorry, we're short-staffed.
I assumed someone else
had done the paperwork.
Damn it.
Come on! Damn it.
- What are you doing out of bed?
- I gotta get a candy bar.
You're about to have surgery.
You can't eat.
- Mr. Freeark, please.
- My dad's Mr. Freeark.
- Well...
- He's got a combover
- and an annoying wife named Kimberley.
- Rick. Listen.
- Earlier I was out of line.
- No. You got me to think.
I don't want to be a guy sitting
in a bar with a stump for a hand,
having a smoke ten years down the line,
bragging about how
I was better than Dave Navarro.
Yeah, you don't want
to be creepy bitter guy.
Here's the thing.
My last cigarette was this morning.
Only I didn't know
it was my last cigarette.
What the hell do you think you're doing?
McDreamy's being McDouchey.
He's making me stand at the back of the
OR while he reattaches Rick's fingers.
I mean, I can't even touch a retractor.
I hate him.
Truth.
Did you move in with Burke or not?
I told him I moved in with him
but I'm keeping my old apartment.
What? I sleep with Burke every night.
My clothes are there.
- I still have my apartment. Big deal.
- You have to tell him.
Actually, I don't.
So...
I'm supposed to go to dinner
at your fake apartment
- with the guy you fake live with?
- I wouldn't have you over to dinner.
- That's weird.
- This is my point.
- Stop with the lying.
- And you're being honest?
The last time you called him McDreamy,
you were all atwitter with love.
- We're just friends.
- Uh-huh?
We are.
- West Nile Virus? Are you kidding me?
- No. Look at her.
She's feverish. Weaker than this
morning. Could be decompensating.
She's been here for a month. You seen
any mosquitoes in this hospital lately?
Oh, such a handsome young man.
Those chocolatey eyes.
In order to test you, Mrs. Larson,
we have to do a spinal tap.
Will you be doing it?
Yes, ma'am.
Well, then... call me Sophie.
Nice meeting you, Irish!
So, if you'll just sign here
we can go ahead
- and schedule you for surgery.
- OK.
You know,
you are a gorgeous young woman.
Look at you.
You should smile more.
Any available IV nurse to the ER.
Mr. Cline.
Oh. Uh...
- Do me a favor.
- Sure.
Don't tell her you saw me.
I'm not sure that I'm going to go in.
She's... she can be exhausting.
Yeah, she's... really happy.
You know, I thought it was just
falling in love, the wedding,
but I was hoping the honeymoon
would be over by now.
I mean... it's not normal. Right?
Nobody's that happy.
- Run another tox screen on Naomi Cline.
- On whose orders?
Dr. Burke's, of course.
I'm sorry to bother you. The paramedics
are on their way in with Yumi Miyazaki.
She collapsed at the Taste of Seattle
and is vomiting blood.
Damned fool. Probably tore
her esophagus in two by now.
Are you OK?
Complications of Boerhaave's Syndrome.
Go.
Pleural effusion, sepsis, shock.
She's cyanotic with shallow
breath sounds. BP 76 over 42,
tachycardia to the 130's.
Started her on high flow O2.
- On her second bolus of saline.
- Let's get her to the OR.
They're ready and waiting.
Her coach should be
the one on this gurney.
Let's keep our eyes on the prize, Karev.
Saving this woman's life.
- I'll meet you guys up there.
- Me too.
Hey, hey. What are you gonna do?
- Punch him out?
- Yeah.
You're gonna kick his ass,
get yourself kicked out of the program
before you open your scores
in case you failed?
God, you're such an idiot.
Dr. Karev, how do I begin
the esophagomyotomy?
Cut proximal and distal to the tear
to expose the mucosal defect.
Correct. Then we'll move
to the débridement of the defect...
Dr. Bailey,
those aren't Braxton Hicks contractions.
I believe you are in preterm labor.
Why didn't you call me sooner?
All right. Get out of here.
- I was gonna fashion a gastric patch.
- I taught you the procedure.
Now leave.
The clamp.
Dr. Cloner to obstetrics.
I got paged Dr. Grey.
Jeffery wanted to give me the results of
the extensive blood work that I ordered.
You forged my signature?
- That's really bad, right?
- Yeah. That's really bad.
Naomi is not on drugs.
The tests came back negative.
- They did?
- They did. Again.
Next time you forge my signature,
let me know. Save me a trip.
That's it?
You're not gonna yell "Damn it, Grey"
and storm out?
- I will if you want me to.
- No.
Dr. Burke. Here's another one. Her
serotonin level. It's through the roof.
Dr. Grey. You took a detailed history.
- When did Mrs. Cline develop asthma?
- After the first surgery. Why?
We found a carcinoid tumor in the lung.
Very rare.
Almost impossible to diagnose.
It masks itself as a bunch
of seemingly unrelated symptoms:
- adult onset asthma, valve failure...
- Increased serotonin in the blood.
Which creates a false sense of euphoria.
So, Naomi's not actually this happy?
She just has a tumor?
- Exactly.
- Thank God.
You people with your tumors. I tell you,
I'm infected with love.
I'm sorry.
Your body is lying to your mind.
Oh, let the lie continue. Right, baby?
- How soon can you cure her?
- Tomorrow.
If all goes well,
Naomi goes back to normal.
Great. Thank you both.
Thank you for not chewing me out
for forging your signature.
Thank you.
I know it was probably you
who convinced Cristina.
She's very strong,
but she listens to you.
If you told her to move in...
Anyway, thank you.
No problem.
Do you have any sensation
in your left arm at all?
No.
Actually, could I watch?
I wanna see every blood vessel
and nerve I'm gonna screw up
if I ever smoke again.
Not that I'm gonna. Ever again.
I smoked my last cigarette.
OK. Let's get started.
The nursing home
said she never showed up.
- How exactly is that possible?
- She wouldn't leave.
My mother is old and infirm.
You couldn't make her leave?
Have you met your mother?
Fine. Where is she now?
Hi. She's in the
Infectious Diseases Service.
Infectious disease. Since when
does she have an infectious disease?
She doesn't.
She just doesn't want to leave.
- She's unbelievable.
- Yeah, she is.
- Is her room ready? I can get her.
- They've had the room ready for weeks.
No, not at Sugar Maple.
I meant at your house.
- I'm sorry?
- The pink room.
At your house.
We got a car that matches the
description. Want to head over there?
- Hi, Sophie.
- Irish.
What a wonderful surprise.
You won't catch my disease, will you?
No, I think I'll be OK.
Sophie, your daughter was just here.
Nursing homes are for old people.
I know I'm elderly.
I do know that.
But if I have to go to that place...
I'm afraid I'll become old.
I don't think that's possible.
Oh.
You know that I would
keep you here if I could.
Oh, no, darling.
You can't waste any more time with me.
You have to go balls out with the dog.
Excuse me?
So she chose an animal over you.
So what? Women are fools.
That's old news.
But life's too short
for you to give in, Irish.
So fight.
You fight for what's yours.
Now that, my friend... is a swagger.
I'll be closing the peritoneal
cavity with zero chromic sutures.
Thank you.
Chief.
Let's get back to it.
Pull back on that retractor.
Give me more suction. I'll
need a sponge on a stick. More suction.
- What's going on?
- I tried, but you wouldn't listen.
It is now 6:07. The second shift nurses
start at six. They're not coming in.
Do you know what a sick out
will do to this hospital?
I've already put in the call for temps.
- What's this?
- Notification.
We go on strike in ten days.
Doing good, Yumi.
You're doing just fine.
We should get the translator.
She doesn't understand.
We'll be back.
What the hell are you doing here?
I never would have...
I thought she would be fine.
- I'm sorry.
- Don't tell me. Tell her.
Tell her how her career is over
because of you.
Way better than punching him out.
Hey, can you...
- You want me to open it?
- Yeah, I know, it's...
I can't.
- I shouldn't. I mean...
- You already think I'm an idiot.
It won't be any great shock.
Congratulations. You are not an idiot.
Except when you're being an idiot.
Good.
Hey, how's he doing?
Jonesing for a cigarette, but I think
he'll make it to the end of the day.
Good.
- I was being nice to her.
- OK.
I can be nice without being...
McDreamy. I know.
I really can.
OK.
OK, then.
Bed rest at home until the baby comes.
You do know what bed rest is, Miranda?
- Yeah. Hell.
- Hell with TV and books.
Here. It's from all of us.
I may be 47 months pregnant.
I may be on bed rest.
I may not be able to see my own feet.
But I am Dr. Bailey.
I hear everything. I know everything.
I am watching each and every one of you.
And I will return.
How many hours
do they expect us to work?
I agree.
Strike?
Strike.
You are all
a bunch of arrogant surgeons.
- Hey.
That was Izzie.
She refuses to take the dog home.
Mm-hm.
Fine. If you want me to tell Burke
I didn't move in, I'll tell him.
No. Don't.
- What?
- Don't tell him.
At least, not right now. Or tonight.
I just mean wait. It can wait.
I lied about Derek.
We're not just friends.
I mean, I'm not.
He's still McDreamy.
I know.
You don't get to choose.
Huh?
I know you've been going through a bad
time. I know you miss Shepherd.
And I know that your life has been
admittedly pretty unpleasant these days.
You get points for breathing in and out.
You get to be a little selfish.
But you don't get to
choose a dog over me.
I'm George.
I sleep down the hall from you.
I buy your tampons.
I have held your hand
every time you've asked.
I've earned the right to be seen,
to be respected,
to not have you think of me as less
than a dog that you got at the pound.
So...
I'm not moving out.
Whether you like it or not, I'm staying.
No matter how hard we try
to ignore it or deny it,
eventually the lies fall away...
I'm glad you moved in.
So am I.
... whether we like it or not.
OK, Doc. Let's go.
Hey, Doc. Hey, buddy.
- Hey.
- Welcome home.
He's beautiful.
- I brought his toys.
- Here's his food and his water dish.
Here.
Thanks for doing this.
I know it's a lot to ask.
It's all right.
It's just a dog.
Right? Come on, Doc.
- We'll just... wait by the car.
- OK.
So, he chews everything.
So don't leave anything out.
He hates cats
and small, little, yappy dogs.
- Oh, not house-broken.
- Oh.
- Probably should have told you that.
- Yeah.
You don't have to do this, you know?
Well, you know, I got all this land.
It's just going to waste.
Derek.
It's just a dog.
It doesn't mean anything. He'll be fine.
Yeah.
- OK. Good night.
- Good night.
But here's the truth about the truth:
It hurts.
So... we lie.
www.tvsubtitles.net