NARRATOR (LLM_UNCERTAIN): The game -
NARRATOR (LLM_UNCERTAIN): they say a person either has what it takes to play or they don't.
NARRATOR (LLM_UNCERTAIN): My mother was one of the greats.
NARRATOR (LLM_UNCERTAIN): Me, on the other hand -
NARRATOR (LLM_UNCERTAIN): I'm kind of screwed.
DR. MEREDITH GREY (DB_VALIDATED, original: MEREDITH): This is, uh...
DR. MEREDITH GREY (DB_VALIDATED, original: MEREDITH): Humiliating on so many levels.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: You have to go.
DR. DEREK SHEPHERD: Why don't you just come back down here, and we'll pick up where we left off?
DR. MEREDITH GREY: No, seriously. You have to go. I'm late,
DR. MEREDITH GREY: which isn't what you want to be on  your first day of work, so...
DR. DEREK SHEPHERD: So, uh, you actually live here.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: No.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Yes, kind of.
DR. DEREK SHEPHERD: It's nice - a little dusty -
DR. DEREK SHEPHERD: odd, but it's nice.
DR. DEREK SHEPHERD: So, how do you kind of live here?
DR. MEREDITH GREY: I moved two weeks ago from Boston.  It was my mother's house. I'm selling it.
DR. DEREK SHEPHERD: Oh, I'm sorry.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: For what?
DR. DEREK SHEPHERD: You said "was."
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Oh, my mother's not dead. She's -
DR. MEREDITH GREY: You know what? We don't have to do the thing.
DR. DEREK SHEPHERD: Oh, we can do anything you want.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: No, the thing - exchange the details, pretend we care.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: I'm gonna go upstairs and take a shower, okay?
DR. MEREDITH GREY: And when I get back down here, you won't be here, so, um...
DR. MEREDITH GREY: goodbye, um...
DR. DEREK SHEPHERD: Derek.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Derek. Right. Meredith.
DR. DEREK SHEPHERD: Meredith.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Yeah. Mm-hmm.
DR. DEREK SHEPHERD: - Nice meeting you. - Bye, Derek.
DR. RICHARD WEBBER (LLM_UNCERTAIN): Each of you comes here today hopeful,
DR. RICHARD WEBBER: wanting in on the game.
DR. RICHARD WEBBER (LLM_UNCERTAIN): A month ago, you were in med school,  being taught by doctors.
DR. RICHARD WEBBER (LLM_UNCERTAIN): Today...
DR. RICHARD WEBBER (LLM_UNCERTAIN): you are the doctors.
DR. RICHARD WEBBER: The 7 years you spend here as a surgical resident
DR. RICHARD WEBBER: will be the best and worst of your life.
DR. RICHARD WEBBER (LLM_UNCERTAIN): You will be pushed to the breaking point.
DR. RICHARD WEBBER (LLM_UNCERTAIN): Look around you.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: Say hello to your competition.
DR. RICHARD WEBBER: Eight of you will switch to an easier specialty.
DR. RICHARD WEBBER (LLM_UNCERTAIN): Five of you will crack under the pressure.
DR. RICHARD WEBBER: Two of you will be asked to leave.
DR. RICHARD WEBBER: This is your starting line.
DR. RICHARD WEBBER (LLM_UNCERTAIN): This is your arena.
DR. RICHARD WEBBER: How well you play...
DR. RICHARD WEBBER: that's up to you.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Like I said...
DR. MEREDITH GREY: I'm screwed.
UNIDENTIFIED RESIDENT OR STAFF (LLM_UNCERTAIN): Okay, Martin, Robinson, Bond, Hawkins.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: Only 6 women out of 20.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: Yeah. I hear one of them's a model.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: Seriously, that's gonna help  with the respect thing?
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: - You're Cristina, right? - Patton, Monroe...
DR. CRISTINA YANG: Which resident are you assigned to?  I got bailey.
DR. MEREDITH GREY (DB_VALIDATED, original: MEREDITH GREY): The Nazi? Me too.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: You got the Nazi? So did I.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: At least we'll be tortured together, right?
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: I'm George O’Malley.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: Uh, we met at the mixer. You had on a black dress
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: with a slit up the side, strappy sandals...
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: Now you think I'm gay. No, I'm not gay.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: It's - it's just that you were - you  were very unforgettable.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: O’Malley, Yang, Grey, Stevens.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: And I'm totally forgettable.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: - Bailey? - End of the hall.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: That's the Nazi?
DR. ISOBEL STEVENS (DB_VALIDATED, original: IZZIE STEVENS): I thought the Nazi would be a guy.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: I thought the Nazi would be a Nazi.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Maybe it's professional jealousy.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: Maybe she's brilliant, and they call her a Nazi because they're jealous.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: Maybe she's nice.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: Let me guess - you're the model.
DR. ISOBEL STEVENS: Hi, I'm Isobel Stevens, but everyone calls me "Izzie."
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: I have five rules. Memorize them.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: Rule number one - don't bother sucking up.  I already hate you. That's not gonna change.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: Trauma protocol, phone list, pagers - nurses will page you.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: You will answer every page at a run -  a run - that's rule number two.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: Your first shift starts now and  lasts 48 hours.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: You're interns, grunts, nobodies, bottom of the surgical food chain.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: You run labs, write orders, work every second night until you drop, and don't complain.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: On-call rooms - attendings hog them.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: Sleep when you can where you can, which brings me to rule number three.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: If I'm sleeping, don't wake me unless your patient is actually dying.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: Rule number four - the dying patient better not be dead when I get there.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: Not only will you have killed someone, you would have woke me for no good reason. We clear?
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Yes?
DR. MEREDITH GREY: You said five rules. That was only four.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: Rule number five - when I move, you move.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: Get out of my way!
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: What do we got?
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Katie Bryce, 15-year-old female, new onset seizures, intermittent for the past week.
PARAMEDIC (LLM_UNCERTAIN): I.V. lost en route, started grand mal seizing as we descended.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY (DB_VALIDATED, original: DR. BAILEY): All right, get her on her side.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: Izzie, 10 milligrams diazepam I.M.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: No, no. The white lead is on the right.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: Righty, whity - smoke over fire.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: A large-bore I.V. Don't let the blood hemolyze. Let's go!
DR. MEREDITH GREY: What do we have? A wet fish on dry land.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: Absolutely, Dr. Burke.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: Dr. Bailey, let's shotgun her.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY (DB_VALIDATED, original: DR. BAILEY): That means every test in the book - C.T., CBC, chem-7, tox screen.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: Cristina, you're on labs. George, patient work-ups.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: Meredith, get Katie for a C.T.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: She's your responsibility now.
DR. ISOBEL STEVENS: Wait. What about me?
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: Honey, you get to do rectal exams.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY (LLM_UNCERTAIN): What are you doing here?
DR. CRISTINA YANG: Katie Bryce's labs came out clear. There's nothing
DR. CRISTINA YANG: in the results that explain her seizures.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: - I just thought you wanna know. - Okay.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: I heard every year, the attending on call picks the best intern
DR. CRISTINA YANG: and lets them perform a procedure during the first shift.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: I'm just saying it's what I heard.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: Go away... now.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: Yeah, sounds good.
MR. TONY SAVITCH: He'll be fine?
DR. ISOBEL STEVENS (DB_VALIDATED, original: IZZIE STEVENS): You'll be fine.
MR. TONY SAVITCH: If you don't count the fact that my bacon days are over, sure.
DR. ISOBEL STEVENS (DB_VALIDATED, original: IZZIE STEVENS): So, bypass surgery tomorrow with Dr. Burke - I hear he's good.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: And, after that, you can have all the bacon-flavored soy product you can eat.
MR. TONY SAVITCH: Mmm. Kill me now.
DR. ISOBEL STEVENS (DB_VALIDATED, original: IZZIE STEVENS): I wish I could, but I'm a healer.
NURSE (LLM_UNCERTAIN): You're lost.
DR. MEREDITH GREY (DB_VALIDATED, original: MEREDITH GREY): I'm not lost.
DR. MEREDITH GREY (DB_VALIDATED, original: MEREDITH GREY): How are you feeling?
KATIE BRYCE: How do you think I'm feeling?
KATIE BRYCE: I'm missing my pageant.
DR. MEREDITH GREY (DB_VALIDATED, original: MEREDITH GREY): You're missing your pageant?
KATIE BRYCE: The Spokane teen miss.
KATIE BRYCE: I was in the top 10 after the first 2 rounds.
KATIE BRYCE: This is my year.
KATIE BRYCE: I could have won.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY (DB_VALIDATED, original: GEORGE O'MALLEY): Hello.
KATIE BRYCE: You're so lost. What are you, like, new?
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: Okay, so I'm just gonna insert my fingers into your rectum.
PATIENT (RECTAL EXAM): No.
PATIENT (RECTAL EXAM): Out.
ANOTHER PATIENT OR NURSE: Out.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: Bet you missed a lot when you first started out.
KATIE BRYCE: I twisted my ankle in talent rehearsal.
KATIE BRYCE: I do rhythmic gymnastics, which is, like, really cool.
KATIE BRYCE: Nobody else does it.
KATIE BRYCE: And I tripped over my ribbon. And I didn't get stuck with someone this clueless,
KATIE BRYCE: and that was, like, a nurse.
KATIE BRYCE: You and I are gonna have so much fun together.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: This shift is a marathon, not a sprint. Eat.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: I can't.
DR. ISOBEL STEVENS (DB_VALIDATED, original: IZZIE STEVENS): You should eat something.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY (DB_VALIDATED, original: GEORGE O'MALLEY): You try eating after performing 17 rectal exams. The Nazi hates me.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: The Nazi’s a resident. I have attendings hating me.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: You know Meredith is inbred?
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: Like it's uncommon around here to be a doctors' parents -
DR. CRISTINA YANG: No, royally inbred - her mother is Ellis Grey.
DR. ISOBEL STEVENS: Shut up. The Ellis Grey?
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY (DB_VALIDATED, original: GEORGE O'MALLEY): Who's Ellis Grey?
DR. CRISTINA YANG (DB_VALIDATED, original: CRISTINA YANG): The Grey Method. Where'd you go to med school - Mexico?
DR. ISOBEL STEVENS (DB_VALIDATED, original: IZZIE STEVENS): She was one of the first big chick surgeons.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY (DB_VALIDATED, original: GEORGE O'MALLEY): She's a living legend. Yeah, she won the harper Avery twice.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY (DB_VALIDATED, original: GEORGE O'MALLEY): So I didn't know one thing.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: Talk about parental pressure.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: God, I would kill to have Ellis Grey as a mother.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: I'd kill to be Ellis Grey.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: All I need is one good case.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Katie Bryce is a pain in the ass.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: If I hadn't taken the hippocratic oath, I'd Kevorkian her with my bare hands.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: What?
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: Good afternoon, interns.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: It's posted, but I thought I'd share the good news personally.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: As you know, the honor of performing the first surgery
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: is reserved for the intern that shows the most promise.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: As I'm running the O.R. today, I get to make that choice.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: George O’Malley.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: Me?
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: You'll scrub in for an appendectomy this afternoon.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: Congratulations.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: Enjoy it.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: Did he say me?
DR. ALEX KAREV (LLM_UNCERTAIN): I've seen his file. George O’Malley barely made the cut to get in this program.
DR. ALEX KAREV (LLM_UNCERTAIN): He's not your guy.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: He's my guy, all right.
DR. ALEX KAREV (LLM_UNCERTAIN): Every year, you pick your guy, and every year, your guy suffers more than any other intern.
DR. ALEX KAREV: Terrorize one, and the rest fall in line.
DR. ALEX KAREV (LLM_UNCERTAIN): I get it, I respect it, but George O’Malley’s a puppy.
NURSE OLIVIA HARPER (LLM_UNCERTAIN): - Katie Bryce - 3604? - It's right there.
MR. BRYCE (DB_VALIDATED, original: KATIE BRYCE'S PARENT): Thank you.
MR. BRYCE (DB_VALIDATED, original: KATIE BRYCE'S PARENT): Katie, honey, mom and dad are here.
DR. MEREDITH GREY (LLM_UNCERTAIN): They gave her a sedative for the C.T. scan, so she's a little groggy.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Will she be all right?
MR. BRYCE: Our doctor at home said that she might need an operation. Is that true?
DR. MEREDITH GREY: What kind of operation?
DR. MEREDITH GREY: She's, um - well...
DR. MEREDITH GREY: You know what? I'm not the doctor.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: I'm a doctor, but I'm not Katie's doctor, so I'll go get him for you.
DR. MEREDITH GREY (LLM_UNCERTAIN): What?
DR. MEREDITH GREY (LLM_UNCERTAIN): Katie's parents have questions. Do you talk to them, or do I ask Burke?
DR. CRISTINA YANG (LLM_UNCERTAIN): No, Burke's off the case. Katie belongs to the new
DR. CRISTINA YANG (LLM_UNCERTAIN): attending now, Dr. Shepherd. He's over there.
DR. MEREDITH GREY (LLM_UNCERTAIN): Dr. Shepherd.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): Dr. Shepherd?
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): This morning, it was Derek.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): Now it's Dr. Shepherd.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): Dr. Shepherd, we should pretend it never happened.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): What never happened - you sleeping with me last night, or you throwing me out this morning?
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): Because both are fond memories I'd like to hold onto.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: No, there will be no memories.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: I'm not the girl in the bar anymore, and you're not the guy.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): This can't exist.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: You get that, right?
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): You took advantage of me, and now you want to forget about it.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): I was drunk, vulnerable, and good-looking, and you took advantage.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Okay, I was the one who was drunk, and you are not that good-looking.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Maybe not today.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): Last night, I was very good-looking. I had my red shirt on. You took advantage.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: I did not take advantage.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): Want to take advantage again - say, friday night?
DR. MEREDITH GREY: No.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: You're an attending, and I'm your intern.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): Stop looking at me like that.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): Like what?
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Like you've seen me naked.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Dr. Shepherd, this is inappropriate.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: Has that ever occurred to you?
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY (DB_VALIDATED, original: INTERN (LIKELY GEORGE O'MALLEY OR ANOTHER INTERN RECITING STEPS)): Open, identify, ligate, remove, irrigate, close.
INTERN (LIKELY ANOTHER INTERN ECHOING THE MANTRA) (LLM_UNCERTAIN): Open, identify, ligate, remove, irrigate, close.
DR. ALEX KAREV (DB_VALIDATED, original: ALEX KAREV): He's gonna faint. He's a fainter.
DR. CRISTINA YANG (DB_VALIDATED, original: CRISTINA YANG): No, code brown, right in his pants.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: He's all about the flop sweat. He's gonna sweat himself unsterile.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: 10 bucks says he messes up the Mcburney.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: $15 says he cries.
DR. ALEX KAREV: I'll put $20 on a total meltdown.
DR. MEREDITH GREY (DB_VALIDATED, original: MEREDITH GREY): $50 says he pulls the whole thing off.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: That's one of us down there, the first one of us.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Where's your loyalty?
CRISTINA YANG AND ALEX KAREV: - $75 says he can't even I.D. the appendix. - I'll take that action.
DR. PRESTON BURKE: Okay, O’Malley, let's see what you can do.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Here it comes.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY (DB_VALIDATED, original: GEORGE O'MALLEY): Scalpel.
SURGICAL NURSE (LLM_UNCERTAIN): Scalpel.
DR. CRISTINA YANG (DB_VALIDATED, original: CRISTINA YANG): That burke is trouble.
DR. PRESTON BURKE: More pressure.
DR. PRESTON BURKE: The human flesh is a tough shell. Dig in.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY (DB_VALIDATED, original: GEORGE O'MALLEY): Pickups.
SURGICAL NURSE (LLM_UNCERTAIN): Pickups.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY (DB_VALIDATED, original: GEORGE O'MALLEY): Clamp.
SURGICAL NURSE (LLM_UNCERTAIN): Clamp.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: I'm there.
DR. ALEX KAREV: Damn, he got the peritoneum open. I'm out.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: I told you - he's gonna pull it off.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY (DB_VALIDATED, original: GEORGE O'MALLEY): Scalpel.
SURGICAL NURSE (LLM_UNCERTAIN): Scalpel.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: Appendix is out.
DR. PRESTON BURKE: Not bad.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: Thank you.
DR. PRESTON BURKE: Now all you have to do is invert the stump into the cecum
DR. PRESTON BURKE: and simultaneously pull up on the purse strings,
DR. PRESTON BURKE: but be careful not to...
DR. PRESTON BURKE: break them.
DR. PRESTON BURKE: You ripped the cecum.
DR. PRESTON BURKE: You've got a bleeder.
DR. PRESTON BURKE: You're filling with stool. What do you do now?
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: Uh...
DR. PRESTON BURKE: Think. You start the suction, and you start digging
DR. PRESTON BURKE: for those purse strings before she bleeds to death.
DR. PRESTON BURKE: Give him a clamp.
SURGICAL NURSE (LLM_UNCERTAIN): B.P.'s dropping.
KATIE BRYCE: He's choking.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Come on, George.
DR. PRESTON BURKE: Today. Pull your balls out of your back pocket. Let's go.
DR. PRESTON BURKE: What are you waiting for? Suction.
SURGICAL NURSE (LLM_UNCERTAIN): Getting too low, folks.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: Dr. Burke.
DR. PRESTON BURKE: Get out of the way.
DR. ALEX KAREV (DB_VALIDATED, original: ALEX KAREV): Pansy-ass idiot.
DR. PRESTON BURKE: Get him out of here.
DR. PRESTON BURKE (LLM_UNCERTAIN): Suction. Clamp.
CRISTINA YANG AND ALEX KAREV: - He's 007. - 007, yep.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: - A total 007. - What's "007" mean?
DR. CRISTINA YANG: License to kill.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: 007. They're calling me "007," aren't they?
DR. CRISTINA YANG (DB_VALIDATED, original: CRISTINA): - No one's calling you 007. - No one's calling you 007.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: On the elevator, murphy whispered, "007."
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: How many times do we have to go through this, George? 5, 10?
DR. CRISTINA YANG (DB_VALIDATED, original: CRISTINA): Give me a number, or else I'm gonna hit you.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: Murphy whispered, "007," and everyone laughed.
DR. ISOBEL STEVENS (DB_VALIDATED, original: IZZIE): He wasn't talking about you.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: Are you sure?
DR. CRISTINA YANG (DB_VALIDATED, original: CRISTINA): Would we lie to you?
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: Yes.
DR. CRISTINA YANG (DB_VALIDATED, original: CRISTINA): 007 is a state of mind.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: Says the girl who finished first in her class at Stanford.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Oh, man. It's 911 for Katie Bryce.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: I got to go.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: Maybe I should have gone into geriatrics.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: No one minds when you kill an old person.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: Surgery is hot. It's the marines. It's macho. It's hostile. It's hard-core.
DR. CRISTINA YANG (DB_VALIDATED, original: CRISTINA): Geriatrics is for freaks who live with their mothers and never have sex.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: I've got to get my own place.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Excuse me! Excuse me!
KATIE BRYCE: Took you long enough.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: You're okay? The nurse paged me "911."
KATIE BRYCE: I had to go all "exorcist" to get her to even pick up the phone.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Wait.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: There's nothing wrong with you?
KATIE BRYCE: I'm bored.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: You little...
DR. MEREDITH GREY: - I'm not a cruise director. - You don't have to wig out.
KATIE BRYCE: The pageant's supposed to be on cable, but this crappy hospital doesn't get the channel.
KATIE BRYCE: If that cow kylie wood is gonna walk off with my crown, I have to see it.
KATIE BRYCE: Can you call someone?
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Okay, this is an actual hospital.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: There are sick people here.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Go to sleep, and stop wasting my time.
KATIE BRYCE: But I can't sleep. My head's all full.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: That's called "thinking."
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Go with it.
DR. ISOBEL STEVENS (DB_VALIDATED, original: IZZIE): What do you need?
NURSE (LLM_UNCERTAIN): Mr. Jones has junky veins, and he really needs antibiotics.
DR. ISOBEL STEVENS (DB_VALIDATED, original: IZZIE): I should start a central line.
DR. PRESTON BURKE: So start one.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: You don't know how.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: I've never done one.
NURSE: Well, you know what that means.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: Can't we just page someone else?
NURSE: She's the on-call resident.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: Okay.
DR. ISOBEL STEVENS: Okay, I'll just - I'll wake her.
DR. ISOBEL STEVENS (DB_VALIDATED, original: IZZIE): - Dr. Bailey, I don't mean to bother you. - Then don't.
DR. ISOBEL STEVENS (DB_VALIDATED, original: IZZIE): - It's Mr. Jones. - Is he dying?
DR. ISOBEL STEVENS (DB_VALIDATED, original: IZZIE): No.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: Then stop talking to me.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: What is it?!
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: Next time you wake me, he better be so close to dead, there's a tag on his toe.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: Here. Take these to the lab.
DR. ISOBEL STEVENS (DB_VALIDATED, original: IZZIE STEVENS): 4-b's got post-op pneumonia.
DR. ALEX KAREV (DB_VALIDATED, original: ALEX KAREV): Let's start antibiotics.
DR. ISOBEL STEVENS (DB_VALIDATED, original: IZZIE STEVENS): Are you sure that's the right diagnosis?
DR. ALEX KAREV: Well, I don't know. I'm only an intern.
DR. ALEX KAREV: Why don't you go spend 4 years in med school and then let me know if it's the right diagnosis?
DR. ISOBEL STEVENS (DB_VALIDATED, original: IZZIE STEVENS): She's short of breath. She's got fever. She's post-op.
DR. ALEX KAREV: Start the antibiotics.
DR. ALEX KAREV: God, I hate nurses.
DR. ALEX KAREV: I'm Alex.
DR. ALEX KAREV: I'm with Jeremy. You're with the Nazi, right?
DR. ISOBEL STEVENS (DB_VALIDATED, original: IZZIE STEVENS): She may not have pneumonia, you know? She could be splinting, or have a P.E.
DR. ALEX KAREV: Like I said, I hate nurses.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: What did you just say?
DR. ISOBEL STEVENS (DB_VALIDATED, original: IZZIE STEVENS): Did you just call me a nurse?
DR. ALEX KAREV: Well, if the white cap fits.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Damn it, Katie.
DR. ALEX KAREV: Is she seeing anybody?
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: I don't know.
DR. ALEX KAREV: She's hot.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: I'm friends with her.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: I mean kind of friends - not actually friends, exactly,
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: but we're tight, and we hang out - really, only just today.
DR. ALEX KAREV: - Dude. - Dude, stop talking.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY (DB_VALIDATED, original: DR. BAILEY): What took you so long?
NURSE (LLM_UNCERTAIN): She's having multiple grand mal seizures.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Now, how do you want to proceed?
NURSE: Dr. Grey, are you listening to me?!
NURSE: She's got diazepam - 2 milligrams lorazepam - I just gave the second dose.
NURSE (LLM_UNCERTAIN): Dr. Grey, you need to tell us what you want to do.
NURSE (LLM_UNCERTAIN): Dr. Grey!
DR. MEREDITH GREY (DB_VALIDATED, original: MEREDITH GREY): - Okay, she's full on lorazepam? - She's had 4 milligrams.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: You paged Dr. Bailey and Dr. Shepherd?
NURSE: Lorazepam's not working.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Phenobarbital - load her with phenobarbital.
NURSE: Pheno's in.
NURSE: No change.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: - You paged Dr. Shepherd? - I just told you.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Well, page him again, stat.
NURSE (LLM_UNCERTAIN): What do you want to do?
NURSE (LLM_UNCERTAIN): Dr. Grey, you need to tell us what you want to do.
NURSE (LLM_UNCERTAIN): - Heart stopped. - Code blue! Code blue!
NURSE (LLM_UNCERTAIN): Code blue! Code blue!
DR. MEREDITH GREY (DB_VALIDATED, original: MEREDITH GREY): Wait.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Charge the pads to 200.
NURSE: Charge.
DR. MEREDITH GREY (DB_VALIDATED, original: MEREDITH GREY): Clear.
NURSE: Still v-fib. Nothing.
NURSE: Charging.
NURSE: 19 seconds.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Charge them to 300.
NURSE: 300. Anything?
NURSE: 27 seconds.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Charge to 360.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Come on, Katie.
NURSE: 49 seconds.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: At 60 seconds, you're supposed to admin her another drug.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Charge again!
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: Charge again.
DR. MEREDITH GREY (DB_VALIDATED, original: MEREDITH GREY): Anything?
NURSE: I see sinus rhythm.
NURSE: Blood pressure's coming up.
DR. MEREDITH GREY (DB_VALIDATED, original: MEREDITH GREY): All right.
NURSE: Pressure's returning.
NURSE: Rate's coming back.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: What the hell happened?
DR. MEREDITH GREY: She had a seizure, and her heart stopped.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY (DB_VALIDATED, original: DR. BAILEY): You were supposed to be monitoring her.
NURSE (LLM_UNCERTAIN): - I checked on her - - I got her. Just - just go.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: Somebody give me her -
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: give me her chart, please.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: You get a 911, you page me immediately,
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: not in the 5 minutes it takes you to get to the emergency, immediately.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: You're on my team, and if somebody dies, it's my ass.
DR. MIRANDA BAILEY: Meredith?
DR. MEREDITH GREY: You tell anyone, ever...
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): You said it was a seizure disorder.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): Now you're saying it isn't?
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): I'm saying that I don't know.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): What do you think it could be?
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): I don't know.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): When will you know?
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): I don't have an answer for you.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): - For now, Katie is stable, and - - Wait one damn minute.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): We came here because this hospital is supposed to be the best in Washington.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): That's my kid in there - my kid -
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): and you have the audacity to stand here and tell me, "I don't know."
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): Mr. Bryce -
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): No, I want someone else, a doctor who knows what they're doing.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): You get me someone else, someone better than you.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): Mr. Bryce, I assure you that I am working hard on Katie's case.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): No, you're not. If you were, you'd be able to give me some answers.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): I put you on the bypass machine, which pumps blood for your heart.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): Fix your ticker, take you off the machine - I'm done - simple procedure.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): So I shouldn't worry?
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): I'm very good at what I do.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): But still it's surgery.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): There are some risks.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): I'll see you in the O.R. this afternoon, Mr. Savitch.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): You're not gonna leave me alone with that guy, are you?
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): Oh, I'll be outside the O.R. the whole time.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: No, Dr. Burke is very good.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: Don't worry.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): I'll see you after.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): He'll be fine, right?
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): Tony's gonna sail through it.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: You have nothing to worry about - I promise.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: I gotta go.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): What are you doing?
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): I'm suturing a banana with the vain hope that it wakes up my brain.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): What are you smiling at, 007?
DR. MEREDITH GREY: I'm sorry. I get mean when I'm tired.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: You know what?
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: I don't care.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: I comforted a family, and I got to hang out in the O.R. today. All is well.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Does anybody know why we're here?
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): Well, good morning.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): I'm gonna do something pretty rare for a surgeon.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): I'm gonna ask interns for help.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: I've got this kid, Katie Bryce.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: Right now, she's a mystery.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): She doesn't respond to our meds.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): The labs are clean, the scans are pure,
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): but she's having seizures - grand mal seizures with no visible cause.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): She's a ticking clock.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): She's gonna die if I don't make a diagnosis, which is where you come in.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): I can't do it alone.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): I need your extra minds, extra eyes.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): I need you to play detective. I need you to find out why Katie is having seizures.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): I know you're tired. You're busy. You got more work than you can possibly handle.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): I understand, so I'm gonna give you an incentive.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): Whoever finds the answer rides with me.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): Katie needs surgery.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): You get to do what no interns get to do - scrub in to assist on an advanced procedure.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Dr. Bailey's gonna hand you Katie's chart.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): The clock is ticking fast, people.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): If we're gonna save Katie's life, we have to do it soon.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): Did you just page me?
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Yes. 4-B's still short of breath.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): Look, give the antibiotics time to work.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): The antibiotics should have worked by now.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): She's old. She's freaking ancient.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: She's lucky she's still breathing.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): I got a shot to scrub in downstairs on a patient that wasn't alive during the civil war.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): Don't page me again.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Hey, I want in on shepherd's surgery.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: You've been the intern on Katie since the start.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: You want to work together?
DR. MEREDITH GREY: If we find the answer, we have a 50-50 chance of scrubbing in.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: I'll work with you, but I don't want in on the surgery. You can have it.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: You're kidding? It's the biggest opportunity any intern will ever get.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: I don't want to spend any more time with Shepherd than I have to.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: What do you have against shepherd?
DR. MEREDITH GREY: If we find the answer, the surgery's yours. Do you want to work together or not?
DR. CRISTINA YANG: Deal.
DR. MEREDITH GREY (DB_VALIDATED, original: MEREDITH GREY): So she doesn't have anoxia, chronic renal failure, or acidosis.
DR. CRISTINA YANG (DB_VALIDATED, original: CRISTINA YANG): It's not a tumor, because her C.T.'s clean.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: Are you seriously not gonna tell me why you won't work with Shepherd?
DR. MEREDITH GREY: No.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: What about infection?
DR. MEREDITH GREY: No, there's no white count, and she has no C.T. lesions, no fevers,
DR. CRISTINA YANG: nothing in her spinal tap. Just tell me.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: You can't comment, make a face, or react in any way.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: We had sex.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: What about an aneurysm?
DR. MEREDITH GREY: No blood on the C.T. and no headaches.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: Okay, there's no drug use, no pregnancy, no trauma.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: Was he good?
DR. CRISTINA YANG: I mean, he looks like he'd be good. Was it any good?
DR. MEREDITH GREY: We're out of answers.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: What if no one comes up with anything?
DR. MEREDITH GREY: You mean what if she dies?
DR. CRISTINA YANG: Yeah.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: This is gonna sound really bad, but I really wanted that surgery.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: She's just never gonna get the chance to turn into a person.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: The sum total of her existence will be almost winning miss teen whatever.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: You know what her pageant talent is?
DR. CRISTINA YANG: They have talent?
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Rhythmic gymnastics.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: Oh, come on.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: What is rhythmic gymnastics? I can't even say it.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: I don't know what it is.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: I think it's something with a ball and a -
DR. CRISTINA YANG: What?
DR. CRISTINA YANG: Meredith, what?
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Get up. Come on.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: The only thing that she would possibly need is an angiogram.
DR. MEREDITH GREY (DB_VALIDATED, original: MEREDITH GREY): Oh. Oh, Dr. Shepherd, just one moment.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: Katie competes in beauty pageants.
DR. MEREDITH GREY (DB_VALIDATED, original: MEREDITH GREY): I know that, but we have to save her life, anyway.
DR. DEREK SHEPHERD (LLM_UNCERTAIN): She has no headaches, no neck pain, her C.T. is clean.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: - There's no medical proof of an aneurysm. - Right.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: - But what if she has an aneurysm, anyway? - There are no indicators.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: She twisted her ankle practicing for the pageant.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: - I appreciate you trying to help, but - - She fell when she twisted her ankle, she fell.
DR. CRISTINA YANG (DB_VALIDATED, original: CRISTINA YANG): It was no big deal, not even a bump on the head. She
DR. MEREDITH GREY: got up, iced her ankle, and everything was fine.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: It was a fall so minor, her doctor didn't even
DR. CRISTINA YANG: think to mention it when I was taking her history,
DR. MEREDITH GREY: but she did fall.
DR. DEREK SHEPHERD (LLM_UNCERTAIN): You know what the chance is that a minor fall could burst an aneurysm?
DR. DEREK SHEPHERD: One in a million - literally.
DR. DEREK SHEPHERD (LLM_UNCERTAIN): Let's go.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: Where?
DR. DEREK SHEPHERD: To find out if Katie's one in a million.
DR. DEREK SHEPHERD: I'll be damned.
DR. DEREK SHEPHERD: There it is.
DR. DEREK SHEPHERD: It's minute, but it's there.
DR. DEREK SHEPHERD: It's a subarachnoid hemorrhage.
DR. DEREK SHEPHERD: She's bleeding into her brain.
DR. DEREK SHEPHERD: She could have gone through her entire life without it ever being a problem.
DR. DEREK SHEPHERD (LLM_UNCERTAIN): - One tap in the right spot... - And it exploded.
DR. DEREK SHEPHERD: Exactly. Now I can fix it.
DR. DEREK SHEPHERD: You two did great work.
DR. DEREK SHEPHERD: Love to stay and kiss your asses, but I got to tell Katie's parents she's having surgery.
DR. DEREK SHEPHERD: - Katie Bryce's chart, please. - Here you go.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: Dr. Shepherd, you'd said that you'd pick someone to scrub in if we helped?
DR. DEREK SHEPHERD: Oh, yes, right. I'm sorry I can't take you both.
DR. DEREK SHEPHERD: It's gonna be a full house.
DR. DEREK SHEPHERD: Meredith, I'll see you in O.R.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): Good. Thank you.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Cristina...
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: Wow, that was quick.
DR. PRESTON BURKE: His heart had too much damage to give him a bypass.
DR. PRESTON BURKE (DB_VALIDATED, original: DR. BURKE): I had to let him go.
DR. PRESTON BURKE (DB_VALIDATED, original: DR. BURKE): It happens - rarely, but it does happen -
DR. PRESTON BURKE: the worst part of the game.
INTERN (LLM_UNCERTAIN): But I told his wife - I told Gloria that he would be fine.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: - I promised her that - - You what?
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: - They have four little girls. - This is my case.
DR. PRESTON BURKE (DB_VALIDATED, original: DR. BURKE): Did you hear me promise?
DR. PRESTON BURKE: The only one that can keep a promise like that is
DR. PRESTON BURKE: god, and I haven't seen him holding a scalpel lately.
DR. PRESTON BURKE: You never promise a patient's family a good outcome!
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: I thought...
DR. PRESTON BURKE: You're important enough to make promises to Mrs. Savitch?
DR. PRESTON BURKE: You get to be the one to tell her that she's a widow.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): Izzie.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): - Maybe Meredith couldn't - - Izzie.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: - I'll tell him I changed my mind. - Don't do me any favors. It's fine.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: - Cristina - - You did a cutthroat thing. Deal with it.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: Don't come to me for absolution. You want to be a shark, be a shark.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: - I'm not - - Oh, yes, you are.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: Only it makes you feel all bad in your warm, gooey places.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: No, screw you.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: I don't get picked for surgeries 'cause I slept with my boss,
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): and I didn't get into med school 'cause I have a famous mother.
DR. CRISTINA YANG: Some of us have to earn what we get.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): Gloria, there were complications in the surgery.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: Tony's heart had a lot of damage.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): We tried to take him off bypass, but...
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): there wasn't anything we could have done.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: What are you talking about?
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: He...
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: Tony died.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: He's dead.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: Gloria...
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: I am so sorry.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Please...
DR. MEREDITH GREY: go away.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: I promised I'd make her look cool.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): Apparently, being a bald beauty queen is the worst
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): thing that happened in the history of the world.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Did you choose me for the surgery because I slept with you?
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): Yes.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): I'm kidding.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: I'm not gonna scrub in for surgery.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: You should ask Cristina. She really wants it.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): You're Katie's doctor.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): And on your first day, with very little training, you helped save her life.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): You earned the right to follow her case through to the finish.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): You shouldn't let the fact that we had sex get in the way of you taking your shot.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: I wish I wanted to be a chef
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: or a ski instructor or a kindergarten teacher.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: You know, I would have been a really good postal worker.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: I'm dependable.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: You know, my parents tell everyone they meet that their son's a surgeon,
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: as if it's a big accomplishment -
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: superhero or something.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: If they could see me now.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: When I told my mother I wanted to go to medical school,
DR. MEREDITH GREY: she tried to talk me out of it -
DR. MEREDITH GREY: said I didn't have what it takes to be a surgeon,
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: that I'd never make it.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: So the way I see it, superhero sounds pretty damn good.
DR. GEORGE O'MALLEY: We're gonna survive this, right?
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): She's still short of breath. Did you get an abg or a chest film?
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): Oh, yes, sir, I did.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: And what did you see?
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): Oh, well, I had a lot of patients last night.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): Name the common causes of post-op fever.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): - Uh, yes. - From your head, not from a book.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): Don't look it up. Learn it. It should be in your head.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): Name the common causes of post-op fever.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): Uh... the common causes of post-
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): Can anybody name the common causes of post-op fever?
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Wind, Water, Wound, Walking, Wonder drugs - the five W's -
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): most of the time, it's Wind -
DR. MEREDITH GREY: splinting or pneumonia.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Pneumonia's easy to assume, especially if you're too busy to do the tests.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): What do you think's wrong with 4-b?
DR. MEREDITH GREY: The fourth "W," "Walking."
DR. MEREDITH GREY: I think she's a prime candidate for a pulmonary embolus.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): How would you diagnose?
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Spiral C.T., V/Q scan, provide O2,
DR. MEREDITH GREY: dose with heparin, and consult for an IVC filter.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): Do exactly as she says, then tell your resident that I want you off this case.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): I'd know you anywhere. You're the spitting image of your mother.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): Welcome to the game.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): All right, everybody. It's a beautiful night to save lives.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): Let's have some fun.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): I can't think of any one reason why I want to be a surgeon...
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): but I can think of a thousand reasons why I should quit.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): They make it hard on purpose.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): There are lives in our hands.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): There comes a moment when it's more than just a game...
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): And you either take that step forward
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): or turn around and walk away.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): I could quit,
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): but here's the thing...
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): I love the playing field.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): - It was good surgery. - Yeah.
DR. MEREDITH GREY (DB_VALIDATED, original: MEREDITH GREY): We don't have to do that thing where I say something, and then you say something,
DR. MEREDITH GREY (DB_VALIDATED, original: MEREDITH GREY): and then somebody cries, and there's a moment.
DR. CRISTINA YANG (DB_VALIDATED, original: CRISTINA YANG): Yuck.
DR. MEREDITH GREY (DB_VALIDATED, original: MEREDITH GREY): Good.
DR. CRISTINA YANG (DB_VALIDATED, original: CRISTINA YANG): You should get some sleep.
DR. CRISTINA YANG (DB_VALIDATED, original: CRISTINA YANG): You look like crap.
DR. MEREDITH GREY (DB_VALIDATED, original: MEREDITH GREY): I look better than you.
DR. CRISTINA YANG (DB_VALIDATED, original: CRISTINA YANG): That's not possible.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: That was amazing.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: You practice on cadavers...
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): you observe...
DR. MEREDITH GREY: and you think you know what you're gonna feel like, standing over that table, but...
DR. MEREDITH GREY: that was such a high.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: I don't know why anybody does drugs.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): Yeah.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): I should, uh, go do this.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: You should.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): I'll see you around.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): See you around.
UNKNOWN (LOW_CONF): See you.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: So...
DR. MEREDITH GREY: I made it through my first shift.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: We all did.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: The other interns are all good people. You'd like them...
DR. MEREDITH GREY: I think.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: I don't know - maybe.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: I like them.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: Oh, and I changed my mind.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: I'm not gonna sell the house.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: I'm gonna keep it.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: I'll have to get a couple of roommates, but...
DR. MEREDITH GREY: it's home, you know?
DR. ELLIS GREY: Are you the doctor?
DR. MEREDITH GREY: No.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: I'm not your doctor,
DR. MEREDITH GREY: but I am a doctor.
DR. ELLIS GREY (DB_VALIDATED, original: ELLIS GREY): What's your name?
DR. MEREDITH GREY: It's me, mom - Meredith.
DR. ELLIS GREY: All right.
DR. ELLIS GREY: I used to be a doctor, I think.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: You were a doctor, mom.
DR. MEREDITH GREY: You were a surgeon.