Meredith Grey: The game.
Meredith Grey: They say a person either has what it takes to play or they don't.
Meredith Grey: My mother was one of the greats.
Meredith Grey: Me, on the other hand, I'm kind of screwed.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): This is, uh... Humiliating on so many levels.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): You have to go.
Derek Shepherd / Meredith Grey (PVM): Why don't you just come back down here and we'll pick up where we left off?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): No, seriously.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): You have to go.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm late.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Which isn't what you want to be on your first day of work, so... So, uh, you actually live here?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): No.
Derek Shepherd / Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Yes.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Kind of.
Derek Shepherd / Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): It's nice.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): A little dusty.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Odd, but it's nice.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): So how do you kind of live here?
Meredith Grey: I moved two weeks ago from Boston.
Meredith Grey: It was my mother's house.
Meredith Grey: I'm selling it.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Oh, I'm sorry.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): For what?
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): You said was.
Meredith / Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, my mother's not dead.
Meredith / Meredith Grey (PVM): She's... You know what?
Meredith / Meredith Grey (PVM): We don't have to do the thing.
Derek / Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh.
Derek / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): We can do anything you want.
Meredith / Meredith Grey (PVM): No, the thing.
Meredith / Meredith Grey (PVM): Exchange the details.
Meredith / Meredith Grey (PVM): Pretend we care.
Meredith / Meredith Grey (PVM): Look, I'm gonna go upstairs and take a shower, okay?
Meredith / Meredith Grey (PVM): And when I get back down here, you won't be here.
Meredith / Meredith Grey (PVM): So, um... Goodbye.
Derek / Meredith Grey (PVM): Um...
Dr. Derek Shepherd: Derek.
Meredith Grey: Derek.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: Right, Meredith.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: Meredith?
Meredith Grey: Yeah.
Meredith Grey: Mm-hmm.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: Nice meeting you.
Meredith Grey: Bye, Derek.
Meredith Grey: Each of you comes here today hopeful, wanting in on the game.
Meredith Grey: A month ago, you were in med school being taught by doctors.
Meredith Grey: Today, you are the doctors.
Meredith Grey: The seven years you spend here as a surgical resident will be the best and worst of your life.
Meredith Grey: You will be pushed to the breaking point.
Meredith Grey: Look around you.
Dr. Richard Webber / Meredith Grey (PVM): Say hello to your competition.
Dr. Richard Webber / Meredith Grey (PVM): Eight of you will switch to an easier specialty.
Dr. Richard Webber / Meredith Grey (PVM): Five of you will crack under the pressure.
Dr. Richard Webber / Meredith Grey (PVM): Two of you will be asked to leave.
Dr. Richard Webber / Meredith Grey (PVM): This is your starting line.
Dr. Richard Webber / Meredith Grey (PVM): This is your arena.
Dr. Richard Webber / Meredith Grey (PVM): How well you play, that's up to you.
Meredith Grey: Like I said, I'm screwed.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Meredith Grey OR George O'Malley (PVM): OK, Martin, Robinson, Vaughn, Hawkins, Vaughn.
Unknown Intern / Meredith Grey (PVM): Only six women out of 20.
Unknown Intern / Meredith Grey (PVM): Yeah, I hear one of them's a model.
Unknown Intern / Meredith Grey (PVM): Seriously, that's going to help with the respect thing?
Unknown Intern / Meredith Grey OR George O'Malley (PVM): You're Christina, right?
Dr. Miranda Bailey / George O'Malley (PVM): Hutton, Monroe, Krug, Osborne.
Unknown Intern / Meredith Grey OR George O'Malley (PVM): Here we go.
Unknown Intern / Meredith Grey (PVM): Which resident are you assigned to?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): I got Bailey.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Nazi?
Unknown Intern / Meredith Grey (PVM): Me too.
Unknown Intern / Meredith Grey (PVM): You got the Nazi?
Unknown Intern / Meredith Grey (PVM): So did I. At least we'll be tortured together, right?
George O'Malley: I'm George.
George O'Malley: O'Malley, we met at the mixer you had on a black dress with a slit at the side, strappy sandals.
George O'Malley: Now you think I'm gay.
George O'Malley: No, I'm not gay.
George O'Malley: It's just that you were very unforgettable.
Unidentified Announcer or Resident / George O'Malley (PVM): O'Malley, Yang, Gray, Steven.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): That's the Nazi?
Cristina Yang / George O'Malley (PVM): I thought the Nazi would be a guy.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR George O'Malley (PVM): I thought the Nazi would be... a Nazi.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Maybe it's professional jealousy.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Maybe she's brilliant and they call her a Nazi because they're jealous.
George O'Malley / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Maybe she's nice.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Let me guess, you're the model.
Dr. Izzie Stevens: Hi, I'm Isabelle Stevens, but everyone calls me Izzy.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: I have five rules.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Memorize them.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Rule number one, don't bother sucking up.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: I already hate you.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: That's not going to change.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Trauma protocol, phone list, pagers.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Nurses will page you.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: You answer every page at a run.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: A run, that's rule number two.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Your first shift starts now and lasts 48 hours.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Your interns, grunts, nobodies, bottom of the surgical food chain.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Run labs, write orders, work every second night until you drop, and don't complain.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: On call rooms.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Attendings hog them.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Sleep when you can, where you can.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Which brings me to rule number three.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: If I'm sleeping, don't wake me unless your patient is actually dying.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Rule number four, the dying patient better not be dead when I get there.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Not only will you have killed someone, you would have woke me for no good reason.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: We clear?
Interns / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Yes.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): You said five rules.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): That was only four.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Rule number five, when I move, you move.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: What do we got?
Paramedic / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Katie Bryce, 15-year-old female, new onset seizures, intermittent for the past week.
Paramedic / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): IV lost in root, started grandma seizing as we descended.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: All right, get on her side.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Izzy, 10 milligrams diazepam IM.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: No, no, the white lead is on the right.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Righty, whitey, smoke over fire.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: A large bore IV, don't let the blood hemolyze.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Let's go.
Dr. Preston Burke: We got no wet fish on dry land.
Intern / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Absolutely, Dr. Burke.
Dr. Preston Burke: Dr. Bailey, no shotgun.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: That means every test in the book, CT, CBC, CHEM-7, tox screen.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Christina, you're on labs.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: George, patient workups.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Meredith, get Katie for a CT.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: She's your responsibility now.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Wait, what about me?
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Honey, you get to do rectal exams.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): What are you doing here?
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Good morning.
Christina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Katie, Bryce's labs came out clear.
Christina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): There's nothing in the results that explain her seizures.
Christina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): I just thought you'd want to know.
Meredith Grey / Unknown (PVM): OK.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): I heard every year the attending on-call picks the best intern and lets them perform a procedure during the first shift.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm just saying it's what I heard.
Christina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Get away.
Christina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Now.
Izzy Stevens / Meredith Grey OR Alex Karev (PVM): Yeah, sounds good.
Izzy Stevens / Alex Karev (PVM): You'll be fine.
Patient (Katie Bryce) / Meredith Grey OR George O'Malley OR Alex Karev (PVM): If you don't count the fact that my bacon days are over, sure.
Patient (Katie Bryce) / George O'Malley (PVM): Should I bypass surgery tomorrow with Dr. Burke?
Izzy Stevens / George O'Malley (PVM): I hear he's good.
Izzy Stevens / George O'Malley OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): And after that, you can have all the bacon-flavored soy product you can eat.
Patient (Katie Bryce) / George O'Malley (PVM): Mm, kill me now.
Izzy Stevens / George O'Malley OR George O'Malley (PVM): I wish I could, but I'm a healer.
Dr. Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): You're lost.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm not lost.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): How are you feeling?
Katie Bryce: How do you think I'm feeling?
Katie Bryce: I'm missing my pageant.
Meredith Grey / Katie Bryce (PVM): You're missing your pageant.
Katie Bryce: The Spokane Teen Miss.
Katie Bryce / Katie Bryce (PVM): I was in the top ten after the first two rounds.
Katie Bryce / Katie Bryce (PVM): This is my year.
Katie Bryce / Katie Bryce OR Meredith Grey (PVM): I could have won.
Meredith Grey / Katie Bryce OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Hello?
Katie Bryce / Katie Bryce (PVM): You're so lost.
Katie Bryce / Katie Bryce OR Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): What are you, like, new?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Okay, so I'm just gonna insert my fingers into your rectum.
Katie Bryce / George O'Malley OR Meredith Grey (PVM): I bet you missed a lot when you first started out.
Katie Bryce / Katie Bryce (PVM): I twisted my ankle in talent rehearsal.
Katie Bryce / Katie Bryce (PVM): I do rhythmic gymnastics, which is, like, really cool.
Katie Bryce / Katie Bryce (PVM): Nobody else does it.
Katie Bryce / Katie Bryce (PVM): And I tripped over my ribbon, and I didn't get stuck with someone this clueless.
Katie Bryce / Katie Bryce OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): And that was, like, a nurse.
Katie Bryce / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You and I are going to have so much fun together.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Yeah.
Miranda Bailey / Alex Karev (PVM): A shift is a marathon, not a sprint.
Miranda Bailey / Alex Karev (PVM): Eat.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Alex Karev (PVM): I can't.
Miranda Bailey / Alex Karev (PVM): You should eat something.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You try eating after performing 17 rectal exams.
George O'Malley / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): The Nazi hates me.
Cristina Yang / Alex Karev (PVM): The Nazi's a resident.
Cristina Yang / Alex Karev OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I have attendings hating me.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You know Meredith is inbred?
Cristina Yang / Alex Karev OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Like it's uncommon around here to be a doctor's parent.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey OR Alex Karev OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): No, royally inbred.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Her mother is Alice Gray.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Shut up, the Alice Gray.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): Who's Alice Gray?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Alice.
Alex Karev / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Where'd you go to med school, Mexico?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): She was one of the first big chick surgeons.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I mean, she practically invented the pep double.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): She's a living legend.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): You know, she won the Harper Avery twice.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): So I didn't know one thing.
Alex Karev / Meredith Grey (PVM): Talk about points of pressure.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): God, I would kill to have Ellis Gray as a mother.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): I'd kill to be Ellis Gray.
Alex Karev / Meredith Grey (PVM): All I need is one big kiss.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Come on.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Katie Bryce is a pain in the ass.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): If I hadn't checked in the Hippocratic Oath, I could work in her with my bare hands.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): What?
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Good afternoon, interns.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: It's posted, but I thought I'd share the good news personally.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: As you know, the honor of performing first surgery is reserved for the intern that shows the most promise.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: As I'm running the OR today, I get to make that choice.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: George O'Malley.
George O'Malley: Me?
Dr. Miranda Bailey: You'll scrub in for an appendectomy this afternoon.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Congratulations.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Enjoy.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Alex Karev (PVM): Did he say me?
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I've seen his file.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): George O'Malley barely made the cut to get in this program.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): He's not your guy.
Dr. Richard Webber / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Oh, he's my guy, all right.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Every year, you pick your guy.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): And every year, your guy suffers more than any other internal search.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Terrorize one, and the rest fall in line.
Dr. Richard Webber / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I get it.
Dr. Richard Webber / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I respect it.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): But George O'Malley's a puppy.
Nurse / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Katie Bryce, 36 and 4.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Thank you.
Nurse / Meredith Grey (PVM): Katie, honey, mom and dad are here.
Dr. Isobel 'Izzie' Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): They gave her a sedative for the CT scan, so she's a little groggy.
Katie's Mom / Meredith Grey (PVM): Will she be all right?
Katie's Dad / Mr. Bryce (PVM): Our doctor at home said that she might need an operation.
Katie's Mom / Mr. Bryce (PVM): Is that true?
Katie's Dad / Meredith Grey (PVM): What kind of operation?
Dr. Isobel Stevens: She's, um, well, you know what?
Dr. Isobel Stevens: I'm not the doctor.
Dr. Isobel Stevens: I'm a doctor, but I'm not Katie's doctor.
Dr. Isobel Stevens: So I'll go get him for you.
Dr. Isobel 'Izzie' Stevens / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): What?
Dr. Isobel 'Izzie' Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Katie's parents have questions.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Do you talk to them, or do I ask Burke?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): No, Burke's off the case.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Katie belongs to the new attending now.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Dr. Shepherd, he's over there.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Eric, can I talk to you for a second?
Eric (intern) / Meredith Grey (PVM): Actually, I was... Dr. Shepard?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Dr. Shepard?
Dr. Derek Shepherd: This morning it was Derek.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: Now it's Dr. Shepherd.
Meredith Grey: Dr. Shepherd, we should pretend it never happened.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: What never happened?
Meredith Grey: You sleeping with me last night?
Dr. Derek Shepherd: Or you throwing me out this morning?
Dr. Derek Shepherd: Because both are fond memories I like to hold on to.
Meredith Grey: No.
Meredith Grey: There will be no memories.
Meredith Grey: I'm not the girl in the bar anymore, and you're not the guy.
Meredith Grey: This can't exist.
Meredith Grey: You get that, right?
Dr. Derek Shepherd: You took advantage of me, and now you want to forget about it.
Meredith Grey: I did not take... I was drunk, vulnerable, and good-looking, and you took advantage.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: Okay, I was the one who was drunk, and you are not that good-looking.
Meredith Grey: Maybe not today.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: Last night?
Meredith Grey: Last night I was very good-looking.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: I had my red shirt on, my good-looking shirt, and you took advantage.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): I did not take advantage.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Well, take advantage again.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Say Friday night.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): No.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): You're an attending, and I'm your intern.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Stop looking at me like that.
Derek Shepherd / Meredith Grey (PVM): Like what?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Like you've seen me naked.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Dr. Shepherd, this is inappropriate.
Derek Shepherd / Meredith Grey (PVM): Has that ever occurred to you?
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): Open, identify, ligate, remove, irrigate, close.
Alex Karev / Meredith Grey (PVM): He's going to faint.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR George O'Malley (PVM): He's a fainter.
Alex Karev / Meredith Grey OR George O'Malley (PVM): No, code brown right in his pants.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey OR George O'Malley (PVM): He's all about the flop sweat.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): He's going to sweat himself unsterile.
Alex Karev / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): $10 says he messes up the McBurney.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): $15 says he cries.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): I'll put $20 on a total meltdown.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): $50 says he pulls the whole thing off.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): That's one of us down there.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): The first one of us.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Where's your loyalty?
Alex Karev / Meredith Grey (PVM): 75 says he can't even ID the appendix.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I'll take that, actually.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): OK, O'Malley, let's see what you can do.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Here it comes.
George O'Malley / Alex Karev OR Alex Karev (PVM): Scalpel.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): More pressure.
Dr. Bailey / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Human flesh is a tough shell.
Dr. Bailey / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Dig in.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Pickups?
Nurse (Bokhee or scrub nurse) / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Pickups.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Clamps?
Nurse (Bokhee or scrub nurse) / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Clamps.
Dr. Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Let's move.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm there.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Damn, he got the first knee in my mouth.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey OR George O'Malley OR Katie Bryce (PVM): I told you, he's gonna pull it off.
George O'Malley / Alex Karev OR Alex Karev (PVM): Scalpel.
Dr. Bailey / Mr. Bryce OR Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Alex Karev OR Alex Karev (PVM): Appendix is out.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Alex Karev (PVM): Not bad.
George O'Malley: Thank you.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Now all you have to do is invert the stump into the sequel and simultaneously pull up on the purse strings, but be careful not to break them.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You ripped a seagum.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You've got a bleeding.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You're filling with stool.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): What do you do now?
George O'Malley: Uh, think.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You start the suction, and you start digging for those purse strings before she bleeds to death.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Bucky, give him a clamp.
Nurse / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): BP's dropping.
Nurse / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): He's choking.
Intern (likely Cristina or Izzie) / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Come on, George.
Intern (likely Cristina or Alex) / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Today.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Pull your balls out of your back pocket.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Let's go.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): What are you waiting for?
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Suction?
Nurse / Meredith Grey (PVM): Getting too low, folks.
Nurse / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Dr. Burke.
Dr. Preston Burke: Get out of the way.
Dr. Preston Burke: Pansy-ass idiot.
Dr. Preston Burke: Get him out of here.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Preston Burke OR Alex Karev (PVM): Suction.
Dr. Burke / Alex Karev (PVM): Clamp.
Intern (likely Alex Karev) / Alex Karev (PVM): It's 007.
Intern (likely Cristina Yang) / Alex Karev (PVM): 007, yep.
Intern (likely Izzie Stevens) / Alex Karev (PVM): A total 007.
Intern (likely Meredith Grey) / Alex Karev OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): What's 007 mean?
Intern (likely Alex Karev) / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): License to kill.
Interns (group, likely Alex, Cristina, Izzie) / George O'Malley (PVM): 007.
George O'Malley: They're calling me 007, aren't they?
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): No one was calling you 007.
George O'Malley: I was on the elevator and Murphy whispered 007.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey OR George O'Malley (PVM): How many times do we have to go through this, George?
George O'Malley: Five?
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Ten?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR George O'Malley (PVM): Give me a number or else I'm gonna hit you.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey OR George O'Malley (PVM): Murphy whispered 007 and everyone laughed.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): He wasn't talking about you.
George O'Malley / George O'Malley (PVM): Are you sure?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Would we lie to you?
George O'Malley / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Yes.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR George O'Malley (PVM): 007 is a state of mind.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR George O'Malley (PVM): Well, it says the girl finished first in her class at Stanford.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, man.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): It's 911 for Katie Bryce.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): I gotta go.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR Alex Karev (PVM): They should have gone into geriatrics.
Alex Karev / Meredith Grey (PVM): No one minds when you kill an old person.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Surgery is hot.
Alex Karev / Meredith Grey (PVM): It's the Marines.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): It's macho.
Alex Karev / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): It's hostile.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): It's hardcore.
Alex Karev / George O'Malley OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Geriatrics is for freaks who live with their mothers and never have sex.
George O'Malley / George O'Malley (PVM): I've got to get my own place.
Meredith Grey / Katie Bryce (PVM): Excuse me.
Cristina Yang / Katie Bryce (PVM): Excuse me.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Katie Bryce (PVM): Took you long enough.
Meredith Grey / Katie Bryce (PVM): You're OK?
Katie Bryce / Katie Bryce (PVM): The nurse paged me 911.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Katie Bryce (PVM): I had to go all exorcist to get her to even pick up the phone.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Wait.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): There's nothing wrong with you?
Katie Bryce: I'm bored.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): You little.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Katie Bryce (PVM): I'm not a cruise director.
Katie Bryce: You don't have to wig out.
Katie Bryce: The pageant's supposed to be on cable, but this crappy hospital doesn't get the channel.
Katie Bryce: That cow, Kylie Wood, is going to walk off with my crown.
Katie Bryce: I have to see it.
Katie Bryce: Can you call someone?
Meredith Grey / Katie Bryce (PVM): Okay.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): This is an actual hospital.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): There are sick people here.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Go to sleep and stop wasting my time.
Katie Bryce: But I can't sleep.
Katie Bryce: My head's all full.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): That's called thinking.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Go with it.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): What do you need?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Mr. Jones has junky veins and he really needs antibiotics.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I should start a central line.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): So start one.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): You don't know how.
Izzie Stevens / Gloria (PVM): I've never done one.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Well, you know what that means.
Intern 1 (likely George or Izzie) / Meredith Grey (PVM): Can't we just pinch someone else?
Intern 2 (likely Izzie or George) / Meredith Grey (PVM): She's the on-call resident.
Intern (likely George or Izzie) / Meredith Grey (PVM): Dr. Bailey, I don't mean to bother you, but... Then don't.
Intern (likely George or Izzie) / Meredith Grey (PVM): It's Mr. Jones.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Is he dying?
Intern (likely George or Izzie) / Meredith Grey (PVM): No.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Then stop talking to me.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: What is it?
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Next time you wake me, he better be so close to dead there's a tag on his tongue.
Intern (likely George or Izzie) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): 4B's got post-op pneumonia.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Let's start antibiotics.
Intern (likely George or Izzie) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Are you sure that's the right diagnosis?
Intern (likely George or Izzie) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Well, I don't know.
Intern (likely George or Izzie) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I'm only an intern.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Here's an idea.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Why don't you go spend four years in med school and then let me know if it's the right diagnosis?
Intern (likely George or Izzie) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): She's short of breath.
Intern (likely George or Izzie) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): She's got fever.
Intern (likely George or Izzie) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): She's post-op.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Start the antibiotics.
Intern (likely Alex Karev) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): God, I hate nurses.
Alex Karev: I'm Alex.
Jeremy's Partner (likely another intern, possibly Izzie or George) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I'm with Jeremy.
Alex Karev / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You're with the Nazi, right?
Alex Karev / Meredith Grey (PVM): She may not have pneumonia, you know.
Alex Karev / Meredith Grey (PVM): She could be splinting or have a PE.
Alex Karev: Like I said, I hate nurses.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): What did you just say?
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Did you just call me a nurse?
Alex Karev: Well, if the white cat fits.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Damn it, Katie.
Alex Karev: She's seeing anybody?
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): I don't know.
Alex Karev: She's hot.
George O'Malley / Alex Karev (PVM): I'm friends with her.
George O'Malley / Alex Karev (PVM): I mean, kind of friends.
George O'Malley / Alex Karev (PVM): Not, you know, actually friends.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey OR Alex Karev (PVM): Not exactly, but we're tight.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey OR Alex Karev (PVM): And we hang out.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey OR Alex Karev (PVM): I mean, really, only, like, just today.
Alex Karev / Meredith Grey (PVM): Dude.
Other Male Intern / Meredith Grey (PVM): Dude.
Alex Karev / Meredith Grey (PVM): Stop talking.
Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey OR Mr. Bryce (PVM): What took you so long?
Nurse / Mr. Bryce (PVM): She's having multiple grand mal seizures.
Miranda Bailey / Mr. Bryce (PVM): Now, how do you want to proceed?
Miranda Bailey / Mr. Bryce (PVM): Dr. Gray, are you listening to me?
Nurse / Mr. Bryce OR Meredith Grey (PVM): She's got diazepam, two milligrams of diazepam.
Nurse / Mr. Bryce (PVM): I just gave the second dose.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Preston Burke OR Mr. Bryce (PVM): Dr. Gray, you need to tell us what you want to do.
Nurse / Meredith Grey (PVM): Okay, she's full on lorazepam.
Nurse / Meredith Grey (PVM): She's had four milligrams.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): You page Dr. Bailey and Dr. Shepherd.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Lorazepam's not working.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Phenobarbital.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Load her with phenobarbital.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Pheno's in.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): No change.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): You page Dr. Shepherd.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): I just told you.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Well, page him again.
Unknown / Meredith Grey (PVM): It's Dad.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Bryce (PVM): What do you want to do?
Meredith Grey / Mr. Bryce (PVM): Dr. Bailey, you need to tell us what you want to do.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Bryce (PVM): Heart stop.
Izzie Stevens / Unknown (PVM): Oh, look!
Cristina Yang / Unknown (PVM): Oh, look!
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Charge of pounds to 200.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Charge.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Clear.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Still beef, if nothing.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Charging.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): 19 seconds.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Charge to 300.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): 300.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Anything?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): 27 seconds.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Charge to 360.
Unknown (likely a doctor or intern) / Meredith Grey (PVM): Come on, Katie.
Unknown (likely a nurse or intern monitoring time) / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Preston Burke OR Mr. Bryce (PVM): 49 seconds.
Unknown (likely a doctor or intern) / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Preston Burke OR Mr. Bryce (PVM): At 60 seconds, you're supposed to admit or nothing's wrong.
Unknown (likely a doctor or intern) / Meredith Grey (PVM): Charge again.
Unknown (likely a nurse or another doctor) / Meredith Grey (PVM): Charge again.
Unknown (likely a doctor) / Meredith Grey (PVM): Anything?
Unknown (likely a nurse or intern monitoring the patient) / Meredith Grey (PVM): I see sinus rhythm.
Unknown (likely a nurse or intern) / Meredith Grey (PVM): Blood pressure's coming up.
Unknown (likely a doctor) / Meredith Grey (PVM): Right.
Unknown (likely a nurse or intern) / Meredith Grey (PVM): Pressure's returning.
Unknown (likely a nurse or intern) / Meredith Grey (PVM): Rate's coming back.
Unknown (likely Dr. Shepherd or Dr. Burke) / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): What the hell happened?
Unknown (likely an intern or nurse) / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): She had a seizure and her heart stopped.
Unknown (likely Dr. Shepherd or Dr. Burke) / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): You were supposed to be monitoring her.
Unknown (likely Meredith Grey or Cristina Yang) / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): I checked on her and she... I got her.
Unknown (likely Dr. Shepherd or Dr. Burke) / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Just go.
Unknown (likely Dr. Shepherd or Dr. Burke) / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Somebody get me her.
Unknown (likely Dr. Shepherd or Dr. Burke) / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Give me a chart, please.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You get a 911, you page me immediately.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Not in the five minutes it takes you to get to the emergency.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Immediately.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You on my team, and if somebody dies, it's my ass.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You hear me?
Unknown (likely intern being addressed) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Right?
Unknown (likely Dr. Burke) / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey OR Mr. Bryce OR Katie Bryce (PVM): You tell anyone ever.
Unknown (likely intern, possibly Meredith Grey) / Mr. Bryce (PVM): You said it was a seizure disorder.
Mr. Bryce / Mr. Bryce (PVM): Now you're saying it isn't?
Dr. Shepherd / Mr. Bryce (PVM): I'm saying that I don't know.
Mr. Bryce / Meredith Grey OR Mr. Bryce (PVM): Well, what do you think it could be?
Dr. Shepherd / Meredith Grey (PVM): I don't know.
Mr. Bryce / Mr. Bryce (PVM): When will you know?
Dr. Shepherd / Mr. Bryce (PVM): I don't have an answer for you for now.
Dr. Shepherd / Meredith Grey OR Mr. Bryce OR Mr. Bryce (PVM): Katie is stable and everything.
Mr. Bryce: Wait one damn minute.
Mr. Bryce: We came here because this hospital is supposed to be the best in Washington.
Mr. Bryce / Mr. Bryce (PVM): That's my kid in there.
Mr. Bryce / Mr. Bryce (PVM): My kid.
Mr. Bryce: And you have the audacity to stand here and tell me I don't know.
Dr. Shepherd / Mr. Bryce (PVM): Mr. Bryce.
Mr. Bryce: No, I want someone else, a doctor who knows what they're doing.
Mr. Bryce: You get me someone else, someone better than you.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Preston Burke OR Mr. Bryce (PVM): Mr. Bryce, I assure you that I am working hard on Katie's case.
Mr. Bryce: No, you're not.
Mr. Bryce: If you were, you'd be able to give me some answers.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I put you on a bypass machine, which pumps blood for your heart.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Fix your ticker, take you off the machine.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I'm done.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Simple procedure.
Patient's family member / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): So I shouldn't worry?
Dr. Burke / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I'm very good at what I do.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): It still is surgery.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): There are some risks.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I'll see you in the OR this afternoon, Mr. Savage.
Mr. Savage / Unknown (PVM): OK.
Tony (patient's family) / George O'Malley OR Alex Karev (PVM): You're not going to leave me here alone with that guy, are you?
Dr. Bailey / George O'Malley (PVM): Oh, I'll be outside the OR the whole time.
Dr. Bailey / George O'Malley (PVM): Dr. Burke is very good.
Dr. Bailey / George O'Malley (PVM): Don't worry.
Dr. Bailey / Meredith Grey OR George O'Malley OR Alex Karev (PVM): I'll see you after.
Tony (patient's family) / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): He'll be fine, right?
Dr. Bailey / Alex Karev (PVM): Tony's going to sail through.
Dr. Bailey / Alex Karev (PVM): You have nothing to worry about.
Dr. Bailey / Alex Karev (PVM): I promise.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): What are you doing?
George O'Malley / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I'm suturing a banana with the vain hope that it wakes up my brain.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Why are you smiling at 007?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I'm sorry I get mean when I'm tired.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You know what?
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): I don't care.
George O'Malley / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Meredith Grey (PVM): I comforted the family, and I got to hang out in the OR today.
George O'Malley / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): All is well.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Does anybody know why we're here?
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Well, good morning.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Good morning.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): I'm going to do something pretty rare for a surgeon.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): I'm going to ask interns for help.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): I've got this kid, Katie Bryce.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Right now, she's a mystery.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): She doesn't respond to our meds.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Her labs are clean, scans are pure, but she's having seizures, grand mal seizures with no visible cause.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): She's a ticking clock.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): She's gonna die if I don't make a diagnosis, which is where you come in.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): I can't do it alone.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): I need your extra minds, extra eyes.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): I need you to play detective.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): I need you to find out why Katie is having seizures.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): I know you're tired, you're busy, you got more work than you could possibly handle.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): I understand.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): So I'm gonna give you an incentive.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Whoever finds the answer rides with me.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Katie needs surgery.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): You get to do what no interns get to do, scrub in to assist on an advanced procedure.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Dr. Bailey's gonna hand you Katie's chart.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): The clock is ticking fast, people.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): If we're gonna save Katie's life, we have to do it soon.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Did you just page me?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Katie Bryce (PVM): Yes, 4B's still short of breath.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Look, give the antibiotics time to work.
Meredith Grey / Katie Bryce (PVM): The antibiotics should have worked by now.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): She's old.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): She's freaking ancient.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): She's lucky she's still breathing.
George O'Malley / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I got a shot to scrub in downstairs on a patient who wasn't alive during the Civil War.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Don't page me again.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Hey, I want in on Shepard's surgery.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): You've been the intern on Kitty since the start.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): You want to work together?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): If we find the answer, we have a 50-50 chance of scrubbing in.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): I'll work with you, but I don't want in on the surgery.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): You can have it.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Are you kidding?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): It's the biggest opportunity any intern will ever get.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): I don't want to spend any more time with Shepard than I have to.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): What do you have against Shepard?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): If we find the answer, the surgery's yours.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Do you want to work together or not?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Deal.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): So she doesn't have anoxia, chronic renal failure, or acidosis.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): It's not a tumor because her CT's clean.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Are you seriously not going to tell me why you won't work with Shepard?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): No.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): What about infection?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): No, there's no white count.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): She has no CT lesions, no fevers, nothing in her spinal tap.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Just tell me.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): You can't comment, make a face, or react in any way.
Meredith Grey: We had sex.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): What about an aneurysm?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): No blood on the CT and no headaches.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): There's no drug use, no pregnancy, no trauma.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Was he good?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): I mean, he looks like he'd be good.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Was it any good?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): A lot of answers.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): What if no one comes up with anything?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): You mean what if she dies?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Yeah.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): This is gonna sound really bad, but I really wanted that surgery.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): She's just never going to get the chance to turn into a person.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Some total of her existence will be almost winning Miss Teen whatever.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): You know what her pageant talent is?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): They have talent?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Rhythmic gymnastics.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, come on.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): What is rhythmic gymnastics?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): I don't know.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): I can't even say it.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): I don't know what it is.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I think it's something with, like, a ball and a...
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): What?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Meredith, what?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Get up.
Unknown / Meredith Grey (PVM): Come on.
Unknown / Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, Dr. Shepherd, just one moment.
Unknown / Meredith Grey (PVM): Katie competes in beauty pageants.
Dr. Shepherd / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): I know that, but we have to save her life anyway.
Unknown / Meredith Grey (PVM): Okay, she has no headaches, no neck pain.
Unknown / Meredith Grey (PVM): Her CT is clean.
Unknown / Meredith Grey (PVM): There's no medical proof of an aneurysm.
Dr. Shepherd / Meredith Grey (PVM): Right.
Unknown / Meredith Grey (PVM): But what if she has an aneurysm anyway?
Dr. Shepherd / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): There are no indicators.
Unknown / Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, but she twisted her ankle a few weeks ago when she was practicing for the pageant.
Dr. Shepherd / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Look, I appreciate you trying to help me.
Unknown / Meredith Grey (PVM): She fell.
Unknown / Meredith Grey (PVM): When she twisted her ankle, she fell.
Unknown / Meredith Grey (PVM): It was no big deal, not even a bump on the head.
Unknown / Meredith Grey (PVM): You know, she got right back up, iced her ankle, and everything was fine.
Dr. Shepherd / Meredith Grey (PVM): It was a false cell minor.
Unknown / Meredith Grey (PVM): Her doctor didn't even think to mention it when I was taking her history, but she did.
Unknown / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): She did fall.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Well, you know what the chances that a minor fall could burst an aneurysm?
Unknown / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): One in a million, literally.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Let's go.
Unknown / Meredith Grey (PVM): Where?
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Mine out of Katie's one in a million.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): I'll be damned.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Here it is.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): It's minute, but it's there.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Meredith Grey (PVM): It's a subarachnoid hemorrhage.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Meredith Grey (PVM): She's bleeding into her brain.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): She could have gone through her entire life without it ever being a problem.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): One tap in the right spot.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Exploded.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Exactly.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Now I get to fix it.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): You two did great work.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: I'd love to stay and kiss your asses, but I gotta tell Katie's parents she's having surgery.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: Katie Bryce's chart, please.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Here you go.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Uh, Dr. Shepard, you said that you'd pick someone to scrub in if we helped?
Dr. Derek Shepherd: Oh, yes, right.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: Um, I'm sorry I can't thank you both.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: It's gonna be a full house.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: Meredith, I'll see you in O.R.
Meredith Grey / Katie Bryce (PVM): Okay.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Christina.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): When it doesn't rain, it snores.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Yeah, the cookie crumbles, but in whose hand?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): All things said and all things done.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Life is short.
Meredith Grey / Gloria (PVM): And plenty done, life's too short, oh
George O'Malley / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Alex Karev (PVM): Wow, that was quick.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): His heart had too much damage to get him off the bypass.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I had to let him go.
Preston Burke / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): It happens rarely, but it does happen.
Preston Burke / Alex Karev (PVM): The worst part of the game.
George O'Malley / Alex Karev (PVM): But I... I told... I told Gloria that he would be fine.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Alex Karev (PVM): I promised her that... You what?
George O'Malley / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): They have four little girls.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I don't want you to promise anything.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): This is my case.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Did you hear me promise?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): The only one that can keep a promise like that is God, and I haven't seen him holding a scalpel lately.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You never promise a patient's family a good outcome.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I thought you were important enough to make promises to Mrs. Savage.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You get to be the one to tell her that she's a widow.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Is he?
George O'Malley / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Maybe Meredith couldn't see.
George O'Malley / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Izzy.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): I'll tell him I changed my mind.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You know, don't do me any favors.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): It's fine.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Christina.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You know what?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You did a cutthroat thing.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Deal with it.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Don't come to me for absolution.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You want to be a shark, be a shark.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I'm not.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Oh, yes, you are.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Only it makes you feel all bad in your warm, gooey places.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Now, screw you.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I don't get picked for surgeries because I slept with my boss and I didn't get into med school because I have a famous mother.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You know, some of us have to earn what we get.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / George O'Malley (PVM): Gloria, there were complications in the surgery.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / George O'Malley (PVM): Tony's heart had a lot of damage.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / George O'Malley (PVM): We tried to take him off bypass.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / George O'Malley (PVM): There wasn't anything we could have done.
Gloria: What are you talking about?
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Alex Karev (PVM): He... Tony died.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Alex Karev (PVM): He's dead.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Alex Karev (PVM): Gloria, I'm so sorry.
Gloria: Please.
Gloria: Oh, my God.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): I promised I'd make her look cool.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Apparently being a bald beauty queen is the worst thing that happened in the history of the world.
Meredith Grey: Did you choose me for the surgery because I slept with you?
Dr. Derek Shepherd: Yes.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: I'm kidding.
Meredith Grey: I'm not going to scrub in for surgery.
Meredith Grey: You should ask Christina.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Meredith Grey (PVM): She really wants it.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): You're Katie's doctor.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): And on your first day, with very little training, you helped save her life.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): You earned the right to follow her case through to the finish.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: You shouldn't let the fact that we had sex get in the way of you taking your shot.
Dr. George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): I wish I wanted to be a chef, or a ski instructor, or a kindergarten teacher.
Dr. George O'Malley / Alex Karev (PVM): You know, I would have been a really good postal worker.
Dr. George O'Malley / George O'Malley (PVM): I'm dependable.
Dr. George O'Malley / George O'Malley (PVM): You know, my parents tell everyone they meet that their son's a surgeon.
Dr. George O'Malley / George O'Malley (PVM): As if it's a big accomplishment.
Dr. George O'Malley / George O'Malley (PVM): Superhero or something.
Dr. George O'Malley / George O'Malley (PVM): If they could see me now.
Dr. Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): When I told my mother I wanted to go to medical school, she tried to talk me out of it.
Dr. Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Said I didn't have what it takes to be a surgeon.
Dr. Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): That I'd never make it.
Dr. Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): So...
Dr. Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): The way I see it, superhero sounds pretty damn good.
Dr. Meredith Grey / George O'Malley (PVM): We're going to survive this, right?
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): She's still short of breath.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Did you get an ABG or a chest film?
Dr. George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, yes, sir, I did.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): And what did you see?
Dr. George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, well, I, uh, I had a lot of patients last night.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Name the common causes of post-op fever.
Dr. George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): Uh, yes.
Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): From your head, not from a book.
Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Don't look it up.
Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Learn it.
Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): It should be in your head.
Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Name the common causes of post-op fever.
Intern (likely George O'Malley) / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Uh, the common causes of post-caus... Can anybody name the common causes of post-op fever?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Wind, water, wound, walking, wonder drugs, the five Ws.
Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Most of the time, it's wind, splinting, or pneumonia.
Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Pneumonia is easy to assume, especially if you're too busy to do the tests.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): What do you think's wrong with 4B?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): The fourth W, walking.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): I think she's a prime candidate for a pulmonary embolus.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): How would you diagnose?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Spiral CT, VQ scan, provide O2, dose with heparin, and consult for an IVC filter.
Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Do exactly as she says, then tell your resident that I want you off this case.
Richard Webber / Meredith Grey (PVM): I'd know you anywhere.
Richard Webber / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): You're the spitting image of your mother.
Richard Webber / Meredith Grey (PVM): Welcome to the gang.
Derek Shepherd / Meredith Grey (PVM): All right, everybody.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: It's a beautiful night to save lives.
Derek Shepherd / Meredith Grey (PVM): Let's have some fun.
Meredith Grey: I can't think of any one reason why I want to be a surgeon.
Meredith Grey: But I can think of a thousand reasons why I should quit.
Meredith Grey: They make it hard on purpose.
Meredith Grey: There are lives in our hands.
Meredith Grey: There comes a moment when it's more than just a game.
Meredith Grey: And you either take that step forward or turn around and walk away.
Meredith Grey: I could quit.
Meredith Grey: But here's the thing.
Meredith Grey: I love the playing field.
Derek Shepherd / Meredith Grey OR Gloria (PVM): That's good surgery.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Yeah.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): We don't have to do that thing where, you know, I say something, and then you say something, and then somebody cries, and there's, like, a moment.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Good.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You should get some sleep.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): You look like crap.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): I look better than you.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): It's not possible.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): That was amazing.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): You practice on cadavers.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): You observe.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): And you think you know what you're going to feel like standing over that table, but that was such a high.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): I don't know why anybody does drugs.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Yeah.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Yeah.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): I should go do this.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): You should.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): I'll see you around.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): See you around.
Intern (possibly George or Cristina) / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): See ya.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): So I made it through my first shift.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): We all did.
Meredith Grey: The other interns are all good people.
Meredith Grey: You'd like them.
Meredith Grey: I think.
Meredith Grey: I don't know.
Meredith Grey: Maybe.
Meredith Grey: I like them.
Meredith Grey: Oh, and I changed my mind.
Meredith Grey: I'm not going to sell the house.
Meredith Grey: I'm going to keep it.
Meredith Grey: I'll have to get a couple of roommates, but...
Meredith Grey: It's home, you know?
Meredith Grey: Are you the doctor?
Meredith Grey: No.
Meredith Grey: I'm not your doctor.
Meredith Grey: But I am a doctor.
Meredith Grey: What's your name?
Meredith Grey: It's me, Mom.
Meredith Grey: Meredith.
Meredith Grey: All right.
Meredith Grey: I used to be a doctor, I think.
Meredith Grey: You were a doctor, Mom.
Meredith Grey: You were a surgeon.