- Previously on Grey's
Anatomy: - He's gone.
Just wanted to get something
for the morning sickness.
So my patient is not pregnant?
I could find patients
for a clinical trial.
- Don't want you
getting hopes up.
- My hopes are not up.
You haven't slept
with her yet, have you?
- Know what's better than sex?
- What?
Anticipation.
You are a crass,
predatory ape of a man
who just happens to
be a decent surgeon.
Any chance you people
wanna get a drink?
She's saying she needs a friend.
There's this person.
In my head.
She is brilliant. Capable.
She can do chest
tubes and craniotomies.
She can run a code
without freaking out.
She's a really good surgeon.
Maybe even a great surgeon.
She's me.
Only so much better.
This is good news. Reflects
well on Seattle Grace.
Yes, sir.
- Is Yang gonna have
a problem with it?
- I'd say so.
I'm afraid I'll never become
this person in my head,
because something
keeps getting in my way.
What's getting in your way?
Every time Derek walks into a room,
all I can think about is his tongue.
- In my mouth.
- So, you think
about kissing Derek?
It's making surgery
very difficult.
So I need some
tools to help me stop.
I need some therapy
tools so that I can move on.
Sure you want to move on?
We have our fifth
clinical trial patient today.
And the first four? We've learned
a lot, but we haven't saved one.
And I really want to save one.
So I can't be distracted
by things like tongues.
- So I need the tools. Now.
- You're having fantasies
about Derek.
The only way to get rid of them
is to remind yourself of the reality.
- Which is?
- You tell me.
Kissing's not going to
happen 'cause he's with Rose?
Powerful stuff, reality.
Good morning.
There's something I wanted
to say to you last night,
but by the time I thought
of it you were gone. I...
It's not my intention to torture
you. It's just not a thing I take lightly.
The sex, with a new guy.
Rose, it's OK.
It's like I said last
night, I respect that.
No, not the thing
I wanted to say.
The thing I wanted to say is...
I'm worth the wait.
- Has Cristina seen it?
- Not yet.
She's gonna freak.
Let's take it down.
- You can't.
- She never has to know.
- She's gonna hear about it.
- Who's gonna hear about what?
What is going on?
- Nothing.
Izzie, move your hand.
Oh, come on, move it.
Good for him.
No one wins the Harper Avery. I mean,
obviously, someone wins the Harper Avery
one person once a year,
but that's like no one.
Burke won it. That is so weird, we
know someone who won the Harper Avery.
You look like crap.
Joe let me pick up
some shifts at the bar.
- Working at the bar?
- Do me a favor.
Talk to Meredith.
See if she'd be OK
if Rebecca moved
in for a couple weeks.
- What?
- We're gonna get our own place.
It's gonna take me a while
to save a security deposit.
- She's married.
- Yeah, well,
she's leaving her husband.
- She's telling him now.
- What about her kid?
I don't know. It's a mess,
but we're figuring it out.
Look, just ask
Mer. I'd do it myself,
but I don't want to
put her on the spot.
Alex, wait.
She's pregnant. She's knocked
up. Look, just talk to Meredith.
He's with Rose. He's with Rose.
- Sorry I'm late.
- Just getting started.
Darren, Mr. Covington.
- I'm Dr. Grey.
- Jonathan Evett.
I've been treating
Darren at the VA.
We're glad you got
him into the clinical trial.
So you're going to inject
a virus into my son's brain.
Not in the brain,
Dad. In the tumor.
The theory is that the virus
will attack the tumor and shrink it.
Does it work? Has
anybody gotten better?
No.
But with each patient we
learn, make adjustments.
There's an enormous
amount of risk involved.
That's OK. He survived
two tours in Afghanistan.
He's used to risk. Sir.
Mr. Covington.
- Todd.
- Your dad called me.
What'd you do, call
my whole platoon, Dad?
If you're gonna beat this, you
need your friends by your side.
Dr. Sloan?
Hey, I've got a baby out
here, needs to get to daycare.
Dr. Bailey.
Dr. Bailey's baby.
It appears Nurse Tanya is
no longer available for
your liposuction at ten.
Shall I cancel the procedure?
Give me another nurse.
Give me Kate. Yeah.
Really?
Dr. Torres? Dr. Sloan would like
to use Nurse Kate this morning.
Currently she's scheduled
for your arthroplasty,
but if you're willing to move
it, perhaps she could do both.
Ow!
- Dr. Torres? I know you're in there.
- Fine.
Just an hour later or an hour
earlier, whatever. Hey, Tuck.
Don't judge me, Bailey.
Who would like to present?
Kyra Marshall. End stage cardiomyopathy
and COPD awaiting a heart transplant.
Antibody levels were so elevated she
was in danger of rejecting any donor heart.
How did we counteract that?
High levels of chemotherapy
to suppress her immune system.
What precautions have we taken
to make sure that she is
not exposed to infection?
She's in a clean room,
a sterile environment
with strict isolation protocols.
Which are?
Yang, am I boring you? Because if
you'd rather spend the day in the morgue,
I have about 50 cadaver hearts that
need to be harvested for my research.
So Kyra Marshall's protocols...
I would love to
go to the morgue.
Thank you.
- Do I have to go?
- She's your resident.
Let Yang be an example to all of
you. There is no shame in grunt work.
Now, let's meet our
"mom in a plastic bubble."
Get me out of here, Lucas.
I need to get out of here!
- Get them
to let me out of here.
- Honey, calm down.
You said I'd have a heart in
three weeks, and it's been eight.
It has been eight weeks without
touching another human being.
- Kyra, listen to me.
- No!
- Kyra, you need
to listen to me.
- I want to leave!
I want to hug my kids, and
I want to kiss my husband.
And, God, I'm
going crazy in here.
- Kyra, come here. Kyra, take my hand.
- No.
Kyra, take my hand.
You are going to
leave here soon.
That is what I came to tell you.
We have a heart for you.
We have a heart.
- You paged me, chief?
- Human Resources called.
As of this morning, the nurses
are boycotting your surgeries.
I haven't done
anything to the nurses.
Nothing that could get us sued.
Well, they felt strongly
enough about it
that they sent their union rep.
Adele?
Hello, Richard, Dr. Sloan.
Wait, your wife's
the union goon?
Nurse mediator, Dr. Sloan.
And you know Wayne
Sheehan from Human Resources.
- But how did you...?
- Adele used to be a nurse.
Apparently she's
gotten back into the field.
That's right, Richard. I'm
not just a housewife anymore.
There've been complaints
about Dr. Sloan of a sexual nature,
complaints which this hospital
has, up until now, ignored.
Hey, everything I
did was consensual.
In fact, some of them
even begged for it.
No formal harassment
complaints have been filed.
However, the board has decided
to aggressively protect itself
from possible future litigation.
So, as of today, if
a hospital employee
is having a sexual relationship
with another employee,
they have got to register it.
Three other hospitals in the state are
already implementing policies like this.
- It's called date and tell.
- This some kind of joke?
Do you want to wait until you have
a $20-million lawsuit on your hands?
Fill out the form. Shut up
and fill out the damn form.
And you too, Richard.
Adele, what's going on?
I've been talking about
getting recertified for years.
I finally went and did it.
- Look, if you
needed more money...
- I don't need more money.
I have 50 percent of yours.
What I need is to
be taken seriously.
I'm working. I'm
loving it. I've changed.
Well... that's good.
I'm glad.
You know...
- I've changed, too.
- How?
I'm spending more time at home.
I'm... I'm delegating.
- I've heard that before.
- No, no.
I've gotten myself an intern.
My own intern.
- The chief's intern.
- Hmm.
Change.
Feels good, doesn't it?
Dr. Yang, are you OK?
I just wanted to check
because you passed up
a really awesome
transplant case with Dr. Hahn.
Is this about the
thing with Dr. Burke?
I know that you two
were together, and...
♪ I made it through
the wilderness ♪
♪ Somehow I made it through ♪
♪ Didn't know how lost I was ♪
♪ Until I found you ♪
- ♪ I was beat incomplete ♪
- Um...
- Should I be doing something?
- ♪ I'd been had ♪
- Can I help you?
- ♪ I was sad and blue ♪
♪ But you made me feel ♪
♪ Yeah, you made me feel ♪
♪ Shiny and new ♪
- ♪ Like a virgin ♪
- ♪ Hey ♪
- ♪ Touched for the...
- ♪ Touched for
the very first time ♪
♪ Like a vir... ♪
Um...
I'll just go upstairs
and go charting.
♪ Like a virgin ♪
We need to get
aggressive with the virus.
If we inject the tumor in two
sites we can actually saturate it
and have a real impact.
OK, now needle number
one will go into the tumor here,
by the middle cerebral artery.
Needle number
two goes right here.
Now, for the virus
to take full effect,
we need to inject it at
exactly the same time.
- Same time.
- Mm-hm.
You're needle number two.
Don't be nervous,
we're gonna practice.
Now, we'll use the fluorescein
to help us isolate the tumor
from the surrounding tissue.
OK.
Now, remember, we have
to be completely in synch.
OK? Let me know
when you're ready.
He's with Rose. He's with Rose.
- O'Malley?
- Oh, hey, chief.
- What are you doing?
- Just running labs
for Meredith.
Running labs for Meredith?
Does that sit right with you,
George O'Malley running labs?
Well, I'm
Meredith's intern, sir.
Well, it doesn't
sit right with me.
I've been watching you,
O'Malley, and frankly, I'm worried.
A guy like you can't
get too comfortable.
A guy like you
needs a challenge.
Needs change.
Now that you mention it, I have
been feeling a little unchallenged.
You're George O'Malley.
What would you think about
being my intern? The chief's intern?
The chief's intern?
George O'Malley,
intern to the chief.
- George O'Malley,
- Yes.
Is that even a real thing?
It is if I say it is.
Do you like princesses?
Um, yeah, sure.
When you take out Mommy's
broken heart, what happens?
Well, we're gonna put her
on a heart lung machine.
It's like in Snow White when
she eats the poison apple
and she dies for a while,
but she's not really dead.
- My mom's going to be dead?
- Snow White dies?
When they're little you
skip over the scary parts.
- I'm really sorry.
- It's OK, you don't have kids.
How would you know?
Rebecca, hi, it's
Dr. Stevens, again.
I have your test results. I really
need you to call me back. Thanks.
If I can't get hold
of my patient,
is it OK to give her
test results to her friend?
- No.
- What if her friend
is changing his life for her
because he thinks she's
pregnant and she's not?
You want to win yourself a Harper
Avery, master the basics of privacy.
The chief needs to know who you've slept
with by the end of the day. Be thorough.
Chief needs to know who you've slept
The chief needs to know
who you've slept with
by the end of the
day. Be thorough.
- This is no one's business.
- It's the chief's business,
so it's my business.
- I'm the chief's intern.
- Let me see that.
Oh. The chief said
you're the only person
in the hospital who is exempt.
Congratulations.
Uh-huh.
What do they mean
by "sexual relations"?
Yes, they mean relations
that are sexual in nature.
Yeah, I got that,
but there are levels.
Of intimacy.
Oh! Uh...
Well, they don't
need to know the...
They just want to know the...
highest level.
OK, then. Um, I won't
need one of these.
Oh.
Sure. OK.
I just don't know
how to turn this back.
- Freak.
- I am not a...
- I am the chief's intern.
- Mm-hm. OK. That's not a real job.
I just need the form
by the end of the day.
Now, let's see, what's going
on in Seattle Grace today.
One of our former surgeons
won the Harper Avery Award,
another is leading a trial that will
change the course of neurosurgery,
and last but not least, one of our
surgeons has screwed so many nurses
that now everyone has to
document their sexual histories.
Walk tall, my friend, walk tall.
- You putting Rose on that form?
- That's none of your business.
That's a "no," which means she
still hasn't let you sleep with her.
What's she got,
treasure up there?
It's because I don't
have a penis, isn't it?
Um...
I publish more, I do
double the research.
I deserve this more than Burke.
It's a big men's club and it's not fair.
Huh. I didn't even realize
you were being considered.
I wasn't going to
mention it until I won.
Then I was going to be all nonchalant
like awards don't matter to me.
It was gonna be very
impressive and humble.
Now Burke's gone and
ruined my whole act.
You want to meet me at Joe's
tonight? We can trash talk him.
Oh.
I can't, I have
this other thing.
What? I do, I
have this... thing.
Hey, can you talk to the nurses?
I need someone
to stand up to them,
tell them to call off the
boycott, tell them I'm a good guy.
Here's the problem. We
don't think you are a good guy.
Dr. Torres thinks I'm a
good guy. Don't you, Callie?
Um...
- On call room. Now.
- Whoa. You think
I'm a very good guy.
Little pinch.
What's the recovery
period for brain surgery?
It varies, but usually at
least four to six weeks.
You'll be stuck with
me for four to six weeks.
Don't be an idiot, Todd.
You deploy in five days, man.
That was before I knew
you had a brain tumor.
No, don't screw this up for
yourself. You're a soldier.
I'm probably not gonna
make it through surgery.
Cool. Then I'll be good
to go in about five days,
so why are we even
having this argument?
Why did you come, man?
How could I not?
God, you're so paranoid.
Mr. Covington!
Get out.
Don't make me throw you out.
What's wrong?
Nothing's wrong, sir.
Nothing at all.
Thank you for the
consult, Dr. Sloan.
- No.
- I haven't said anything.
- Not talking to the nurses.
- You're dating my best friend.
- Helping me is a duty,
as his girl.
- No.
You're one of them.
Tell them I'm a good guy.
A good guy who's
mind-blowingly good at sex.
Yeah, see, but that, all
the talk about all the sex,
that's not what I think
of as good guy behavior.
You know what you are?
You're a tease. I
hate women like you.
You string guys along
acting like sex is some prize,
this thing they have to earn.
You're afraid that once you
give it up, he'll lose interest.
Oh, and by the way,
I am a good guy.
Time for a haircut, Darren.
Mr. Covington, would
you mind waiting outside?
- I get nervous
when I'm being watched.
- No problem.
Thanks.
- Thanks.
- You look like you
could use a break.
Yeah, the... not
talking about the thing
everybody's thinking about
gets a little exhausting.
You know, my
dad's not a bad guy.
He's just a soldier.
- We're all soldiers.
- Todd's down in the lobby.
He's such an idiot.
He should just go. Put me
out of his mind and just...
- That's not so easy to do.
- It'd be better for everyone.
With Dr. Evett hanging around,
Todd can't risk getting outed.
He'd lose everything
he worked for.
- Crazy that you
even have to worry.
- Don't ask, don't tell.
Yeah, I knew the
deal when I signed on.
You keep your personal life
separate from your work life.
I just never thought I'd
meet my personal life at work.
- I can still go get Todd.
- No. I can't.
My dad, I can't.
I know what you're thinking.
Brave soldier can't even
step up to his own father.
I was thinking this is hard.
The gay part or the tumor part?
The whole part.
I need your form. Lexie! I
need you to fill out a form.
- What's this?
- Sex police.
Meredith, I'm gonna
need your form.
Don't ask, don't tell,
George. Forms are stupid.
I'm still gonna need
it, though. Pen?
- I think I'll
take one of those.
- What? Why?
Oh.
- Just...
- Thank you.
- I'm so sorry.
- Do you want me
to get Cristina?
Derek is with Rose. And I
am OK that Derek is with Rose.
Get Cristina. Get her form.
You don't want to go
near Cristina right now.
- Is she crying?
- No.
- She staring ahead
being scary quiet?
- She's singing.
- I still need your form.
- Here, perv boy. Enjoy.
This isn't complete.
It's fine.
What?
Oh, right. Sorry, I forgot.
- He forgot he had sex with me?
- I just collect forms.
He forgot he had sex with me?
♪ You're so fine
and you're mine ♪
Stop singing.
♪ Make me strong ♪
♪ Yeah, you make me
bold 'Cause your love... ♪
You're going to win your
own Harper Avery Award.
- ♪ Yeah, your love
thawed out ♪
- Burke wouldn't have a career
if it hadn't been for you.
You saved him when
he had his tremor.
The Harper Avery Board
may not know it, but he does.
♪ Like a virgin Hey! ♪
♪ Touched for
the very first time ♪
I'm in therapy.
Because he's with Rose. I'm
way more screwed up than you are.
Thank you.
That makes me
feel a little better.
You're welcome.
Chief, it... Adele.
Is it true you have every
member of the hospital
filling out this form, listing their
personal and sexual relations?
That's right. We are
taking this very seriously.
But I am exempt
from this? Me. Just me.
I'm not even asked if I
need to fill out a form?
You're Bailey. I don't even
want to see you holding the form.
OK, then.
What you don't know about women.
What?
Tyler will be taking
everyone's temperature.
Because of Mrs.
Marshall's immune system,
anyone over 100
degrees is not scrubbing in.
- One hundred point four.
- Sorry, Karev.
Come on. I'm fine.
No, apparently, you're not.
I'm not putting
Mrs. Marshall at risk.
Page Yang, she's scrubbing in.
You go get Mrs.
Marshall's family.
You're on babysitting
duty the rest of the day.
Darren.
We can take a moment.
- No.
- Are you sure?
No.
Let's just go.
OK, remember what I said.
We have to be in total synch
for the virus to have
maximum infiltration.
OK?
Ready?
Go.
Easy, slow down.
Easy, slow down, slow
down. Look at me. Look at me.
Don't look at the
machine, look at me.
Slowly.
Breathe.
That's it.
The virus is in.
We're standing on
the moon, Dr. Grey.
The donor heart's on its way.
Can't imagine how you
must feel about Burke's award.
You actually helped
him with all that research,
he didn't even mention
you in the article.
Well, I guess it's no surprise.
His arrogance is legendary.
Well, I thought we finally
had some common ground.
Good for you.
Refusing to trash
him. Rising above.
That's very impressive, mature.
He would love it if he
knew how bitter I am.
Well, I am not gonna
give him that satisfaction.
I am going to follow
your example, Yang.
Congratulations,
Preston, I wish you well.
I wanted to drop off the form myself,
answer any questions you might have.
Questions about what?
There are interns
listed on this form.
I require the energy of youth.
Dr. Shepherd was just a
moment of weakness for both of us.
- Dr. Sloan?
- That was many moments.
- In on call rooms. Very hot.
- Mmm, steamy.
- I'm surprised
you haven't listed me.
- You're not my type.
- All right, Dr. Bailey,
I get the joke.
- See, this is a joke to you.
I am a single woman.
I've been a single
woman for some time now,
but the very idea that I could
have a sexual encounter,
a consensual sexual
encounter, is a joke to you?
Dr. Bailey...
So much so, that you
would single me out
of this entire hospital,
as the one person
who couldn't interest
a member of the opposite sex?
It's... It's just...
- It's harassment.
- Adele!
Just, shame on you,
sir! Just shame on you!
I made it all up, Wayne.
- Liquids. For your fever. Drink this.
- I'm fine.
Can't keep working
at Joe's. You're sick.
- You're run-down.
- I'm fine.
Getting in the
way of your career.
You're taking on too much.
You and Rebecca need to talk.
She can't just move.
- Slow down.
- What's your problem?
You can't pass a
baby without stopping.
The only baby in the world
you're not happy about is mine.
- It's not that
I'm not happy for you.
- What?
- Nothing.
- Yeah. That's what I thought.
You can run, but you can't hide.
What? No, I
wasn't... I was just...
So are we on for
tonight or what?
Um... I don't know. I mean, I
told you I have this other thing.
I don't make friends easily.
I'm awkward and
I'm bad at small talk.
And I generally don't
like people I don't know.
But I made friends with you.
And now you have this
thing, and that thing is Sloan.
Are you mad that I'm
sleeping with Mark Sloan?
I'm not mad you're
sleeping with Sloan.
I'm mad that you didn't tell me you're
sleeping with Sloan. I'm mad at you.
Instead of telling me and admitting
that you're one of those girls
who goes all poofy when she
gets a boyfriend, you disappear.
With your "thing."
Mark Sloan.
I don't make friends easily.
We were able to
saturate the tumor.
We'll do an MRI in the morning
and see if the tumor has shrunk.
But you're optimistic?
Cautiously optimistic.
That was great. Totally in
synch, like we were one person.
- Yeah. It was great. You did great.
- Thanks.
Obviously his intracranial pressure's
going to need to be monitored overnight.
So, you just tell
me the parameters.
I'll stay. I mean, we can...
We can stay together.
How'd it go?
Great. It went
really, really well.
Dr. Grey had one of the...
She had one of the...
one of the injections.
Well, I was just... I was heading
home and I didn't know if you wanted...
Yeah, right.
I need to stay here tonight.
- Oh, OK.
- OK?
I'll just...
- OK.
- Rose! Wait.
- Two, I...
- What?
- I can page you
if there's problems.
- I'll stay.
If you want me
to stay, I'll stay.
No, you should go be with Rose.
Sex. Let's go.
Are you coming?
I'm just...
- not in the mood.
- What? You're always
in the mood.
I know.
But I'm just...
All my surgeries
got canceled today.
Wanna go grab a cup of coffee?
- Talk?
- You're useless.
- The donor heart just arrived.
- I think something's wrong!
- She's having
trouble breathing.
- I think her lung has dropped.
- Page Hahn!
- Right away, Dr. Karev.
She's not moving!
What are you doing?
You can't go in there!
You can't break
the isolation barrier!
Mr. Marshall, get
your kids out of here!
- Is she dying?
- Mr. Marshall, your kids!
Don't let her die,
please don't let her die!
OK. Jessie, Zoe,
this is the scary part,
so I need you guys to turn
around. Come on, just turn around.
I know what I'm doing.
I'll tell you when it's over.
OK, Zoe, Jesse. It's OK. You
can look at your mommy now.
- Mommy's OK. Oh, God!
- It's OK. It's OK.
Here are the forms. Alphabetized,
broken down by department.
See that, Adele? I didn't have
to lift a finger. I'm delegating.
- Well, I've seen
some progress today.
- Well, thank you.
Dr. Webber, may I have
a word with you, privately?
I'll be right outside.
I gave up a major surgery today and all
my friends think I'm a brownnosing perv.
But I... It was worth it because
I thought that you saw me.
But, all due respect, sir, you're using
me to get back together with your wife.
O'Malley.
I don't know if
it's possible to quit
a thing that isn't
even a real thing,
- but I do. I quit.
- O'Malley, wait.
The truth is I do
see you, O'Malley.
I see how hard you work.
The chief's intern is not a
real job. But I'd like it to be.
Let's give him acetaminophen,
add 500 of vancomycin.
- Good.
- And blood
and urine cultures also.
If you want to take a
break, I'll sit with him.
- No, I'm OK.
- OK.
♪ And that kiss ♪
♪ That kiss was so, so true ♪
♪ I guess I should know better ♪
V-fib! V-fib.
- Charge paddles to 300.
- They're charged.
- Clear!
- Clear.
I know my being here
makes you feel uncomfortable,
but I was trained not to leave a man
when he's down. Our man is down.
- Todd.
- We both love him.
- Todd...
- No!
All I want to know
is how he's doing.
Oh, God.
♪ When it comes to falling ♪
Dr. Karev saved your life,
but the chance that you were
exposed to infection is too great.
- Can she get another heart?
- You'll be
at the top of the list.
But I'm going to have
to stay in isolation, right?
Dr. Karev.
Since the barrier was
already breached once today,
we don't think a few minutes with
your family would be such a bad idea.
As long as they scrub in and
take the necessary precautions.
So I can see my kids? They
can come in here with me?
I'll go get them
scrubbed in right now.
Guys, let's get scrubbed
in so we can see Mom.
Pathetic.
Well, are you coming?
To an on call room?
Now, I'm going to save you. Do
you want to be saved? Or don't you?
Spinal tap showed encephalitis.
The virus reverted.
There's no way we
could have predicted this.
I shouldn't have
said I could handle it.
I shouldn't have let you go.
No, you did everything right.
You did what I would've done.
On my way here, I
stopped and I got this.
For when we get it right.
Because we will.
We will succeed and
we will save someone.
Then, when we do, we're going
to open this bottle of champagne.
And we're going to drink to Phillip
Robinson and Darren Covington...
and all the other patients who
helped us change the face of medicine.
And we're going to celebrate.
We're going to use
this as our victory dance.
Meredith, we will.
We're going to open
this bottle of champagne.
Going through all the forms, I
noticed you didn't turn yours in.
- No, sir.
- Well, I need you to.
The hospital is still liable,
even though Dr. Burke isn't here.
There. My sexual
relationship. Preston Burke.
- On paper. Satisfied?
- I know this is
difficult for you.
No, it's not difficult,
sir. It is simple.
Burke is not here. He's
gone. And he's the better for it.
He's winning the Harper Avery Award
and being celebrated all over the world.
That is not difficult.
He's out there. And I'm here.
Where everything is the same.
I still live in his apartment.
I walk the same halls of this
hospital. I wear the same scrubs.
Not even that is not
difficult. This is where I am.
This is where I choose to be.
But, sir, when his
hand was shaking,
I performed his surgeries.
I kept his secrets,
I nursed his pride.
You know it and I know it
and he knows it. He knows it.
And yet, nowhere in that newspaper
article does my name appear.
I am the unseen
hand to his brilliance.
Excuse me.
And yet while everything is...
the same, it's
very, very different.
Now, I'm lucky if I
get to hold a clamp.
Hahn treats me like...
I was his hand and
now I'm a ghost.
That's not difficult.
It's unbearable.
I know everybody is
proud of him, but I'm not.
And I do not wish him well.
This boycott has
gone on long enough.
Now, OK, I have
no authority here,
but I would like to offer
my thoughts on Dr. Sloan.
- You're doing great.
- OK.
This man is a whore,
has always been a whore,
will probably always be a whore.
But that's not a secret.
He's not keeping it hidden.
You knew who he was before
you got involved with him.
And now you want to be all,
"Woe is me, he doesn't call me back,
he's dating other
women." He's nasty!
And that's not just you.
He's sleeping with other
doctors and orderlies
and cafeteria workers.
But he's a doctor here
and a pretty good one.
So let us all close our knees,
and get back to our jobs,
so he can get back to his job and
help the people that really need it!
Disperse!
Oh, my God.
Hi.
My baby.
I heard you did great.
- Alex.
- You think I'm scum.
You think I can't do this!
But it's my kid, Izzie, my kid.
And what you
think doesn't matter!
I want him to have
a military burial.
It was a good day.
Heading home.
Heading home early.
Maybe you have changed.
That's a nice blouse.
The way you're looking
at me now, Richard...
That's harassment.
Maybe even a great day.
- Good night.
- Get in touch
with that patient?
- No.
- Did you tell her friend?
No.
Even though it
killed me, I didn't tell.
You're growing, Stevens.
Yeah, well, I
wish it would stop.
My husband is out on a date.
Right now. On a date.
♪ And the difference
astounding I should expect ♪
I was a good doctor.
Even when it was hard.
I was the me in my head.
♪ And leave the
rest at arm's length ♪
♪ When they reach out, don't
touch them, don't touch them ♪
I just called three of my ex-boyfriends
to find out how unforgettable I am.
I left messages, I'm
sure they'll call me back.
So you made a mistake
and you slept with Alex.
No one has made more mistakes
or slept with more
inappropriate people
or been more publicly
humiliated than me.
Let me be an inspiration.
Look at me, I am
the chief's intern.
I am the man at the
right hand of the man.
That...
OK, I've been avoiding you.
And I know it's stupid
and based on nothing,
But, when she was
here, Addison said...
Well, she implied
that we were...
That I was...
That, um...
you and I might be lesbians.
There was a moment when
I thought, "I can't do this."
Well, I'm glad some
things haven't changed.
"I can't do this alone."
The most refined, professional,
ladylike doctor in this hospital
came to my defense tonight.
The best she could come
up with was, "He's a whore."
I'm a whore.
I slept with her.
And the whole time I was
thinking about Meredith.
Who's the bigger whore?
But I closed my eyes and
imagined myself doing it.
And I did.
I blocked out the fear.
And I did it.
It was a really good day.
I'm just gonna say this because your
insurance only covers 20 sessions.
And I feel we should
get right to the point.
That was a load of crap.
It was not a good day.
Your patient died alone, unable
to tell the love of his life how he felt.
Yeah, but he did it for his
boyfriend. I think it was kind of heroic.
- It's a load of crap.
- Stop saying that.
Let me draw the
parallels for you.
The tragic patient dies alone
while the love of his life
is literally in the next room.
- That's you.
- What are you talking about?
- I'm not dying alone.
- But I think you are.
And you're telling
yourself you're a hero.
- When in reality,
all you are is alone.
- That is a load of crap.
He's with Rose.
You know what? I'm
not going to do this.
- He's with Rose.
- Why keep saying that?
If you can't see what's wrong
with that sentence, "He's with Rose,"
we're never gonna get
anywhere. He's with Rose.
OK, so he's with Rose! So what?
He's with Rose, that
means he's not with you.
And do you know
why he's not with you?
You're scared.
Are you calling me a coward?
- I think you're
very frightened, Dr. Grey.
- Are you calling me a coward?
What do you think?