Previously on "Grey's anatomy"...
You and Burke, are you okay ?
We're existing in total silence.
That hand is worth $2 million.
I want it fixed.
Mark and I...
It wasn't a one-night stand.
I was in love with him.
At least, I thought I was.
Your sister Molly's just been admitted
for an emergency c-section.
Molly's not my sister.
She is. You have the same father.
Why didn't you stay and fight for us ?
I did. I... I tried.
Why didn't you try harder ?
You are officially off my service.
But for what it's worth,
I think you're gonna miss me.
Harold O'Malley, 63,
diagnosed with esophageal cancer
and severe aortic regurge.
You think I want to die
and leave my boy in charge ?
You are not gonna die.
Morning.
Are you watching me sleep ?
Maybe.
Are you some kind of weirdo
who watches women sleep ?
Maybe.
- Izzie.
- What ?
I just dropped $8.7 million
on the floor.
And ?
I shouldn't be able to drop
$8.7 million on the floor.
You need to deposit that check.
George...
your father's surgery is tomorrow.
Any chance you're misplacing
your anxiety on me and my check ?
No, there is no chance.
That check ruins my morning
every morning.
It belongs in the bank.
Would you just please...
as a favor to me...
would you just...
put it in the bank ? Please.
Mm. No.
But... if you're nice to me
for the next seven minutes,
I will give you a ride to work.
You don't deserve $8.7 million !
Mm. So true. So true.
- How's Burke doing ?
- I don't know.
She doesn't know.
He just had surgery yesterday,
and you don't know how he's doing ?
They're not speaking.
I thout they made up.
- They did, sort of.
- But she's still nospeaking to him ?
He's not speaking to me.
They're not speaking to each other.
Okay.
Did you ask Derek about burke's hand ?
I don't want to get in the middle of it.
Derek and I are happy. Could we
just keep it that way for while ?
You know, you could always swallow your
pride and just ask him yourself.
Her gut's not big enough for that.
Oh, Alex, you hurt me.
Oh, Georgie.
Quiet down !
Everyone, quiet down !
- Morning, everybody.
- Good morning.
- Uh, who's presenting ?
- Oh !
Oh ! Can Georgie do it ?
He's real good.
Come on, Georgie. Yeah !
Come on.
Harold O'Malley, 63, status...
post-aortic valve replacement.
Morning chest x-ray showed no atelectasis
after aggressive C.P.T. for the last two days.
Um, scheduled for a transhiatal
esophagectomy tomorrow morning at 9 :00.
That's it.
Um, for the next few minutes, I think it
would be best if the extended family
could wait out in the waitg area.
Just a few minutes, guys,
and then you can come back.
How are you feeling, mr. O'Malley ?
He's feeling great.
"Better than ever," he said.
Which is why we had everybody
come out today,
because we figured after today,
he maybe won't be feeling
so great for a while.
Uh, after the surgery, uh, then when
do we start chemo and stuff ?
That protocol depends on what we find
when we open you up, Harold.
What  do you mean, what you find ?
Uh, Grey.
There's only so much they can tell
from labs and scans,
so they really need to get a good look
inside to see if the cancer has spread.
And if it's spread, that changes
how much chemo he needs ?
That changes a lot
Like what ?
I'll let the oncologist explain
that to you later today, Harold.
And dr. Grey will be taking you through
a final battery of preoperative
tests before we go.
- So, um--
- So it would be best if the party went home.
Dr. Shepherd. Uh, dr. Burke's hand...
has he had any tremors ?
That's confidential.
Uh, but I'm... I'm one of his doctors.
You're also his girlfriend.
Ask him yourself.
Good morning, everyone.
Who's presenting ? Morning.
Preston Burke, post-op day one from I
and d of a compressive hematoma
to the brachial exus.
He is afebrile, and vital signs
were stable overnight.
Incisions are clean with no signs
of infection.
Last morphine was given
at 2 :00 this morning.
Ask about the hand.
You ask.
No, it's just one question.
Dr. Yang...
Something you want to share
with the rest of us ?
No, ma'am. Sorry.
Look good, Preston.
- Take it easy on the nurses.
- I'll do my best.
- O'malley. Your father's surgery
is today ?
- Tomorrow.
- You okay, honey?
- Yeah.
Can you just help me...
Scoliosis ?
- Looks like a birth defect.
- Looks like hell.
What are you all staring at ?
Really, if you're expecting me to be the
brave and heartwarming differently-abled girl,
that isn't gonna happen,
so go ahead and do your thing.
Stevens.
Heather Douglas, 17, past medical
history of vater syndrome.
Which is ?
Vater syndrome is a genetic condition
that affects the vertebrae, anus,
trachea, esophagus and renal system.
Wow. Give this girl a medal.
She memorized the whole acronym.
Which I assure you is a hell of a lot
easier than living with it.
Stevens.
Right. Um,
Heather is... is in today for a
lithotripsy to remove kidney stones
and a thoracoplasty to alleviate
pressure on her lungs.
Can  I ask...
I-I know I'm just supposed to
be here to remove a few ribs,
but I'm wondering if you've ever
tried anything more radical
to treat the spinal curvature ?
Let's see. If by "more radical,"
you mean having a steel rod
inserted into my spine,
then, yeah, we've tried.
The rod just bent.
Removing the kidney stones may
seem minor, but it will really improve
your quality of life.
Really ? So this surgery
is gonna get me laid ?
Heather, stop it.
Mom, I'm sorry, but she's talking about
improving my quality of life,
and I don't think doctors should make
promises they can't keep.
Laura Grey-Thompson, born four days ago
with jejunal atresia.
Corrected surgically. Uh, post-op course--
Oh, I'm--I'm sorry. Am I interrupting ?
Her mom and grandma ha-have the flu,
and they asked me to get an update.
Oh, she's doing very well, mr. Grey.
We'll be out of here in just a minute.
- Dr. Grey, you were saying ?
- Um...
Excuse me, uh...
I'll just come back a little later.
- Grey ?
- Um...
Laura Grey-Thompson, had some dilation
of the bowels on x-ray this morning.
We need to do a barium enema to make
sure there's no intestinal stricture.
Dr. Grey, I'd like you to stick
with mr. O'Malley this week.
Yang, pit. Karev, Sloan. Stevens,
prep Heather Douglas for surgery.
- O'Malley.
- Yes.
- You're taking the rest of this week off ?
- Yes, ma'am.
- May as well take today, too,
spend some time with your family.
- Thank you.
Uh, dr. Bailey, as things progress
with my dad,
you know, sometimes we--
with families-- we coddle them,
sugarcoat things. It would help me if you
were straight with me as things progress.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Uh, dr. Bailey. Dr. Bailey.
I know that I'm supposed to prep
her only, but any chance I can
scrub in on Heather Douglas ?
- I mean, a vater patient isn't
something you see very often.
- No.
But I'm ready.
I am ready.
Your psychiatrist has not
given you an all clear.
He's... I have done everything
he has asked me to do, everything,
except deposit my inheritance check,
which...
Wait, you have not deposited
a nearly $9-million check yet ?
It... it's...
He is being unreasonable.
That check has nothing to do with any...
What's unreasonable is that you're losing
thousands of dollars a day in interest.
That's unreasonable. You clearly
are not reasonable yet,
which, I think, is the point your
psychiatrist is trying to make.
- Hey, I need C.B.C. and a chem-7
on Harold O'Malley.
I need these labs asap.
Everybody needs everything "asap."
Oh, yes. And all throughout this
hospital, people are dying while
you give me crap about "asap."
- Hey, are you okay ?
- Why wouldn't I be ?
Your father? Freezing up on rounds...
Oh, God. That was mortifying.
- Thank you. Thanks.
- Oh, okay. It wasn't mortifying ?
I just wish the baby would get well and
go home and Thatcher would go with her.
Is that wrong ?
Oh, wrong would be, if you wished
the baby wouldn't get well.
Okay, good. Thanks.
You  know, if you want to thank me, you
could ask Derek if Burke has had any tremors.
- Talk to him.
- No.'Cause then he wins.
Wins what ?
Forget it.
Do you have a father ?
I have a stepfather.
He's nice. I see him for yom kippur.
Karev, what did I tell you
about how I like my charts ?
I like to round on pre-op
before post-op.
Do you like wasting my time ?
Is it fun for you ?
No, sir.
Then get it right.
Do you like abusing the interns ?
Is it fun for you ?
Yes, it is,
and in case you've forgotten, you don't
get the high horse this week, Addison.
Not this week.
He's an ass.
You know Shepherd pretty well, yeah ?
Lots of hair, too many women, likes
elevators and long walks on the beach.
So, um, what's the best way
to get him to do something ?
What kind of something?
A consult that the patient
hasn't requested
but that the friendly neighborhood ortho
resident thinks is worth pursuing.
Shepherd thinks he's busier and maybe a little
bit more important than everyone else.
Standard neurosurgeon breed.
- Exactly.
- Okay, so ?
So he'll say no
until you stare him down.
"Stare  him down"?
Stare him down.
- You're way too hot to be a doctor.
- Okay.
I mean, aren't people who look like you
supposed to be dumb ?
I'm just saying, you're not gonna
be in my surgery, are you?
'Cause I'm a little too young to die.
I will not be in on your surgery.
See ? I knew it.
You're not even a doctor.
I am a doctor. It's just that when my...
fiancé dropped dead not too long ago,
I went a little nuts, and, uh,
no surgeries for me for a while.
Well, so much for my theory that life
doesn't suck for pretty people.
I'm sorry I was such a bitch to you.
Well... you're in pain. Sometimes I'm
a bitch for no good reason at all.
- Oh, dr. Shepherd.
- Yes.
I am so sorry to bother you.
I know you're very, very busy,
but there's a girl here. She's 17 years old
with severe scoliosis from vater syndrome.
She's here for thoracoplasty because
her ribs are pressing against her lungs,
and she's already had two spinal fusions
and a segmental spinal instrumentation
that didn't work. She's bent over
at 9 degrees, which clearly sucks.
"Clearly sucks," is that
your professional assessment ?
My professional assessment
is that we can help her.
My day is impossible.
I'll come by for a csult
in the morning.
I'm  a good starer.
Doctors, could I get a word ?
- Oh, how are you feeling, Harold ?
- Feelin' great. Feelin' fine.
It's just that the oncologist...
he said that, uh, if the cancer
is in other organs,
he said that maybe you wouldn't
proceed with the surgery.
That's right, Harold.
If the cancer's spread to your other
organs, it would compromise your
ability to recover from the surgery.
So if you close me up and then send
me home, I get, what,
a couple of weeks to live ?
- You'd have... weeks or months, yes.
- No
No, you gotta take the tumor out,'cause I can survive this. I know I can.
O'Malleys, we're figers.
Mr. O'Malley, it... it's just not
a good idea to...
You know, my wife...
We've been married 40 years.
I make her crazy, but...
40 years. She needs me.
My family needs me.
I can't let you close me up and then
tell them that there's nothing that can
be done when I know I can fight it.
So I...
I'm asking for your word.
I want you to take the tumor out.
Mr. O'Malley, my job
is to do the best I can for you
medically. After...
well, closing me up and sending me home
to die isn't best for me,
not medically or any other way.
Please... Take the tumor out.
All right.
All right ?
This falls under confidentiality ?
If you're asking if you can
tell his son, the answer's no.
- You're watching me sleep again ?
You're cute when you sleep.
What can I say ?
Yeah, but don't you sleep ?
Why are you always up before the alarm ?
I'm a light sleeper. It's no big deal.
So something woke you up.
It's no big deal.
It's just that...
- You snore a little.
- What ?
- I do not.
- Yes, you do. I love it.
I find it charming that such a big noise
can come from such a little person.
- Do you know what's not charming ?
- What ?
- Your morning breath.
I'm sorry. What?
I'm just saying, seeing how you're
always up before me, you might
consider brushing your teeth.
Okay, this is me brushing my teeth.
Thank you.
- Surgery's today ?
- Yeah.
- I'm okay.
- Yeah. I have a really good feeling.
- Yeah ?
- Yeah.
- I didn't even bake anything for you.
- Thank you.
Aha. Bone dry cappuccino.
At least something's dry around here.
Does it ever stop raining in this hellhole ?
Not really.
Great. Good to know.
What the hell is this, Karev, vanilla ?
Are you trying to poison me or are you just
trying to make my day a little bit worse ?
Mark.
Coffee cart must have screwed up.
You know, if you can't handle coffee,
you can't handle plastics.
Maybe you oughta head back to the gynie
squad where life was all squishy and pink.
Squishy and pink
though it may be, I have an amazing
surgery today, Karev, if you want in.
Good morning, dr. Burke.
Yes, it is.
Beautiful morning.
I love watching the rain.
Feeling good ?
Not too much pain ?
Feeling great.
And... your hand... your right hand...
Feelin' good today ?
I'm sorry, Olivia, you're just you're
gonna have to tell dr. Yang that I'm
not ready to give her that information.
Right. Okay, then. Sorry.
uh-huh. Uh-huh.
You know Cristina's stalking your room ?
I do.
Your father ?
Yeah. The surgery my dad's having...
has a 50% morbidity rate.
Oh, O'Malley... that statistic,
it means 50% of the people who undergo
the surgery survive.
If you're gonna hang your hat on statistics,
then you have to look at them from both sides.
Heather, I've looked
at your case history,
and I know you've been through a lot of very
painful and very unsuccessful surgeries,
but if you're up for it, I think I could
significantly help with the spinal curvature.
By "help," you mean what, exactly ?
I mean, I think I can get you
standing up straight.
Are you messing with me ?
'Cause it's not nice
to mock crippled kids.
You see this...
This curved part here ?
I'd remove it.
You... You want to remove a portion
of my daughter's spine ?
And I would replace it with a titanium
mesh cage that would fill in the space
between the vertebra.
I've seen case studies.
There have been quite a few successes.
And... And the ones
that aren't successful ?
They result in paralysis or death.
But dr. Shepherd is the best there is.
- She's 17.
- Mom,
I know you still think death is the
worst thing that can happen to a person.
Death is not the worst thing.
I'm in.
They're gonna cut out a piece of
her spine... Heather Douglas.
Doctors Shepherd and Torres, they're...
They're gonna straighten her spine.
And ?
And...
It's a once-in-a-lifetime surgery.
Please. She's my patient. I've gotten to
know her. I would really like to scrub in.
- Did you deposit the check ?
- It's my money.
I should get to do what I want with it.
Uh, you get a 5% return on 6-month cd ?
In the time we've been standing here,
you could've just made $400.
Dr. Bailey.
It's not reasonable, Stevens.
Dad, it's your discard.
I'm sorry about running over bucky.
- What ?
- Your dog.
That yappy dog bucky.
When you were a kid,
I ran over him, and I told you he ran
away. I'm sorry about that.
- You ran over my dog on purpose ?
- Of course not.
He was chasing after the truck like always
and he got caught up under the tire.
You were so sensitive. You were such
a soft kid, I couldn't bear to tell ya.
I wasn't soft.
I mean it good, Georgie.
You were kind and you loved animals.
You were always looking to help people.
And I couldn't face you and tell you
that I killed your dog so...
I told you a lie.
I'm saying I'm sorry.
Okay.
You're a good kid, Georgie.
Always  been
such a good kid.
I want to tell you--
Dad, stop acting like you're dying.
You're not dying, okay ?
I want to tell you that I think you're
crazy if you let that Callie get away.
- Dad, please !
- No, she gets you.
She gets you in a way that your
family never has. I'm sorry about that,
That you grew up feeling
so different all the time.
- That's another thing I'm sorry about.
- Dad, stop it.
Stop apologizing, stop saying good-bye.
You can't...
that's no way to go into surgery.
I'm gonna die someday, Georgie.
We're all gonna die,
and lying here in this bed gives me
time to think about all the things
I haven't said is all.
Okay.
Well, just discard.
- Anything you want to say to me ?
- Dad !
I'm discarding.
Dog murderer
Tell me what I wanna hear.
If I die, you'll kill me.
He's a quick study.
Meredith. Hello.
- Hello.
- I'm...
- Uh, how are you ?
- Good.
Uh, busy with work.
We have a patient.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Uh, all right, then.
- Oh, I'm so... Uh, nice seeing you.
- Okay.
That your ex-boyfriend.
No, that's my ex-father.
You see, Grey ?
Good exposure to the esophageal hiatus.
Yes, sir.
Now we will inspect
and palpate the abdominal cavity.
Oh...
Those are the mets, right ?
Throughout the stomach,
the celiac lymph nodes, the liver.
- It's everywhere.
- So that's it ? We're closing him back up ?
No.
We will proceed.
- But I thought...
- The patient asked us to proceed.
- What does that mean exactly ?
- This man asked for a chance to fight.
What it means is...
He's gonna have to fight like hell.
But he can recover ?
There's a chance ?
There's a chance.
Dr. Grey, the request from the patient...
It was private.
Yes.
Okay.
- Preston.
- Oh, Addison.
How you feeling ?
Better.
Looking forward to going home.
Well, I'm sure dr. Yang is looking forward
to having you back there as well.
Uh, maybe. I wouldn't know.
Why wouldn't you know ?
What...
is... is that over ?
No, it's not over.
It's just... silent.
Oh, yeah, yes. I heard something about this.
Um, one of the nurses was talking.
I just thought it was gossip.
- It's not.
- So you're not talking to her. Why not ?
- Did you ever play say "uncle"?
- Say "uncle"?
Someone bends your arm behind your back
harder and harder until you say "uncle."
And then what happens ?
Then they have all the power.
I see.
- So you are not saying "uncle."
- Yes.
And neither is she.
- It seems that way.
- That's pathetic.
- Well, you may be right.
- I am right.
If you did something wrong,
then you apologize.
Well, I didn't do anything wrong.
Did she ?
She doesn't seem to think so.
That's pathetic.
- Hey.
- You're all alone. Where's your family ?
- Eating. They like to eat.
You're pacing.
Yeah.
It's just, he's been
in surgery for a while.
That's good. It means
they're being thorough.
Or it means there are complications.
- Somebody would've told you
if there were complications.
- Right.
- It's okay to be scared.
- I'm not scared.
- I'm just sayin', if you are...
- You can talk to me.
You sure about that ?
Okay, now I'm scared of you.
Damn it.
I was staring you down.
- Staring me down ?
- Yeah, it worked on Shepherd.
Seriously?
Wait, wait. Let me try it again.
- No, it's not...
- No ?
I'm still scared.
Hold on. I'll be right back.
Uh, you should prepare yourself,
because this is a much more extensive
surgery than the heart valve.
There's probably still a tube in
his throat helping him breathe,
and half his stomach was cut out
and part of his esophagus,
so there's gonna be a big scar.
- Okay.
- Just... be prepared.
Welcome back, sweetheart.
Dad looks like something
out of the butcher shop.
That's a cool scar.
You need to breathe.
he's my dad.
- I know.
- He's my dad.
Oh, you have got to be kidding me.
where is George ?
He spent the night at the hospital.
- And you slept in his bed.
- Mm-hmm.
All night ?
No. Just after you fell asleep.
So you're telling me
that my snoring is so bad--
How did you deal with it for all those nights
before I found out about your wife ?
He usually sleeps on the couch,
sets an alarm,
gets back in bed before you wake up.
Yeah, I didn't want to hurt your feelings.
Well, I'm gonna do more
than hurt your feelings.
What are you doing ?
Oh. Stop it.
I'm gonna hurt your feelings'cause...
Can I... help you ?
I, um...
I-I inherited $8 million.
- I'm sorry ?
- Almost 9, actually.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Thank you.
- I'm sorry. Did you say--
- Here, just take it.
- Just take it, please.
- Is that...
It's covered in food.
Is this some kind of joke ?
It is kind of a joke...
A really cruel joke.
- I'm sorry. You want to deposit this ?
- If I wanted to deposit it,
Do you think that I would look like this ?
I don't understand.
I'm supposed to do something good.
I'm supposed to do something good,
and...
and I didn't... Can... Can you just
deposit the damn thing already ?!
I'm surprised they proceeded
with the surgery.
Me, too. I guess they think he has a strong
enough constitution to fight the cancer.
Is he conscious ?
Still intubated,
so they have him sedated.
The main concern
for the next few days.
Will be multisystem organ failure.
That is that the surgery was too intense
for his weakened organs to support.
You want to watch the kidneys
because if the kidneys fail, that's a sign
that everything else is starting to go.
- So we're watching the kidneys.
- You're watching the kidneys.
Thank you.
Oh, do you mind me asking,
Uh, how's your hand ?
I don't mind if you ask.
I will mind if you tell Cristina.
You two have a strange relationship.
Yes, we do.
And when you go home, you're gonna have
your very own room. Yes, you do.
and your mom, she got one of those, um,
you know, uh, those stencils.
Mm-hmm.
And she made little butterflies
and flowers.
You need something ?
No, I'm fine.
Oh, it gets quiet in here.
You're the one who paged me ?
I started my shift ten minutes ago, noticed
her stomach looked a little distended.
Her stomach's distended ?
I... I didn't notice that.
It's hard to see.
Page dr. Montgomery, stat.
Is everything okay ? Is this bad ?
Well, let's just wait for
dr. Montgomery.
What's the matter ?
- My father's here.
- Your father ?
The one I don't talk to
and barely know, he's here.
What, is he here to see you ?
- No. He's here with his other family.
- Oh, sorry.
Where do you sleep at the trailer ?
- What ?
- When we sleep at the trailer,
where do you sleep ?
You know the hammock outside?
Sorry.
I'm a girl with abandonment issues.
You have to sleep with me from now on.
Okay.
A note from my hack
of a shrink. I get to scrub in.
- Not till I say so.
- I deposited the damn check.
You cheap son of a bitch bastards
are going straight to hell...
straight to hell !
Ms. Douglas?
Insurance bastards.
They say the surgery's too experimental.
They won't pay.
It's a $200,000 surgery,
plus a hospital stay, plus rehab.
Even if I get three jobs...
Son of a bitch bastards.
Looks like there won't be a surgery
to scrub in on. Sorry, stevens.
Talk to me.
Her abdomen was distended and she needed
an increased ventilatory support,
- so I ordered some x-rays.
- I'm sorry. I was talking to her.
I didn't notice.
She's got massive free air
trapped beath her diaphragm.
Mr. Grey, we need to get
Laura into surgery.
What ? Another surgery ? Why ?
Her x-rays indicate there's
a perforation in the bowel.
We need to get in there right away.
Here's a consent form.
We need you to sign it.
I don't... I... I don't know...
her... her mother has the flu.
What, you're not authorized to sign ?
I am. But I... I'd like to fill her in
we don't have time
for you to not know, mr. Grey.
Your granddaughter doesn't have time.
All right.
Take out more of the bowel.
I need better visualization.
It's so tiny, I'm afraid
I might crush it.
Oh, it's tougher than you think.
Go ahead and give it a little squeeze.
Cool. Thanks.
Look at that. The N.G. Tube has eroded
right through the stomach wall.
I may have to resect an entire portion
of the stomach.
She's hypotensive.
Push 30 ccs of albumin.
- Whew.
- Scary.
You're telling me.
This is Meredith's Grey's niece.
If I lost her, people might
think I did it on purpose.
- How's it going ?
- Okay.
They had a scare a minute ago,
but she stabilized.
Your, uh, father is pacing
up and down the halls.
He's worried.
Maybe you can give him an update.
He's not a big fan of mine.
- He's not a big fan of mine either.
- Oh, I can't imagine that's true.
Your mother was a force
to be reckoned with.
If she wanted things a certain way, I...
I'm saying your father
was a good man when I knew him.
He may have a side in this that
you don't know anything about.
What, you think he tried to send me a
card every year and my mother has a
whole drawer full of unopened cards ?
Because it's not often that my life
turns out that way.
I don't know. You don't know either
until you ask him.
Hey. How's he doing ?
Uh, Georgie is obsessed
with our dad's pee.
Yeah, this is weird,
- even for georgie.
- Boys, be nice.
It's his kidney function.
I'm obsessed with his
kidney function, not his pee.
And I'm not obsessed.
I'm excited.
You're not gonna drink that,
are you, Georgie ?
130 ccs!
130 ccs of shiny, yellow urine !
130 ccs in how long?
- Four hours.
- No way !
That is fantastic!
Thank you !
Thank you.
Mark.
I'm sorry you're hurting.
You're sorry I'm hurting
or you're sorry ?
Karev.
Oh. Hey. I was, uh
- just checking the baby's capillary refills
- No, it's good, it's good.
We all need a little human contact
from time to time.
It sucks. It's like she hasn't had
a chance to deserve this, you know ?
Is that why you want to go into plastics,
'cause people sign up
for the pain they get ?
Yeah. For the most part, they do, yeah.
You're right. It does suck
watching them struggle.
And that part never stops sucking.
But... then when you get
to see a baby heal and, um...
they get to go home and...
you just imagine this whole life
that they're gonna live,
there's nothing better than that.
And that part never changes.
But...
- if you want to go back to plastics...
- Nah.
The vanilla latte ?
- I did that on purpose.
- Why ?
'Cause he was rude to you.
- I'm, uh, sorry.
- No, I'm sorry.
- Sorry.
- Gosh, I'm... really sorry.
- No, I'm okay. I'm, uh,
I'm just, um... I'm gonna...
Yeah, okay. Yeah. Yeah.
(Travis'"love will come through" playing)
Oh, hey. You need some help ?
I can walk to the bathroom myself.
I've been doing it my whole life,
and nothing's changing any time soon,
so just get out of my way, okay ?
"And I can't live alone in this lie"
"so look up take it away"
"don't look da-da-da down..."
meredith.
"The mountain"
"if the world isn't turning
your heart won't return"
"anyone, anything, anyhow"
"so take me don't leave me"
"take me don't leave me"
"baby love will come through
it's just waiting for you"
"baby
love will come through
"well, I stand at the crossroads
of high roads and low roads
and I got a feeling it's right"
"if it's real, what I'm feeling there's no
make believing the sound of the wings
of the flight of a dove"
"take it away don't look da-da-da down
the mountain"
"if the world isn't turning your heart
won't return anyone, anything, anyhow"
"so take me don't leave me
take me don't leave me"
"baby love will come through
it's just waiting for you"
"love will come through"
Transcript : Raceman - Synchro : ChipounetteF
Traduction : Chryssie, Tbdb - Relecture : Cookie
www.forom.com