Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Wake up.
Dr. Meredith Grey: Remember when you were a kid and your biggest worry was, like, if you'd get a bike for your birthday or if you'd get to eat cookies for breakfast?
Dr. Meredith Grey: Being an adult?
Dr. Meredith Grey: Totally overrated.
Dr. Meredith Grey: I mean, seriously, don't be fooled by all the hot shoes and the great sex and the no parents anywhere telling you what to do.
Dr. Meredith Grey: Adulthood is responsibility.
Lawyer / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Her lawyer has been managing her estate with a limited power of attorney, but your mother's Alzheimer's is advancing.
Lawyer / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): So while she's still lucid enough to consent, she needs to sign everything over to you.
Dr. Meredith Grey: Me?
Dr. Meredith Grey: responsibility it really does suck look I haven't slept in 48 hours I'm getting my first shot at heart surgery this morning I'm missing rounds are you sure there isn't anybody here or the attorney I mean do I really have to be the one to handle this we're talking about her estate her finances her medical care you really want to leave her life in someone else's hands she's your mother really really sucks
Dr. Meredith Grey: Adults have to be places and do things and earn a living and pay the rent.
Dr. Meredith Grey: And if you're training to be a surgeon, holding a human heart in your hands?
Dr. Meredith Grey: Hello, talk about responsibility.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): What was that, Dr. Gray?
Dr. Meredith Grey: Sorry, it slipped.
Dr. Meredith Grey: My hands.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): It's okay, I'm done.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): You can release Mrs. Patterson's heart now.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Very gently.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): All right.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Let's warm her up.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Get her off bypass.
Dr. Meredith Grey: Kind of makes bikes and cookies look really, really good, doesn't it?
Izzy Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I wish I could hold a heart.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): A monkey could hold a heart.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You're Matt Burke, didn't ask you.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): George, I need more ice and chips.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Who else did you invite?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Izzy, we said the list was jocks only.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Surgery, trauma, plastics.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Who else?
Alex Karev / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Just some people from Peds.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): You invited the preschoolers to Meredith's house.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Next thing you'll say that you invited the shrinks.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): She invited mental defects.
Alex Karev / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): This party is DOA.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You know, Meredith thinks this is going to be just like a little small meet your boyfriend cocktail thing.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Did you clear this with her?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): No, but I will.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I promise.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Why are you wasting the only weekend your boyfriend is in town on a big party?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Is he bad in bed?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): No, I just want him to meet some of my friends.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Right.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): 60 Geeks and Scrubs are your friends.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Bad sex.
Alex Karev / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Jerry Frost (PVM): Sucks for you.
George O'Malley / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Jerry Frost (PVM): I heard there's a party tonight at Meredith's house.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Oh, really?
George O'Malley / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Mrs. Drake (PVM): A party?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Uh, news to me.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Mrs. Drake (PVM): No party.
Cristina Yang / Jerry Frost (PVM): They're losing her or what?
Dr. Burke / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Are the grafts here open?
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Temperature?
Nurse / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): She's at 96 and rising.
Dr. Burke / Mr. Patterson (PVM): She should be doing this on her own.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): That's her phone.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Continue the compressions.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Come on, Mrs. Patterson.
Nurse / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Paddle sets are below 90.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Charge.
Nurse / Mr. Patterson (PVM): 10 joules.
Dr. Burke / Mr. Patterson (PVM): Clear.
Unknown (likely a surgeon or intern in surgery) / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Come on, Mrs. Patterson.
Unknown (likely a surgeon or intern in surgery) / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Give me 20.
Unknown (likely a nurse or surgeon) / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Charge.
Unknown (likely a surgeon or intern in surgery) / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): There.
Unknown (likely a surgeon or intern in surgery) / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): We have rhythm.
Unknown (likely a nurse or intern) / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Nothing yet.
Unknown (likely a nurse or intern) / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): There we go.
Unknown (likely a surgeon or intern in surgery) / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Reluctant heart.
Unknown (likely a surgeon or intern in surgery) / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): All right.
Unknown (likely lead surgeon) / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Let's close and keep an eye on it.
Unknown (likely lead surgeon) / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Good work, everyone.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): The scariest part about responsibility?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): When you screw up and let it slip right through your fingers.
George O'Malley / Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Hey, I heard you did a cabbage with Brooke.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Yeah.
George O'Malley / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Did you get to hold the harp?
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): All right.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): It's an amazing feeling, isn't it?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You never forget the first time.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It was pretty great just to watch.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Vicarious thrills, you know?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Yeah.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): I'll see you later.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Bye.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I think maybe I did something to the heart when I was holding it.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I nodded off a little, squeezed it.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Oh, please.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): The heart's a tough muscle.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It can take a squeeze or two.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): My fingernail popped a glove.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Cut straight through.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): George, what if I punctured Mrs. Patterson's heart?
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): If you hadn't punctured it, you know, you would have known when they reperfused.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): They got her heart beating.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): The woman's okay.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): So I shouldn't tell Burke?
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Tell him what?
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You know, um... Nothing happened.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): The woman's okay, right?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): She's okay.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): She's fine.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): She's fine.
Dr. Meredith Grey: Nobody knows where they might end up.
Dr. Meredith Grey: Nobody knows.
Dr. Meredith Grey: Oh, oh, suppose.
Dr. Burke / Jerry Frost (PVM): What do you see, George?
George O'Malley / Mrs. Drake OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Jerry Frost (PVM): Hyperinflated lungs, cloudy with boule.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Seriously diminished capacity.
Dr. Burke / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): She must be having trouble breathing.
Dr. Burke / Jerry Frost (PVM): Course of action?
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): A bulectomy procedure.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Remove the boule, reduce the pressure.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Says here we operated on her back in 99, so Mrs. Drake has been through this before, but talk her through it anyway.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): And resists the anti-smoking lectures.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): She feels bad enough already.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): So do you think if they put a picture of these in a pack of cigarettes, people would stop smoking?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Jerry Frost (PVM): How long has your back been hurting you?
Mrs. Drake: It's chronic.
Mrs. Drake: It means I have it all the time.
Meredith Grey / Jerry Frost (PVM): I know what chronic means.
Meredith Grey / Jerry Frost (PVM): What kind of pain are you having?
Mrs. Drake: Oh, man, the pain's bad.
Patient (likely Mrs. Drake) / Jerry Frost (PVM): It's like thousands of samurai warriors stabbing their swords into my spine.
Patient (likely Mrs. Drake) / Dr. George O'Malley OR Jerry Frost (PVM): I'm allergic to aspirin, most NSAIDs.
Doctor (likely George or Meredith) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): So maybe we'll start you on morphine.
Patient (likely Mrs. Drake) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Yeah, the only things that'll work are
Patient (likely Mrs. Drake) / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Demerol or Dilaudid, a ton of Dilaudid.
Patient (likely Mrs. Drake) / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): That'll set me straight.
Doctor (likely George or Meredith) / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): The standard starting dose is two.
Patient (likely Mrs. Drake) / Jerry Frost (PVM): Did you see that Tom Cruise samurai movie?
Doctor (likely George or Meredith) / Unknown (PVM): Hm?
Patient (likely Mrs. Drake) / Jerry Frost OR Jerry Frost (PVM): Pow, pow, pow.
Doctor (likely George or Meredith) / Jerry Frost (PVM): Exaggerated and overly specific description of his pain.
Doctor (likely George or Meredith) / Jerry Frost (PVM): A self-prescription, uh, pow, pow, pow.
Doctor (likely George or Meredith) / Jerry Frost (PVM): He's a Dilaudid junkie.
Doctor (likely George or Meredith) / Jerry Frost (PVM): So what do you do?
Doctor (likely George or Meredith) / Jerry Frost (PVM): Well, you check the database for history, refer to a program, and discharge.
Doctor (likely George or Meredith) / Jerry Frost (PVM): After you give him something.
Doctor (likely George or Meredith) / Jerry Frost (PVM): That's exactly what he wants.
Doctor (likely George or Meredith) / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Chunky or not, you still have to treat his pain as if it were real.
Doctor (likely George or Meredith) / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Why?
Doctor (likely George or Meredith) / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): It's the first rule in pain management.
Doctor (likely George or Meredith) / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Always err on the side of caution.
Doctor (likely George or Meredith) / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): He's in our care.
Doctor (likely George or Meredith) / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): He says he's in pain.
Doctor (likely George or Meredith) / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Start a central line.
Doctor (likely George or Meredith) / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): His veins are shot.
Patient (likely Mrs. Drake) / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): The surgery before was supposed to help, but it never felt right.
Doctor (likely George or Meredith) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Probably would have been a good idea to quit smoking.
Patient (likely Mrs. Drake) / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I did.
Patient (likely Mrs. Drake) / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Poor pack of day habit.
Patient (likely Mrs. Drake) / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Oh, it was hell.
Doctor (likely George or Meredith) / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Here you go, Mrs. Drake.
Mrs. Drake: Didn't do any damn good.
George / Mr. Sturman OR Mrs. Drake (PVM): Really?
George / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Because it looked, I mean, from the damage, we all thought you probably were still smoking.
Mrs. Drake: Cold turkey.
Mrs. Drake: Five years ago, what'd I get for my trouble?
Mrs. Drake: I still had to quit my job at the restaurant.
Mrs. Drake: But even sitting, it hurt.
George / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Here you go.
Mrs. Drake: Nobody believed me.
Mrs. Drake: They all said it was in my head.
George / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I've seen the films.
George / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It's not all in your head.
Mrs. Drake: You're right about that.
Mrs. Drake: Hey, come here.
Mrs. Drake: You're too damn young to be a doctor.
George / Mrs. Drake (PVM): Hey.
Mrs. Drake: What?
Dr. George O'Malley: I'm older than I look.
Mrs. Drake: Do you think this is going to work this time?
Dr. George O'Malley: I think it's your best option.
Mrs. Drake: Great shooter, huh?
Dr. George O'Malley: Yes, ma'am.
Mrs. Drake: I like that.
George / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Hi, Mr. Patterson.
Mr. Patterson: Hi.
George / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Hemodynamic stable?
Other Intern / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Yeah, MAP is stayed around 8, cardiac output at 5.
Senior Doctor / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Mr. Patterson (PVM): That's good, Dr. Gray.
George / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): That's fine, Mr. Patterson.
Mr. Patterson: But it's not good.
George / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Well, heart surgery takes a lot out of the patient.
Doctor (possibly Meredith or another intern/resident) / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): But we're monitoring your wife very carefully, and she should be fine.
Doctor (possibly Meredith or another intern/resident) / Mrs. Drake (PVM): Mr. Sturman, let's see about getting you out of here today.
Doctor (possibly Meredith or another intern/resident) / Mrs. Drake (PVM): How you feeling?
Mr. Sturman: Pretty OK, except I don't think I ever want to have a bowel obstruction again.
Doctor (possibly Meredith or another intern/resident) / Mr. Sturman OR Mrs. Drake (PVM): Really?
Doctor (possibly Meredith or another intern/resident) / Mr. Sturman OR Mrs. Drake (PVM): Wow, because we get people in here all the time requesting them.
Doctor (possibly Meredith or another intern/resident) / Mrs. Drake (PVM): So you're keeping non-clear fluids?
Doctor (possibly Meredith or another intern/resident) / Mrs. Drake (PVM): And my all-time favorite question to ask a patient, have you pooped yet?
Mr. Sturman: I'm not exactly sure.
Doctor (possibly Meredith or another intern/resident) / Mr. Sturman OR Mrs. Drake (PVM): I think you probably know.
Doctor (possibly Meredith or another intern/resident) / Mrs. Drake (PVM): Past gas?
Mr. Sturman: Yes.
Doctor (possibly Meredith or another intern/resident) / Mrs. Drake (PVM): Really, yes?
Doctor (possibly Meredith or another intern/resident) / Mrs. Drake (PVM): Because if I bring in my handy lie detector.
Mr. Sturman: OK, no.
Mr. Sturman: I shouldn't try and lie, I know.
Mr. Sturman: I went to medical school.
Doctor (possibly Meredith or another intern/resident) / Mrs. Drake (PVM): You went to med school?
Mr. Sturman: Yeah, dropped out my last year of clinical.
Mr. Sturman: Too many hours, and I was staring into the ice-cold eyes of divorce.
Doctor (possibly Meredith or another intern/resident) / Jerry Frost (PVM): Wow.
Mr. Sturman: Yeah.
Mr. Sturman: I do research now, and I have a life, a family.
Mr. Sturman: No offense.
Doctor (possibly Meredith or another intern/resident) / Mr. Sturman OR Mrs. Drake (PVM): You know, I mean... Oh, no, no.
Doctor (possibly Meredith or another intern/resident) / Mrs. Drake (PVM): Um, that's okay.
Doctor (possibly Meredith or another intern/resident) / Mr. Sturman OR Mrs. Drake (PVM): I'm just one of those people who believe you can have both.
Mr. Sturman: Maybe so.
Mr. Sturman: But your first responsibility is always going to be your patient.
Doctor (possibly Meredith or another intern/resident) / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Dr. Shepard?
Doctor (possibly Meredith or another intern/resident) / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Okay.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Okay.
Unknown (Possibly Cristina Yang or George O'Malley) / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You're always the same You're always the same
Dr. Burke / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Jerry Frost OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Call this a spaghetti procedure.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Preston Burke OR Jerry Frost (PVM): We cut and deflate the boulet to facilitate gentle manipulation of Mrs. Drake's lung.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Dr. Bailey, you see that?
Dr. Bailey / Jerry Frost (PVM): Sir?
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Preston Burke OR Jerry Frost (PVM): Oh, my ever-loving.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): We need to open her up.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): I'm taking out the scope.
Dr. Bailey / Jerry Frost (PVM): You heard him, people.
Dr. Bailey / Mr. Patterson (PVM): Let's move.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Lights.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Preston Burke OR Mr. Sturman OR Jerry Frost (PVM): All right, let's get set up.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Preston Burke OR Mr. Sturman OR Jerry Frost (PVM): Tin blade.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Here you go.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Tractors.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Tractors.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): That's a couple ready.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Tunnel.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Thank you.
Dr. Burke / Jerry Frost OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): That rib spreader.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Mr. Patterson (PVM): Suction.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Is that a towel?
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Where did that come from?
Dr. Burke / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Best guess, her surgery five years ago.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Jerry Frost (PVM): Something careless this way comes.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): A towel?
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Not good.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): She complained of pressure on her chest and nobody took her seriously.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Not good for the patient, not good for the hospital, not good.
Dr. Burke / Jerry Frost (PVM): Christina, hit the files.
Miranda Bailey / Jerry Frost (PVM): Find out everything you can about that initial operation.
Miranda Bailey / Jerry Frost (PVM): Who was in that room?
Miranda Bailey / Jerry Frost (PVM): Who was responsible for closing it?
Miranda Bailey / Jerry Frost (PVM): George, you stay with the patient.
Miranda Bailey / Jerry Frost (PVM): Keep her happy.
Miranda Bailey / Jerry Frost (PVM): She seems to like you.
Dr. George O'Malley: Right, OK.
Dr. George O'Malley: Um, how long do you think?
Dr. George O'Malley: I mean, just technically, I'm off at 6.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Am I invited?
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Excuse me?
Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Am I invited to the party?
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Oh, well, yeah.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Yes, yeah, of course.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): What was I supposed to say?
Miranda Bailey / Jerry Frost OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Okay, yeah, great.
Cristina Yang / Jerry Frost (PVM): All right, 14 cases.
Izzie Stevens / Jerry Frost (PVM): Uh, what kind?
Cristina Yang / Jerry Frost (PVM): I don't know, maybe an assortment?
Cristina Yang / Jerry Frost (PVM): Microbrews, locals.
Cristina Yang / Jerry Frost (PVM): Make sure they throw in some bar nuts.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Jerry Frost (PVM): I'm ordering office supplies.
Cristina Yang / Jerry Frost OR Mr. Sturman OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Jerry Frost (PVM): Oh, yeah, sure.
Izzie Stevens / Jerry Frost (PVM): Microbrews, local, and throw in some bar nuts.
Cristina Yang / Jerry Frost (PVM): Seven o'clock would be better than five.
Alex Karev / Jerry Frost OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Uh, hey, any luck?
Meredith Grey / Mr. Sturman OR Jerry Frost (PVM): Hey, if I do, will you invite me to the party?
Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Yeah, great.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Okay, thanks.
Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Take it easy.
Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Hey, Mr. Frost.
Mrs. Drake / Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Where the hell have you been?
George / Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): We're gonna take care of you, all right?
George / Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Now just hang on.
Mrs. Drake / Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Where the hell have you been?
George / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): How's that?
Senior Doctor (possibly Dr. Bailey) / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): When I tell you to start a central line, you start a central line.
Senior Doctor (possibly Dr. Bailey) / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): No judgment, no question.
Junior Doctor (possibly George) / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): The guy's been in seven hospitals in the last four months.
Junior Doctor (possibly George) / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): He's a major addict.
Junior Doctor (possibly George) / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): The patient has a three lumbar fusion.
Junior Doctor (possibly George) / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): He's a junkie.
Junior Doctor (possibly George) / Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I mean, we shouldn't be giving him... Yeah, he's an addict, but his pain is real.
Senior Doctor (possibly Dr. Bailey) / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Now, lose the attitude, get down there, start a central line.
Mrs. Drake / Unknown (PVM): Oh, God.
Mrs. Drake / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Mrs. Drake (PVM): Told me I had a towel inside me.
George / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Who told you that?
Mrs. Drake / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): A surgeon.
Mrs. Drake / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Owner, man.
Mrs. Drake / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Handsome.
George / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): That's Dr. Weber.
George / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He's our chief.
Mrs. Drake / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Yeah.
Mrs. Drake / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): There was a towel that somebody left last time.
George / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Yes, ma'am.
Mrs. Drake / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Who would do that?
Mrs. Drake / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): That doesn't seem right, does it?
George / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): No, ma'am, no.
George / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It doesn't.
Mrs. Drake / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): That's walking around with a towel inside of me.
Mrs. Drake / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): How could that happen?
Mrs. Drake / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): So what happens now?
Dr. Burke / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Jerry Frost (PVM): Now you keep this to yourself while we work it out.
Dr. Burke / Mr. Sturman OR Jerry Frost (PVM): Do this for me.
Unknown (likely a nurse or intern) / Mr. Sturman (PVM): Dr. Stevens called the CCU.
Unknown (likely a nurse or intern) / Mr. Sturman (PVM): Dr. Stevens called CCU.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): You sure?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Because you seem not okay.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): I'm fine.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Cabbage was long.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Well, let me take you out to dinner tonight.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): You can tell me all about it.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Real food, waiters, big chunks of carbs in a basket.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): I can't.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Forget about the party.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): You know about the party?
Dr. Burke / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Your friends will be at the party.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): You and I can be alone somewhere else.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): How do you know about the party?
Dr. Burke / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Thanks for not inviting me, by the way.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): That felt good.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Dinner.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Think about dinner.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Perfect opportunity.
Cristina Yang / Unknown (PVM): Well...
Dr. Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): What happened?
Nurse / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Started having some swelling over her sternum, and then the blood just started gushing.
Nurse / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Dr. Burke is on his way right now.
Unknown (family member or bystander) / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Is she dying?
Dr. Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Somebody get him out of here.
Dr. Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Keep applying pressure.
Unknown (possibly a nurse or orderly) / Mr. Patterson (PVM): Sir.
Dr. Stevens / Mr. Patterson (PVM): Tyler, call 4-N-O-R.
Dr. Burke / Mr. Patterson (PVM): What the hell happened?
Dr. Burke / Mr. Patterson (PVM): She got a protamine?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): For a protocol, no allergic, anaphylactic, or histamine responses.
Dr. Burke / Mr. Patterson (PVM): Her last counts?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): PT, PTT, INR, platelet counts were all stable.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Even her H and H were stable.
Dr. Burke / Mr. Patterson (PVM): What the hell went wrong?
Dr. Burke / Mr. Patterson (PVM): Let's move.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Hold on.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Mr. Patterson (PVM): I popped a glove.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): What?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): In surgery, when I was holding it, I popped a glove with my fingernail.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): I think I may have nicked her heart.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Let's go, people.
Dr. Burke / Mr. Patterson OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): What were you thinking about?
Dr. Burke / Mr. Patterson (PVM): You had every opportunity to speak up before I closed her chest.
Dr. Burke / Mr. Patterson (PVM): Every opportunity.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Mr. Patterson (PVM): Suction.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm sorry.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Mr. Patterson (PVM): And then you go and confess in front of her husband?
Dr. Burke / Mr. Patterson OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): You don't even know if you were the cause.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): You have no idea.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Sturman (PVM): I'm sorry, Spencer.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): There.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Loading.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Over here.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): There.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Look at the wall, Rocha.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): It's a hell of a lot more than a fingernail.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Her ventricular walls are weak.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): I just had a conversation with Mr. Patterson.
Dr. Preston Burke: I want copies of his wife's chart in my office by 5.
Dr. Preston Burke: Tomorrow morning, the two of you are going to meet with me and legal, and you better damn well be able to explain what happened here.
Dr. Preston Burke: People poking holes in hearts, leaving towels in people.
Dr. Preston Burke: You're going to go back and talk to the husband.
Dr. Preston Burke: Review the history, apologize profusely.
Dr. Preston Burke: Your ass is on the line here, Dr. Gray.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You got called before the chief?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Tomorrow morning.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I mean, I could get kicked out of the program.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I could, right?
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You're not getting kicked out.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Patterson's just going to sue.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Patterson is not going to sue, and you're not getting kicked out.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): What the hell were you thinking, telling Burke?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): That was so stupid.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I told her not to.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I got to take this.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Biggs, thank you.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Very comforting.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I'll watch your books.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Mrs. Drake (PVM): Okay, so the beer is coming at 7, and some of the floor nurses are bringing wine.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Nurses?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): You invited nurses?
Izzie Stevens / Mrs. Drake (PVM): Did you clear this with Meredith?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Mrs. Drake (PVM): A few more people isn't gonna make a difference, okay?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): A party is a party.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): And the bigger the party, the less time for bad sex with the hockey player.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Mrs. Drake (PVM): Would you stop saying that?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Okay.
Izzie Stevens / Mrs. Drake (PVM): Hank and I have great sex.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Mm-hmm.
Cristina Yang / Mrs. Drake (PVM): All the time.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley OR Mrs. Drake (PVM): In fact, we'll probably have sex after the party or during the party.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): As long as you clear it with Meredith...
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Mrs. Drake (PVM): You just need to realize that doctors can have fun.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): We're not all workaholics with God complexes.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): We are workaholics with God complexes.
Richard Webber / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): And the notary can be there at 6.30 too.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): And the home's physician will be there to attest to her mental competency.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Okay.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Is there anything else I need to bring beside my license?
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): My checkbook.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): It's 6.30.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I'll be there.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): I heard.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): It's a notary thing, a thing to get notarized.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): You're talking about the heart thing.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Do you want to talk about that?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): We're adults.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): When did that happen?
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): And how do we make it stop?
Unknown / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Dr. Yang?
Unknown / Unknown (PVM): Dr. Burke?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): That bypass graph got a little complicated.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): There's nothing I couldn't handle.
Preston Burke / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Good.
Cristina Yang / Unknown (PVM): Uh-huh.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Yeah.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Mm-hmm.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Listen, I'll call you back.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Patterson (PVM): That was my lawyer.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Mr. Patterson (PVM): He's advising me not to talk to you.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Mr. Patterson, I know that you're frustrated and angry.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): But I need, we need, some more information about your wife.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Mr. Patterson (PVM): The walls of her heart are abnormally thin.
Mr. Patterson: Hey, don't blame this on my wife.
Mr. Patterson: I heard from your very mouth what happened.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Patterson (PVM): I know.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Mr. Patterson (PVM): But we can't treat her.
Mr. Patterson: No, she was in the best shape of her life.
Mr. Patterson: You ask a cardiologist.
Mr. Patterson: She had lost 100 pounds.
Mr. Patterson: Don't you dare try to hang this on her.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Mr. Patterson OR Mr. Patterson (PVM): Mr. Patterson, please.
Mr. Patterson: What you talking?
Jerry Frost: You don't like me very much, do you?
Alex Karev / Jerry Frost (PVM): Well, Jerry, it's not you specifically.
Alex Karev / Jerry Frost (PVM): It's just, uh, it's just people like you, that's all.
Jerry Frost: Ah, feeling pretty good.
Jerry Frost: Paying's about a three.
Alex Karev / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): A three?
Alex Karev / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): That's excellent.
Alex Karev / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Mr. Frost, I'm glad we could help you out, as well as County, Mercy West, Seattle Press.
Alex Karev / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): A lot of people have helped you out lately, Jerry.
Alex Karev / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): I'm pleased we could do our part.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Who's on discharge today, Dr. Karev?
Dr. Alex Karev: Izzy Stevens.
Dr. Alex Karev: Mr. Frost, Dr. Stevens is gonna come in to discharge you.
Jerry Frost: Well, well, well, you can't discharge me.
Jerry Frost: I'm in pain.
Alex Karev / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): You were in pain.
Alex Karev / Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Now you're not.
Alex Karev / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Dr. Karev here is gonna recommend some wonderful treatment programs for you.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Go home.
Care Team Member / Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Get some help.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You can't just do that.
Care Team Member / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You just did, my friend.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Okay.
Notary / Mrs. Drake (PVM): Any luck yet?
Meredith Grey / Mr. Sturman (PVM): Not, uh...
Care Team Member / Mrs. Drake (PVM): Looks like you're gonna have to spend another night.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Sturman OR Mr. Sturman (PVM): I hate to miss the party.
Notary / Mr. Sturman (PVM): You gonna make it?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Alex Karev OR Mrs. Drake (PVM): Well, you are the last person on my list, so it's looking pretty good.
Notary / Mr. Sturman (PVM): So, doctors have lives after all.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Sturman (PVM): Who'da thunk?
Attending Physician / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Dr. Stevens, discharge my guy in 3.42.
Dr. Izzie Stevens / Mrs. Drake (PVM): Don't look at me like that.
Dr. Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Mrs. Drake (PVM): It's not gonna take very long.
Dr. Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Mrs. Drake (PVM): It's not.
Dr. Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley OR Jerry Frost (PVM): You paged me?
Dr. Izzie Stevens / Mrs. Drake (PVM): I'm gonna be a while.
Dr. Izzie Stevens / Mrs. Drake (PVM): Do you think you could get home to sign for the beer?
Dr. George O'Malley / Jerry Frost (PVM): Why don't you have your boyfriend sign for it?
Dr. Alex Karev / Mrs. Drake (PVM): You have a very annoying way of sneaking up on people.
Dr. George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Maybe if you were a little less creepy.
Dr. Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I wouldn't come anyway.
Dr. George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I hate big parties.
Dr. Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Is Meredith the only person in this hospital who doesn't know the size of this thing?
Dr. Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I'm telling her.
Dr. Izzie Stevens / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): You can't.
Dr. Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): She's gone already.
Dr. Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): What?
Dr. Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Already?
George / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I think she had, um, excuse me, an errand to run.
Izzie / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You don't think Mary's really going to mind about the party, right?
George / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I want you to make it very clear to her that I had nothing to do with this party.
George / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Nothing.
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, I'm sorry I'm late.
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): It's the traffic.
Ellis Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): It doesn't matter, dear.
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): OK.
Ellis Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Don't tell me the notary didn't show.
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, everybody's here.
George / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): It's just your mother isn't.
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Mom?
Ellis Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): What do you people want from me?
George / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): We need you to sign the lawyer's papers.
Ellis Grey / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I have a cranial reconstruction in half an hour.
Ellis Grey / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I need to go.
Meredith / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): OK, Mom.
George / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): We're all here.
Izzie / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): We have a notary.
George / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I need you to focus.
Izzie / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): And I need you to sign these papers.
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Mom, look at me.
Ellis Grey / Mrs. Drake (PVM): It's an emergency surgery.
Ellis Grey / Mrs. Drake (PVM): I don't have time for this.
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): She can't sign anything now.
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): She's sundowning.
Izzie / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): We should have done this earlier in the day.
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I couldn't come earlier in the day.
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I have a job and a life, and I'm here now.
George / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Well, you're going to have to come back tomorrow when she's lucid.
Mrs. Drake / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You know, why did she put this off for so long?
Mrs. Drake / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): And why did you let her?
Mrs. Drake / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Doesn't it strike you as slightly irresponsible?
Mrs. Drake / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I mean, what the hell is wrong with you people?
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Get it to you first.
Alex / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Izzy, I'm gonna kill you.
Alex / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Jerry Frost (PVM): You could touch that, but I'd have to kill you.
Izzy / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): So if I could tell a thing?
Alex / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): It's been taken care of.
Izzy / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Okay.
Alex / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You don't need to concern yourself with it.
Izzy / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): So what's going to happen?
Alex / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): We're not going to talk about it anymore is what's going to happen.
Alex / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): We clear?
Alex / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You had too much alcohol to understand me.
Izzy / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You're very clear.
Alex / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Good.
Izzy / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You have any bourbon?
Mr. Frost / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You can't discharge a man in pain.
Mr. Frost / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Ow, you're hurting me.
Alex / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You're the one who's making it more difficult.
Alex / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Stop resisting.
Mr. Frost / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Jerry Frost (PVM): Just give me the edidemarol.
Mr. Frost / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Come on.
Alex / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Mr. Frost, you have to.
Mr. Frost / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Jerry Frost (PVM): I'm not leaving.
Mr. Frost / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Jerry Frost (PVM): No, no, no.
Mr. Frost / Jerry Frost (PVM): Don't go.
Mr. Frost / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Jerry Frost (PVM): Wait, wait, wait.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Stop.
Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Stop.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Stop.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Jerry.
Alex Karev / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Jerry.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Concussion?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): He's blown his left pupil.
Alex Karev / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Paige Shepherd.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): We gotta get him down to CT.
Alex Karev / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): That was one hard fall.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): What do you see?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Subdural bleed.
Alex Karev / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): With midline shift.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): We have to evacuate this now.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Anywhere else you have to be, Dr. Stevens, or are you in?
Dr. Izzie Stevens: Brain surgery?
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Mm-hmm.
Dr. Izzie Stevens: Are you kidding me?
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): That's what I thought.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Sturman OR Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Rosemary, heaven restores you in life.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): You're coming with me.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Here you go.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Where is Izzy?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): She didn't clear it with you.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): This was supposed to be a meet the boyfriend, get together little thingy.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Izzy has a lot of friends.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Excuse me.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Izzy doesn't know this many people!
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I told her to clear it with you!
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I can't handle this!
Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You want me to kick everyone out?
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm gonna kick everyone out!
Izzie / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Baby, you made it!
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Screw it.
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Hold this.
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): And give me this.
Meredith / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): George!
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Georgie, come here!
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Come on, Georgie!
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): George, come here!
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Come on!
Meredith / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Jerry Frost (PVM): See it?
Hank / Jerry Frost (PVM): Yeah, it's hard to miss.
Meredith / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): A little more than he bargained for.
Hank / Jerry Frost (PVM): Maybe he's lucky.
Meredith / Jerry Frost (PVM): Maybe this is his way out of the hole.
Hank / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): The hole?
Meredith / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Jerry Frost (PVM): Interesting expression.
Hank / Jerry Frost (PVM): My father was into smack pretty heavy.
Hank / Jerry Frost (PVM): He was a musician.
Hank / Jerry Frost (PVM): He was tolerated in his line of work.
Hank / Jerry Frost (PVM): Not good for the family at home.
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Why do we want to be surgeons anyway?
Meredith / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Surgery's a very serious business.
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Full house.
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Right on flash.
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Get naked.
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Baby boy.
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Sexy.
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Surgery's stupid.
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You're sexy.
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): It's stupid.
Hank / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): It's stupid.
Hank / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Give me that.
Intern / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You're drunk.
Hank / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm not driving.
Izzie / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm not on call.
Izzie / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm in my own house.
Izzie / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): My life is crap.
Izzie / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): And it's my party, and I'll get drunk if I want to.
Intern / Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Is, um, is he Stevens?
Intern / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, you must be Hank.
Intern / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): He's very large and hockey-like.
Intern / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): No, Izzy's not here right now.
Hank / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Okay.
Intern / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Jerry Frost (PVM): You and Izzy will give birth to very tall blonde girls.
Intern / Jerry Frost (PVM): Kind of like Barbies.
Hank / Jerry Frost (PVM): Izzy said she was gonna be at home.
Hank / Jerry Frost (PVM): She didn't say there was gonna be a party.
Intern / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Which pisses both of us off.
Intern / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Would you like some tequila?
Intern / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): It helps.
Hank / Jerry Frost (PVM): When do you think she's gonna get here?
Intern / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Jerry Frost (PVM): Don't know.
Intern / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): But we're low on ice, Hank.
Hank / Jerry Frost (PVM): I'm serious.
Intern / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Jerry Frost (PVM): So am I.
Intern / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): We're interns, Hank.
Intern / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): The hospital owns us.
Intern / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): It's what we do.
Hank / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Bye.
Intern / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Nice to meet you.
Intern / Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Can you guys see him through recovery?
Alex Karev / Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Yeah, I'll take it.
George O'Malley / Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): No, I can do it.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Alex Karev OR Jerry Frost OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): It's OK, Seamans.
Alex Karev / Dr. Alex Karev OR Jerry Frost (PVM): No, he's my patient now, too.
George O'Malley / Dr. Alex Karev OR Jerry Frost (PVM): No, I got it.
Izzie Stevens / Jerry Frost (PVM): See your hockey player.
Alex Karev / Jerry Frost (PVM): I'm serious.
George O'Malley / Jerry Frost (PVM): Yeah, OK.
Izzie Stevens / Jerry Frost (PVM): I guess.
Izzie Stevens / Jerry Frost (PVM): Thanks, Alex.
Dr. Alex Karev: No problem.
Derek Shepherd / Mrs. Drake (PVM): Hey.
Meredith Grey / Mrs. Drake (PVM): Hey.
Derek Shepherd / Mrs. Drake (PVM): What are you doing here?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Mrs. Drake (PVM): I'm sorry I didn't have a chance to call.
Meredith Grey / Mrs. Drake (PVM): My patient needed brain surgery.
Meredith Grey / Mrs. Drake (PVM): Like we were inside his brain.
Meredith Grey / Mrs. Drake (PVM): How cool is that?
Hank / Mrs. Drake (PVM): Oh, my God.
Hank / Jerry Frost OR Mrs. Drake (PVM): There's a party at your house.
Meredith Grey / Mrs. Drake (PVM): Yeah, did you get a chance to hang out?
Meredith Grey / Mrs. Drake (PVM): Why don't you meet some of the people I work with?
Hank / Mr. Sturman (PVM): I don't care about the people you work with.
Hank / Mr. Sturman (PVM): I just want to see you.
Meredith Grey / Mrs. Drake (PVM): Hm.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Sturman OR Mrs. Drake OR Mr. Sturman (PVM): Well, you didn't mind meeting the people I worked with when they were models.
Hank / Mr. Sturman (PVM): Yeah, well, when they were models, you actually showed up to your own parties.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Yeah.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): This is my life now, Hank.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I work 100-hour weeks.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I can't always show up to my own parties on time, and my patients have to come first.
Hank / Jerry Frost OR Mrs. Drake (PVM): Yeah, I just flew across the entire country, and there's a hundred people at your house.
Meredith / Jerry Frost OR Mrs. Drake (PVM): Yeah, a hundred people will understand what I do all day.
Meredith / Mrs. Drake (PVM): I shouldn't have to apologize for that.
Cristina / Jerry Frost OR Mr. Sturman (PVM): No, you shouldn't.
Meredith / Jerry Frost OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Look, let's just go by the party for a little while.
Meredith / Mr. Sturman OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): You'll really like everyone once you get a chance to know them.
Hank / Mr. Sturman OR Mr. Sturman (PVM): Let's just go.
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Mr. Sturman (PVM): Hank, come on.
Hank / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I'll call you.
Unknown (Song Lyric) / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): In a place I dream about where the sun never goes out and the sky is deep and blue, won't you take me there with you?
Unknown (Song Lyric) / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Shade our skin like the sun's shining
Cristina / Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): You know, in some states you get arrested for that.
Derek / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): So you blew me off for a bottle of tequila.
Meredith / Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Tequila's no good for you.
Derek / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Doesn't call, doesn't write.
Meredith / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): It's not nearly as much fun to wake up to.
Meredith / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Take me for a ride, Derek.
Derek / Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): You know, it sounds like the party's winding down.
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Yeah.
Derek / Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Listen to me.
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): What?
Derek / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You should probably sneak inside, though.
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): We did enough sneaking for the night.
Derek / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): It was good sneaking, but enough sneaking.
Meredith / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Yeah, I say we're pretty good sneakers.
Cristina / Jerry Frost (PVM): You mind moving this tail wagon?
Cristina / Jerry Frost (PVM): You're blocking me in.
Izzie / Mr. Patterson OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Apparently not good enough.
Cristina / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): When's your meeting with the chief?
Meredith / Mrs. Drake (PVM): In an hour.
Izzie / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Holy mother of destruction.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You missed Dr. Palooza.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Apparently, you didn't.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I should probably never speak to you again.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Mrs. Drake (PVM): I'm so sorry, Meredith.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Mrs. Drake (PVM): I had no idea it was going to get so.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): It's OK.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Really, I don't care.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): What would I be doing anyway?
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Preparing for your career-altering meeting.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Sorry.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): That heart wall shouldn't have torn.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Anything in the patient's history?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Husband said she was in the best shape of her life.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): She lost 100 pounds last year.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): 100 pounds in a year?
Dr. Burke / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): How's her muscle mass?
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Do you even know whose that was?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I'm hoping it was yours.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): No.
Chief Webber / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): What do you think?
Alex Karev / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): 50 says Meredith gets tossed out on her ass, and Burke walks away clean.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Please be nice to her.
Dr. Meredith Grey: So I have done a lot of research on this, and Dr. Burke has been kind enough to help me.
Dr. Meredith Grey: And I understand my responsibility and what I've done wrong here.
Dr. Meredith Grey: However, I do think the patient's history is significant in this case.
Dr. Meredith Grey: She still weighs 200 pounds, which is why no one even noticed it.
Dr. Meredith Grey: But with that kind of a weight drop, it doesn't matter how much you weigh.
Dr. Meredith Grey: Technically, you're anorexic.
Dr. Meredith Grey: So along with all that fat, she was losing muscle, heart muscle.
Dr. Meredith Grey: That certainly could be the reason for a small poke to become a large tear.
Chief Webber / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): That still doesn't change the fact, though.
Hospital Administrator / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): The small poke wasn't reported by Dr. Gray at the time of the occurrence.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): And if I could change that?
Hospital Administrator / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): And you can't.
Hospital Administrator / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): You've left yourself and the hospital open to a tremendous amount of liability.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Oh, no, no.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Not if the patient's weight loss caused the problem.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm sorry.
Hospital Administrator / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): I have no choice here other than to rectify.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): I've spoken to the husband.
Hospital Administrator / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): And I believe that as long as his wife remains stable, I can't take your beliefs to the bank, Dr. Burke.
Hospital Administrator / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Mr. Patterson (PVM): Dr. Gray made a huge error.
Dr. Burke / Mr. Patterson (PVM): And she reported it.
Hospital Administrator / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Too late.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): And in front of the patient's husband.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Patterson (PVM): But she reported it.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Patterson (PVM): She spoke up.
Dr. Preston Burke: Five years ago, as a CT fellow, I had a nagging feeling that I didn't check the body cavity of a lung patient closely enough before I closed.
Dr. Preston Burke: The patient seemed fine post-op, and I was in a hurry.
Dr. Preston Burke: And yesterday, you and Dr. Bailey pulled a towel out from under that patient's lung.
Dr. Preston Burke: Why didn't I report it at an appropriate time?
Dr. Preston Burke: Maybe because I was afraid that I would be called into a meeting where some hospital lawyer's fear of liability could end my career.
Dr. Preston Burke: Even great doctors make mistakes.
Dr. Preston Burke: And when we do, we've got to have a chance to be able to speak up without fear of retribution.
Dr. Preston Burke: Or everyone suffers.
Dr. Preston Burke: Dr. Gray spoke up.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Responsibility.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): It really does suck.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Meredith, you OK?
Dr. Meredith Grey: Yeah, one month probation.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Good.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): That's good.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Yeah.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Burke saved my ass in there.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Don't you all have something better to do?
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Come on, people, move.
Cristina Yang / Jerry Frost (PVM): He was always going to tell them about the towel.
Cristina Yang / Jerry Frost (PVM): Just wanted to wait for the right time.
Cristina Yang / Jerry Frost (PVM): Information is power.
Dr. Meredith Grey: Unfortunately, once you get past the age of braces and training bras, responsibility doesn't go away.
Rehab Counselor / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Jerry, this is Sloan.
Rehab Counselor / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): She's here to talk to you, if you want, about options for rehab.
Dr. Meredith Grey: It can't be avoided.
Dr. Meredith Grey: Mrs. Drake, I cannot begin to tell you how truly sorry I am.
Dr. Meredith Grey: Either someone makes us face it, or we suffer the consequences.
Nurse / Mr. Sturman (PVM): Easy.
Mr. Sturman: I did it.
Mr. Sturman: I pooped.
Nurse / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): All right.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Jerry Frost (PVM): Missed your party?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Life as a surgeon.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): And loving every minute of it.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You watch TV, and pass me the phone.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I need a conversation.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You're feeling down, just like this town.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): And your eyes say, oh.
Dr. Meredith Grey: And still, adulthood has its perks.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Thanks for the coffee.
Dr. Meredith Grey: The kind who'd take her clothes off and sit in a room full of frozen faces.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Sturman (PVM): I heard she went to find God in the Indian subcontinent.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Mr. Sturman (PVM): It's mad she had to go so far.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I mean the shoes, the sex, the no parents anywhere telling you what to do.
Dr. Meredith Grey: That's pretty damn good.