My mother used to
say this about residency:
It takes a year to
learn how to cut.
It takes a lifetime
to learn not to.
I'm up. I'm here.
What's going on?
Jackson's BP, it's a little down
from yesterday. No big deal.
But if we make a
few calls, get pushy,
we could get him bumped a
few spots up on the transplant list.
Dr. Bailey, you paged me 911.
At 2:30 in the morning. To chat?
- You like to chat. You're chatty.
- Not at 2:30 in the morning!
Look, he's young, he's
near the top of the list.
UNOS will find him organs when
they find him organs, and God knows,
staying up all night chatting
about it is not gonna help.
Now, I'm going to get some
sleep. I suggest you do the same.
He's running out of time.
They always are.
Welcome to Peds.
Of all of the tools
on a surgical tray,
sound judgment is the
trickiest one to master.
And without it,
we're all just toddlers
running around with ten blades.
Ohhh. I asked them not to wake you.
"Whatever it is can wait till morning.
- Dr. Shepherd needs his sleep."
- Your latest head CT shows
the brain contusions expanding.
We need to get you into OR right away.
This... this brain
thing, it could kill me?
If we don't treat it, yes.
- You find that funny.
- I'm sorry, it's just
they're gonna
execute me in five days.
Five days.
Might as well take my chances
with this brain thing, right?
- Mr. Dunn...
- You've got to admit,
it's a nice way to go,
plenty of attractive females.
All the Jell-o I could want.
Have you tried the strawberry?
- It'll change your life.
- You're refusing surgery?
Either way, I'm going
to die, Dr. Shepherd.
Might as well do
it on your watch.
Why do you have to
live in Meredith's attic?
How am I supposed to sneak
out with that frat party going?
- Don't you kids ever sleep?
- They're cleaning the house
for Dr. Shepherd's mother.
Mrs. Shepherd's coming?
- To Seattle?
- So?
That woman practically raised
me, taught me right from wrong.
If she found out that I was...
with you, that we were...
You're Meredith Grey's
little sister, forbidden fruit.
You are 25. You're a fetus.
Twenty-four. I
skipped third grade.
I feel dirty.
Ten bucks says she tanks
in the first five minutes.
I have faith in Death.
She's holding that bottle
of tequila like it's a life vest.
- Don't listen to them. She'll love you.
- No. Mothers don't love me.
Mothers like bright and
bubbly and happy and...
- Izzie. Mothers love Izzie.
- They do.
- Mothers do love Izzie.
- My mother would've loved you.
Uh, I stashed all the tequila, took
the condoms out of the cookie jar.
I replaced all your trashy magazines
with issues of Annals of Surgery.
- OK?
- OK.
Does it smell musty in here?
My mom's house smells
like peppermint. It's homey.
- My house isn't homey?
- I feel at home.
- This place is a palace.
- Why isn't my house homey?
- It's just a feeling!
- Izzie can't fix a feeling!
She's freaking out. Tell
her something I can fix.
Rebecca peed on
that couch cushion.
I've been sleeping
there for weeks.
Thanks, Alex.
You're a good friend.
You're welcome. Keep drinking.
- Mark?
- Hey, there you are.
- Wanna drink?
- It's 4:00 am.
You're right. I
should've called first.
Hey, I hear your mom's
coming into town. Good times.
You'll be fine.
Just keep the talking to a
minimum. Short nuggets of Meredith.
That's all anyone really needs.
If you get stuck, just smile.
You have a really great smile.
That's just scary.
Mer? Are you sure you want
to wear your hair like that?
You're wearing an
alarmingly high ponytail.
Your mother is coming.
Mr. Dunn, the swelling in
your brain is increasing rapidly.
- The longer we wait,
the worse it gets.
- Excellent.
- Go, team.
- I suggest
you reconsider surgery.
Have you seen the inside of
a maximum-security prison?
Believe me, if you have to
die, this is the place to do it.
In good company.
You two vigilantly monitor
Mr. Dunn's elevating ICP's,
you will do hourly exams. When
he goes unconscious, which he will,
- we'll rush him to surgery.
- You can't do that. Can he do that?
When you're unconscious and
can no longer make decisions,
a two-doctor consent
is needed to treat you.
I'm gonna be dead as a
doornail in five days! Dr. Grey...
- We're done.
- Would you fix
a broken television
- before you throw it out?
- He's got a point.
Trying to cheat the system.
We're not gonna let him do it.
- What's the problem?
- I have an infection
- from a little
surgery I had done.
- In Hong Kong.
My crazy-ass brother got crazy-ass
elective surgery in Hong Kong.
- Who does that?
- Short people.
Desperate short people!
I had my legs lengthened. I couldn't
find a surgeon who would do it here.
Look, it's barbaric.
They broke his legs,
and they hooked him up to
some medieval torture device.
Yeah, that's to pull the bones
apart. That's the lengthening process.
It's controversial. I
don't perform it myself.
Can I take a look?
They said it'd give
me two whole inches.
- Any word from UNOS?
- Not yet.
Dr. Karev is in constant
contact with them.
How much longer will we wait?
Are livers and intestines hard to find?
Jackson's blood is O positive,
shouldn't be difficult to match.
He's had blood transfusions,
which means there could be
extra antibodies that are hard to
match, so we need patience, Melinda.
In the meantime, I need to run some
tests on Jackson to check electrolytes.
We're gonna do everything we
can to help your son, Mrs. Prescott.
All of us.
- You. You're squirrelly.
- I'm sorry?
I don't trust you. I don't
trust you in this hospital,
and I don't trust you with
my patient of three years
who is extremely important.
- I...
- If you want to stay
on this case,
you will stay out of my way,
you will do what I tell you,
and if you have something
to say to or about my patient,
you will raise your hand
and wait to be called on.
You've got to be kidding me.
- Yes?
- This is a joke, right?
Do I look like I'm laughing?
- You're upset.
- I don't get upset
with patients.
You're mad at me for killing
those women. I get that.
Would you feel differently if
you knew I was beaten as a child?
Every day. It's how
I learned to read.
I used to hide under the sink
and sound out the letters
on the detergent box.
- Is that true?
- Did it make you feel better?
Whatever helps you
sleep at night, Dr. Grey.
Cool.
Did you do something bad?
Traffic violation.
What's wrong with you, kid?
I need a new liver
and a new intestine.
Yeah? You want mine?
Are you in the north terminal?
That's where she's supposed to be.
No. Don't go
anywhere, just wait.
I found her. There's a town
car waiting at the airport.
I don't need a fancy car, I hopped
on the bus. Saved you money.
So this cruise... you happened
to have a layover in Seattle?
I've always wanted to
check out the Space Needle.
I understand you can see
Mt. Rainier from the top.
- Anything else?
- Are you gonna take me or not?
I got back-to-back surgeries.
Got to give me notice.
Yeah, I gave birth to five
doctors. I know the drill.
I can wait, maybe meet your
colleagues. Is that Mark Sloan?
- Mark Sloan!
- Mrs. Shepherd. You look great.
Oh, damn. We'll catch up later?
Perfect timing.
- Mom, this is Meredith.
- Meredith! Finally.
- Hi.
- My son's been acting
like a dog
with his favorite bone, hiding
you. I hope you're free for lunch.
I can't wait to dive right in
and find out all about you.
Mer looks weird. Does
she look weird to you?
- Like she's gonna
pee her pants.
- Crap. I made her hydrate.
Meeting the family always
blows. I'd never make you do that.
Me, either. One of the many
perks of dating a dead guy.
- Who's that lady
touching Meredith?
- Derek's mom.
- Huh. That's why
she looks so weird.
- She does not look weird.
I've got it under control.
Mer is doing... great.
Looks like she's gonna pee.
Dr. Yang, you mind checking
in on some of my post-ops?
ER's swamped with traumas.
Also, would you like to go on a date?
- I'm sorry?
- A date.
You said not to play hot
and cold with you, so...
I'll pick you up around eight.
And make sure Mr. Kenner
in room 2212 gets that enema.
He's been holding
on to it for days.
OK.
'Cause that wasn't weird.
Another perk to dating a
dead guy: no awkward dates.
Two to one. But who's counting.
Why can't I have that nice
man's organs? He offered.
You know how in school there
are rules you have to follow?
Same goes for here. We
have to follow the rules,
or else we get in big trouble.
And what that man offered
you is definitely against the rules.
She's fighting with the
insurance people again.
You're not supposed to
worry about stuff like that.
Tell her something good today.
Even if nothing good
happens. She needs good news.
I've got a body full of
high-quality parts here.
Three-day liquidation sale.
Everything must go.
Even if we could do it, you
have to be a match for him.
Which means we have to
cross match your blood with his.
Good thing we're
both in a hospital then.
Let... let me save
a life before I go.
It's the least I can do.
So you really expect me to
believe you want to do this for a kid?
Whatever helps you
sleep at night, Dr. Grey.
The infection's made its
way deep into the bone.
We're gonna take the rods out.
Clean out the
infected skin and bone.
I won't get my two inches?
All that pain, for nothing?
Mr. Ruben, at this point, you're
lucky to keep your legs at all.
That's easy for you to say.
What are you, 5'10, 5'11?
- Leave the doctors alone.
- Shut up, Gary.
You are over six feet tall!
Do you have any
idea what it's like
to have everybody you know
literally look down on you?
Or how humiliating it is to have
to ask for help from a teenager
at the grocery store because
you can't reach the top shelf?
I've gone on two dates
in the last six months
with women I met over the Internet.
No one wants to see me again.
- No one wants
to date the short guy.
- Chuck...
I wanted those two inches,
Gary. I wanted them so bad.
It's two inches. What's the
difference between 5'3 " and 5'5"?
5'5" you can say out loud.
OK. I made a list of the best
pediatric GI's in the country.
We can get one of these guys to
come do a TIPS procedure on him.
On a kid who needs a new liver?
Like putting a Band-Aid
on a bullet wound.
- You have a better idea?
- I do.
Wait for UNOS. Trusting the
process. Why can't you do that?
Because I'm tired of waiting
while this kid gets worse.
Jackson's tired, his mother is.
The only one who's happy to sit
and twiddle her thumbs is you!
I've been patient with
you, I've been nice,
but I am really over you constantly
telling me how to do my job.
- Somebody's got to...
- I have 20 other kids...
Shut up!
Respectfully.
Respectfully, shut up.
Because we got organs.
I wish you could get organs delivered
instead of having to go pick them up.
I hate flying. I always feel much closer
to death on a plane than in the OR.
- Don't you?
- I do now.
I met Izzie the other day.
She's very pretty.
So do you think she's the one?
I... I don't know.
Well, we're at that age, right?
Marriage, babies.
- That the plan?
- I don't know!
I'm sorry, I don't
make plans, OK?
If there's a future, great. If not,
I'll get over it. I always do. OK?
OK.
I think it's nice. Your date.
You and the pig murderer
make a good couple.
- OK.
- What are you gonna do?
- What are you gonna talk about?
- You care?
Yeah, why do you care?
You only get to do a first
date once. It should be fun
and sexy and...
Ask really good questions.
Ask him why he first decided
he wanted to save lives.
- Ask him what
his best surgery was.
- I know how to go on a date.
Why is Meredith
eating pot roast?
It's a show lunch for the mommy.
She's freaking out. That
ponytail is gonna blow.
Derek tells me you
grew up here in Seattle.
- Are your parents...?
- Dead.
Meredith's mother
died last year.
Oh.
I'm so sorry. And your father?
Oh. You know,
I should go check
on the patient.
Who's the serial killer...
who's here.
Not killing people.
So that's good.
- I should go.
- Yeah.
OK.
Family isn't her
favorite topic, OK?
- She's had a rough time of it.
- I didn't say a word.
I know what you're thinking.
I was thinking... it
must be awful for you.
Treating a murderer.
Dad died a long
time ago. I'm fine.
- What are you doing?
- Sleep with me,
you lunch with me.
- New rule.
- You let interns sit with you?
- That's so cool.
- Wanna go halfsies
on that cookie?
What are you
gonna trade me for it?
You guys, they have Tater Tots!
I have to go.
- Mark?
- Mrs. Shepherd.
- You've been avoiding me.
- What? No.
You have the same look on your
face as you did when you were ten
and put Derek's favorite
frog in the microwave.
- I never pressed start.
- What's going on?
I'm sleeping with her.
- Oh, Mark, not again! How could you?
- No... No.
Not Meredith. God, no.
Meredith's little sister.
Which one is she?
The... one with the juice box.
- Are my new organs here yet?
- Not yet.
But we're gonna get
you all prepped now
so we can put them in
as soon as they get here.
When you wake up, you'll be a
brand-new boy with brand-new parts.
I can't believe this is it.
The thought of us getting to live
our lives outside this hospital...
Don't get me wrong,
I love our chats.
But it'll be nice
not to see my face.
So freaking nice!
- It's just a kid.
- Yep. Let's go get his organs.
Am I hallucinating or is
that a really high ponytail?
You're not hallucinating.
But once your brain starts to
herniate, I can't promise anything.
So I'm really circling
the drain here?
You should just take my organs
right now. Help that poor kid.
They found him organs.
They're flying them over right now.
He's going to be fine.
Did you know that
they let you choose?
Hanging or lethal. You
get to pick your poison.
Literally.
Which one would you choose?
Medically speaking,
which one's...
better?
Well, with hanging,
your neck breaks, which
severs your spinal cord,
which causes blood pressure to
drop, and you lose consciousness.
You don't actually
die for several minutes.
And with lethal injection,
they inject an anesthetic
first which puts you to sleep,
and then a paralytic which
stops your diaphragm and lungs.
And then potassium,
which stops your heart.
Was... was I a match?
Yes, you were.
Can I help you with something?
Were you looking for Dr. Shep...?
- Are you a good girl?
- I... What?
A good girl. I don't mean perfect,
I mean... relatively speaking.
- Are you?
- Yes.
How many sexual partners
have you had? I won't judge.
Um, six. No, s-seven.
Kinda six, kinda seven.
- Criminal record?
- Speeding ticket.
- How fast?
- Twelve miles over.
- That's fast.
- It isn't too... Way too fast.
But it was downhill. I
was coasting, ma'am.
I don't suppose
you can tell me...
where the gift shop is?
First floor, east wing.
- It's like pudding in here.
- It's why I don't do
this procedure.
You're living with broken legs for
months, you're in excruciating pain.
All for a few inches.
Pain and agony for a
little bit of pleasure. I get it.
If it's that bad, why
don't you just stop sleep...
- doing what you're doing?
- It doesn't feel bad
when I'm...
doing it. It's good. It's great.
And maybe if you weren't so scared
of getting burned you'd feel the same.
I used to walk tall around here.
I used to walk tall.
Then came George.
He took off at least an inch.
And Erica went and left me.
That shaved off a few more.
I got shorter.
All that humiliation makes you shorter.
So, yeah, I am scared of getting hurt.
One more personal disaster right
now would cut me off at the knees.
So Valentine's Day.
Personally, I think you
can't go wrong with jewelry.
- I could recommend some places.
- What is wrong with you?
- What?
- We just took
a liver and intestine
from a little kid.
A dead little kid.
And you don't even care.
You're talking about rainbows
and relationships and crap.
What the hell is wrong with you?
You don't think I know they
just pulled the plug on a kid?
You don't think I get that?
You don't think I know about the tiny,
tiny coffin they're gonna stick him in?
I know about the tiny coffins.
I see them all the
time. In my sleep.
So if you don't mind,
I'm gonna keep talking
relationships and
rainbows and crap,
and I'm gonna make
plans for tomorrow.
Because that's what you
do, Karev. You make plans.
You have to. You turn your back
on the tiny coffins and face forward.
To the next kid.
- How's our death-row guy?
- Pissing me off.
Blossoming brain
contusions, refusing surgery.
- Thinks he'll get
a stay of execution?
- No, he'd like to die here.
He wants to control
it. He wants to choose.
I went overboard buying
bears for your nieces.
- Mom, this is Major Owen Hunt.
- Major?
I was a Navy nurse for 25
years. Where were you stationed?
- In the thick of it. In Iraq.
- Welcome home.
- You must have stories.
- Not any worth telling, ma'am.
- I finished your post-ops.
- Thank you, Dr. Yang.
- What was
your best surgery ever?
- What?
Nothing. Uh, stupid.
- Finishing the vena cava.
- Anastomosis looks good.
All that's left is to
release the clamps.
You should do the honors,
Miranda. He's your patient.
Thank you, Dr. Robbins.
Call on me.
Call on me!
There's a spot on the duodenum.
What the hell is that?
- I don't feel good.
- ICP is critical. We can't wait.
- We have to get him
down to the OR.
- No. No.
- We have to get you to surgery.
- I'm not scared of dying.
I just don't want to do it strapped
down on a table like some animal.
Please... Please, Dr. Grey.
Let me go.
OK, start bagging him.
- Intubate, get him into the OR.
- Yeah, right here.
I need another doctor's
signature, consent to operate.
Meredith, sign.
Sign the form.
Meredith, sign the form!
Yang, you're scrubbing in.
He's clotting and clotting
and clotting. Is there a source?
This can't be happening.
Not to this little boy.
- This is not happening...
- These organs are dead.
They're making him sicker.
Keeping them in is doing harm.
- He will die if you
leave them in.
- He'll die if we take them out!
Pressure's dropping.
Try a portacaval shunt.
It'll bypass the liver.
- That's a temporary fix.
- Got any better ideas?
I don't see what choice we have.
How much time
to find new organs?
Twenty-four hours.
Get some more laps in here too.
We're going to put this piece of
skull in Mr. Dunn's abdomen. Why?
To allow the swelling
in the brain to resolve.
Circulation of abdomen preserves
the bone marrow in the skull piece.
- Very good.
- Thanks for
letting me scrub in.
I guess we finally see
eye to eye on something.
Are we ever gonna find
out why it clotted off?
Sometimes the body,
the pieces just break.
- I'm like that.
- Yeah? You dying for no reason?
My life is in pieces,
all of the time.
And they keep breaking, and as soon
as I fix one, another one goes down.
I'm not trying to piss you off.
I'm just trying to keep it together.
Piece by piece.
♪ The way to come back home ♪
♪ I tried to make a point ♪
♪ To sell the last
of what I own ♪
♪ Well I can feel your breeze ♪
♪ Begin to choke
my living soul ♪
♪ But I promise
that it's worth it ♪
That ponytail...
looks ridiculous.
♪ I tried to make the words
become a kingdom to your soul ♪
♪ No matter how I try, It's
just a lyric nothing more ♪
- She's a lovely girl.
- A lovely girl
who's off-limits.
Baloney. She isn't
the problem, you are.
You have very low expectations
for yourself, Mark Sloan.
Since you were a little boy.
And it's time to raise them.
She's 24.
You have the emotional maturity of
a horny 15 year old. You need young.
Mm.
We had to shave off a quarter inch
of leg bone in order to save the legs.
You mean I'm shorter?
I'm a quarter of
an inch shorter?
Quarter inch.
It's not a big deal.
Yeah. I'm under 5'3".
I am 5'2" and three quarters.
But maybe I can still just squeeze
over the height requirement
- at the amusement park.
- Do you know
why I never played
varsity basketball?
- You didn't make the team?
- No. I didn't try out
for the team.
I didn't want to make you feel
bad for being too short to play.
Even now, if I have a bad
day, I can't talk to my brother
because maybe you had
a bad day and you're short!
I couldn't even be depressed
about Lori leaving me
because you don't have a
girlfriend and you're short!
By the way, the reason
you don't have a girlfriend
isn't because you're
short. It's because all you do
is talk about being short!
No one knows how short
you are except for you, dude.
No one cares.
- I'm an ass, aren't I?
- Yeah.
And you're short.
Good night. Nice to meet you.
Major Hunt? How
have you been sleeping?
- I'm sorry?
- When I can't sleep,
I use Valerian root.
I know you doctors don't think
much of herbs, but I find it helps.
Have you been sleeping?
Since you came back?
I'm fine, ma'am.
I... sleep just fine.
Good night.
- How's your head feel,
Mr. Dunn?
- Why didn't you just let me go?
- You're not dying here.
- What are you so scared of?
- Losing control?
- ICP's stable. Continue neuro exams.
Keep an eye on his blood
pressure. I don't want it dropping.
Or maybe you know deep
down, you're no better than I am.
You decide who lives
and dies all the time.
For you, they call it
medicine, not a capital offense.
Nobody gets to choose. Not
me, not a patient in this hospital
and certainly not the
women you slaughtered.
So when I say you're not
gonna die in this hospital,
I mean there is no way in hell
I will let you die in this hospital.
You don't get off that easy.
I'm nothing like you.
Meredith.
I was just looking for Derek.
I thought you'd be with him.
You seem like a
very nice person.
You've been kind and
you've given me a chance.
It seems like you
want to like me.
So it's only fair
you should know...
the pink and the ponytail
and the smiling with the teeth?
I'm a fraud. It's fake.
I'm not the kind of girl mothers
like. I'm not happy and bubbly.
I'm dark and cloudy,
because I'm the type
of crazy person who...
feels bad for serial killers.
It was very nice to
meet you, Meredith.
♪ Let me take you
to my secret place ♪
♪ High above the earth ♪
What's wrong?
- I want to meet your mother.
- Iz.
I want to go on a date with you. I
want to eat dinner in a restaurant
and not look like a crazy
person talking to myself.
I want to walk down the street
with you and hold your hand.
I want to tell my friends
about you and I want...
I want...
- What?
- I want you alive.
♪ What would you do
to make things right? ♪
Are you breaking up
with me, Izzie Stevens?
I think I am.
- So you wanna get a drink?
- I would, but I have plans.
Right.
- Walk tall.
- What?
All you can do is be brave
enough to get out there.
You fought. You loved.
You lost.
Walk tall, Torres.
♪ Now you're in the
heart of a secret place ♪
You're late. Really late.
They closed the kitchen.
I didn't want you to
think I stood you up.
Are you drunk?
I haven't been on a date in five
years, since before I entered the military.
- I wanted to take the edge off.
- You're late and drunk?
I will make this up to you. I
promise. This is not what you deserve.
This is not what you deserve. I
will make this up to you. I promise.
Before you say anything
else, Dr. Goodtimes, shower.
You smell like a distillery.
No. Not here! I...
Your father always wanted
you to have this for the right girl.
Addy wasn't right, clearly.
You spent less than
an hour with Meredith.
- You barely even know her.
- I know enough.
I know it's easier to have compassion
for a good person than a murderer.
I know how angry
you still are about Dad.
Of course I'm angry.
Aren't you?
I still can't sleep on
his side of the bed,
the mattress is
wearing unevenly,
but no.
No, not angry. Not anymore.
Sweetheart...
- You see things
in black and white.
- Mm.
Meredith doesn't.
You need a spoonful of that.
You need her.
- She's the one.
- Yeah.
Yang! Yang!
- I thought of my best surgery.
- You're wearing shoes in my
shower.
First blast injury in the
field. Body was mangled.
Homemade explosive device, wires
embedded five inches in the abdomen.
Arms and legs hanging on by threads
of skin. Never seen anything like it.
Not in a textbook, not in residency.
Incredible. Body full of holes.
Trauma surgeon's dream. I
put tourniquets on where I could,
started tying off arteries with my bare
hands, but bleeding was everywhere:
stomach, chest...
Best pressure I could
think of was my own body.
I laid there for two hours
on top of him, not moving,
trying to keep that dam from
bursting with my hands, knees, elbows.
Body... full of holes,
and... he never bled out.
I wouldn't let him.
He made it to the hospital, home.
A month later, he sent me a letter
thanking me for saving his
life. Then he shot himself.
That was my best surgery.
♪ He will surely die ♪
And my worst.
♪ And his body will break ♪
We're human.
We make mistakes.
♪ Into the night ♪
We misestimate.
♪ Where the spirits scream ♪
We call it wrong.
♪ He will leave this world
and become a dream ♪
♪ Oh, my father was a sailor ♪
But when a surgeon
makes a bad judgment call,
it's not as simple.
So I checked and we have a
few vacation days coming up.
Maybe we could take a road
trip, stop in Iowa, see some corn.
- Doesn't your mom live in Iowa?
- Yeah.
I think she'd like to meet you.
Or not. Bad idea. Forget it.
There's a bottle of tequila in the
laundry room that has our name on it.
Don't move.
Alex...
We gotta talk.
♪ I will leave this world
and become a dream ♪
People get hurt.
They bleed.
I'm so sorry, I just heard.
What happens now?
Now, we wait for a miracle.
So we struggle
over every stitch,
we agonize...
over every suture.
During surgery, Dr. Shepherd
removed a piece of your skull.
Which means your brain is
only covered by dura mater.
It's virtually exposed. If somehow
that area were to be damaged,
it would cause intracranial bleeding,
which could cause your brain to swell
worse than it did today, which
would result in brain death.
So, as your doctor, I need you to
be very careful not to damage it.
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
Dr. Grey?
Are you doing
this for the kid...
or for me?
Because the snap judgments,
the ones that come to us quickly
and easily, without hesitation...
Whatever helps
you sleep at night.
They're the ones
that haunt us forever.