- Previously on Grey's
Anatomy: - I'm in love with you.
I hope you're in
love with me too.
I was named chief resident.
I failed my intern exam.
- You can start
from the very beginning.
- Repeat my internship?
- I met a woman last night.
- Hi.
- You met a woman
last night?
- I'm Lexie Grey.
- He's gone.
- I can't leave you.
- But you're
constantly leaving me.
- It's over. So over.
In the practice of medicine,
change is inevitable.
New surgical techniques are
created, procedures are updated,
levels of expertise increase.
Innovation is everything.
Nothing remains
the same for long.
We either adapt to change...
or we get left behind.
♪ I can make it on time
if I jump out of bed ♪
♪ If I skip to wear clothes
and get running instead ♪
♪ I can make it in time ♪
I have five rules.
Memorize them.
Number one: Don't suck up. I
hate you. That's not gonna change.
Trauma protocols, lists,
pagers. Nurses page you.
You answer every page at a
run. A run. That's rule number two.
You're supposed to follow me.
Your first shift starts
now and lasts 36 hours.
You're grunts, nobodies, the
bottom of the surgical food chain.
Run labs, write orders and work
every second night until you drop.
And you don't complain.
On-call room. Sleep when
you can, where you can.
But not with anybody. Not
attendings. Especially not attendings.
Sleeping with attendings,
not a good idea. Where was I?
Um... rule number three.
If you're sleeping, do not wake
you unless a patient's actually dying.
Patient better not be
dead when I get there
because not only
will you have killed,
you will have woken
me for no reason.
Are we clear?
- Yes?
- That was four rules. You said five.
Rule number five:
When I move, you move.
Go!
- I hate them.
- You don't. You hate you.
That was hideous.
I feel like a fraud.
I rocked it. I think
I'm the new Nazi.
- You are not the new Nazi.
- Meredith, I need
to talk to you.
- George. Hi.
- Hey.
- How was your vacation?
- Fine. Meredith, could we...?
Because mine was... I didn't do
much. Hung out alone. For 17 days.
Which is the last
time that I saw you.
The day of Cristina's
wedding, which was, well...
Mer and Cristina went on
her honeymoon without me.
Girl-on-girl honeymoon.
Alex took a road trip
to see Ava without me.
I did not go to see Ava.
Rebecca. I didn't see
her. I drove in that direction.
Why is everyone so tingly and hurt?
I'm the one who was left at the altar.
I'm fine, by the way.
I honeymooned in
Hawaii and I snorkeled.
- What did you do, George?
- Meredith, I need
to talk to you.
Hey! You want to know... Hey, um,
this is for residents only. No interns.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, get out of here!
- Babies.
- Go away.
- 007s in training.
- Seriously.
I guess I should be going too.
No! We didn't mean you.
- I'm an intern!
- What did you want?
Is this how it's going to
be? Bambi has to deal.
- At least he came back.
- Cut him slack.
He failed his exam and
got left back in kindergarten.
He wouldn't even look at me.
Have you seen Burke?
No. Have you seen Derek?
- No.
- Wait. You haven't seen either
- since the wedding?
- Nope.
- And you're all fine?
- Yep.
You're either incredibly
healthy or completely messed up.
Your interns are
back from holiday.
They're not my interns.
They're residents. I'm free.
Right. Well, here, nurse. The
point is, Dr. Yang? The Burke thing?
She doesn't know.
I'm supposed to tell her.
Burke asked me to tell her.
- Any thoughts?
- Honesty
always works best.
That's true. You want to get
together for a drink after work?
- Why?
- Well, I don't know.
Might be a good idea...
You don't have
anybody to talk to.
- No, I have people to talk to.
- Addison is gone. Burke isn't around.
You and Grey aren't smelling
each other in the elevators.
- I have people
to talk to.
- Who?
I have...
Chief! I have the
chief to talk to.
- Get together for a drink?
- I don't drink.
- Bailey, we need to talk.
- Traumas coming in.
- Avoiding me. We need to talk.
- About choosing Torres to be
your chief resident? Respectfully,
no. We're not going to talk.
- Somebody mention
a drink? I'm in.
- Nobody.
- You mentioned a drink.
- I did not.
All right, people. We've got
three MVC's rolling in back to back
from a multi-car pile up. We need every
trauma room open and everyone suited up.
- Is there anything
I should do, sir?
- Save lives.
No. I mean, as, uh, chief
resident. Anything in particular?
Make sure your residents run their
traumas. First day on their own...
Where are the residents
you've assigned to this ER?
Oh... Oh... I, uh...
I paged them. I
paged them. Bailey?
- What?
- I... I paged Grey, Yang,
Stevens and Karev,
but they're not here yet.
- When I page them,
they come running.
- Get it together, Torres.
Yes, sir. OK, you did not have
to say that in front of the chief.
You asked... boss.
- There's Derek.
- Is Burke with him?
- I don't see him.
- Where have you been?
- We have MVC's due any second.
- We're here, aren't we?
Just get ready, OK?
And monitor your interns.
One, Two, go get stat packs.
Three, Four, meet the ambulances.
- One and Two?
- I know. I can't
remember their names.
- I don't respond to a number.
- George, go wait
for the ambulance.
- The rest, come with me.
- Against the wall
and out of the
way unless I call.
OK. This is what's
called a trauma situation.
So there's gonna be lots of
activity and a lot of patients.
So if you guys have any
questions at all, just ask. OK?
I heard she killed a guy
and had to go on probation.
Great. We're stuck with a dud.
- Hey. You're
an intern. Again.
- Yeah.
- I won't tell anybody.
- That's OK. It doesn't matter.
Do you know which
one is Meredith Grey?
Yeah. I haven't told her you're
here yet. I was going to, but...
- So you know who I am.
- Yeah, I know who you are.
What's she like? I mean, is she
nice? Because my dad, he won't tell me.
- Is she...?
- Excuse me.
- Grey, don't let them
just stand here.
- Let's move, people.
Unrestrained driver, DOA at the scene.
Just need someone to pronounce him.
Crap. Dead guy. Why'd you
get me excited with sirens?
OK, who wants to see a dead guy?
Nancy Walters, 34 years
old, 35 weeks pregnant.
Complete upper arm amputation.
Pressure applied. Two
large-bore IVs started.
Did he say arm? My arm is gone?
Miss Walters, you're gonna
be OK. Grey? Check the wound.
I really need my arm.
- 45-year-old male, knee injury.
- That guy, the guy that's dead?
He hit a deer and then the lady
hit him and then I hit the lady.
Knee's blowing
up like a balloon.
Hey, I'm hungry. Can
I get something to eat?
OK, everybody get a good
look? Time of death, 8:22.
Not time of death.
This guy is not dead.
- He was dead!
- He's not dead now! Bag him!
We've got a guy who's
risen from the dead.
Get out of the way!
- Are you Meredith Grey?
- Yeah.
- I'm Lexie.
- Great. Move!
Lexie Grey. I'm...
I'm your sister.
That girl out there? The dopey
wide-eyed one? Apparently, we're related.
- You met Lexie?
- You knew.
You knew about it
and didn't tell me?
- I kind of had a lot going on.
- This is trauma room one.
As you can see,
it's... There's a trauma.
Do you need some help?
Tell me you need some help.
- It's a little crowded in here, Iz.
- - What do you got?
Nancy Walters.
Complete amputation.
Baby looks fine, but she's
having some contractions.
- Mind if I take a look?
- Clean cut.
You want to rub up against me,
you got to buy me a drink first.
Hang antibiotics
and put on a dressing.
There's a chance of a good
recovery here. Do we have an arm?
- They're looking for it.
- My baby has no father.
He's already down two arms,
so he really needs
me to have an arm.
Get me that arm.
OK, somebody set up for
traumatic effusion drainage.
And order him four of morphine.
She means one of you.
18-gauge needle, 20-cc syringe.
And the damn morphine.
Hey, morphine's cool, but
I'd kill for something to eat.
Healthy appetite after a trauma like
this? That's a very good sign, Joey.
- Need surgery?
- Here.
Depends on the X-rays.
The knee looks good. No surgery.
OK. This is Cristina... Dr. Yang.
This is Dr. Yang. She's working.
Yep. Saving lives
and taking names.
So I have these interns
and nothing to do.
And, uh, I think I'm a really bad
teacher and I think they hate me.
And now I'm a fraud, so any chance
you want to let me in on this? Please?
Izzie, this guy was dead
and now he's undead.
So that kind of makes him like a
zombie. And my personal zombie.
So, no, you can't get in on this.
Now go be a fraud somewhere else.
- I don't like you.
- Mmm...
Let's go, people.
- Excuse me.
- Where have you been?
- I've been waiting for these.
- I got... I met my sister.
For the first time ever which
got me, you know, weird.
So then I got lost on my way to X-ray
because I was all in my head, you know,
- about meeting Meredith.
- Meredith is your sister?
Meredith Grey. Lexie Grey.
We're half-sisters. So you know her?
- Oh, we need to page
Dr. Shepherd.
- Dr. Shepherd.
He's the neurosurgeon?
OK, somebody page Derek
Shepherd right freaking now!
Grey. Seattle Grace. Thank you.
Hi. How are you?
I have a patient with a severed arm
and no one seems to be able to find it.
- Have you seen it?
- Your severed arm?
No, I haven't. Meredith...?
Hey, I'm so sorry about before. I
was so nervous about meeting you.
Don't block the ER doors.
That was a good lesson.
- You're the girl
from the bar.
- Sorry?
The girl from the bar.
Oh, my God. Yeah.
- Oh, my God! Yeah!
- Yeah.
- Oh, my God. You work here.
- Yeah. I do.
The girl from the bar?
I'm the girl from the bar.
- She hates me. My sister hates me.
- Meredith is your sister?
- My half-sister.
- Oh.
Hey, you're Dr. Shepherd.
I'm supposed to be
finding you for a consult.
Hey! There you are. I
missed you this morning.
Didn't want to be late for my
second first day as an intern.
Maybe you can look at it like
this: You have one up on everyone.
You're gonna be, like,
the rock star intern.
That's how everyone's
gonna see me.
Or maybe they'll see
you as the Daddy intern.
What?
What did you just say?
I'm not pregnant. I just...
I might be pregnant.
Yeah, my boobs are
a little sore which...
I'm trying to cheer you
up, George. This is...
I mean, if I am knocked
up, that's a good thing, right?
Callie, I'm just a little
distracted. I'm having a bad day.
OK, you're having a bad month.
OK. Yeah, I'm
having a bad month.
Love you.
- Help! We need a doctor's help!
- Your inside voice.
We found an arm in the
road. Here, I bagged that.
That's my arm.
Dad! Dad! Tell them she's hurt!
Dad, come on! Tell
the doctor she's hurt!
Any way we can go
with the severed arm?
Is that your blood?
Are you hurt?
She's in our truck
and she's not moving!
Please! She's
bleeding really bad!
There's another crash victim!
We need gloves, IVs, gauze,
ab pads, trauma gowns.
Still want to baby-sit the arm?
Come on!
Michael!
No way.
Is she dead?
Michael, this is a hospital
and I'm a people doctor. I...
- Can you save her?
- Michael. Come on.
- I'm sorry, but she's...
- Roadkill.
She opened her eyes.
Look, she's still alive!
Oh, God, don't
look at me like that.
- Or like that.
- - Go back to the truck.
- Please. Please.
- OK. All right. All right.
I need a jumbo catheter,
a 16-gauge needle,
the biggest Ambu bag you can
find and something that shaves fur.
What's the matter with you people?
When I say move, you move. Move!
The back of his skull is disconnected
from his first cervical vertebra.
Internally
decapitated. Holy crap.
- 90 percent die in the field.
- The other ten?
I've never seen one.
Always a first time? I mean,
he came back from the dead.
Henry, I'm Dr. Shepherd. Back of your
skull is disconnected from your spine.
I'm gonna try and reconnect it in
surgery. Do you understand me?
Blink once for
yes, twice for no.
Good. I know it's
scary but I promise you
I'm going to do
everything I can.
Do you have family?
All right. We're gonna
contact them, OK?
Let's get him in a
halo. Contact his family.
Find out if he's an organ donor.
You. Finish the splint,
get him up on crutches.
Hey. How's Joey?
He's a hungry hippo
missing a kneecap.
Can't you assign
me something good?
- I don't switch out patients.
- It's not surgical.
- Waste of my skills.
- You're staying with Joey.
- Come on.
- No!
Fine. Then I'm going to Bailey.
You are a resident.
Go where I say!
- My arm is gone.
- We have the arm
and Dr. Sloan is checking right
now to see if we can reattach it.
- Is there someone
we can call?
- There's no...
No, I just... I just moved
here. I'm all by myself.
There's no one. I have no one.
Well, Dr. Sloan should
be here any minute.
I wanted a kid and...
I was sick of waiting
for the right guy so...
And my family...
In my family, you don't
go out and get pregnant.
Now I'm alone and
I'm having a baby
and I don't have a father for
the baby and I don't have an arm.
It's OK. Here's Dr. Sloan.
Nancy, I'm happy to report
that your arm is in good shape.
Dr. Grey here is going
to clean it up a little
and then I'm gonna put that
arm back where it belongs, OK?
OK.
OK. We got a 150-pound female
with lacerations on
the chest and haunches.
Short breaths. Recommendations?
Doctor? Michael's a big boy.
He doesn't need
make-believe medicine. Right?
It's not make-believe.
She can help.
Michael, enough. I apologize.
- We're wasting time.
- No kidding.
- Michael.
- Please don't let her die.
Michael. It is a deer.
We're gonna take her home
and skin her and freeze the meat.
- Why?
- Because that's
what you do.
You don't save
them, you eat them.
No, Dad. The
doctor can save her!
- No.
- You don't know that.
My son needs to learn to
grow up and face things.
You're right. I am
not helping him.
I'm helping Bambi.
So get me the Ambu bag
and saline. I'm starting an IV.
Thank you.
Still no sign of Burke.
You've got a severed arm.
- My arm. Mine. Get away from it.
- Maybe he's not on today.
- Maybe you should
just see him.
- Oh, no, no.
If I never see
him, I won't care.
I've seen Derek and
Derek has seen me.
- And?
- Awkward. Plus he seems
to know Lexie.
- And?
- More awkward.
Your intern is my
half-sister. How weird?
I'm trying to save Bambi's life. My
interns think I'm a loser. Severed arm.
- Callie's a bitch.
- Word.
She won't let me off my patient.
Nothing wrong. He's a nut.
- Severed arm.
- Does anybody know
about deer?
- They taste good.
- Evil.
George, severed arm. Plus,
Mer's half-sister is my intern.
Izzie's playing Dr. Dolittle.
Oh, and Alex hates your wife.
Dr. Sloan's ready for the arm.
- I'll say it. George is being an ass.
- I think it's my fault.
I said some things and
now he's not talking to me.
Why is he complaining?
Chick interns are hot.
- He's married, Alex.
- Yeah. He's married.
You know who's seriously
hot? That Lexie girl.
Get out. Before I hurt you.
I'm going over Callie to Bailey.
Callie is over Bailey's head.
Spiritually, Bailey's
over everyone's head.
Dr. Bailey. How
are things going?
- I wouldn't know. Ask Dr. Torres.
- Miranda.
I don't want to talk.
It is not like you
not to want to talk.
- Fine. How's your wife?
- Well, she's... she's good.
I haven't moved back in yet.
She hasn't let me
move back in yet.
She's not taking my calls.
Wait. That's not what
I want to talk about.
Chief resident. We're
gonna have this conversation.
Are you ordering me
to talk to you about this?
- No, I'm not ordering you...
- OK, then. Goodbye, sir.
I talked to the
family. On their way.
I've put an OR on hold.
We don't have much time.
Can I get a progress note?
Uh, do you maybe want
to have a drink later?
- What?
- A drink.
Give me one reason
why we can't hang out.
- I don't like you.
- Because of Meredith?
I don't like you
because you're you.
Hmm.
How is Meredith by
the way? Is she OK?
- She's fine.
- She's always fine. That's her problem.
We're fine people.
We do fine. We're fine.
How's Dr. Burke? I haven't
seen him around. Is he off today?
- Here.
- Thank you, doctor.
Dr. Burke handed in his letter
of resignation two weeks ago.
He wanted me to tell you.
- He's gone?
- Sorry.
- Well, don't be. I'm...
- Fine?
Yeah.
- Circulatory system
of a deer?
- Shut up.
Oh... Dr. Bailey, couldn't you use
an extra set of hands in the OR today?
I saw an appy on the
board. I'm great at appys.
Torres. She's in charge
of what cases you get.
Hard to set a kneecap
when your patient's in the pit,
- don't you think?
- Whatever.
- I don't know
how you did it.
- Did what?
Get them to listen to you.
Give you some respect.
Dr. Bailey, you wouldn't
happen to know anything about
the anatomy of a deer?
Not my intern, not my
business. Not anymore.
Your husband's
injuries are severe as...
They're traumatic
in the extreme.
I'm sorry. What does that mean?
The only thing holding his head
onto his body is skin and muscle.
If he moves even a fraction
of an inch, it could kill him.
So are you saying that...
I'm saying that when you see
him, this could be the last time.
This could be the last
time you see him alive.
Are you in pain, sweetie?
Good. Two blinks.
You aren't in pain.
Why isn't Daddy answering?
Right now we just need to wish
Daddy good luck in his surgery
and tell him how
much we love him. OK?
Because we do. I love
you so much, Henry.
What's... What's three blinks?
We've only been
working with one and two.
Is it I love you? Are you
telling us you love us?
Three blinks is "I love you."
We're gonna be fine, Henry.
You're gonna make it and
we're all gonna be just fine.
It's time to go.
OK, guys, let's let these
doctors fix Daddy up.
- George.
- Hey.
George, why are you avoiding me?
- I'm on my way to surgery.
- I don't mean
right now. I mean...
Not one word in 17 days?
I tell you that I love
you and not one word?
- Where have you been?
- Right here!
Exactly where I was a year ago.
I'm sorry. I...
Sorry.
I'm freaking out.
I'm an intern again.
Yeah, we're all freaking
out. We're all freaking out.
Interns who think I'm crazy.
I might actually be crazy because
day one of me being in charge,
I'm rescuing Bambi.
We're all freaking out.
Since when did you
start calling me Bambi?
- What? I'm not
calling you Bambi.
- No. I mean, I know. I under...
I expect it from
Cristina or Alex. But...
I'm Bambi! I'm
Bambi, George, OK?
If anyone in this situation
is a sad little cartoon
character, it's me.
I'm all alone in the forest.
All alone in the forest, George.
And my mother's been shot
by a hunter, and where are you?
Where the hell are you?
I'm on my way to surgery.
♪ Your tainted heart
My tainted love ♪
♪ Repent now... ♪
I really am up for a drink,
you know. If you need to talk.
- What would I need
to talk about?
- Meredith.
You were lucky, man.
That girl jerked you around.
- No idea what
you're talking about.
- Hey, I'm just...
Seemed like you could
use a friend about now.
Meredith's mother
never wanted her.
Her father was never around.
She has a right to be damaged.
And us together?
It's a big step for her.
Her friend gets left on the altar. She
sees things like this, they don't work.
She panics, she wants this,
she doesn't know how to have it.
Know what? That's not her fault.
Don't talk to me about Meredith.
You don't know what you're talking
about. And I don't want a friend.
OK, Nancy. I want you to
count back from 100, OK?
- No. No, I am not ready.
- It's just like
going to sleep.
I can't do this alone. I don't
want to be alone anymore.
- I know.
- No, I'm scared!
- I am scared, Meredith!
I know.
I think it's very brave,
what you're doing.
It's better to be alone
and feel like a success
than to be in a relationship
and feel like a failure all the time.
That's what I think.
So let's just take
care of your arm.
Then we'll deal with
the rest later, OK?
Well, looks like I'm
back to babysitting.
What the hell? Who took my
clamps? The bandage scissors?
Joey.
Foreign body. His abdomen's
rigid. Somebody page Dr. Bailey now!
Go! Come on, Joey.
- You like hamburgers,
don't you?
- Yeah.
- Spaghetti with
meatballs and lasagna?
- Mm-hmm.
That's beef. That's
cow you're eating, son.
What do you mean?
Could we have the
circle-of-life lesson later?
I need to get in.
- Sorry.
- Yeah.
Her eyes are glassy.
You. Get in here and
ventilate. Give me this.
- We're losing her.
- This is childish
and ridiculous.
It's not. It's not childish to hold
on to hope. It's actually very hard.
Your son wants to believe some
things can work out for the best.
Get me the paddles.
- Come on.
- What's she doing?
Insuring we never see the
inside of an OR this year.
She's in v-fib. I'm going to shock.
Charge to 300 and stand back.
OK. Clear.
Oh, my God! Oh,
my God! She's alive.
It worked. She's OK.
Everything's gonna be OK.
Oh, my God!
Got a big bleeder. Dr. Grey,
press and hold right here.
She's having contractions.
Take a look.
Probably the stress.
No, these are strong,
two minutes apart.
Call OB and get someone in here.
I don't think
there's time to call.
- Her water broke.
- Call Peds. Get a warmer in here.
Baby's coming.
Get her in stirrups.
Reverse Trendelenburg?
- Have the nurse press her abdomen.
- - Without jostling.
- I'm holding onto
a major artery here.
- OK. Clamp.
Scissors.
I got it. I got him.
- Great job, George.
- Thanks.
Yeah, we're all heroes.
Now, if no one minds, I'd like to
get this woman's arm sewn on.
Like she said,
she's gonna need it.
Starting the fusion now.
Did he just move?
- Oh, he definitely moved.
- Anesthesia's light.
- Yang, stabilize his neck.
- OK. Grab his feet.
Under the drape and do not
contaminate the sterile field.
Till he is under. We can't risk
even the slightest movement.
You cannot move.
Do you hear me?
This is not an option.
Everything is not gonna
be fine if you move.
It will be the opposite of fine.
You cannot leave. The
people you love, they need you.
Not just the memory
that you loved them.
Anyone care to explain to me
how my patient wound up in this OR
and I wasn't even
informed? Karev?
- Look...
- Dr. Karev didn't page you
because he knows
how to prioritize.
Ten minutes ago
this patient was coding
from a perfed abdomen.
Under the circumstances,
Dr. Karev's quick
thinking is the reason
that your patient
is even still alive.
I'll expect a fully dictated chart
before you leave tonight, Karev.
- Jackpot.
- Did he swallow those?
Poor fool, must
suffer from pica.
Uncontrollable urge to
eat any and everything.
Check it out. It's
a buffalo nickel.
Dr. Bailey. I saw
you were scrubbed in.
I thought I'd stop by.
- See what you've got.
- What I've got?
Two dollars and 37
cents, sir. In change.
It's like a cute
festival in here.
I delivered that
one an hour ago.
Oh, my God. Well, why aren't
you, like, jumping up and down?
I've done this
before! This is déjà vu!
Uh...
George, you didn't pass your
intern test. You know, it happens.
It's nobody's fault. Right?
Yeah. Yeah, it's nobody's fault.
It's just that Callie gave
Cristina the study cards,
Meredith didn't write anything,
Cristina planned a wedding, Izzie...
Izzie just had to...
You know, I'm responsible.
I've always been responsible.
I'm not saying "What about me?
When do I get what I want? When do
I get to be someone other than the guy
who repeats his
intern year?" But...
- But what about you.
- Yeah.
I didn't plan on being here.
I was all set for an
internship at Mass Gen.
And then my mother gets the
hiccups and I'm at a funeral.
We all have problems.
Moms die and dads drink so much
they don't even know
what year they're in.
And sisters, I...
I didn't even know there was a
Meredith Grey until a couple months ago.
And she won't... She doesn't
even want to talk to me.
I don't want to be here.
You know, I...
I'd give anything
to not be here.
You know, to have my life
work out the way I planned.
To even have time to
ask, "What about me?"
So you change. You get over it.
I'm here now, so...
And you?
You delivered a baby today.
So stop feeling
sorry for yourself.
You...
are kind of awesome.
I know.
Karev, why don't you make sure
Psych's prepared to consult on the patient.
Thank you.
Whether you like it or
not, we're gonna talk.
- Chief.
- I know you're angry.
No, I'm not angry.
I'm not disappointed.
I'm speechless.
I don't want to talk
because I'm speechless.
It makes me speechless to
realize you didn't think that
I would have made an
excellent chief resident.
Right. You would have made
an excellent chief resident.
But you'll make an even
more excellent surgeon.
You belong in the OR, Bailey.
Focus on honing those skills,
not on how well you can juggle
schedules or fill out paperwork.
Believe me, I know.
You'll thank me
for this one day.
But not today.
I'm the one that
could use a friend.
I said you could use a
friend. I could use a friend.
- Mark. I...
- I didn't come
to Seattle for Addison.
I didn't come to Seattle to be
chief. I came to Seattle for you. OK?
I came to Seattle
to get you back.
I know. I want to take it back
now, but I already said it, so...
Yeah. Maybe we
should have a drink.
- We could.
- Yeah. Not today.
I know you didn't wake
up expecting this was how
your first day was gonna go.
You thought you get to reattach
an arm or observe brain surgery.
Instead, you helped
save the life of a deer.
You can bitch and complain
about it or adjust your expectations.
Like it or not,
you're stuck with me.
I'm the kind of doctor who lets a kid
convince her she can do the impossible.
Plus, when I woke
up this morning,
I thought today was
gonna go differently.
I thought I was gonna
get the good interns.
Instead, I get
stuck with the duds.
So I have to adjust my
expectations as well.
♪ This is a place
where I feel at home ♪
♪ I... ♪
♪ Built ♪
♪ A home for you ♪
♪ For me ♪
- What?
- We heard...
We heard you
delivered a baby today.
On your first day as an intern.
- Yeah.
- What was it like?
Did you do it by yourself?
Was it like...? Did your head
explode with the amazingness?
Your very first day.
It was pretty... He
came out really fast.
I had to, uh, you know,
determine the position of the cord.
You know what a
reverse Trendelenburg is?
Filled this entire bag with coins
from my patient's stomach today.
No kidding.
♪ Out in the garden where
we planted the seeds... ♪
I miss Rebecca.
♪ There is a tree as old as me ♪
I miss Burke.
♪ Branches were sewn ♪
♪ By the color of green ♪
You want some money?
Change.
We don't like it.
We fear it.
What? You want to
humiliate me some more?
Because I get it. I suck. I
suck at my job. I suck as a wife.
I suck all around. So go ahead.
Humiliate me some more. Please.
♪ When the gusts
came around... ♪
Hope tomorrow's better.
But we can't stop
it from coming.
Meredith?
♪ I held on as tightly
as you held onto me ♪
Meredith.
We either adapt to change...
or we get left behind.
♪ And I built ♪
♪ A home ♪
♪ For you ♪
♪ For me ♪
I... um...
You're not ready for this.
No.
I asked for too much.
I think so.
So this is it?
- Yeah.
- We're breaking up.
We're breaking up.
It hurts to grow.
Anybody who tells
you it doesn't is lying.
We're broken up.
It's done.
- A breakup kiss.
- I want some breakup sex.
- Yeah. Breakup sex.
But here's the truth:
Sometimes, the
more things change,
the more they stay the same.
And sometimes, oh,
sometimes, change is good.
I love you too.
Sometimes, change is...
everything.