Great surgeons aren't
made, they're born.
It takes gestation, incubation,
sacrifice. A lot of sacrifice.
But after all the blood and guts
and gooey stuff is washed away,
that surgeon you
become? Totally worth it.
Welcome back.
Aah... I am not back. I
am here for a surgery.
I know.
Uh, charts, labs, a security key
card and key to the doctor's lounge.
Ah, look, they used my old
picture. It's like I never left.
- Addie! You're back.
- I am not back.
Oh, you're back. You're gonna
smell the stink and sweat of surgery
and you're gonna be back.
See? Nothing ever
changes around here.
- Things change.
- Welcome back.
I am not back!
Well, I just had no idea that
sunrise yoga would be so intense.
- Told you.
- Dr. Hahn.
I have the 3-D ultrasounds
and MRI's for today's patient.
You decided who's gonna
scrub in? I diagnosed the mother
- when she came in, so...
- Films.
First day. My clinical trial.
My baby. All grown up.
Nobody cares about your trial
or your sick terminal patients
who'd rather be left for dead.
- You're just jealous.
- Yeah.
Anyone can come up with a
trial. I could come up with one.
- Jealous.
- Not that it'd matter
'cause Hahn wouldn't sign
off. Won't even talk to me.
- She enjoyed talking to me.
- About what?
Her hopes. Her dreams. Then
we would braid each other's hair.
- Least I'm not living
in the clinic.
- The clinic is my happy place.
Can you use your sparkle pager
to get me on Hahn's surgery?
Can't think about the sparkle pager
because my clinical trial starts today.
- Sparkle pager stealer!
- Thank you!
OK. The both of you
need to take a moment,
dig down deep
and you'll discover
you're happy for me that I've
found my path to medical history.
- I'm not happy for her.
- Oh, me neither.
Karnofsky score is still 80 and his
CBC and liver enzymes are good.
- That's better than expected.
- I know.
Doesn't mean good. Don't want
you getting emotionally involved.
- Don't want you
getting hopes up.
- My hopes are not up.
All right then,
Dr. Grey. Let's do this.
- OK.
- Good. Chart, please.
Hey!
- Hey.
- Hey! Come here, you!
- Hey!
Whoo!
Wow, it's... Wow, it's
great to see you guys.
- How's L.A.?
- Yeah, it is.
It's great, it's fun. It's
the sun and surfing. It's...
You surf?
No, I don't surf.
Anyway... Hey, look, I hugged
you there! Did you see that?
You stole my husband from
me, I hugged you. I've grown.
I have and I can be
happy for the happy couple.
Right? I'm all "L.A." and like,
one with myself, so I feel really...
- Yeah.
- Mmm...
OK, well, I'm going
to go save a life now.
Really great... Great to
see you. Really. Cheers.
- Happy couple?
- See you after rounds.
- Hey.
- There she is!
Just coming in to check
on my patient's skin flap.
Amazing, right? Pulled a couple
of stem cells from the baby in utero,
six weeks later, I have
grown skin. Like God.
- Nice.
- What do you say
we lock that door
and tear one off
for old time's sake?
This place is exactly the same.
You are exactly the same.
Except now I grow skin
for babies. Like God.
Come on, I'm horny. The
nurses are shutting me down.
Aww. Thanks for my skin flap.
- That a euphemism?
- Nope.
- I am so coding.
- Coding hard.
What is that? Complaining? If you're
gonna complain, do it to my face.
Fine. There's nothing to do.
Can we go to the pit or something?
You're down here to learn
patient care, bedside manner
and a whole host of things you
cannot learn in the pit. So suck it up!
Hi. I'm Dr. Stevens. What
seems to be your problem?
- We...
- My wife thinks
she may be pregnant.
- OK, we'll get you a test.
- Code.
Excuse me, won't you?
What is wrong with you people?
What is that smell? Is that...
- That Scotch?
- It's seeping out
of Leo's pores.
You're hung-over?
You're all hung-over?
- Don't blame us,
blame O'Malley.
- George?
- He and Lexie Grey had a party.
- George had a party?
You're about to
experience medical history,
medical greatness,
medical majesty.
About to experience the beginning
of something extraordinary.
Take in the moment.
Dr. Cruz to OR Six.
OK. Dr. Grey, did you warn
the interns what to expect?
I told them to expect greatness.
Yes. In addition to the
greatness, the patient may be
inappropriately emotional,
he's aggressive... abusive.
Don't take it personally. OK? Don't
engage. It's the tumor talking. OK?
Mr. Robinson, Mrs. Robinson.
Dr. Grey and I want to say
how grateful we are that you've
decided to participate in our trial.
I know it's a hard
decision to make.
It is a chance, right?
It's our only chance.
If the surgery doesn't
kill me, the tumor will.
What have I got to lose, right?
As we discussed, the treatment
has never been tested on humans.
We're going to inject a
live virus into the tumor.
We can't take the tumor out. Our
hope is reduce the tumor from within.
- Dr. O'Malley?
- Over the past month,
Mr. Robinson
has experienced vision loss,
increasingly severe headaches that in...
Nice, huh? First thing I noticed
about her? Hell of an ass.
Like a nice piece of ass? She
could do a little more on top.
He's started picking
out husbands for me.
Was anyone talking to you?
- It's the tumor talking.
- Just the tumor talking.
So you single or what?
- Dr. Montgomery.
- Dr. Karev.
- Hey.
- We're hugging?
- Yep.
I hug now. It's what I do,
so... So you're my guy, huh?
You think I'd let anyone
else in on a case like this?
- I'll catch up with you
in a second.
- OK.
You... You don't own a phone?
I needed to see you in person.
I have a really huge case today. I wish
I could hang out, I really do, but I...
I'm pregnant.
I didn't mean to blurt it,
I'm sorry I blurted it, but I...
You never have time to talk, so I
kind of had no choice but to blurt.
Are you keeping it or are
you having an abortion?
I have a really big case.
Ectopia cordis. The baby's heart is
growing outside of its body, in utero.
Less than 200 cases
have ever been reported.
- Only a handful have survived.
- I was on one of these
ten years ago.
The baby squeezed its
own heart in utero and died.
He squeezed his own heart
with his tiny little hands?
You said there's a possibility
of a diaphragmatic hernia?
Yeah.
You and I have got a lot of
work to do on this little guy.
- You up for it?
- Always.
What about my work? I grew an
amazing flap of the baby's own skin.
Pretend all you want. But
I know you're impressed.
You!
- What's up, Bro'Malley?
- You.
Hey, you paged me?
O'Malley! What's up, party dude?
Know what I did last night?
I googled recipes. I spent
the night with a search engine.
But... That was just...
It was so spontaneous.
I... didn't think you'd want
to hang out with interns.
- Code.
- Code!
- What is that?
- It's just something
we came up...
Well, he came up
with it. "You coded."
- You coded!
- You coded.
It was really funny after
seven or eight shots.
- Hey! So we're all set
for tonight.
- Tonight? What's tonight?
Oh, um... The interns, we're just
having a darts tournament thing at Joe's.
Oh, my God, I love darts!
- Oh, do you wanna come?
- Yeah! Absolutely! Yey!
You so coded.
You know, I don't know, I
thought it'd be weird coming back.
Gotta say... I find it
strangely comforting
that everything
is the same here.
OK. In L.A., people say things.
But in Seattle there's this
strange culture of wordlessness
wherein I'm supposed
to suss what one is feeling
by the slight raise of an eyebrow
or the beginnings of a frown.
Any chance you want to tell me
what's going on with you, Miranda?
Just... a lot has changed
since you left. Just a lot.
Come on, name one thing
that has changed in this hospital.
The clinic is actually making
money. The Chief's wife left him.
Derek and Meredith
broke up. And I...
Whoa, whoa. Derek
and Meredith broke up?
Uh, like I said. A lot of
things have changed.
Nikki Jones, 25-year-old
female, 35 weeks pregnant.
Six weeks ago she was
diagnosed with ectopia cordis.
Which, as you know,
means that your baby's heart
is currently growing on
the outside of his body.
Which doesn't get any less
bizarre the more times I hear it.
Not bizarre, baby. Just
unique. Our son is one of a kind.
Wearing his heart on his sleeve.
This surgery is going to
take place in two OR's.
- It'll work like a dance.
- Dr. Karev and I
- will begin with the delivery.
- I'll stay
to close your incision.
While I bring your
baby to OR Two.
Where I'll work on
your baby's heart.
And I'll attend to your
baby's intestinal problem.
Wait. Intestinal problem?
We've detected there might be a
slight defect on your baby's diaphragm.
We just want to be prepared
for every contingency.
I just wish I could keep him
inside me. Keep him protected.
He's protected no matter
what. By us. By our love.
Something about that guy
makes me wanna punch him out.
Yet you didn't, for which
I am grateful, Karev.
- Hippies. Annoying, huh?
- Go away.
Hey. How great is she?
- She's great.
- Did I tell you?
- You told me.
- Did she tell you?
- Tell me what?
- Anything. Everything.
Does she know you're divorced?
- You're divorced?
- Yeah.
Which, as it turns out...
Was the best thing that
could have happened, really.
No kidding?
- You headed...?
- Yeah.
- I'll walk with you.
- OK.
It seems there's been a lot of
change, even since the last checkup.
Behavior's getting more erratic?
That's a nice way of putting it.
You've been incredibly
strong, Jennifer. This is...
You've been incredibly strong.
If you really want to help, you
could bring some single men by.
Phillip. Please stop.
Jennifer, we're in a hospital
full of eligible doctors,
and you're a waitress
with no prospects,
who needs to learn how to use her ass
to catch a new guy before I bite the dust!
It's just the tumor talking.
- It's just the tumor talking.
- It is. It's just the tumor talking.
And he's laughing again
because the idea of me
with another man
is just hilarious.
No, no it's not.
I just can't see.
- What? What can't you see?
- Anything.
I'm blind.
No response to light.
If I remember correctly,
you're a good-looking guy, right?
Just 'cause I'm blind doesn't mean you
can ignore me, you sick twisted bastard!
Playing games with people's
lives, slicing open people's brains.
Mr. Robinson, I'm sorry,
but I believe it's possible the
tumor is infiltrating the optic nerve.
We should consider moving the
surgery. Maybe even doing it today.
What about you, Dr. Grey?
You're a sexy little thing.
Do you think, Dr. Shepherd here
is attractive enough for my wife?
Hmm?
Jennifer, this
isn't easy, I know.
My husband is probably
going to die today.
We're moving up the
surgery, and he might die.
And all he can do is try to
fix me up with other men.
And I know... I know it's the
tumor talking. But, if he dies,
my last memory is going to be
of him calling me a piece of ass.
I'm not involved and
my hopes are not up.
Hmm.
I'm having trouble finding a
heartbeat on an ultrasound.
That's what happens, when
you have Scotch for dinner.
It's hard to follow the basics.
Oh! Rebecca. Hi.
I really didn't want an ultrasound.
I just wanted to get something
for the morning
sickness. It's really bad.
- So you're pregnant?
- Yeah. Just like five weeks
or so.
An ultrasound can be
hard to read this early on,
Let's take a blood sample,
make sure everything's on track.
OK. Dr. Stevens, do you know
when Dr. Karev will be out of surgery?
I just wanted to say hi.
Um, I... I don't know
that he's gone in yet.
You broke up with Meredith Grey?
Doing a trial together, if
that makes you feel better.
I hugged her. Hugged her.
And you're not even together?
What the hell happened?
OK, fine. Tell me
about the clinical trial.
Well, if it doesn't go well,
I'm killing people for sport.
When I walk into
an OR, I'm an expert.
I can stop a bleed,
I can remove a clot.
I'm the expert. But
in a clinical trial...
I'm experimenting.
Groping around in the dark.
Hoping to do the right thing.
She wants greatness from me.
- She's expecting greatness.
- OK, seriously.
Derek, what are you doing?
I'm seeing somebody else.
She's lovely.
She's really lovely.
Hey. You came.
You have to stop paging
me. Can't deal with this now.
I have a big case today...
I'm as scared about
this as you are.
I'm not scared. I'm just...
Look, you don't want me, OK?
This is not a thing you want
me for. I won't be good at it.
I'm not father material.
You have a husband. He doesn't
have to know that it's mine, OK?
No, it's not OK. Alex, I'm just
asking you to get over yourself
for one minute and talk to me so
we can figure this thing out. Together.
I have to go.
I'll be making the incision
from here to here, and be extra...
Excuse me. What you said
about further complications...
No, we can't think like that.
There's nothing else wrong with him.
Our intention is to have a healthy baby.
He'll be strong and happy and healthy.
Don't you understand
what we're trying to tell you?
Chances are, your baby's gonna
need a lot more than just heart surgery.
- Dr. Karev.
- Chances are, he won't.
Can't cross your fingers
and hope this'll go away.
Dr. Karev.
He's not prepared. I
was trying to prepare him.
They're having a baby. That
baby's gonna be screwed up
'cause he's coming into a world
where his parents are unprepared.
They wanna talk
about loving each other,
as if that has anything to do with
having the ability to raise a baby.
A sick baby! He's not prepared.
I was trying to prepare him.
Karev. Right now, you're feeling
all your feelings right out in the open.
Do me a favor and
stuff them back in.
- Interesting advice.
- Don't start with me.
She's no longer
allowed in my apartment.
No more tea parties or wine
parties or whatever you two have.
- What are you talking about?
- Hahn. She's unfair.
Refuses to teach me. I got in
at Mass Gen, Johns Hopkins.
I could've gotten in anywhere,
and she won't teach me!
All right, look. Erica,
she's a really good listener.
She comes off harsh at first,
but she's got a really good heart,
so just tell her
how you feel. OK?
Tell her how I feel?
Well, I don't speak "Girl."
Sorry about that. I mention
I live with Yang, now?
What? Why are you
looking at me like that?
Callie. Are you speaking
the vagina monologues now?
- What?
- I'm all for it, OK?
I think it's fantastic. Erica?
I mean, she seems great.
I really do like her,
actually, I do. Are you?
You want to know if
Erica and I are a couple?
Because I defended her to Yang?
Because you seem like a
couple. A really happy couple.
Um... OK, that's...
That's just...
That's insane is what
it is. I'm... I like penis.
I mean, I'm a huge,
huge fan of penis.
Hilarious.
You've been living in Los
Angeles way too long. Way too long.
- George!
- George! George!
Hey! Listen, I am
just the messenger.
But you should know that
people are prepared to drop out.
Nobody wants to get drunk
and play darts with their boss.
- Want me to take back
the invitation?
- I'm the messenger.
What's that about? More special
plans with your special friends?
I would like us to talk today. I
would like us to talk because
I care and I want
to know things,
and I have 15 minutes to
hear about your feelings.
So Alex? Alex,
you look thoughtful.
I'm very interested to hear... I
mean, what are your thoughts?
Izzie. Your thoughts?
Your feelings?
- Honestly?
- Uh-huh.
Little worried about Alex
because his Jane Doe girlfriend
keeps showing up like
something out of Fatal Attraction.
Her name is Rebecca
Pope, she's not my girlfriend.
Really? You guys
haven't had sex at all?
- Recently?
- She's married. She has a husband.
Does it hurt that she's married? I
mean, does that hurt your heart?
- What's the matter with you?
- Trying to talk "Girl."
Well, you coded. Right?
What? It's the new slang.
Everybody's saying it.
The way you just said
that? That was you coding.
Whatever. Unlike Meredith
with her trials and Petri dishes,
and Cristina who has to
practice talking like a human,
I actually care
about patient care!
- Need the sparkle pager.
- Not giving you the pager.
I can't talk "Girl," and I
shouldn't have to talk "Girl"
because I diagnosed the
patient. I need the pager.
- You can't have it!
- Stop! Stop it!
Give it. Give it to me!
Um...
Anyone ever think
you two were a couple?
No, because we screw
boys like whores on tequila.
Then try to marry them
or drown ourselves.
Huh...
You know, make Hahn let me
scrub in, or I'm making you move out.
- What? You...
- Desperate times.
Sorry that took so long.
Congratulations, you're pregnant.
You're sure?
A big day for pregnant
ladies. Everywhere I turn.
Weird. Only supposed
to give you a couple,
but this is a supply of
vitamins, samples. They're free.
No, I... We need to
schedule an abortion.
OK. I'm sorry, I...
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I don't mean to intrude, but...
You might want to sit with this for a
few days before you make your decision.
There's no decision to make.
I'm HIV-positive. And
the condom broke.
I got tested already, and
I will, again, in six months,
but so far I'm fine.
Please, I just... I want
to get this over with.
Is there any chance that
we can take care of it today?
Yeah. Let me see
what I can set up.
Thank you.
Nurse Santos to Geriatrics.
- Here.
- All right.
- Torres.
- Hey.
Do me a favor and put
Yang on your surgery.
- Only if you buy drinks
at Joe's.
- Done.
Dr. Montgomery?
Do me a favor? Can
you talk to my patient?
Don't work here, anymore.
She's pregnant and HIV-positive.
Thinks she has to terminate.
- She doesn't.
- I know, but she doesn't.
- It's not my area of expertise.
- I don't work here anymore,
Stevens.
If I worked here, I'd be
performing surgery after surgery.
I might even be back with my husband,
who's, apparently, on the market.
I'm not saying that I want
to get back with my husband.
It's just that things
were simpler with him
than the messy, messy
single life I am currently living.
Which was not my
point, by the way.
My point was... that I
no longer work here.
Which means, you need to pull
your face out of the potato chip trough,
- and tend your patients
yourself.
- I know, but...
You're a fighter. What happened?
I lost a lot of fights.
Well, time to get back up. Go.
Be the change you
want to see in the world.
You just quote Gandhi to me?
So... Time to
take her to the OR.
I'm not an idiot. We heard you.
It could be bad.
There's always a whole lot of
bad to focus on if you want to.
But there's hope too, right?
There's always hope too.
- Jennifer?
- No, it's Dr. Shepherd.
I hate this. Not
being able to see.
I just want to see Jennifer.
Phillip, this is an
extremely risky operation.
You may have a few weeks to live.
Could spend that time with Jennifer.
You don't have to
do this surgery today.
I'm trying to fix Jennifer up. I
don't want to leave her alone.
That's the one thing about
all of this I really can't stand.
I just want her to be
all right when I'm gone.
You need to tell her that.
Before you go into surgery,
you need to remember this conversation,
and you need to tell her that.
Hey. I only have five minutes
because we moved the surgery up.
But I did want to come
and say that, obviously,
he doesn't know me at all. I'm
not the one emotionally involved.
- He's the one
emotionally involved.
- He?
Derek told me not
to get my hopes up.
Anybody who knows me knows
I'm not a hopeful person to begin with.
Right.
I came up with this
clinical trial. It's my baby.
Does he honestly think
that I've walked into this with
no understanding of how hard it'll be?
Seriously, no wonder we didn't work out.
Because he told you
not to get your hopes up?
Exactly. I gotta go.
Surgery's about to start.
- The surgery with no hope?
- Shut up.
So who's the new mystery
woman that Derek's dating?
Who's the unlucky McRebound?
What? Oh, is the whole
"Mc" thing over now?
Surely things haven't
changed that much here?
Addison. The woman standing
immediately to your right,
the one handing you
the surgical instruments...
- Hey.
Six dates, heavy petting, lots
of tongue. Good guy. Scalpel?
We can have the baby? You're
saying we can have the baby.
- A healthy baby?
- With proper
prenatal treatment,
the risks to your baby
are substantially reduced.
Haven't found you an OB, I think
the process might prove difficult...
Doesn't matter. We'll figure it
out. We can figure anything out.
I can't believe this! Thank you!
No! No. Do not thank her.
I asked you to do one thing, I
asked you to schedule an abortion.
- Sarah.
- No.
She just walks in here and gets
your hopes up, and that's not OK!
I was diagnosed at 19. And I
have learned how to deal with it.
But I will not put that onto a baby! I
cannot bring a baby into this world
who could possibly
have this disease. I won't!
Now, could you please
just schedule the abortion?
And, do me a favor, don't come
back! I'd like a different doctor.
Phillip, remember
what we talked about?
Jennifer? Jen? Jennifer!
I don't want to leave you alone.
I want you to meet someone.
I want you to
promise me you'll try.
Because I can't do this thinking
I'm leaving you alone. OK?
OK. OK.
Maybe I'll make
it. I hope I make it.
♪ Don't you wish you were? ♪
♪ Don't you wish I was? ♪
♪ Something more than mystery ♪
♪ To uncover ♪
Go ahead. A little bit
further. Good, keep him flat.
OK. Got him, Karev?
Placenta looks good.
- You OK to close, Dr. Bailey?
- Yep.
Membrane's intact.
Oh, no. She's hemorrhaging.
This blood is moving a little too
fast. I need another set of hands here!
Her uterus isn't
contracting. Damn it.
Where's Montgomery?
The mom is in distress.
They're trying to close.
Get the baby to Hahn.
Addie knows what she's doing.
I think I've been
hiding in the clinic.
Yeah? OK, listen, Izzie?
I lost the contest. I
couldn't hack cardio.
- I performed CPR on a deer.
- Izzie!
- I think I've been hiding.
- You can't play darts with us.
- What?
- I shouldn't have to say this.
- You should get this.
- Get what?
You're not an intern anymore.
I'm not a resident. And, that sucks,
but I'm trying to
make the best of it.
Trying to stop complaining
and embrace what I have.
What I have is new friends
who don't want to get drunk
and play darts with their boss.
- I'm their boss.
- Yes. Yeah. You're their boss.
You're in charge. And
you should get that.
I gotta do something.
Get in here.
I thought I made myself clear.
You did. I didn't. Get in here!
- Listen and learn.
- I knew it. You disapprove.
You're here to push
some kind of agenda, right?
No. No.
Listen, if you wanna have an
abortion because you want to,
that's between you and
whatever god you believe in.
But if you wanna
have an abortion
'cause you think that's
what medicine is telling you,
that's between you and me. I
was ineffectual. I was unclear.
I've been on my heels a little
bit lately, and I was unclear.
So just listen, OK?
I wasn't telling you there is some
chance your baby might not be born sick.
I was telling you there is a
98 percent chance your baby
could be born perfectly
healthy. A 98 percent chance.
There's a higher chance of
being born with Down Syndrome
than there is of you
passing HIV on to your child.
I don't... I just... I can't...
I know you gave up about
having children a long time ago,
and I understand that it's difficult
to readjust your thinking so quickly,
but if you take your
meds responsibly,
there's no reason why you can't
have a beautiful, healthy baby.
This is your chance.
If you want it.
This is your chance to be a mom.
- A 98 percent chance?
- Ninety-eight percent chance.
Thank you.
We are on a clock here, Dr. Karev.
We need Montgomery now.
She's coming. She'll be here.
Heart rate's down to
the 60's, he's bradycardic.
- Damn it, we could lose him.
- Tell me what to do.
Massage the heart.
Gently.
I can feel it getting stronger.
- Heart rate's back up
to the 140's.
- I pushed 60 cc of bolus NS.
Good job, Karev.
You can step back now.
♪ Please, just once again ♪
And now...
All right, moment of truth.
Injecting the virus
into the tumor.
All right, we're doing this one
stage repair to prevent infection.
Ready for the skin graft.
- Complete heart block.
- Damn.
Injection went into the
intra-arterial. Push one of Atropine.
- Not responding!
- Push another one. Come on, come on.
Need another set
of hands over here.
- OK, there we go.
- It's controlled, right?
Yeah, it's controlled.
I got it, I got it. Go.
Look at that. Beating inside
his chest for the very first time.
And God admired
his amazing skin flap.
And he saw that it was good.
- How is he?
- - I was able to reduce the heart
almost all the way into
the pericardial space.
No intestines in the way?
No diaphragmatic hernia?
No anything. His heart's
in. It's beating. He's perfect.
Patient number one.
Treatment failed. Call it, Dr. Grey.
Time of death, 19:33.
Hey. The parents
were right. The baby?
No further complications.
Yeah, and mom's
OK, too. It's a good day.
You seem sad... Miranda.
We're not gonna
do this. I can't share.
I can't catch up
with you. I can't talk.
Because if I did, if I told
you Tucker moved out...
if I told you I haven't
slept alone in 12 years...
If I told you that my heart
hurt so much, sometimes,
I want to rip it from my chest
with my own little hands...
I would fall apart. And I
don't have time to fall apart.
Not that I'm not
happy to see you. I am.
But I wish that you
would go home,
so the choice to talk and
fall apart would go away.
I got my hopes up.
Yeah, me too.
- Dr. Shepherd.
- Yes?
It was a pleasure
working with you today.
Dr. Grey.
♪ For things we've always
had But have no eyes to see ♪
♪ Somethin' new
is going to happen ♪
I do miss some of this.
I could put the
paperwork through tonight.
You could start work tomorrow.
♪ All these buildings
and mountains
♪ Slowly they'll arise ♪
I needed to come back
to see that it
was right to leave.
You need to fill my position.
I was Gandhi, Dr. Montgomery.
I was so freaking Gandhi,
I kicked Gandhi's ass.
It's an L.A. thing.
♪ Before our eyes ♪
Aren't you gonna
be late for your party?
I'll blow them off. I'd rather
hang out with you anyway.
George, I get it. I don't have
to like it, but I get it. So, go.
Go "code" or whatever.
You know, whenever anyone says
something really funny and I laugh,
I always look around to
see if you think it's funny too.
Even when you're not
there, I still look around.
Go.
Ooh...
I bet you wish you'd taken
the stairs right about now.
Giving birth may be all
intense and magical and stuff.
But the act itself? It's
not exactly pleasant.
But it's also a beginning
of something incredible.
I am. I am very, very funny.
You would not
believe what she...
Wait, wait, wait. Hang
on, hang on, hang on.
You've got a hair
that is caught...
- caught in your lip gloss.
- Something new.
Sorry, you were saying?
- I'm funny, apparently.
- Funny?
- Yes, it turns out I am.
- Apparently.
Any of you ladies want to dance?
Ugh! For the thousandth
time, the answer is no, Mark.
- Beat it, Sloan.
- I'll dance with you.
Something unpredictable.
- Dr. Montgomery.
- Hi.
- Dr. Hahn?
- Yang.
Yang?
OK, is it because I'm
Asian? Is that your problem?
- You don't like Asian people?
- Excuse me?
Why won't you teach me?
You're not without skill.
You're not without talent.
So stop seeking my
approval. I'm not gonna tell you
what a good little girl you are.
That's not my job. And it doesn't
make you any better at yours.
Jeez. Little hard on
her, don't you think?
- I think she reminds me of me.
- Something true.
She's pretty, huh?
She's beautiful.
Something worth loving.
- You want to get outta here?
- Like you wouldn't believe.
Something worth missing.
Dr. Stevens? Labs
for Rebecca Pope.
Thanks very much.
Wait, no, this... This can't
be right. You sure this is right?
- You're leaving already?
- I have a plane to catch.
I walk on the beach now. I buy
aromatherapy candles. I'm very Zen.
But I want to kick your ass so
badly right now, it is killing me.
- Excuse me?
- I'm talking about Derek.
Derek Christopher Shepherd.
Are you letting him get away?
Because, I swear
to God, Meredith,
if you let him ride off into the
sunset with that doe-eyed little thing...
- Of course I'm sure.
- So my patient is not pregnant?
Apparently not.
♪ Please don't make
my feel good go away ♪
Something that will
change your life...
forever.