If you're normal,
one of the few things you
can count on in life is death.
- Hello.
- These are amazing.
They're all about the medicine.
There's no personal crap,
no talk about boyfriends or feelings.
She hardly even mentions you.
Thanks for pointing that out. What about
when she held the retractor six hours?
If you're a surgeon, even that
comfort is taken away from you.
- Like Harry Potter books
I never had.
- Did you read the part
where she did
the pyloric stenosis
on the three-week-old baby?
♪ I won't bite Oh, come
on and give it to me ♪
Surgeons cheat death,
we prolong it, we deny it.
♪ Oh, I really like it ♪
Hold on! He's in v-fib!
Charge to 300! Clear!
Up to 360! Clear!
We stand and defiantly
give death the finger.
Good. Let's go.
Grey, you're late.
She has Skills Lab.
Good morning, Cristina. It
feels like minutes. See you later.
No, Tucker, I did not say I
won't do the marriage counseling.
I can't do it in the
mornings again.
I'm now 20 minutes
late for work.
- I'll see you tonight.
- Marriage counseling?
- How's that going?
- You heard us arguing about it.
How you think it's going?
You're doing a craniotomy on
my patient Rosemary Bullard today.
Gonna be awake or
yawning into her brain?
- Meredith kept me up.
- Don't need to hear
your dirty...
Talking on the
phone with Cristina.
Aw, and stole your sleep?
Did you say,
"Yang goes or I go"?
I don't think I'd win that one.
- Those two come as a set.
- Before, she had Burke. Burke helped.
- True.
- Counseling's a good move.
- Addison and I did counseling.
- Right before you got divorced?
Ladies and gentlemen,
allow me to introduce...
Stan.
State-of-the-art
computerized patient simulator.
Stan can educate you
in airway management,
trauma assessment and care.
He breathes, he
pulsates, he seizes,
he hemorrhages, he secretes.
And he speaks. Hello, Stan.
Hello, doctor. I'm
not feeling well.
Stan will say what he needs.
He's more forgiving
than most patients.
You kill him, he'll keep
coming back for more.
Make good use of him, people.
- We're operating on robots?
- Can we go back to pigs?
- What about people?
- When the chief decides who
gets the first solo
surgery, be ready.
Solo surgery?
- When do we find out?
- Is he deciding soon?
I do not know what it will be,
I do not know when it will be.
I do know that the
winner should be prepared
to do any surgical procedure,
and will choose
one intern to scrub in.
So practice your skills,
impress your attendings
and do not make me look stupid.
Grey, Stevens, you're with Hahn.
Yang, the pit.
Karev and O'Malley,
- you're Skills Lab. Get to know...
- Dibs!
- Mine.
- I am having chest pain.
Just to be clear, we are not
cracking open any chests today?
- No, Stevens.
- With solo surgery coming up,
we were hoping to
be on a cool surgical...
I'm gonna stop you right there.
I don't get attached to
patients. But I like this guy.
I have spent almost two
years giving his family hope
and then taking it away. This
procedure can buy him time
until he gets another
shot at a transplant.
Make sure it works.
- Absolutely.
- Of course.
- Familiar with the case?
- Michael Norris,
44-year old male
with congenital hypertrophic
cardiomyopathy who has failed
treatment at Seattle Pres.
Waiting on a transplant
since narrowly missing out
on one on May 14th of 2000.
- Wait. May 14th?
- What?
- That's... That's Denny's heart.
That's the heart
I stole for Denny.
I need you to have
sex with Cristina Yang.
Good morning.
Distract. Give her something
to do besides call my girlfriend
- and wake me up.
- Yang. No.
No. Too serious. Humorless.
Un-fun. Not my type.
Yang should be your type.
She's intense,
intelligent, complicated.
She's like a single-malt Scotch.
And you are used
to... beer bongs.
- Callie Torres is no beer bong.
- Wait, I get it.
You don't think you have a
shot. You're probably right.
- Oh, I have a shot.
- Then try. As a favor to me.
No. I'm not your stud horse.
- You can't just tell me to...
- You slept with my wife.
Yeah, I'll give it a shot.
- Is that too tight?
- OK, yeah.
- OK.
- Feels pretty good.
- OK, good.
- Put one...
Are you guys shooting
drugs? Oh, my God!
- No, we're practicing IVs.
- How else are we supposed
to learn?
- Yang never lets us
do anything.
- Practicing on each other?
We did it at Baylor, it's cool.
No. It's not cool. It's crazy.
- Like creepy, basement crazy.
- Don't tell anyone!
- Don't worry.
- I'm next.
Hold still now.
Ah, Dr. Hunt, got a second?
It's about to get loud
in here, but shoot.
We're awarding a solo surgery to a
second-year resident. I want your take.
- One second.
- Unidentified male,
mid-thirties.
Lost vitals, shocked
him into sinus tach.
- Possible fractures of arms.
- OK, on three.
- Two, three. Good, good.
- Open right tib/fib,
rigid abdomen.
- What doesn't he have?
- Found under an overpass.
- Cops thinks someone
threw him over.
- After they beat him to death?
- It's a contest,
the solo surgery?
- You have fresh eyes.
You don't know them personally,
you don't have any history,
any relationship. That
perspective is rare here.
I'll give it some thought.
Dr. Webber, regarding
the solo surgery, I presume
it's gonna be a general
surgery? I wanna be prepared...
You'll know when you all know.
And one more thing. If
my ER reports are right,
you've been working three
days. When do you sleep?
Keep tabs on all attendings?
- His IV blew.
- He needs that access now!
- I'm doing it.
- This will buy him some time
- until you get that line in.
- Yeah.
If you were less worried about winning
contests, you might have thought of it.
So you're gonna give me
a heart attack? Literally?
Uh... It's a technique
called "alcohol ablation."
Through a catheter
in your femoral artery,
Dr. Hahn will inject ethanol
straight into your heart.
The alcohol will incinerate
any tissue cells it touches.
- Dr. Stevens?
- Um...
We're gonna be burning away
the muscle in your ventricle
that's blocking your
ability to get oxygen.
If we're successful, you
should feel immediate relief.
Just like that? I'll
be able to breathe?
- Just like that.
- And he can't be asleep
- during the procedure?
- I'm afraid not.
Dr. Stevens will be asking you
to cough, inhale and exhale...
And checking to
see if I'm dead yet?
Mike, stop.
I mean, it is a
heart attack, right?
It's a dangerous procedure.
But it's one we can monitor
and control. If you don't have it,
the next heart attack you
have, and you will have one...
It'll kill me.
Promise you'll keep me awake.
I... I don't want to miss this.
I want Mike's latest echo and
angio before he goes to the cath lab.
- Wow! Are you freaking out?
- What?
- Why? Do you think I should be?
- This patient? In Denny's room?
- It's a lot of Denny
for one day.
- It is a lot.
A lot. Is it a lot of
Denny for you, too?
I mean, how much Denny
are you experiencing?
Iz, you can do this.
- My pain is getting worse.
- I hate this.
I'm not gonna win
the solo surgery
practicing on Plastic Man.
You're not gonna
win because you suck.
Your bedside
manner is what sucks.
- What? What did you say?
- Ain't technology amazing?
Screw this. I'm gonna
practice medicine.
You play with your doll.
What's the matter?
Scared of a little education?
You are so awesome!
- Ow.
- No! No! No! No! Stan!
What's a guy have to do
to get a beating this bad?
Maybe he'll tell us
when he wakes up.
Let's hope he
makes it that long.
Three, run these to the lab,
then go by the morgue
and get the forms
- for an unclaimed body.
- He's gonna need a chest tube.
I was hoping, with solo
surgery coming up...
With the solo surgery coming up,
your job is to impress me. So, go.
Dr. Yang, with the
solo surgery coming up,
your job is to impress me.
- You're planning for his death.
- I was trying to be prepared. Sorry.
I can't use sorry. I
could use a doctor.
Be one.
The kind of metastases you have
are prone to spontaneous bleeding.
So there are considerable
risks to the surgery.
- You're saying this one...
- Might be dicier.
Much dicier than
previous surgeries.
I want to be clear,
you can live with this.
For months, if not longer.
Not... Not like this.
Not feeling this bad.
I understand risks
are part of the package.
That's why you people make me
go cross-eyed signing all these forms.
You're signing a "Do
Not Resuscitate" order?
If it's my time to go...
She doesn't want to be
on life-support kind of thing.
- She'd hate that.
- I just hate lying
around like that.
I don't want that.
OK.
- Goodbye, darling.
- Goodbye, love.
Sorry. We do this every time.
She signs the paper,
we kiss goodbye.
Then after the surgery,
we say hello again.
That sounds like a plan to me.
You rest up. We'll be
bringing you up soon.
That there is the
Holy Grail of marriage.
Something to aspire to.
- What happens to them?
- You sign, attending signs,
- pink copy goes in his chart.
- No, I mean the bodies.
The unclaimed bodies.
What happens to them?
If they remained unclaimed for
a certain time, they're cremated,
- the ones that haven't
been preserved.
- Preserved?
For medical research,
gross anatomy,
- surgical study,
that sort of thing.
- For, like, med students?
Exactly. For med students.
To practice on?
You're pretty.
Um...
Thank you all for being here. I
appreciate the opportunity to learn
and I'm sorry you had to die.
Oh! Uh... Instrument trays!
- We got a rhythm.
- We got to get him up to surgery.
- He's bleeding through
his leg splint.
- So the chief has asked me
to watch the second
years for the solo surgery.
- What's your take, as a class?
- They're a mixed bag.
Yang's very good.
She's... hardcore.
She'll be a cardio god.
- She's my roommate.
- And Stevens?
She's smart. Good with patients,
very compassionate, supposedly.
She did sleep with my
ex-husband while we were married.
I'm more interested
in the doctor part.
Right. Obviously.
Of course you are.
New scans, good.
Splenic subcapsular hematoma...
I can look. Go update his chart.
- Dr. Yang, you paged me?
- Patient in
Trauma One.
You paged me for a consult? I
was hoping you wanted to see me.
I did. The patient has a
shattered nose and cheekbones
and a fractured left
mandible. Trauma One.
OK, Mike, the catheters
are in. It's time to inject.
OK, just hold tight.
Stevens, over here, please.
I specifically chose you for this case
because you connect well with patients.
That's something I've been
told to work on not doing.
Mike needs you talking to him.
He's scared, his pulse
is elevating, step up.
OK.
Hey, Mike, you're doing great.
You're gonna feel
a little bit of burning.
Will that make it...?
There it is. Oh, God!
- Try not to move.
- Try to lay still. Try to breathe.
- Make it stop!
- Mike, we can't stop
but it's gonna end soon. Hang
in there. Stevens, talk to him.
- I'm sorry.
- - Grey, how's his pressure?
Eighty-five systolic.
Stevens, talk! Help him!
Stevens, get him to
cough. Get him to breathe.
- Stevens!
- Pressure's stabilizing.
OK, how you doing, Mike?
I still... can't breathe.
Does that mean
we're not successful?
There were two arterial
routes I could choose.
- The next time we do this...
- No. I can't...
I won't do this again.
Please, I can't do this again.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Tell Stevens to find me
so I can permanently
throw her off my service.
Dr. Hahn, I know you have
a history with this patient.
In a weird way, Izzie does, too.
A history? With my patient?
No, with Denny Duquette.
Tell her to find me.
The tumor's position
has been altered.
I need an ultrasound
localization.
I took care of the Yang
problem, by the way.
Already? That sounds too easy.
If it doesn't feel like
work, it's not going to work.
Where did you learn
that? Marriage counseling?
Of course not.
It's a complete waste of
time. This couple, the Bullards,
I bet they never got counseling.
They just take the
bad with the good.
Damn it. Tumor's hemorrhaging.
Her brain's starting to swell.
- Push 70 of mannitol!
- She's bradying down.
One of atropine. Let's make sure
these two get a chance to say hello again.
- Have you seen Izzie?
- No.
You got anything I can scrub
in on? Robo-patient sucks.
Listen, Izzie is having a
rough day. So if you see her...
- No, I'm having a rough day.
- What happened?
Hunt. Hunt hates
me. He hates me!
- He kissed you.
- Yes.
That was... before.
Now, he hates my guts.
This is worse than Hahn.
I have no idea what I did
or said or what?
I gotta get off this case.
Ah! Dr. Yang.
Our guy scheduled for
surgery? I want to know when
- I'm gonna see you next?
- He's not stable.
Oh! Then we
might have time to...
I've just been paged down.
This does not happen to me.
Bow to me, for I am
the queen of the interns.
I have assembled an army
of the dead to teach us things.
Cadavers. I got us cadavers
to practice on. A whole bunch.
You got cadavers?
Human cadavers?
In the tunnels.
Meet there for lunch.
- Hey.
Let me ask you something.
Do you know if Izzie Stevens
had some sort of a relationship
with Denny Duquette?
You mean, besides
the engagement?
And the cutting his LVAD wire
so she could move him
up the transplant list?
Izzie was on probationary leave.
She was nearly kicked
out of the program.
- I forget you weren't
here then.
- No, I wasn't.
I was at another hospital,
watching my patient's heart
get stolen out of his chest.
Did you page me
down here for sex?
Because I'm not
really in the mood.
- Want to see some dead guys?
- Why?
- Come on.
- Why would you say that? Why?
Cadavers.
- For practice. For solo surgery.
- What is this?
I heard you were
having a crappy day.
I thought this
would cheer you up.
- What?
- It's like a bouquet.
Of corpses. That is so...
I'm sorry. No. That's
crazy. He's dead.
He's dead. Just so
many dead people today.
- These are for interns!
- Go play with the dummy!
- Come on!
- I cannot help it.
- I'm dying.
- But I'm applying pressure!
Must be something
you're forgetting.
- For crying out loud!
- I'm surprised you even passed
- your intern exam.
- Oh, my God!
I'm sorry. I couldn't resist.
- Chief, I have to talk to you.
- Hey, Hahn, come in.
I want you to watch
this. Let's blow an artery.
I'm bleeding out!
I'm bleeding out.
It's about Izzie Stevens
and Denny Duquette.
How is Stevens
still working here?
How is Seattle
Grace still accredited?
This thing goes unreported? No
wonder this place is number 12!
- Stop right there.
- I want an ethics panel
assembled.
I want Stevens's role in this
investigated and Bailey's as well.
- She was her superior...
- Slow!
No! My patient lost
a heart over this.
Someone is gonna lose their job!
Stop! We are not
digging this up.
It didn't go unreported. It was
reported to me. I dealt with it.
Stevens was punished. She's
learned and she's on her way
to becoming an excellent surgeon.
That's the kind of hospital I'm running.
This issue has
been laid to rest.
It's in the past,
that's where it stays.
It's not in the past for me!
It's lying on a bed in
the ICU, about to die!
Then your responsibility is to
make sure that doesn't happen.
It was a difficult surgery,
especially at her age.
We're not sure how
she's going to respond.
Oh, sure.
The waiting is
always the hard part.
- Ed, she might not make it.
- I know.
I know.
Iz.
- You're hiding from Hahn?
- Sure. Her, too.
- Is Mike OK?
- No. The ablation failed.
He's refusing to try
again, so Hahn's... Um...
- You should go talk to her.
- I stole his heart, Meredith.
I stole it for Denny.
I stole it for myself.
And now I'm supposed to hold
his hand while we torture him?
I can't even look at him.
It's my fault that he's here.
So, anyway, I'm hiding.
Yang, suction here, please.
Sloan's coming in for
the mandibular repair?
Sorry about before. Everybody's
up in everybody else's business here.
Better to keep things
professional, if you can.
Yes. One minute you're
working with people,
then you're friends with
them and then... whatever.
Suddenly there's all this
pressure to define what you are,
like it's all black and white.
You are this or you're that.
You are aware you're
doing it again, right?
Dr. Hunt? How's our mystery man?
Still with us. He's a fighter.
Hate to be the
other guy. Callie.
Dr. Yang, I know cracking
chests is more your thing,
but you'd be surprised how exciting it
can be when I manipulate a little skin.
Actually, Dr. Yang,
why don't you scrub out.
We've got enough hands in here.
OK.
Hey, I heard he went
up. Can I scrub in?
Shut it. If I'm not in,
you're not in. You stink.
- I showered.
- You smell like formaldehyde.
You smell like death.
Why do you smell like death?
Uh...
I see dead people!
- Get out.
- I need off Hunt case.
In a one-time offer,
I'll trade my beaten-to-a-pulp
trauma-palooza
of a patient for no less than
three of your cadavers. Pony up.
Deal. Take three.
I need to be with people.
Preferably live
people, but whatever.
Alex, by the way, thank you
for bringing me the corpses.
It was very sweet.
Dr. Hunt and Dr. Sloan
are still operating.
- Could I try...?
- No!
Check this out: my dead mommy
taught me a cool way to hold instruments.
If you palm it, you
can switch off faster.
When your dead mommy teaches
you things, can you see her?
- No. I'm reading her journals.
- Duh, I was kidding. Obviously.
I did see her once, though.
And that bomb squad guy.
And Denny.
- Today?
- No. I was dead at the time.
I feel my mom with me sometimes.
I got to get off this case.
♪ Some people have nothing
and want nothing and are free ♪
♪ Some people want
to burn the world ♪
- Could I...?
- No!
Please don't be in there,
please don't be in there.
Please don't be in there.
Dr. Hahn, I came to apologize
and ask if I could please
be let off your service.
No. If I can convince Mike
to have another ablation,
you're gonna be there
to see him through it,
to look him in the eye,
to help him through the pain
that you have caused him.
If he dies, I want
you there for that too,
because you're responsible.
He decided. He won't
do another procedure.
I'm going to...
go check him out.
Dr. Stevens.
She'll be OK. This has...
This has been
coming for a long time.
She'll be OK. She'll...
She'll move on.
If you die,
she will not get over it.
She will not move on.
She'll think she can.
She'll even think she has.
And out of the blue, you'll
be right there with her,
so close she'll think she can
touch you, and then all of this
will just...
be happening for
her all over again.
She will not be able to move on.
They're not doing anything.
Make them do something!
- They're standing around!
- They're keeping her
comfortable.
That's all they can do.
You and Rosie agreed,
there would be no extreme measures
taken if her time came. Her time is here.
- What's going on?
- She's coding.
And Mr. Bullard is
reconsidering the DNR order.
Ed, this was what I warned
you about. This moment.
Even if we try to
resuscitate her,
I'm not sure she'll
wake up again.
Nothing more we can do.
Rosie.
Rosie? Hon?
No.
Stay with me, Rosie.
Rosie? Stay with me.
Don't leave me, Rosie. Stay
with me, Rosie. Don't leave me.
Stay with me. Stay
with me, Rosie!
Stay with me. Come
back, Rosie! Don't leave me.
Stay with me. Don't leave me.
Stay with me,
Rosie. Stay with me.
Stay with me. Don't leave me.
Stay with me, Rosie.
Don't leave me.
Stay with me. Don't leave me.
Stay with me, Rosie.
Please, Rosie. No!
- Please don't...
- Mr. Bullard.
Do something for
her! Do something!
- Mr. Bullard - No! No!
- Let him be. Let him be.
- Please, Rosie.
Please.
I'm glad you
decided to try again.
You can thank Dr. Stevens.
It's her fault we're here, right?
Vitals are stable, he's
ready for the injection.
- The alcohol is going in.
- No, wait. Wait, don't.
Mike, look at me.
Just stay with me.
It's going to hurt, but not as
much as you think it's going to.
He's in SVT. There may be
alcohol backing into his AV node.
Get him to cough,
get him to breathe.
You need to breathe.
Cough for me.
Look at me, Mike. Look at me!
He's in V-tach,
losing consciousness.
Push 100 of lidocaine. Ready.
Oh, man. It's Lexie.
I gotta go. Beaten-to-a-pulp
Guy is coding.
Oh, no. Pulp Guy
is mine. We traded!
- Why didn't you
put in a chest tube?
- I don't know how.
What do you mean? I
learned that my first week.
Yes, you learned. You
know, but I'll never know
because you
won't let me try one,
but you hog all our robots
and you steal all our corpses!
Dude, I think you broke
her. Vitals are stable, for now.
Was there this much
blood in his urine before?
No.
- Bedside cystogram.
- Dibs on that.
It's mine. His bladder
repair is mine, too.
- We traded, I get his bladder.
- We never traded.
To prove you wrong,
next time he crashes,
you put in his chest tube.
Get away from
that man right now!
He was crashing, so
we upped his dopamine...
Are you deaf, Karev? I
said step away from him.
- We were saving his life...
- What you did was pick him over
like vultures, like a bunch
of children fighting over toys.
You treat a man fighting
to live as if he was dead.
You have no sense, no
decency and no respect!
Just get out. Just
get out of here.
♪ What a time to pick a fight ♪
♪ The world is full ♪
♪ Of those tonight ♪
♪ I looked to you ♪
Ed.
Rosemary's gone.
Her heart is no longer
beating on its own.
The second you stop doing
what you're doing, it will stop.
I... I can't be the
one to let her go.
- To let her die.
- I know.
I know you can't.
♪ Save me ♪
OK.
Here you go. Sit down.
Sit down. There you go.
Dr. Bailey.
All right, let's get
the crash cart in here!
Mike! Open your eyes!
Just stay here with me!
I need you to fight, Mike,
fight to stay with Elyse.
You have to live through this.
You need to breathe right now.
Right now!
♪ Save me ♪
♪ What a time ♪
Are you OK?
♪ To pick a fight ♪
♪ The world is full ♪
♪ Of those to find ♪
♪ Save me ♪
You don't have to
do it. Let me. Let me.
♪ The world is full
of those tonight ♪
Dr. Yang, I'll need you to
bring me the post-op report
on our beating victim
before you leave.
I'm sorry, did you
say something?
- Yang, what is wrong with you?
- Sir?
I have had women opt for needless
elective buttock enhancement surgery
just for another chance
to be flirted with by me.
So, what's your deal?
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
I have been hitting
on you all day!
Oh... I...
Really? Oh...
Excuse me.
It was a stupid idea!
It wasn't even my idea.
It was Shepherd's idea.
- Oh, come on.
- That woman is not
single-malt Scotch.
She is bad, cheap wine that gives you
a headache you can feel in your teeth.
Dr. Hunt. Any thoughts on
the second-years after today?
- It's only been a day, sir.
- Of course.
They're undisciplined,
inarticulate and they have
a lot to learn about respect.
Mostly, they're more
interested in personal crap.
I'm not sure they're being
taught anything different.
Honestly, I'm not sure I'll
be staying on. Excuse me, sir.
Tell me I am not
seeing what I'm seeing.
seeing a room full
of human bodies half-open,
- scattered and forgotten about.
- They're unclaimed bodies.
Unclaimed.
Each one of these
people was loved.
Each one of these people
was somebody's somebody.
So we are responsible
for treating them as such.
We claim them and
treat them with respect!
Close them up, cover them up
and put them back
where they belong.
Now!
The wife's here of the beating
victim. She ID'd her husband.
What's his name?
I wondered if you asked his name
so that he could
become a person to you.
They're all people. This
is not a game or a contest
or a competition to see who
gets surgery and who doesn't.
They're people, and
we get to save them.
Now, you're good.
You're excellent.
You can win all the contests.
If that's why you're doing
this, you shouldn't be.
Did you find out his name?
My dad died when I was
nine in a car accident.
I was with him in the car. While
we waited for the ambulance,
I tried to keep his chest closed
so he wouldn't bleed so much.
When he died...
my hands felt his
heart stop beating.
That's why I do this.
It's also why I win
all the contests.
The patient's name is Tom.
Single-malt Scotch.
We're born, we live, we die.
Sometimes, not
necessarily in that order.
Clear!
- Yes! You don't get to die!
- Nice job.
Oh, hi. Thanks. I, uh...
You know, he's just a robot.
I want to take back what I
said before about leaving.
I was overreacting.
I was just...
It was personal. I wondered
if you could forget about it?
Get some sleep, Dr. Hunt.
See you tomorrow.
- Chief?
- Good save, O'Malley.
Thank you.
We put things to rest...
only to have them rise up again.
I'm in.
♪ I separated my
heart from my head ♪
♪ To feel out what's inside ♪
"So, I ended my day with
a segmental colectomy."
- Oh, badass!
- Oh...
Sloan? Seriously?
Did you think we
would double-date?
I'm gonna take my pants
off, if you want to see...
Nope.
I'll see it later. I'm
gonna go downstairs.
So if death is not the end,
what can you count on anymore?
So how's your patient doing?
Well, he still needs a heart,
but I bought him some time.
- Good, I'm glad.
- I went to the chief
about Izzie
and he completely shut me down.
We'll see what he says
when I report this to UNOS.
Whoa. Whoa, whoa,
whoa. Wait, why?
What good would come of that?
- What do you mean?
- What possible good
would it do?
Benefit your patient's outcome?
My patient wouldn't be
here, if it wasn't for her.
Your gonna report to UNOS and cost
this hospital its transplant certification?
Cost our patients organs,
cost people their jobs,
- cost Izzie Stevens her career?
- You're taking Izzie's side?
- Over mine?
- She's a doctor,
one of our doctors.
There's a reason we
have each other's backs.
Do not talk to me about
a code. This is not that.
No, this is that. I don't
know what happened
between Denny and Izzie.
Unless you were in the
middle of that situation,
I don't see how you
make a judgment.
Easy. There's right and wrong.
And this was wrong. And illegal.
There is no gray area here.
You can't kind of think this is OK.
You can't kind of side
with Izzie Stevens.
And you can't
kind of be a lesbian.
Yes, I can.
Because you sure can't
count on anything in life.
- I can't believe I didn't know.
- The chief is right.
No, you.
I don't know you at all.
Life is the most fragile, unstable,
unpredictable thing there is.
♪ It's not OK to make you
wait to make you wonder why ♪
♪ I can't hold you
close or give you hope ♪
♪ That this will be all right ♪
♪ I wanna make it right ♪
No... No.
♪ I've gotta figure this out ♪
You can't be here.
I have to move on.
I love you, and I will always
love you, but I have to move on.
That's why I had that patient today
and that's why I helped save his life.
So I wouldn't feel
guilty anymore,
and I can move on. So, please...
- you have to go.
- Go where?
- Are you OK?
- Yes. Yes.
I am totally OK.
I'm fine. Everything's fine.
I have to change but I'll
meet you at the bar, OK?
OK.
In fact, there's only one thing
about life we can be sure of.
Are you sure you're OK?
It ain't over, till it's over.