Previously on Grey's Anatomy:
If anyone should be celibate,
it's Meredith.
I'm Finn Dandridge. I'm Doc's vet.
I'm off men. No more men.
You brought the baby to work?
I'm covered in mommy.
But I will not be mommy tracked.
You're his doctor, Izzie,
and he's your half-dead,
possibly soon to be all-dead, patient.
You should see them.
They're running and cooking and talking.
They're bonding.
George O'Malley is sweet and kind.
- You live here?
- I'm not crazy.
I just spend so much time here
in the hospital.
Holy crap. George is her McDreamy.
The key to being
a successful intern is what we give up.
Sleep, friends, a normal life.
We sacrifice it all
for that one amazing moment.
That moment when you can
legally call yourself a surgeon.
Thank you.
Oh, thank you, thank you, thank you.
Thanks.
There are days that make the sacrifices
seem worthwhile.
Oh, my God. You're thanking me
for the most boring sex ever?
I didn't know what else to say.
I mean, you did your best.
Oh, great. Thanks. You too.
It's really nice work.
We used to be
really good at this, didn't we?
We're going to do this
until we get it right. Ow! Jeez!
- Perfect. Ow!
- Hospital.
Hello? Hi. No, no, no, no. No.
It's about Doc.
Yeah. No, I'm here.
Yeah, I can pick him up this morning.
Sure. Bye. No. Come on.
Dr. Dandridge. Dr. Dandridge. I...
We'll call you back. We're trying really
hard to have some decent sex here.
Come on. What's so funny?
And then there are the days
where everything feels like a sacrifice.
- Everything OK?
- Yeah. Everything's great.
Hey, Doc. You look good. He looks good.
It may just be a virus. But I'd like
to wait for the blood tests to be sure.
So he can go home today?
Derek says he can pick him up.
- He can go home.
- You hear that, Doc? You can go home.
So you and Derek, uh... you're together?
Uh...
Uh, Derek and I are, um, just friends.
He's married and I'm knitting a sweater.
And, uh, well, I guess I'm rambling,
which I tend to do a lot of lately,
and I wish somebody
would just tell me to shut up.
But my point is... yeah, we're... uh...
He's married and I'm knitting a sweater.
- So you're single?
- Single.
I ask because I was wondering
if you'd like to go out with me.
- Out. With you.
- On a date. Tonight.
A date. Tonight.
And you're repeating everything I say
so that you can buy yourself some time
and figure out how a way
to let me down easy. It's OK. I get it.
No. No. I... I... um...
you know, you're very...
It's just that if I were, you would...
Not dating.
Then there are the sacrifices that you
can't even figure out why you're making.
Another day, and once again
I don't see my name on the board.
Chief, any reason
my name isn't on the board?
Slow day.
He just patted me on the back.
Tell me, when did I become a person
who gets patted on the back?
You think he's mommy tracking you?
What... What have you heard?
How about you handle Denny Duquette
for me today?
Absolutely. Thank you, Dr. Burke.
- I brought you a coffee.
- Oh, thanks. Uh, very thoughtful.
- What?
- Nothing. I'm just dragging a little.
Only did two miles this morning.
O'Malley and I were up to six.
- Oh, you're missing George.
- No. No, of course not.
- Drink your coffee.
- No, that's all right.
- Actually...
- Cappuccino!
Hey, O'Malley!
Big news. Eugene Foote is here.
He's having problems with his pacemaker.
- Here? What? In this hospital?
- Uh-huh.
Who's Eugene Foote?
Genius violinist? Burke's hero?
Burke flew down to San Francisco
to put in his pacemaker.
- Burke has 40 of his albums.
- No. Um, 42.
No, 43. You just got the greatest hits.
The one with the DVD.
- Oh! Right. You want in on Foote?
- Yes.
But, uh, I'm on neuro today
with Dr. Shepherd.
I want in! Hello! I want in!
Hmm? Oh. Sure. Yeah, right.
Burke? Um, I laid on top of you
naked last night.
So why don't you wax nostalgic
about that?
Obviously, I can't
go out with him, right?
Do I look like a chick to you?
Do I look like I care about yeast cream
or tingling feelings?
I mean, he's not in jail or on drugs
or keeping body parts in his basement.
- You want to do him, do him.
- Not do him. Date him.
I'm not doing anybody. I'm knitting.
I need Eugene Foote's chart.
Oh! Who are we talking about?
It's weird, right? I mean,
he's Derek's vet. He's Doc's vet.
He's my vet. He's McVet.
It's weird to date him, right?
- Wait, did you say vet?
- Mm-hmm.
Like animals? Oh, you can't date a vet.
He's not even a real doctor.
Damn it!
Sex. Hot sex. Need that!
Ha-ha, very funny.
- Mustn't have gone well this morning.
- What?
Just run if she looks at you.
I need an intern. Now.
- I'm with Bailey.
- I'm with Burke.
Karev.
I don't do vagina.
Not as a doctor anyway.
Oh. Back talk. You know what?
You just bought yourself a case.
- How are you feeling today, Denny?
- Great.
Be even greater
if you'd get me off this machine.
Denny, you know I would,
but then your heart would stop beating,
and Dr. Burke would yell at me
and that'd be a bad day for both of us.
Is he a candidate for the portable LVAD?
Now, see? That's what I'm talking about.
Half the size, twice the fun.
- You been doing your research, huh?
- I have.
I've already told him,
he's not ready for it yet.
Dr. Stevens, didn't I assign you
to neuro this morning?
Yeah. I was... I'm on my way. But could
you tell him about the complications?
You'd be risking air embolus, v-fib.
The tubing could kink
inside your body,
and we'd have to rush you
to emergency surgery.
Dr. Stevens, unless Mr. Duquette's heart
has suddenly grown a brain,
- you are currently not doing your job.
- I'm going.
- Just don't be stupid, OK?
- You're not the boss of me now, woman.
- I want you to take it out.
- Take it out?
But your heart function has improved
exponentially since we put it in.
- The setting is working well.
- You know my music, Dr. Burke.
Very well, sir. Changed my life.
Well, your contraption
has changed my heartbeat.
It changed my rhythm. I can't play.
And that's a sacrifice
I am unwilling to make.
But you'd be willing to sacrifice
your life for your music?
They're one and the same.
Before we do anything drastic,
just let me try one more setting
on the pacemaker.
Listen, one more setting, Mr. Foote.
Please.
OK, sure.
- Hello, Wards.
- Hi.
We're just waiting on your labs.
How you feeling?
I'm feeling large.
- Large and cow-like.
- Cow?
Mommy is a cow
who needs a quiet talk with the doctor.
- Hey, guys. Who wants ice cream?
- Me! Me!
CBC and CHEM-7 look fine.
Rose?
I'm sorry.
I'm so tired.
Well, you know,
six kids, 38 weeks pregnant.
- A saint would be tired.
- Well... I'm no saint.
This baby, Joseph...
Dr. Shepherd, I need him to be my last.
And I really seem to be
the most fertile woman on the planet.
If you're interested
in other forms of birth control...
No. What I mean is...
today, during the C-section,
I need you to tie my tubes.
And I need you to do it
without my husband ever knowing.
Rose, you're an adult. He's your
husband, not your legal guardian.
Telling him would be entirely up to you.
No, if you charged my insurance
he would see it.
Any bill you sent, he would see it.
I've been saving for this
and I can pay you privately.
So you're saying you want me to do the
surgery and leave no record of it?
Mrs. Ward, if you're being abused,
there are people you can talk to.
Oh. Chris is...
He's the opposite of abusive.
If we pull up your medical records
we won't find broken bones or...
If you pull up my medical records,
you'll find three natural child births,
three C-sections,
two hospital stays for exhaustion,
and one for dehydration because
I was so busy chasing my kids around
I forgot to take a sip of water
for three days.
I think God understands
what I'm going through.
And I think God will forgive me.
But Chris... For him,
religion isn't like a buffet table
where you get to choose what
you want to take and leave the rest.
And the Pope says no to birth control,
so... I need your help.
You don't need our help.
He's not abusing you.
And you don't get to lie to him
and blame it on the Pope.
Dr. Karev.
No offense, but I have no interest
in obstetrics or gynecology.
So if you want to throw me off the case,
feel free.
Dr. Karev,
I may be a board-certified OBIG YN
but I also have fellowships
in maternal-fetal medicine
and medical genetics
and I'm one of the foremost
neonatal surgeons in this country.
When you can top that,
you can mouth off.
Until then, you will do your job
and you will do it right,
which at this point in time
means you keep your mouth shut
unless I give you permission to open it.
Understood?
- Understood?
- Oh, are you giving me permission now?
Good morning, Ms. Graber.
Oh, really? "Good morning?" You haven't
let me sleep in three nights.
This hat is destroying my self-esteem
and I haven't had a seizure.
But we'll go with "Good morning"
if it makes you feel better.
Ms. Graber is here for brain-mapping.
Dr. Stevens?
Brain mapping is where you locate
the area of the brain
where the seizures originate and remove
it with minimal damage to tissue.
Excellent.
Except for the fact that it's not
working, and I'm losing billable hours.
Unless any of you are looking
to get out of a bad marriage?
- No.
- Dr. Shepherd?
Yes. No. I'm fine, thank you.
- Really?
- Yes.
- I'm a good divorce attorney.
- I'm sure.
And there was a look.
Between these two.
- A look?
- No. No look.
What is it? You married young
and now you have nothing in common?
Oh, no, don't tell me. I know.
The conversation is still good
but the sex has gone to pot.
Make her seize? How do we
make someone have a seizure?
Get creative.
If all the normal methods have failed,
then... what are we supposed to do?
Use a strobe light. Get her drunk.
Hang her from the ceiling
and hit her with a Wiffle Ball bat.
Make her seize.
I don't know where to operate.
That means I can't get her
out of my life.
And this woman
is not how I like to start my mornings.
I'm just curious, George.
Curious George.
Get it?
Never mind.
All I'm asking is where you live.
There's an old-school arcade game
that's been known to induce seizures
if you reach level 53.
Our divorce lawyer is so not playing
an arcade game for 53 levels.
Oh, George, by the way,
um, where do you live?
I'm busy doctoring, Dr. Stevens.
No time for chitchat.
Morning, Dr. O'Malley.
Uh... morning, Dr. Torres.
Hmm. So, guess what.
Yes.
Dr. O'Malley,
how's all the doctoring going?
You tell me.
It's an honor to hear you play.
Too good a man to lie.
I'll read your mind: His timing is off.
His rhythm is off.
This man has no business
calling himself Eugene Foote.
You understand, sir, that in the months
since the initial surgery,
scar tissue has formed
around the pacemaker.
Removing it is not nearly
as simple as it sounds.
I picked up the violin at six years old.
It was in my grandfather's attic.
I didn't even know what it was.
But I remember picking it up.
That moment.
I remember putting the bow
to the strings and pulling.
Just that.
Just that screechy little chirp.
And that was it. I was hooked.
You remember a moment like that
in your life?
I know this surgery could kill me.
I also know you're the best,
which makes you
my best shot of survival.
I'd like you to be the one to operate,
Dr. Burke.
But if you won't,
I'll find someone who will.
He's right.
What? He can't play?
He can't play like Eugene Foote.
OK. So, uh, surgery?
He says he will go somewhere else
if I refuse. I might let him.
Why?
Oh, you can't let him
go somewhere else. What are you?
OK, what if it were you?
What if you couldn't
be a surgeon anymore?
Or... Or you could still be one,
but... but not a great one.
Just average. He can get his surgery
somewhere else.
But that surgeon might be average.
EKG, ECHO, and nuclear
all within normal limits.
Denny, in that case, I see no reason
why you can't be up walking.
- Music to my ears, Dr. Bailey.
- Good. So, you have any questions?
- No. It's...
- We can put it off.
No harm in waiting a few weeks if
you have questions. If you're worried.
I've got 20 tubes coming out of my body,
one of which goes directly
into my you-know-what.
At some point I'd like to use
that you-know-what
for something besides peeing into a bag.
Like, for instance,
peeing into a toilet.
It's just...
Izzie gave me medical advice.
You're giving me different advice.
It just so happens that yours
is the advice I want to hear.
Well, Dr. Bailey outranks Dr. Stevens.
So, it's safe to say Dr. Bailey's advice
is the one to follow.
That's not what he's worried about,
Dr. Grey.
He's worried that Dr. Stevens
might get her ego bruised
and her feelings hurt, am I right?
No, no. Definitely no.
It would concern me
if you were making medical decisions
based on how
our Dr. Stevens might feel about it.
Well, in that case,
I say we do this thing.
Screw that dizzy blonde doctor girl.
That's not helping, Denny.
- No?
- No.
What's going on
between Stevens and Denny?
Is it a crush?
Is it an innocent flirtation?
Or is Stevens crossing the line?
I know she likes him.
I can't imagine Izzie would do that.
Uh-huh.
I couldn't imagine you and Yang'd be so
stupid as to fall for your attendings,
but I was wrong about that, wasn't I?
I'm knitting these days.
Plus, I may accept a date
with a veterinarian.
Grey. Do you actually believe I care?
- No.
- Good. Maybe you're not so stupid.
Explain one more time
exactly what this is supposed to do.
Having the TV this close
makes the flickering and flashing
more intense, which can cause seizures.
Oh. Normally I don't have time to watch
TV, but this week I've discovered Oprah.
She's famous in my business for
never marrying that boyfriend of hers.
Wise, wise woman.
You won't say where you live and now
I'm on the outside of your inside jokes.
- When did I end up on the outside?
- You're not.
- Now you're lying. To my face.
- You're being paranoid.
Well, I'm not seizing. But I am having
an acid flashback. Does that count?
Rose... Seven kids... It's a lot.
Are you sure that Chris
isn't feeling the same way?
When we were first married, we were
so broke that I went on the pill.
Chris stopped taking Communion.
When he does that, he thinks he's...
Thinks he's going to hell.
He thinks you're both going to hell.
The reason we haven't had a baby
in four years
is because we abstained for three.
Now can you imagine not being able
to make love to your husband?
Um... the, uh... pill...
I can't hide the pill.
He would find out.
If he found out, what? I mean, he won't
divorce you. He doesn't believe in it.
- See the way he's looking at me?
- Dr. Karev was just leaving.
No, no, no.
Just... just look at him for a minute.
That look he has on his face,
that's how my husband would look at me
if he knew about any of this.
And I can't have my husband
look at me like that.
And I can't have any more babies.
For the record? I am on your side today.
George sucks.
Hmm. Burke doesn't think so.
He's his new best friend.
I wonder if Burke knows where he lives.
How's Denny doing? Bailey's not
caving in on the LVAD thing, is she?
About that...
I thought Alex was kidding when he
said you dumped him for a heart patient.
- Did you dump him for a patient?
- Of course not.
Because Denny's a patient.
We can't fall for our patients.
You're falling for a vet.
I'm considering the possibility
of maybe having a date with a vet.
That's all I'm saying.
My point is, Bailey's on the warpath
about you and Denny. So just be careful.
How's the sponge count, Dr. Karev?
They're all accounted for,
but I see a bleeder here.
It's small.
Get the Bovie and cauterize it.
- I got it.
- That's good.
Uh, there's a little bleeding
near the tube here.
Can you hand me the Bovie, Dr. Karev?
I don't see any abnormal bleeding.
Are you the surgeon here?
- No.
- Then give me the Bovie.
Give me the Bovie, Dr. Karev.
Hey there, Joseph. Welcome to the world.
Rose, before we bring
your family in to see you,
I wanted to let you know that there was
a complication with your surgery.
We had some unexpected bleeding that
caused damage to both fallopian tubes.
So you're saying?
You won't be able to have
any more children.
Thank you, Dr. Shepherd.
As I said, it was... a complication.
I understand.
A complication?
That's what you're calling it?
That's what it was.
One of the most bizarre
obstetric complications ever.
She is our patient.
Our obligation is to her and her only.
- Hey.
- Well, hey.
- Uh, you picked up Doc?
- Yeah. He's home.
- He seems to be doing much better.
- He seems to be doing good.
- I'm not laughing at you.
- No.
No, it's just, you know,
bad sex isn't really something
that wives want announced
to the dirty ex-mistress.
You're not the dirty ex-mistress.
She's your friend. I'm your friend.
We're all... friends.
But you didn't tell her.
No.
How's your day going?
- Great.
- Good.
The vet asked me if we...
- What? What did he ask you?
- If we were together.
- Uh-huh.
- And I set him straight.
- Good day, Meredith.
- You too, Derek.
I'm not drinking another espresso.
I can't.
You can. You're the best
divorce attorney in Seattle.
- The best.
- You can kick that espresso's ass.
- Kick it.
Kick it. Kick. Yeah!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
OK, good. So, caffeine's for seizures.
What's the doughnuts for?
To absorb some of the coffee so
it doesn't burn a hole in your stomach.
Good. OK, good idea.
Mm. Oh. Do you know how long it has
been since I have had a doughnut?
I really, really, really, really, really
like doughnuts.
Why don't you eat them?
Got to stay on top of my game. No time
for exercise. No carbs. No sugar.
Can't have a sugar crash in court.
You know, stupid court!
Court is stupid
because I love doughnuts!
You're making really good progress.
Hey there, Chief.
You here for my big moment?
Yeah, I'm looking forward to it, Denny.
Is there something
I can do for you, Chief?
- His EKG?
- Normal.
- As well as his ECHO and nuclear study.
- Mm-hmm. His perfusion?
He's ready, Chief.
Well, looking good. Carry on.
Thank you, sir.
Die! Die! Oh, yeah! Oh, yeah!
Next level. I'm at the next level.
- God, this is exhilarating!
- Good. Keep going.
Only 12 more levels before
you reach prime seizure potential.
This is fun. Yeah, right? You know?
Like fun that we had at home
back when you used to tell me things.
- Like where you live?
- Don't start that again.
I'm just saying,
there's fun to be had.
All the time with me. Your best friend.
It's not like we're in high school.
Don't do the whispering
under your breath thing.
- If you got something to say, say it.
- Last time you said that it went well.
You're pissed at me because
of what happened with Meredith?
No. Yeah.
Oh. He recorded this at
the Hollywood Bowl a couple years ago.
It's nice.
It's not nice. It's brilliant.
Excuse me. You were one of my wife's
doctors, weren't you? Rose Ward?
Yes, I was.
She just told me there was
a complication with her C-section.
I told you to tell her how you feel,
not to jump into bed with her.
- Whatever you told me.
- Adultery.
Why did you send me in there?
Was it to humiliate me?
If you knew she didn't love me.
What kind of friend does that?
It's just... It was shocking.
Someone says there's a complication
and everything changes.
I... can't... breathe.
- Are all those batteries...
- Yes, they're charged. I checked them.
- He's having runs of V-tach.
- Could be an air embolism.
We got to tamponade.
- BP's not registering.
- Keep transfusing PRBCs.
He has a full ventricular perforation.
Hand me a 20 prolene. Cristina.
Replace my hand with yours.
Yes. And hold on for dear life.
- You didn't want to hear it.
- Yes, I...
- Oh, some denial. I can work with that.
- You wanted to keep on loving her.
- Should we intubate?
- We'll call respiratory to do it.
Rose says it's a blessing.
It's God's will. Maybe it is.
Maybe it is. A blessing, I mean.
This complication.
- His heart's not moving.
- Keep compressing as I was.
No signs of life.
Blood pressure is nonexistent.
- OK, the tubing could be kinked.
- I got this.
- It doesn't look like you've got this.
- I've got this!
Oh, my God! You knew the risks!
- That she was in love with someone.
- I'm getting an aura.
No! I am not saying
that what she did wasn't wrong.
- You need to take...
- She's seizing! Go page Shepherd.
This complication might be God's way
of helping you
- put your seven kids through college.
- What are you saying?
I'm saying get a lawyer.
Time of death: 18:32.
Everything looks good, Denny.
Well, you got to thank Dr. Bailey
for me.
I already thanked her once,
but this here deserves a double-scoop.
I know I don't know you very well.
You want to talk to me about Izzie?
Yeah.
- Because you disapprove?
- No.
This comes from nothing
resembling a high horse.
High horses want nothing to do with me.
You know,
this thing with you and Izzie, it's...
There are strict rules
about doctors dating patients.
You know Izzie pretty well, right?
You think if I went to her and I said,
"Hey, you know, this is going to be
really bad for your career. "
"You probably shouldn't
come and see me anymore,"
You think that'll have
any effect at all?
The thing is, I was healthy
my whole life until I wasn't.
And for the last year, I've had
a lot of time to lay around in bed
and think about my life.
And the things that I remember best?
Well, those are the things that I wasn't
supposed to do and I did them anyway.
So the thing is, Meredith...
life is too damn short
to be following these rules.
May I ask what motive you had
for undermining my authority
- in front of my patient and intern?
- I'm not punishing you, Dr. Bailey.
But you are.
I mean, I had a baby. And so you are.
And now you're sleep deprived.
Every doctor here is sleep deprived.
You just came back from maternity leave,
and I'm not convinced
you're on your game.
This is not a punishment or a reflection
on how highly I value you.
It's just the way it is.
I'm sorry to interrupt, Chief.
That man is asking to talk to you.
Excuse me.
We're closed.
Hey.
I thought you were knitting a sweater.
I am. But I'm also dating.
You. If you still want to.
- I should've called. I was going to...
- No, no.
Uh... don't call. Never call.
Always show up.
- OK.
But I can't tonight.
I've got an errand I have to run.
I run errands.
This shouldn't take long.
We can grab dinner after.
- After?
- After she gives birth.
- We're birthing a horse?
- Yeah.
That was your errand?
You're birthing a horse?
Yeah. I guess I could've
mentioned it before.
But I didn't want to scare you
back to your knitting.
She's getting anxious.
You can wait back here.
- Back here?
- If you want. It gets a little messy.
Are you kidding?
I want to birth a horse.
Richard,
we have to talk about Alex Karev.
I know he's talented,
but his attitude, in my opinion,
has reached an unacceptable low.
Addison.
You've got a bigger problem today
than Alex Karev.
Mr. Ward has been speaking with our
attorney regarding his wife's surgery.
Now I read your chart.
I read the nurse's notes.
Now, can you explain to me what kind
of complication from a C-section
leads to the severing
of both fallopian tubes?
Well, the bad news is...
you had a grand mal seizure.
The good news is we mapped it,
so now we can operate.
No. I've decided against surgery,
Dr. Shepherd.
- I'm sorry?
- No offense.
The risks of craniotomy... when you
explained, they're not very appealing.
Yes, there are risks.
But you have to weigh those risks
with the detrimental effect
your seizures have on your life.
Unless my life is having a detrimental
effect on my seizure disorder.
With you and your wife:
Is the bad sex your big problem
or are all the bigger problems
causing the bad sex?
I'm, uh... I'm not going to answer that.
All right, my point is, I had more fun
today than I can remember.
I don't have any friends.
I don't have any fun. I only have work.
Work and seizures.
It's no coincidence that when the
work stopped, the seizures stopped.
- Until these two started arguing.
- I'll talk to them about that.
No, you don't get it.
Watching people fight... Oh.
It's been my whole life for 15 years.
So, I'm changing my life.
If that doesn't work, I'll come back
here and let you cut open my brain, OK?
All right. Fair enough.
- It's pretty good, huh?
- Yeah, it's pretty good.
- How're you feeling?
- A little sore.
Oh, that's to be expected.
I'm sorry I told Chris
about the complication.
I just... I just thought he should know
that Joseph would be our last.
So he could savor it.
I didn't know he was going to do this.
Rose.
I need you to tell him
that you asked me to tie your tubes.
For you, it's just insurance.
And you don't even have to pay. For me,
it's my marriage. It's my family.
It's my career, Rose.
It's my reputation.
You're the best. People come
from all over the country to see you.
That won't change.
I can't tell him.
Dr. Shepherd... I'm so sorry
because I am so grateful to you.
But I can't tell him.
Is it coming off?
Not exactly.
- I'm sorry.
- Oh, don't be. It was a great date.
Technically it wasn't the date.
It was the errand.
Now... we could go up to my place.
I could cook for you.
Go up to your place?
Well, do you want
to come up to my place?
Yeah. I mean, no.
No, I don't. I... I do. But I don't.
- You don't know?
- No, I do. I mean, I... I know.
No, I don't.
All right, well, here's the deal.
Um... you have two options.
You could come up to my place,
take off all your clothes,
shower off the goo, borrow a shirt,
and I'll cook dinner.
That's door number one.
Door number two... you go home.
I think you ought to take door one.
It involves you naked in my apartment.
But, you know... that's just me.
I should point out that there's
absolutely nothing you could say
that would make me go upstairs with you.
I'm kind of offended that you think
that I would go upstairs with you.
And you should know
that I am celibate. So...
Shut up.
I absolutely cannot have...
sex with you.
If you choose door number one,
I absolutely will not have sex with you.
- You won't?
- I promise I won't.
- I won't even try to kiss you.
- Why not?
- Meredith.
- What?
Choose door number one.
A wise man once said,
"You can have anything in life,
if you will sacrifice
everything else for it. "
I hope it works. You changing your life.
So do I.
OK.
Hey, George.
I don't know much,
but I do know fighting.
And people who fight like you and
Izzie... those people love each other.
She misses her friend.
What he meant is,
nothing comes without a price.
The road to hell
is paved with good intentions.
So before you go into battle, you better
decide how much you're willing to lose.
Dr. Karev.
You did such a good job today
that I'm going to talk to Dr. Bailey
and have you assigned to my service.
- What? For how long?
- For as long as I want.
Your ass is mine until I say otherwise.
Congratulations.
You got it.
I did indeed.
And you're OK?
Are you kidding me? I'm great.
I mean look at this. Some
nice-sized batteries. Colorful wires.
It's what your best-dressed LVAD
patients are wearing these days.
Really? Because it seems so last fall.
You're tall.
I know.
Too often, going after what feels good,
means letting go
of what you know is right.
You did everything you could.
There was an interview that Eugene gave.
I saved it.
I taped it to my bathroom mirror.
He said that he wasn't the most
talented student at music school.
But he said what he lacked
in natural ability
he made up for in discipline.
He practiced.
All the time.
All the time, he practiced.
I wasn't like you.
I wasn't the most talented student
in school.
I wasn't the brightest.
But I was the best.
You practiced.
I practiced.
And letting someone in
means abandoning the walls
you've spent a lifetime building.
He was listless
and hadn't eaten all day.
Oh, no. Let's have a look.
Of course the toughest sacrifices
are the ones we don't see coming.
Hey.
- Is he sick again?
- Yeah.
- George! Hey.
- Hey.
- Oh, hi.
So we spent the night at Callie's
last night,
so we figured
we'd just spend the night here.
Um, OK. So, um... you're back then
just... for tonight?
Well, Callie's here for the night.
I'm, uh... I don't know.
It's my room, you know. I pay rent.
Welcome home.
When we don't have time
to come up with a strategy,
to pick a side
or to measure the potential loss.
You would not believe the day I had.
I went out of my way to give a patient
exactly what she wants,
only to have it explode in my face.
I mean, lawsuit, threats.
Richard's pissed.
- Don't get me started about Alex Karev.
- Get in the shower.
- What?
- Get in the shower with me.
- Honey, it's a very small shower.
- You want to have hot sex?
Thank you!
When that happens,
when the battle chooses us,
and not the other way around,
that's when the sacrifice can turn out
to be more than we can bear.
www.tvsubtitles.net