Previously on Grey's Anatomy:
Can I have the key back?
Heard we broke up, I want it back.
- Can I have it, please?
- You find an apartment yet?
'Cause I was thinking
about getting one.
Can you make sure I
stay on Dr. Hahn's cardio?
Where are guys going? You
going to Joe's? I'll meet you.
I can't sleep. What's
wrong with me?
- Severe abandonment issues.
- Psych is crap.
- Derek kissed Rose?
- Yesterday we were dating
other people.
- That's not the point. Rose is?
- You weren't ready.
Do you want to go to dinner?
We like to think that
we are rational beings.
- ♪ Walking in the corner ♪
- Humane.
- ♪ Peeking over shoulders ♪
- Conscientious.
♪ Waiting for my time to come ♪
- ♪ Walking in the corner ♪
- Civilized.
♪ One day to the other ♪
♪ Butter for my piece of bun ♪
Thoughtful.
♪ Stepping, I'm stompin' ♪
This is your third session.
And you still haven't
said anything yet.
Now, while I love
the quiet time, um...
I read a study that, uh...
says that just the act of
going to therapy is beneficial,
even if you don't say
anything. Even if you just sit.
You thought you'd
come here and just sit?
- That solves your problems?
- I don't have problems.
What brings you here?
But when things fall apart,
even just a little,
it becomes clear. We're
no better than animals.
♪ And if you say I'm not OK ♪
♪ If you say there ain't
no way that I could know ♪
- ♪ If you say I aim too high
from down below ♪
- It's not that bad.
Once we get rid of the
roaches, the apartment...
No, the crapartment.
George, this is our
home. We'll fix it up.
With what money?
We'll figure it
out. I like it here.
I would like it here more if
you would like it here, too.
♪ And I'm hanging
around 'til it's all done ♪
We have opposable thumbs.
Look, I'm fine.
It's just... I just
haven't been sleeping.
You know, it's just been
five weeks and I can't sleep.
Five weeks since what?
♪ I'm working, I
sweat, but it's all good ♪
♪ I'm breaking my
back but it's all good ♪
Look, I work in this hospital.
I try not to listen to gossip,
but this is a very
gossipy place.
There are things
that I've heard.
Derek's not the reason I'm here.
- He's not the reason.
- Then what brings you here?
♪ Well, say you're not
'cause when I'm gone ♪
♪ You'll be callin' but I
won't be at the phone ♪
You know, I got to
go. I'm in this contest.
Dr. Grey, if you...
We think.
♪ And if you say I'm not OK ♪
We walk erect.
I'm up!
We speak.
♪ If you say I aim too
high from down below ♪
We dream.
But deep down we're
all still rooting around
in the primordial ooze.
Biting, clawing,
scratching out an existence
in the cold dark world
like the rest of the
tree toads and sloths.
- ♪ I won't be at the phone ♪
- Oh!
There's a contest going on.
- Sir?
- Your residents.
They've been living in the
hospital around-the-clock
for the last 14 days.
Engaged in a surgical
contest. With a point system.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
They are committed.
It's commitment.
- It's a lion fight.
- OK, I have one baby
to get to daycare.
I have 50 residents on my watch.
Four surgeries on my schedule.
The lions can fight all they
want. I'm not a zookeeper.
Keep your animals under control.
Yes, sir. Keep the
animals under control.
- Ooh!
- Move it!
- She's wretched. And mean.
- No, she's not.
I heard nurses saying
they've only been on five dates.
'Cause Derek knows
she's wretched and mean.
- Yeah.
- What did you do to your hair?
You guys. I know you're
trying to make me feel better
but I have to tell you,
this pausing to talk about
Rose and Derek just means...
Yeah?
- I'm going to win!
- You bitch!
Ow! What?
Keeping it clean was
getting in the way,
so I chopped it off.
It makes me faster and
sleeker like a cheetah.
You chopped your
hair for a stupid contest?
Not stupid. Rock star
contest. Best contest ever.
Try living in the hospital
for two weeks. It's amazing.
- This contest is for residents.
- Yes, I know that!
It doesn't mean he can't live
here. I feel juiced and alive,
my brain is running. I have
never been more on my game.
I'm kind of sad the
contest ends tonight.
- I'm not. I want that prize.
- What prize?
Bailey won't tell
us. But I want it bad.
- Too bad you're never
going to get it.
- So on my game!
- What?
- Yeah. Hi.
Morning. Thank you.
What do you see in
her? Is it the hot sex?
Is she an animal?
Is she a bobcat?
- Mark.
- Come on.
Lady on the streets,
tramp in the sheets?
Oh, yeah. She's
amazing. Hot. Sweaty.
Very dirty, hot, sweaty sex.
You haven't slept with her yet?
She's waiting until we're
serious. She has morals, a lady.
- Know what's better than sex?
- What?
Anticipation.
Anticipation, my friend.
Why didn't anybody wake me?
Why would we help you?
- There's such a thing as honor.
- Dog-eat-dog, Karev.
- Suck it up.
- I'm not doing that.
- You are going to.
- I'm not.
- Callie, Callie. Callie!
- Oh, hey.
- You came in with Dr. Hahn?
- Erica? Yeah.
We went out last night
and then it got kind of late
with the dancing and the...
We never made it home,
so hitched a ride here.
- Hanging out with Dr. Hahn?
- Erica. Yes.
So, you and Hahn are friends?
Erica. Yeah.
See, this is the
downside of the contest.
I'm here, Callie's
living in my apartment
- and hanging out with Hahn.
- They're picking up guys.
I'm past that. I
don't need guys.
I don't need sex.
Competition is my orgasm.
I could be hanging
out with Hahn.
Cristina, would you focus?
It is more fun kicking
your ass when you focus.
- Who's winning?
- Yang.
- Surprised?
- What?
Let me see.
I'm 26 points behind?
That's not possible.
Count again. What
about surgeries?
Three points for
watching. Got to do.
I do do. I can't make
them let me do procedures.
- You got to ask.
- Take charge of
your own destiny.
Make it happen. Like this.
- What do you got?
- Otis Sharon, 61 year-old male,
unconscious on a corner
with a swollen ankle.
Not it.
- I don't know what happened.
- - Initial BP was 90 over palp.
Vitals stable after
a bolus of NS.
OK, he's mine!
All of you back off!
- It's a swollen ankle.
- He passed out.
He's pale, altered, and a rash.
You see a sprained ankle,
I see a medical mystery.
Eighty points.
Stevens is the only one working?
No. We're all
working. We got paged.
The ankle's gone. You
trolling for traumas?
Somebody could come
with a critical injury.
We're proactive.
- We're helping people.
- You're trolling.
I've got no one on
post-op and pre-op. Move!
- Help us! Please help!
- Help my brother!
I'm getting a gurney!
He's bleeding.
- What happened?
- A bear.
- A what?
- He tried to stop the bleeding.
- We were camping.
- You drove here?
Couldn't wait for an
ambulance. I'm fine.
No, you're not. Let
me see your hand.
I'm fine.
- Sir, let's get on this gurney.
- Careful.
OK. Step down
right here. All right.
- Careful.
- Slowly.
Whoa! Whoa!
Intestines in the hands!
- Did you just say...
- Intestine in the hands!
He just touched it. He
just put his hand out.
- And he touched a bear?
- A cub.
And then the mother came.
- I bet she did.
- Why would he do that?
We go camping
all the time. Why...
OK, try to relax, Mr. Robinson.
All right, get me a
chest tube tray, please.
- Did I hear bear attack?
- Complete evisceration.
Get me 100 sux, 20 of etomidate.
Get me an intubation
tray and an OR room now.
You going to put me under?
Sir, it'll be the best thing
that's happened to you all day.
Is my brother going
to be OK? Please.
This whole thing's my
fault. I got to know if he's OK.
They're taking him to
surgery. They don't know.
- We'll keep you informed.
- OK. OK.
Impressive hand, Phillip.
I can see through it.
The bear cub, she just
latched on and wouldn't let go.
When Scott came
over to try to help,
the mother she...
I can't believe
we got out alive.
He has to be all right.
He's going to be all right.
He has to be, right? Right?
He has to be all right.
You don't remember how you fell?
One minute I was
walking down the street,
the next, there were
paramedics over me.
Have you been dizzy?
Like the room is spinning?
Maybe a little.
Any muscle aches?
Fatigue? Fever? Headaches?
Well, now that
you mention it, yes.
Any recent travels?
Well, I go back and forth
to the East Coast for my job.
- Does that count?
- Tick or mosquito bites?
I live near a lake.
I get mosquito
bites all the time.
Oh, God, do I have
something bad, like malaria
- West Nile virus or something?
- Oh, no, no.
There's no need to panic.
We're going to take this
one step at a time. OK?
OK.
Mama Bear wasn't messing around.
Mama bears never mess around.
I have a Ross procedure,
but I want to keep an eye
on his chest tube outputs
and blood pressure.
What's the game plan?
He's a set up for
overwhelming sepsis.
Deal with the life-threatening
blood loss, get out.
You can't touch
him until he's stable.
I'm in OR four. Can
I get hourly updates?
I'd be happy to apprise
you of his condition.
Fine.
You don't get points
for sucking up, Yang.
Shut up.
I hate this contest.
There's a lot of stuff in here.
Stupid, stupid contest.
Stupid. Irresponsible.
I wanna play!
- Good, free stuff.
- I need a butterfly needle,
a Vacutainer, and
maybe an LP kit.
I'm 26 points behind
so I need it fast.
- Why? You got something good?
- A sprained ankle.
26 points for a sprained ankle?
Callie treated what we
thought was a sprained ankle,
patient was malnourished,
had a perforated ulcer and died.
That's the best case scenario.
Not the death part, the
medical mystery part.
80 points for solving
a medical mystery.
The holy grail of
the competition.
Oh, yeah. Sometimes an
ankle's just an ankle though.
Syncope, a very strange rash,
pale, insidious onset in
a guy who travels a lot,
this is not just an ankle!
Oh. Thanks.
Oh, I could do a lot with these.
That's an underpad.
Underpads soak up urine.
Or... it could be a placemat.
Oh! Fruit bowl!
Done. I beat you.
Busted hand and all.
- It's completely illegible.
- He's a slob.
- I still beat her.
- Mr. Robinson,
Dr. O'Malley is going to
come and take you to X-ray.
And I'm going to take your wife
to the waiting room
until you get back.
She said wife. Still
not used to that.
- We're newlyweds.
- Congratulations.
She's my rebound girl.
Um, he's a little hopped
up on pain killers right now.
- Over-sharing.
- She thought she was
my rebound girl,
but I rebounded her all
the way to the church.
Only knew her ten days.
But when you know,
you know. You know?
I'm leaving you.
I'll miss you while you're gone.
Ortho resident to the ER stat.
Are you OK?
It's just... you know,
you marry a man like that
or a man like that marries you.
And he's cute and he's rich...
he's a catch, by
anyone's standards.
So, you sit around waiting
for the other shoe to drop.
Because there's no way a
man like that marries you.
Or me.
He married me.
I'm sorry. I must look
like a crazy woman.
It's OK. But you're
bleeding a little.
Do you mind if I take a look?
Oh, no. I'm fine.
I just scratched myself on a
branch when we were running.
Why are you looking
at me like that?
CT's clear.
But it's deep. That
bear clawed you good.
I didn't even feel it.
Adrenaline's a
pretty powerful drug.
You have to repair the galea, it
should reattach without a problem.
Squeeze my fingers
as hard as you can.
I just got happy.
I just got married
and I'm happy.
I don't have permanent
brain damage, do I?
No. It appears that you do not.
OK, good.
Page me if any
neuro deficits appear.
You got lucky. Your scalp
wasn't completely taken off,
we can sew it on. Your
hair should cover the scar.
- You won't even need surgery.
- Wow. That's great. Thank you.
Dr. Grey will take care of you.
Go back to being
a happy newlywed.
Don't worry. He
and Rose won't last.
He's hypothermic and
his bowels are swollen.
We need to stabilize him in the
ICU and get him back to the OR
when he's less acidotic.
Gives us time to deal with
puncture wounds and lacerations.
I'm sorry, one of you has
several hundred sutures
- ahead of you.
- I'll do it!
- I need practice.
- Your stitches are flawless,
- I need the work.
- Flawless because I practice.
- Karev, it's yours.
- Yes.
- Come on.
- You need to update Hahn
on the condition of
the patient hourly.
A minute an hour. I can
suture the other fifty-nine.
Fine. You both do it.
That's not fair.
This man was a
chew toy for a bear.
There'll be enough to go around.
A lot of enthusiasm for
an afternoon of stitching.
Some people find it boring.
I value the fundamentals.
It's a point a suture. Kiss ass.
It is a hairline fracture.
CSR and CRP's were elevated.
I also appreciated some
swelling in the knee.
What does that mean?
There could be some sort of
inflammatory process going on.
- That sounds bad.
- I don't want you to worry yet.
- Yet?
- Is there someone I can call?
Maybe you shouldn't
be alone here.
Um... How are his labs?
WBC's normal, slightly anemic,
potassium's mildly decreased.
OK. Give him a K-rider,
see if you can tap
the fluid in his knee
for white cells or crystals.
Let me know if it's positive.
- Good luck, Mr. Sharon.
- You think I need luck?
Oh, God. I want to go home.
I want to go home.
Look, I want to go back!
I want to go back
to when I was 30
and I want to stop smoking.
Or back to when I was 20 and
not start smoking in first place.
I want to give up coffee
and junk food and beer
and I want to be healthy like my
ex-wife always nagged me to be.
She was a saint.
She was a saint
and I drove her away.
I want to go back
and not drive her away.
So I don't end up at 60,
sick and fat and alone
and scared in some hospital
with some beautiful young
doctor holding my hand.
She wouldn't be holding
my hand except she's trying
to figure out what horrible
disease I'm going to die of.
I want to go home.
- Whoa. Where's the fire?
- Can't talk now.
Got to kick Karev's
ass suturing.
Since when are you
friends with my mentor?
She's not your mentor
because she treats you like crap.
If you weren't living in
the hospital like a dog,
you'd notice Erica and I
have been friends a while.
- Put in a good word for me?
- Don't talk about you.
- I let you live with me!
- He's in the elevator.
- Who?
- Alex.
Hold it! Hold it!
It needs surgery, but
Callie wants 24 hours
of antibiotic coverage,
so I think we should
just irrigate and splint.
- OK, I'll take care of it.
- Or I could take care of it
and you could take
care of the wife's scalp.
She needs lots of
complex sutures.
You could get lots
of complex practice.
Isn't it like a point a
suture? You don't want that?
This is bigger
than a broken hand.
He provoked a bear and then
drove himself to the hospital.
- He was in shock.
- He married his rebound girl.
- What?
After knowing her for only
ten days. Nobody does that.
Who does that?
I'm thinking brain tumor.
I got married in the
spur of the moment
and I don't have a brain tumor.
That you know of.
- I'll do the scalp.
- You will?
Watch you turn a broken
hand into a neuro problem
just to, uh... get some
extra points? Nope.
It's not about the points.
Watch you turn a broken
hand into a neuro problem
just so you have a
reason to talk to Shepherd?
Nope.
I do not need a reason
to talk to Shepherd!
If I want to talk to
Shepherd I'll talk...
Whoa! Hey.
What is this? Is this a hint?
I should be getting
you more gifts.
A grateful patient
gave them to me.
But since you're asking,
I do like a nice
box of chocolates.
You're gonna die
of a diabetic coma
- I don't want any part.
- Cheapskate.
Crackhead.
Have you seen him?
- I have.
- Have you seen his eyes?
Yeah.
I'm trying to play it cool. I
am playing it so, so cool.
I love him.
Oh, my God. I don't... know you.
I didn't say that.
What's with the flowers?
Are you asking as a
resident or a sister?
- Sister.
- I'm stealing stuff.
OK.
Are you OK?
Resident again now. Stop
stealing crap from the hospital.
Twenty-two.
- Keep a lid on it.
- I like to know where I am.
PH is up to seven
point two-eight.
Not great, but it's improving.
Push another amp
of bicarb for a boost.
- Karev's only at 17.
- You're not helping!
Did you just yell at the Chief?
Uh... S-sorry, sir.
Should end this competition.
No!
I mean, uh... it's-it's fine.
Actually they're
doing some nice work.
Twenty-three. She's beating
the pants off of you, Karev.
Don't you have an
update to deliver?
Hahn can wait a couple minutes.
Yang.
Crap.
I thought you told me to keep
the animals under control?
From time to time, I
like to go to the zoo.
Dr. Hahn. Mr. Robinson
is critical, but stable.
We had to put him on low
dose Levofed for his BP
and he's put out 350
cc's from his chest tube.
I'll look forward to another
scintillating report in an hour.
Of course.
I'm thinking we ought to
have a contest of our own.
You wanna live in the
hospital like rodents?
Different kind of contest.
You and Rose aren't
exclusive, right?
- I'm thinking...
- You're not serious.
One woman, 10 points.
Two women, same time, 20.
You get out before anybody
wakes up, 5 point bonus.
You are serious.
You need a little spice
in your life. I'm trying help.
I am truly a worse human
being for knowing you.
Ow. Ow!
- It's OK, Mr. Sharon.
- It's not OK! It hurts!
I'm alone. I'm all alone and it
hurts and I'm not OK. I'm dying!
By some lucky stroke of fate,
you fractured your
ankle and ended up
at Seattle Grace Hospital
with me as a doctor.
And I am going to find
out what's wrong with you
and I'm gonna do my
damnedest to fix it. If I can't,
I'm gonna assemble
doctors better than me
and they're gonna
do their damnedest.
And you know what's
going to happen?
- What?
- You're gonna live
a healthier life.
Maybe even call your ex-wife
because you're being
given a second chance at life.
And this time... This
time you can do it right.
You're going to
feel a little pressure.
Ow!
Chief? Mr. Robinson's brother.
- Can I talk to him?
- Just for a minute.
Hey, man.
That you, Phil?
How you feeling?
I feel like a bear ate my
guts out or something.
You touched a cub,
man. What the hell?
I wasn't thinking. I'm so sorry.
So, touching the
cub, you knew better?
Of course he knew better.
He's having an
early midlife crisis.
He's going to kill us all.
I'm not having a midlife crisis.
Dude, dude, dude.
You married your midlife crisis.
Just 'cause you
got eaten by a bear,
you don't get to talk
smack about my wife.
Was this spontaneous
wedding out of character for you?
He needs a little rest,
so let's have some quiet.
Where was I?
Fifty-nine.
You are toast.
Tick-tock.
Yang, no running
in the hospital!
Dr. Benton to ICU one.
Why did we do a spinal
tap on an ankle fracture?
He's getting the full work up.
- How many points?
- What?
Look me in the eyes and tell
me you are not putting this man
through painful procedures
because you're
trying to win a contest.
I'm doing this because my
patient had dyspnea on exertion,
headaches, fever, myalgia,
a confluent rash
over his entire body.
I'm working him up for
RMSF and doing Lyme titers,
but I'm worried about
autoimmune or rheumatoid disease
because of his high CRP
and sed rates. Or maybe lupus.
I'm doing a spinal tap
because he was altered
and is amnestic about his fall
earlier. I do want to win this contest.
I also want to make sure that a
man does not leave this hospital
with meningitis or encephalitis
and discover too late
that all we did
was treat his ankle.
All right then. Carry on.
When you hear hoofbeats,
think horses, not zebras, right?
Exactly, O'Malley. Exactly.
Something tells me
you're not just worried about
the damage to my hand.
Phillip, earlier you were
squinting at your paperwork.
I keep telling him
he needs glasses.
And your handwriting was tiny
and wasn't all that
legible. Is that normal?
Well, I've never been a straight
A student if that's what you mean.
Is he done...? Are we done here?
- We could both use some rest.
- Humor me for one more second.
OK. Look straight ahead.
Tell me when you see my fingers.
- I see them.
- Tumor!
Sorry.
This is nice of you. Really.
Dreaming up some brain
tumor to make me feel better
about the fact I
made a bear mad.
It cross your mind I may be the
type dumb enough to pet a bear?
Jennifer. Is he
that type of guy?
Don't ask me, I've only
known him a few months.
Phillip, you knew better.
You touched the cub anyway.
- With your other symptoms...
- What symptoms?
My vision's going
bad, so I get glasses.
It's not just vision.
Brain tumors have been
known to impede judgment,
prompt spontaneity, impulsivity.
He married a trashy
waitress. Right?
I mean, that's what you mean.
That he married a girl
like me. The rebound girl.
I'm just saying I would like him
to have an MRI. Just to be sure.
- Well, the answer's no.
- Do the MRI.
- Honey, I don't need...
- Phillip. Do the damn MRI.
Because you're wrong.
He loves me.
Mr. Robinson is better. We
were able to DC the Levofed.
He's intermittently
awake and lucid.
His chest tube put out 100
cc's since I last saw you,
I'll be back in an hour
with another update.
- Is somebody chasing you?
- Excuse me?
What are you racing around for?
Uh... uh, no reason.
No reason. Not because you're
running towards the finish line
- of this surgical contest?
- Oh, that.
- Yes.
- Are you winning?
Yes. Once I finish my
sutures on Mr. Robinson.
Too bad. I was going
to let you watch me
put Mrs. Witkowsky's
new valve in.
But, if a contest is more important
than a cardiac surgery, so be it.
I'd be happy to watch, Dr. Hahn.
Crap, crap, crap,
crap, crap, crap. Crap!
- Ankle guy?
- CSF is spotless,
the ABG is normal,
the ultrasound is clear.
What am I missing?
- Oh.
- What?
- Right there.
- Where?
- See?
- No.
The fact you're doing
unnecessary medical procedures
to win a contest. No!
The fact you and
Meredith are both doing
- unnecessary procedures to win.
- Meredith has a medical
mystery?
- No, she doesn't.
- Something is wrong.
- Know how I know?
- No.
Great doctors have that
extra instinct, George.
They just know.
Great doctors, they
know when to stop.
I have to have that
instinct, George.
Because my instincts
lately? Very bad.
Really bad. They told
me to go for cardio.
They told me to have
sex with a married man.
- Ow.
- They are not serving me well.
I am in danger of going
extinct if this keeps up.
I am going to win this contest.
If for no other reason
than I have to win it!
You paged me?
I thought you might
like to see this.
Is that bear attack guy?
That's bear attack guy
and his big old brain tumor.
I'm not requiring
an apology, George.
I'm not requiring an apology
because the fact I have
potentially saved a life
is reward enough for me.
- You're calling me in to gloat.
- No.
I need a favor.
- What am I at?
- Eighty-seven.
You're an underdog,
aren't you, Karev?
Sir?
It's not that you don't have
the skills. You have the skills.
But you're scrappy.
You're a fighter. I like that.
I always root for the underdog.
I'm a fighter, but
I'm no underdog.
Like this guy here. He
didn't provoke that bear,
his brother did it.
Now he's fighting for his life,
paying for someone
else's mistakes.
Doesn't make him... an underdog.
It just...
Well, it makes him
have to work harder
to overcome the
cards he got dealt.
No, he's crashing.
Hit that code button!
- We got a code blue! Code blue!
- ♪ You owe it to yourself ♪
- Is this Meredith's patient?
- Yes.
She didn't want to
come to me herself?
- Hey, I'm just her intern.
- ♪ It's already crazy ♪
♪ Old and lonely when
the shade is down ♪
Oh, my God.
Honey, I'm so sorry.
We did absolutely
everything we could.
The stress was just
too much for his body.
♪ Some people don't get much ♪
There's more.
The neurosurgeon is going
to come in and talk to you.
No. No, I need to know.
Please.
I'm sorry. I was
right about the tumor.
You have something
called a malignant glioma.
This kind of tumor
causes behavioral...
It can cause this kind
of inappropriate affect.
- Can you operate?
- No. It's too invasive.
It's been growing a long time.
I'm so sorry.
Good.
Good. I deserve that.
I killed my brother, so I
don't deserve to survive.
Doctor.
I'm a symptom, right? I
mean, I'm like the bear cub.
I'm just a symptom
of this tumor.
That's what we're saying
here, right? Just so I'm clear?
I don't know.
I don't know that.
You're the only one who
can know that for sure.
When you say negative,
do you mean as in bad,
- or as in non-existent?
- Nothing bad came up.
What about all those alphabet
tests you were railing off?
They were elevated or something.
Yeah. Um...
They were nonspecific.
They likely indicated that you
basically have a
relatively minor flu.
I have the flu?
This whole day, everything
you put me through...
you put me through
all of this for the flu?
I'm sorry. I am.
It just, it seemed like
there was something more.
It really seemed...
It's hard to see
the silver lining,
but think of the
discoveries you made.
About yourself and
your life and your ex-wife.
My ex-wife was
a castrating bitch!
She was a castrating bitch!
I've never missed
her for one day
since she left! Not until
today! And I missed her today,
if we were still together
she would've shot me
dead a long time ago,
and I wouldn't have
gone through hell!
I'm sorry. I didn't
mean to. I really...
You treated me like a rat!
Like a rat in some
perverted lab!
God, just give me
my prescription!
I want to get out of here!
The flu is a virus.
It doesn't respond
to antibiotics.
I suggest plenty
of fluids and rest.
Fluids and rest? Fluid and rest?
- I'm sorry.
- Fluids and freaking rest?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm really, really sorry.
Dr. Leone, call the blood bank.
What are you doing?
You spent three hours
watching surgery. Three points.
I'm trusting you screwed up.
I could still win. I could. I
did get a lot of points today.
What's the matter with
you? Where's the trash talk?
She knows I'm the best.
- Who won?
- Congratulations...
- Dr. Grey.
Guy from the bear attack had
a brain tumor, Grey caught it.
80 points, solving a medical
mystery put her over the top.
- I could have found a tumor.
- But you didn't.
You chose to scrub in with
Hahn and watch for three points.
- Now, congratulate Dr. Grey.
- Congratulations.
Hey, don't you want your prize?
Ooh!
- A shiny pager.
- A sparkle pager.
- What's great about
a glitter pager?
- A sparkle pager!
It is special. It is
surgery's holy grail.
Passed down from
resident to resident,
now it belongs to Dr. Grey.
For three months,
whenever you get a surgery,
you have to page this pager
and if Grey wants your surgery,
she has the right
to take it from you.
Come on! Crap.
Enjoy the power, Dr. Grey.
Now may I recommend
you all go home. You smell.
You're greasy.
You need to bathe.
I'm sick of looking at you.
My one-year-old is
sick of looking at you.
Isn't that right?
Sick of looking at
your little ugly faces.
I thought I would
enjoy this more.
Well, give it to
me. I'll enjoy it.
Don't give it to
her. Give it to me.
Oh shut up. It's hers.
She's the winner.
She's not going
to give it to you.
Give it to me.
- This is crap.
- Are you kidding me?
I don't like her.
Sorry, but as your
friend, it's my job to say it.
I don't like Rose.
- Why?
- You're not sleeping with her.
You don't like her because
she's not sleeping with me?
That's a little weird.
- Not weird.
- It's a little weird.
If you were, I could understand
why you spend time with her.
But you're not.
It's just... I
thought that, uh...
You know, I thought it was
just going to be you and me.
- Having sex?
- After!
After Addison, after Meredith.
I have been patient.
I waited while you partnered
up with these chicks, they're over.
And it's supposed to
be just us. You and me.
Two guys on the
prowl, on the hunt.
Having trouble getting
laid and need my help?
I can get laid. I can get
laid whenever I want.
- Uh-huh.
- I do get laid whenever I want.
That's the point.
Women are everywhere.
I only have one
person I can talk to.
- That's sweet.
- Shut up.
- It's warm and fuzzy. Sweet.
- Shut up!
Are you serious
about this woman?
I don't know. Could be.
All right.
- I'll give her a chance.
- Good boy.
You're pathetic. I'm a
lesser man for knowing you.
That's my line.
Can't use my line.
I thought you were
off duty an hour ago.
I'm just catching up
on some paperwork.
It piled up on you during
the contest, I guess.
- You know about that?
- I know about Otis Sharon
and the $120,000 worth
of unnecessary
tests you ordered.
Yeah. Well...
I lost.
And I put a man through
hell for no reason at all.
I was a bad doctor today
with bad instincts
and I deserved to lose.
I don't know why I even
bothered competing.
- So, I don't need to yell?
- You should. You can.
But you don't need to.
OK.
- Stevens?
- Yes, sir?
My year? I lost by two points.
- You...
- You didn't invent the contest.
The contest is a lion fight.
So chin up, put
your shoulders back.
Walk proud. Strut a little.
Don't lick your
wounds, celebrate them.
The scars you bear are
the sign of a competitor.
You were in a
lion fight, Stevens.
Just because you didn't win
doesn't mean you
don't know how to roar.
- Good night.
- Good night, sir.
There's a little
animal in all of us.
And maybe that's
something to celebrate.
♪ What a day to be alive ♪
Our animal instinct is what
makes us seek comfort,
warmth, a pack to run with.
Hi, um...
He-Hello, Dr. Hahn.
- It's OK I invited
somebody over?
- Oh, no. It's fine.
It's an honor to have
you here, Dr. Hahn.
OK. I have to tell you,
you won't believe it.
- Yes.
- I...
was just going in there.
We may feel caged.
- He is! Are you kidding me?
- ♪ What a way to say
good bye ♪
It's not really shocking.
We may feel trapped.
♪ What a wonderful life now ♪
But still, as humans, we
can find ways to feel free.
Before you say anything,
before you say a
word, just hear me out.
I know it's not much.
And I know it's all stolen.
It's all stolen and
hospital-y and stolen.
You can turn me in if you
want to, report me for stealing,
now I'm a thief.
I've never even shoplifted
a piece of gum before
and now I'm a thief.
Except I'm not. I'm a nester.
I'm nesting. This is
me nesting. For you.
Because you hate it here.
You want to be at that big
house with Meredith and Izzie,
things are warm,
you have friends,
there aren't any roaches.
But this can be warm.
And I put out traps
for the roaches.
And I can be your friend.
I can be your friend.
I... don't have
any friends here.
Not... Not really. Except you.
And I don't have a home to
go to anymore. Except here.
I just... I...
- I can be your friend.
- ♪ What a day to give a damn ♪
I complain a lot, don't I?
It's OK.
No.
No. You know what?
I'm going to stop. I'm just
going to stop right now.
I'm going to focus on
what's good, you know?
Like this crapartment.
Like this apartment.
♪ Bring on the
evidence of my life ♪
We are each other's keepers.
♪ Bring on the evening hours ♪
- Wish you had stolen a TV.
- Tried.
- They're bolted to the walls.
- Still.
♪ Bring on the evidence ♪
We are the guardians
of our own humanity.
♪ Of my life ♪
- OK.
I'll see you.
And even though there's
a beast inside all of us...
Hi.
I think I found a
way to save lives.
I don't know for
sure, but I think
we can save people who have
the tumor Mr. Robinson has.
Mr. Robinson is the man
who was mauled by the bear?
I did all this research.
And I found this.
It's rare and still
untested in humans
but I could find
patients for a clinical trial
and I can do the labwork,
and I could track the results.
But I do need a neurosurgeon.
And you're one of the best.
It's not about us. I would
go somewhere else if I could.
♪ And to begin breathing ♪
But... I don't know.
I think I found a
way to save lives.
♪ What a day to visit Seattle ♪
What sets us apart
from the animals
is that we can think,
feel, dream and love.
- ♪ What a day, holy Toldeo ♪
- ♪ Ah, ahh ♪
♪ What a day to get
in the air and go ♪
- ♪ What a day
to give up smoking ♪
- And against all odds...
- ♪ What a day, holy Toldeo ♪
- Against all instinct...
- ♪ What a day to welcome
a baby ♪
- ♪ Ah, ahh ♪
♪ And to begin breathing ♪
OK. I think I'd better
start talking now.
- ♪ To begin breathing ♪
- ♪ Ahh ♪
- ♪ Ah, ahh ♪
- we evolve.
♪ Ah ♪