Previously on Grey's Anatomy:
Alex, tell me you
don't live with Meredith.
The more available he
gets, the more I pull away.
I'm used to being number
one. I'll help. We'll be like a team.
Dr. Hahn has agreed to become our
new head of cardiothoracic surgery.
- Looking forward to it,
Dr. Yang.
- Ah! Good morning.
Trout for breakfast. Again.
Tonight we will
have hot, perfect sex.
- I'm exhausted.
- Maybe tonight's not the perfect night.
♪ Oh, my darlin' ♪
Before we were doctors
we were med students,
which meant we spent a
lot of time studying chemistry.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
♪ They'll call you left ♪
- That was...
- Aerobic.
- Aerobic bad?
- No. No.
Why? Did you think it was bad?
- No.
- OK.
No. I mean, obviously,
we both were nervous.
We've been... we've been
waiting for so long, it was like...
- It better be good.
- Better be worth it.
- It's a lot of pressure.
- Yeah.
- Let's just do it again.
- Let's get back on that horse.
Organic chemistry. Biochemistry.
We learned it all.
- What's new with you?
- Saw my half sister half naked.
- I had dinner and a movie.
- With the Chief.
- Mmm.
Hey. You could stay.
Yeah, I think I'm going to go.
Leave you wanting
more and all that.
But when you're talking
about human chemistry,
only one thing matters.
Either you've
got it or you don't.
Dry cleaning.
Yeah. You want some coffee?
Tell them there is a stain on
the left sleeve of the blue one.
I'm thinking Godfather tonight.
Sounds good.
"I'm gonna make 'em
an offer they can't refuse."
- It's Brando.
- Yeah. I got that.
Stella!
Hey. I'm taking Meredith
Grey from you this week.
Her mother was a good surgeon,
and I want to see
what she's like.
Well, that's not
how it works here.
You get assigned a
resident. There's a schedule.
Well, the schedule doesn't
take into account certain things.
- Like what?
- Like the fact
that I don't want Yang.
You can have Stevens. She's good
and I'm sure Shepherd won't mind.
Won't mind what?
She's sassy.
She's a woman of substance,
you two have nothing in common.
I'm late. I had to drop off
the Chief's dry cleaning.
- You're doing his laundry?
- We're helping each other out.
- Yeah? What's he doing?
- He has an extensive DVD
collection.
You're dating the Chief.
I don't care if you
sleep with Lexie.
- Just can't do it at my house.
- It's my house.
Look, get over it. It was
a one time thing anyway.
- Alex.
- Come on, seriously. One time.
What's the problem
with you and your sister?
She's not my sister.
Hey.
- You look weird.
- I don't look weird.
- What's wrong?
- I look fine.
I know you.
It's horrible.
The sex. With Izzie.
Horrible. It's like
she's trying too hard.
You ever see a porno? Not that
Izzie's a porno. She's an angel.
But it's like she's trying
to channel a porn star.
She's trying to act dirty and
sexy which sounds great, right?
But, in reality, I just
want to say, "Izzie,
just 'cause you can
do that with your legs
- doesn't mean you should."
- Ah!
- I want to run.
- Run. Run. Run now.
Oh!
- I love George.
- Oh, God.
I do. I love him. And I'm
so happy because he's kind
and smart and sweet and sexy.
He's perfect. Except for the
fact he kisses like a chicken.
A chicken pecking the ground
for food, just pecking and pecking.
And when he's pecking at me
like that I forget that I love him.
I forget he's kind,
sweet and sexy.
I wanna scream,
"Stop pecking me!"
Did he peck you
like a chicken, Mer?
- Morning!
- Cristina needs me.
I am painting Burke's apartment,
so I can stop calling
it Burke's apartment.
A happy color. Red, like blood.
Plus I am on cardio
this whole week.
One of the benefits of living
with the person who
makes the schedule.
I'm on post-op again.
Second week in a row.
- Trade with me.
- Oh, yeah. No way.
- I was talking to Meredith.
- Why? I'm with Hahn.
Dude, wake up and
smell the surgical board.
Three days ago there
was a code in room 2037
and no resident to cover it.
The schedule is a mess.
Your mess. Clean it up.
- Chief had on his stern face.
- Yeah. You know, I was...
I was happy this
morning. You know why?
Because I have back
to back surgeries today.
You have on your "I
want something" face.
Will you cover for me?
Just do the Chief Resident
thing so I can stay happy?
- Just today. Please, please?
- You want me to...
Be me. But, you
know, better. Be you.
How's it going, Jerry?
If by how's it going,
you're asking me
if I've had the pleasure of
taking a crap yet, Dr. Karev,
the answer is it's not going,
nothing's going,
nothing's moving.
Five days since your bowel
resection, you should be...
Crapping by now? What's the
problem? You botch the surgery?
Is there crap leaking
out into my body?
- The surgery was a success...
- Listen, Dr. Karev.
Oh, Mama.
I've been divorced twice.
My children won't talk to me.
I've battled addictions,
filed for bankruptcy.
My life has basically sucked.
But, through it all,
the one thing I had going for
me was, I crap like clockwork.
It's a simple pleasure,
I want it back.
So get your little
prescription pad
and write me a prescription
to make me crap.
Grey and Hahn?
OK, she can't do this. She can't
just not teach me. It's her job.
Torres has to make her teach me.
If the chemistry isn't there...
Not chemistry.
She doesn't like me.
- She says it's chemistry.
- You know, I'm going to Torres.
Dr. Torres wanted
me to tell you...
- to find another specialty.
- Why?
It's not gonna work with Hahn.
So you need to find
a way to make it work
with another specialty. I
suggest you try the ER.
- What?
- This isn't a request.
This is an order. From
your Chief Resident.
The ER can be a candy store.
Got car crashes,
impalements. What do you got?
A sprained ankle and
an infected bunion.
It can also strip you
of your will to live.
OK, go, troll, find
me something good.
Dr. Yang.
Has Meredith said
anything about me?
She's been avoiding me for days.
What did I say about
talking about your life?
Help! My... My baby.
I was carrying her down stairs
and I fell and she hit her head.
She was crying in
the car, now she's not.
I'm too scared to look. Someone
please tell me if my baby's alive.
- OK.
- She can't be dead right?
You don't die falling
down the stairs?
Please... let me help. I'll
take the baby. It's fine. OK.
Oh, my God.
She's breathing.
Her fontanel feels
tense. She's lethargic.
Take her to Trauma
Two and page Shepherd.
- Thank you. Thank you so much.
- You're welcome.
- Thank you.
- OK. OK.
Ma'am? You're going to
have to stop hugging me
so I can take care
of your baby. Ma'am?
Ma'am? Ma'am?
I'm not getting a
heartbeat. No pulse.
Get me a crash cart!
She's not breathing.
- Sponge.
- Dr. Yang?
Teresa Brotherton,
lost vitals, coded.
I needled a tension pneumo.
- She regained vitals.
- So much air in the soft tissue
it's obscuring the ultrasound.
Probably punctured an airway
as well as her lung. Feel that?
I was talking to Grey. We've
got it from here, Dr. Yang.
Call CT. Tell them
we're on our way.
And you didn't
see him swallow it?
You were making collages
while our son choked to death.
It was one marble. Brian,
tell your dad you're not dead.
Ask your mom
what "collage art" is.
Maybe if you came to
my studio you could see.
Look. I'm too busy working
to pay for that studio...
OK, Mom! Dad! Just shut up, OK?
Sorry. They're annoying.
- Brian! That's rude.
- Wonder where he gets that?
There's not much we can
do except wait for it to pass.
- So he's fine?
- It was one marble.
He's not choking or
drooling. He'll be fine.
But I still get
something, right?
You said after the
hospital I get what I want.
Absolutely. You were brave.
- Yeah. Anything you want.
- OK.
I want you guys
to get a divorce.
How about a puppy?
- No, Don.
- A boy should have a puppy.
I know we talked
about it, but look...
We'll infiltrate with a
mixture of bupivicaine
and lido with epi
along these areas here.
Is there a surgery that
can make me look like her?
You're much prettier
than Dr. Stevens.
Then how come I can't
remember the last time I had sex?
Bet Dr. Stevens can remember
the last time she had sex.
Harriet, don't
harass the residents.
She still has her looks.
Although, you're already
getting worry lines.
What do you have
to be worried about?
Nothing. I don't
have worry lines.
Your frown line is
already prominent.
Whatever is wrong in your
life, you need to fix it quick.
'Cause once this stuff starts
south, it's a long way back.
Trust me.
- Know what this is?
- Looks like multiple
rib fractures and a
massive hemothorax.
Actually, it's you giving up OR
Two. My patient is emergent.
What do I tell my patient?
If it were me I'd tell
her to age gracefully.
Your baby has a
slight brain contusion.
Her brain's bruised. It's minor.
But I'd like to keep her
here for observation.
I got to tell you, Dr. Shepherd,
I'm listening to you,
but I'm not hearing
anything you're saying.
Dr. Hahn is taking my
wife into surgery right now
and I need to go be with her.
You know what you're doing.
Go ahead and do it. I
need to go be with my wife.
Wait.
What's your daughter's name?
She doesn't have one yet.
We just adopted her a week ago.
Just been trying
to get to know her.
- Clear!
- Charged.
No rhythm.
Clear!
Push intracardiac epi.
There you go.
Get ready to
cross-clamp the aorta.
The heart's responding.
Sinus rhythm.
All right. That's twice in two
hours this woman has died.
Let's pick up the pace. The less
time she's on the table, the better.
Quite a rush, huh?
Hahn took my OR. She's pushy.
Pushy and rude.
Is she doing a
stapled tractotomy?
She's trying to save as
much lung tissue as possible.
Doesn't make up
for pushy and rude.
No. It doesn't.
You paged me?
Yeah. I was wondering, do
you think I can pick her up?
The baby? I mean, the father
hasn't really been down here
and she's been
through so much already.
That's not why you paged me.
- It's not?
- No.
You paged 'cause your legs
are shaking from the other night.
Trying to work up the nerve to
invite me to a friendly on call room.
I paged you because I wanted
to know if you could tell Meredith
that I had no idea that
her house was your house.
I mean, she and I, we
were making progress.
And now she must
think that I'm a stalker.
Sorry. Your issues
can't be my issues.
But I am here for
the sex if you need it.
If I need it?
You know you need it.
Have you seen Dr. Torres?
She promised a breakdown for next week's
ENT conference by the end of the day.
She asked me to pass it along.
Must have slipped
my mind. My apologies.
Oh, good. I mean, this
is good. This... Nice work.
Thank you. I mean, yeah.
Ooh!
Sorry. I'm sorry.
No, it's fine. It's
just... It's just...
Ow! Ow!
- Sorry.
- You go that way. I go...
You know, we... We should...
We should stop for a second.
We should just... We're a
little nervous and awkward.
We just have to admit we're
nervous and we're awkward.
Yeah. A little awkward.
Yeah. Because we're nervous.
We just need to
get over ourselves.
- How?
- Um...
We pick a fantasy.
- What?
- You know, a fantasy.
We could pick a fantasy. Any...
Fantasy.
Any...
I will do anything
that you want me to.
Anything?
- That's what you wanted?
- No.
I mean... Yes.
But that's not what I meant.
- What did you mean then?
- Nothing.
Let's just not ever talk
about this again. Please.
We have chemistry,
George. I know we have it
because we had the best
sex I ever had in my life.
Do you remember that sex?
I do. It's vague and
it's in flashes, but I do.
I want that sex
back. We can do this.
Well, I want that sex back.
I think I chipped my tooth.
I've been trying to do what
you said, but it's not working.
- What... What did I say?
- To try another specialty.
Cristina, I have back
to back surgeries,
and I don't know what
you're talking about so...
Dr. Bailey said it was your
idea, but I thought maybe
- I could have some input...
- Oh, yeah. Yeah. That. The...
Yeah, my idea to... For
you to try other specialties.
So can I... Can I
scrub in with you?
You hate ortho.
No, I love ortho. But I
can't observe anymore.
I need to scrub in.
And even if it's on ortho.
Which I love.
OK.
No, I don't love ortho.
- Morning.
I'm a person of substance.
Plastics isn't all facelifts.
I do many substantial,
life-changing surgeries.
Hmm.
- Hey.
- Um, the stain's still there.
So next time stand there, make sure
you watch them mark it with the tape.
Hmm...
And everyone thinks it's so
easy being the Chief's girlfriend.
- Need to talk, I'm here.
- Yeah.
Oh. Hi. Uh...
I just came by to
update him on the baby.
But I can... come back.
Listen, I had... I had no
idea it was your house.
I... and, you know, I'm not the
girl who sleeps around. I'm not.
It's just, you know, so
much going on at home that...
How is she doing?
Well, she made it through the
night. That's a very good sign.
Oh, yeah? Yeah, well,
she's strong. She'll make it.
She's not going to let that baby
grow up without a mother, huh?
Hey. You're OK.
Oh, no. Don't try to talk, OK?
Your baby's fine.
She's feeding well.
She's doing great. I
can get her if you'd like.
Dr. Grey, why don't
you go get the baby?
You're Dr. Grey too?
Are you two sisters?
No. Just same last name.
I was just thinking about
this crap I took in the Army.
Still nothing? I gave you
a pretty good laxative.
Not strong enough, apparently.
Have a seat, Dr. Karev.
If I can't crap, you're going
to sit here while I reminisce.
Morning, Harriet. Let's get you
out of bed and get you mobile.
I'm in too much
pain. Leave me alone.
Yep, the best thing for
pain is to get you out of bed.
- You'll feel much better.
- I'll feel better if you leave.
- Harriet.
- Stop scowling.
You can scowl later,
when you actually have
something to scowl about,
when your ass expands
and you get a double chin.
But right now you are young.
You should be having fun.
Go! Start enjoying your life.
You're getting
uglier by the minute!
- Hang another bag.
- Stop the...
Her heart stopped again.
They got it started... Look. I
can't deal with her right now.
- Could you take her back?
- Continue CPR.
No rhythm.
Now! Could you
take her away, now!
- Let's go with epi.
- All set.
Uh, Dr. Torres, could
I talk to you a minute?
I'm in the middle of
a shattered femur.
Thank God for men who
ride motorcycles, right?
Right.
There's some scheduling
issues you have to deal with.
Yeah, can you handle
that again? Thanks.
I need to talk to Dr. Torres.
My patient won't crap,
won't stop talking about it.
- I'm done.
- Dr. Torres in there?
My facelift won't walk.
I can't work with her.
Shepherd's ready to discharge
Teresa Brotherton's baby,
but the father's in no condition.
OK. Is there a problem?
Just a little
administrative traffic jam.
Dr. Torres has it under control.
OK, here's what's
going to happen.
Take Crap Man and put him in
the same room with Lazy Facelift.
They can abuse each other.
The baby can stay another
night. Now get out of here.
And if anyone asks,
none of this was my idea.
- Excuse us. Where does it hurt?
- Everywhere.
- Didn't the marble come out?
- Yeah. Last night.
It really hurts. I
ate some more.
You what? You said you
took the rest from his room.
- I did!
- Well, obviously, you didn't!
- Hey. How many did you eat?
- Eight.
Is this what you ate?
Brian, this isn't a
marble. This is a magnet!
Page Dr. Bailey. Tell
her it's an emergency.
Magnets take the path of least
resistance to get to each other.
And if that means going
through the wall of the intestine,
then that's what they're
going to do. There.
I'm looking at a perfed bowel
here. Going to need surgery.
Dr. Bailey. There's
another one. It's moving.
Like a slow-motion gunshot.
Gotta stop it before it rips
through his stomach and kills him.
Come on.
- Here we go, Jerry.
- What the hell is this?
Oh, room shortage. You're
going to have to double up.
- What?
- Yeah. Harriet, meet Jerry.
- This is absurd!
- Not so angry, Jerry.
Not good for the
complexion. Right, Harriet?
Harriet, Jerry may monopolize
the bathroom for a few hours,
so if you need
to go, I'd go now.
- This is unacceptable.
- I don't even think it's legal.
My advice would be to
get yourselves discharged
- as quickly as possible.
- See you.
I have seven magnets in my tray.
He said he swallowed eight.
There's a hole in his diaphragm.
One could have
wandered up to his chest.
- Forceps.
- Gonna repair the diaphragm?
First I want to see if
the magnet will find me.
He did this so his parents
would get a divorce.
They fight all the time,
he made himself sick so
they'd take him seriously.
- I bet they
take him seriously now.
- No.
They said they'd try
not to fight so much.
I'm elbow deep in
their eight-year-old.
Sounds like something a
little extra effort can't fix.
You're probably right.
I am so right about
so many things,
it would make your head spin.
Her hands are beautiful.
I mean, surgically, the finesse.
I was in ortho all day. There's
no finesse to breaking bones.
- Carpentry.
Yeah. You want finesse
you should try plastics.
- It's all finesse.
- Yeah. No room for error
when you're dealing
with someone's face.
It's more than just facelifts.
I'm a board-certified ENT.
I take out tumors.
It's also a lot of facelifts.
But even a facelift...
I'm changing a life.
I'm holding someone's
future in my hands.
Holding a heart is way better.
She's good. Yeah.
She's sleeping, but we
can go in if you want to...
Dr. Hahn said that Teresa's...
Well, she's not in good shape.
Her other lung is leaking now.
They can't operate 'cause her
heart is too weak from all the strain.
So they're gonna see if she's
gonna make it through the night
and reassess in the morning.
- I am so sorry.
- Yeah.
I need to know who to call just
in case my wife doesn't make it.
I can't do this on my own.
I know what I'm capable of,
and I can't raise a
kid without my wife.
A kid that's not
even my own blood.
The kid deserves a family.
And, hey, I'm not a bad guy,
and I see her and
she's good, you know.
She's a good
baby. But I'm not...
You're her father.
She needs you.
She needs you now
more... You're her father.
I don't feel like her father.
I look at her and I just...
I see that she's not
mine, she's just a baby.
What did you do tonight?
I stayed late at work
because my house is a brothel.
What did you do?
- Oh, no!
- What?
Dinner and a movie.
- Dinner and a movie?
- Oh!
Dinner... Oh, dear. I...
I'm sorry. I'll just... OK.
I'm... I'm sorry. I'm sorry. OK.
It's a box of fun. You know?
It's just been too much.
- Too much pressure.
- Yeah.
Too much trying. We just
got to get back to having fun.
- Yeah. So it's a box of props?
- It's a box of fun.
OK.
- Can I...?
- Mmm-hmm.
Yeah.
A box of fun and booze,
because I figure it can't hurt.
Yeah. Yeah. Oh! That's...
No. You know what?
Don't say it. This will work.
- Yeah.
- We will work.
- Need to take the pressure off.
- Yeah.
- We have the house
to ourselves.
- Good.
We're going to have a
drink. And we're going to play.
- We'll play.
- Play.
With our box of fun.
That's...
- Definitely don't wanna go in.
- Alex. George and Izzie?
Yeah.
The Chief just saw me naked.
Huh, nice.
I thought I said no having
sex with her at this house.
I didn't invite her over.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Um, Alex, do you want
to get a drink at Joe's?
Yeah. Sure.
Alex.
There's no rule that says
he can't have a drink with me.
Actually, there is. I'm making
one. No drinking with Alex.
No sleeping with Alex.
- What did I ever do to you?
- Get your own friends.
Get your own life.
Stop living in mine!
Screw you. I'll wait at the car.
I know that was mean,
but she's everywhere.
You say she's not your sister.
Say you don't wanna know her.
So why the hell do
you care so much?
I don't. I don't.
I don't care.
- Morning.
- Hey. Got to get to work.
Yeah, yeah. Me too.
Got to go. Got to go.
All I'm saying is, the next time
you have company, lock the door.
you come over you should knock.
Where is she?
Well, it looks like she
finally got out of bed.
Oh!
Oh, my God!
We're adults, don't
look so shocked!
She always looks like that.
I guess he finally crapped.
- What?
- Even they have chemistry.
Dr. O'Malley. Brian, he's
really going to be OK, right?
Kids bounce back more
quickly than adults so...
We used to be really happy.
- I'm sorry?
- My husband and I. We really were.
Before.
Brian was a colicky baby and
Don lost his job and my mother died
- and all this baggage piled up.
- I'm... I don't...
I just keep thinking that
we have to get back there.
Maybe Brian's right.
Maybe Don and I do need
a break from each other.
We haven't been
happy in a long time.
Pressure's stable.
She put her on a heart and
lung machine in her room?
She wasn't gonna survive
another day without surgery,
too unstable to
transport to the OR,
so Hahn had to bring the OR
to her. It's pretty genius, right?
It's genius.
Dr. Grey. Make sure
her lines are clear.
The last thing we need is a
kink to send her into arrest.
Anybody gets so much as a
bad feeling, we stop and reassess.
She's going to make it, right?
He said he's gonna give the
baby up if she doesn't make it.
She has to make it.
Kind of busy right now, Lex.
- Road trip.
- - Get that out of the way.
Hey.
Mr. Brotherton,
we need to go now.
I will send Dr. Grey out to
you with periodic updates.
I promise I'm going to do
everything in my power to fix your wife.
- I got a thing for her.
- You don't.
I do. I do. I have
a thing for her.
It's going to end badly.
- You don't know.
- Yes, I do.
What do you know?
You're dating the Chief.
That joke's not funny
anymore. It's overused.
- Lover's quarrel?
- Oh, Jesus.
We're not quarreling.
Not a quarrel.
More importantly, we're not...
If I go through the
trouble to choose a movie,
he should have enough
common courtesy
to mention it if he
makes other plans.
A phone call, a note, something.
And if he's not going to
pick up my shirts, just tell me.
I'll pick them up.
I'm perfectly capable of
picking up my own shirts.
No, you're not.
You're not capable of
picking up your shirts.
anything on your own.
If I wasn't around, you'd
starve in a dirty shirt,
- die a lonely death.
- Oh, for God's sake.
I offered a place
to put your trailer,
and you've taken
advantage ever since.
You can't handle picking up
the dry cleaning or cooking,
so I have to pick
up all the slack.
Hold that thought.
You see? He can't
handle the truth.
I definitely have
a thing for her.
- Dr. Holden, 2292.
- Miranda.
Do you have any idea why the
Brothertons' baby's still here?
Dr. Torres decided to keep
the baby here for another day.
Why, if Dr. Shepherd was
ready to discharge her?
I don't know. You
have to ask Dr. Torres.
Mmm-hmm.
If it was me and the
mother kept coding,
I might keep the baby around
so they could get a
little more time together.
Mmm-hmm.
And why did Torres
have Stevens and Karev
put their patients
in the same room?
That's a clear
violation of protocol.
You have to ask her.
But those two patients
were impossible,
and neither one was willing
to follow post-op instruction...
I mean, if it was me, I would
put them both in the same room
so they could encourage
each other to get out of here.
And she told Dr. Yang
to find a new specialty?
That's a pretty odd
thing to say to someone
who has such an
affinity for cardio.
Again, you'll have
to ask Torres,
but it has to do with the fact
that Erica Hahn's putting
her through her paces,
so Yang needs to see
what else is out there,
otherwise she's won't fight
hard enough to stay with cardio.
I'm just guessing. OK,
you need to ask Torres.
That's just what
I'm going to do.
OK, it's been an hour. We
should've heard something.
Well, the fact that we
haven't heard anything is good.
That means that
they've got her in the OR
and they've opened her up.
Yeah, every step of this
that she survives is good.
Oh, God.
So we were able to find one
puncture in her remaining lung.
We're preparing to
place a patch over it.
Hopefully that's the only
leak and the patch will hold.
I should be getting back.
You know, you said your wife
bonded instantly with the baby.
For some people it's
like that. For other people,
they need a little
more time with the baby
before they can
feel like a family.
I bet you know her better
than you think you do.
All I know is that
she cries. OK?
And she eats. A lot.
You know, we were going
through formula like crazy.
And she sleeps with
her hand above her chin.
And she likes my wife.
Teresa soothes her, you know?
She puts her hand
on her back and...
she let's her suck on her
finger. But that's all I know.
That's five things no one
else knows. That's five things.
Patch is secure. Water please.
All right, let's see if I
earned my paycheck today.
Go to manual. Give me a breath.
♪ All of the boys ♪
♪ And all of their poison ♪
♪ They'll rob you blind ♪
♪ And I knew your mother ♪
No bubbles.
So far, so good. Another breath.
♪ Yeah, well, nobody knows ♪
♪ You wish things
were different ♪
I see bubbles.
The patch is secure. Clamp!
Oh, we got another leak. Grey,
hold onto this clamp please!
♪ Yeah, but you try
not to think about it ♪
♪ Most of the time you
just do what you have to ♪
Dr. Torres. You got a moment?
I don't. I have two
more surgeries.
I know the schedule's
crazy. I'll get on it tonight.
- No, you're not, actually.
- OK, you're right.
It may not happen
until tomorrow.
You're not going
to get on it at all.
♪ Yeah, well you're
still so young ♪
♪ But you feel so old ♪
Mr. Brotherton, we did
everything we could, but...
♪ And I think you're
gonna turn soon ♪
♪ I gotta be careful
with my moves ♪
♪ Just might lose you for good ♪
♪ Listen, I can't fight
your demons, yeah ♪
♪ 'Cause I'd have to fight you ♪
♪ 'Cause they're
so far inside you ♪
♪ And I just can't
seem to get through ♪
♪ It ain't none of my business ♪
♪ It ain't none of my place ♪
♪ Yeah, but I still had to try ♪
- Hey.
- Cool lounge.
- Yeah, no interns allowed.
I know that. I was
looking for you.
Because I was wondering
if you would meet me later.
In the on call room.
I can't.
Oh. I thought you said that...
Yeah, I know what
I said. But I can't.
Because of Meredith.
I'm not getting involved in
whatever you two got going on.
I'm not choosing sides.
Except, clearly you are, so...
Dr. George to OR One.
Dr. Bailey.
You've been
covering for Dr. Torres.
Chief, I've just been
shuffling a little paperwork for...
You've been doing the lion's
share of the Chief Resident's work.
All the responsibility
and none of the credit.
You deserve the credit.
You deserve the job.
I should have given it
to you in the first place.
I hope you'll take it now.
Because what you
do and how you do it...
makes this hospital work.
Well, it's about
time you noticed.
Because...
Can I pick her up?
Yeah, of course. Nurse.
- OK.
- Thank you.
It's OK.
I remember a sixth thing.
She hates the car seat.
Unless you put this little duck
up under her head, you know.
Hey.
I'm going to name
you Keisha, OK?
Because that's what your
mommy wanted to name you.
I'm not stalking. I just...
I hate apples. Hate them.
Think they shouldn't
be allowed to be a fruit.
That's one. And two...
I can draw really, really
well on an Etch A Sketch.
Like, really well.
Like, I could be
a professional if,
you know, that
profession existed.
I play the trombone. Badly.
I like math.
And I notice that you do
this thing with your hands
when you're trying
to make a point.
Like this, with your hands.
And I know that's
about you, but I do it too,
so it's also about
me and so that's five.
Five things that I'm
hoping will make it a little bit
harder for you to hate me.
I told her I could draw
with an Etch A Sketch.
Of all the things I
could've chosen...
No wonder she
thinks I'm pathetic.
- I saw your transplant today.
- I know.
- You have
extraordinary technique.
- I know.
Can I buy you a drink?
I have... rather extraordinary
techniques myself.
♪ 'Cause they don't
want him around ♪
You're not attracted to me.
You think you
are, but you're not.
You're attracted to my
skill and my confidence,
and maybe how hot I look
with my hands on a heart.
But mostly you're
attracted to me
because I'm not
attracted to you.
♪ And he's never
gonna be all right ♪
I told her I couldn't
see her anymore.
♪ And he's never
gonna be all right ♪
- You did?
- Whatever.
I don't need another
chick with issues.
Thank you.
♪ And they don't
wanna play with him ♪
Alex.
Will you take my sister home?
Come on. She plays the
trombone and whatever.
Just take her home please.
♪ And it's pouring ♪
♪ And my old man ♪
♪ Well, he is snoring ♪
I finished painting.
I got fired.
♪ Rainy day, please stay ♪
♪ Well, my brother ♪
I married Adele two
years out of college.
There's a lot I need to
learn to do for myself.
♪ On the blue rug ♪
Just pick up your own
shirts from now on.
Taxi Driver?
Meredith is coming over.
Better get back to my trailer.
♪ Rain, rain, don't go away ♪
♪ Sun can come back ♪
"You talking to me?"
De Niro?
♪ Rain, rain, please stay ♪
Alex, I'm... I'm
fine. Thank you.
Really. You can...
You can go. Thanks.
♪ Well, now I am 3,000 miles ♪
♪ From a rainy day ♪
What a pleasant surprise.
It's Dr. Karev, isn't it?
- Yes, sir.
- I don't...
- Don't wanna interrupt you two.
- Wait. Dad, you're going out?
Just down to the store.
- Dad.
- It's just down to the store.
Why don't I go? You
know, my car, it's right here.
- I'm fine.
- What do you need?
Scotch, vodka, gin?
♪ Father's
dreaming of the fall ♪
♪ Mother covers with the shawl ♪
Scotch.
♪ Brother's in the yellow hall ♪
♪ Painting pictures
on the wall ♪
♪ I am listening on the floor ♪
♪ To the sounds I used to know ♪
♪ Rain is falling
to the ground ♪
Uh...
Just... don't tell Meredith.
♪ Rain, rain, don't go away ♪
♪ The sun can come
back another day ♪
What did you do tonight?
Nothing. You?
Nothing.
It's late. Shouldn't
you be going soon?
I just want to lie here
for a few more minutes.
♪ Rain, rain ♪
That was amazing.
Finally!
See? I knew we had it in us.
Now that was as
good as the first time.
No. It was better.
- Way better.
- No, you're right. Because,
well, we were drunk and well,
I'm not married
and that was just...
Incredible.
♪ Rain, rain ♪
You're lying.
Well, so are you.
Chemistry.
Either you've got
it... or you don't.