Dr. Meredith Gray: We live out our lives on the surgical unit.
Dr. Meredith Gray: Seven days a week, 14 hours a day.
Dr. Meredith Gray: We're together more than we're apart.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): George's room is bigger than mine.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): After a while... I have more clothes.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I should have the bigger room.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): ...the ways of residency... I got here first.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): It's Meredith's house.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): She should decide.
Dr. Meredith Gray: ...become the ways of life.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): My room is like two inches bigger than yours.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Number one.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You have a bigger closet.
Dr. Meredith Gray: So why is everything a competition?
Dr. Meredith Gray: Always keep score.
Dr. Meredith Gray: Number two, do whatever you can to outsmart the other guy.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Everywhere else is filled with Meredith's mom's boxes.
George O'Malley / George O'Malley (PVM): Meredith, when is your mom coming back to town anyway?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray OR George O'Malley (PVM): Because maybe we can put her boxes in storage.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Or unpack a few things, make this place a little more homey.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Some throw pillows, lamps, a few paintings.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mrs. Stevenson OR George O'Malley OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Oh, paintings would be nice.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Yeah.
Izzie Stevens / Mrs. Stevenson (PVM): You have all this amazing stuff just packed away.
Izzie Stevens / Mrs. Stevenson OR George O'Malley (PVM): In the back hall, I found this box with like 100 tapes of your mother performing these amazing medical procedures.
Dr. Meredith Gray: Really?
Izzie Stevens / George O'Malley (PVM): We should watch them, Meredith.
Izzie Stevens / George O'Malley (PVM): Do you want to watch?
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Meredith, you want some privacy?
Dr. Meredith Gray: Number three, don't make friends with the enemy.
George O'Malley / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Morning, Dr. Bailey.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Shut up.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: You realize that I'm an attending and you're only a resident?
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You work for me, right?
Dr. Miranda Bailey / George O'Malley OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): No, I've forgotten something.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / George O'Malley (PVM): Something is happening today.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / George O'Malley (PVM): I know I should know what it is, but I just can't.
Resident (e.g., Meredith Grey, Cristina Yang) / George O'Malley OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): All right, nice talking with you, Dr. Bailey.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / George O'Malley (PVM): It's right in front of my face.
Unknown (possibly a nurse or another doctor) / George O'Malley OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Oh, doctor!
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Oh!
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Not enough.
Unknown (possibly a nurse or resident) / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Watch out, watch out.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Who's on bikes killing themselves?
Alex Karev / Bike Race Patient OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Natural selection is what it is.
George O'Malley / Bike Race Patient (PVM): So what's up with the Nazis?
Izzie Stevens / Bike Race Patient (PVM): She offer meds?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): You're not heard of the race?
Dr. Richard Webber (Chief) / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Excellent board.
Dr. Richard Webber (Chief) / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Well-timed, balanced, efficient.
Dr. Richard Webber (Chief) / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): If all goes well, we'll have a early night.
Resident (e.g., Cristina Yang, Alex Karev) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Chief, dead baby bike race started 20 minutes ago.
Dr. Richard Webber (Chief) / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): All right, people, dead baby bike race day.
Resident (e.g., George O'Malley) / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mrs. Stevenson (PVM): Every year, this bar... The dead baby bar.
Resident (e.g., George O'Malley) / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Every year, they hold this underground bike race.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mrs. Stevenson (PVM): Don't you wonder why someone would name a bar something so disgusting?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mrs. Stevenson OR George O'Malley (PVM): Keep your panties on, Nancy Drew.
Resident (e.g., George O'Malley) / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): The race is completely illegal and crazy.
Resident (e.g., George O'Malley) / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Bike Race Patient (PVM): There's a bunch of bike messengers racing against traffic trying to beat each other for free shots of tequila.
Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Bike Race Patient OR Mackie (PVM): No holds barred competition sounds like fun.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mackie (PVM): Yeah, you would think that.
Resident (e.g., George O'Malley) / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): The race doesn't even have any rules, except eye gouging.
Resident (e.g., Izzie Stevens) / Dr. Meredith Gray OR George O'Malley (PVM): No eye gouging.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): We're able to be trapped in the pit, bandaging up idiots when we can be up in the O.R.?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Bike Race Patient (PVM): What kind of people engage in a race that has as its only rule that you can't rip out the eyeballs of another human being?
Miranda Bailey / Bike Race Patient OR George O'Malley (PVM): Men, Georgie, men.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I need someone to get up to the O.R.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): floor.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): The chief needs a right hand.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Oh, and yeah, number four.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: George.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Everything, everything is a competition.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: OK, people, the rules of trauma.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Don't mingle with the ER interns.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: They don't know the ass from their esophagus.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: So fast, discharge fast to get bodies up to the OR yesterday.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: And don't let me catch you fighting over patients, got it?
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Come on, let's go.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mackie (PVM): Oh, it's like candy, but with blood, which is so much better.
Izzie Stevens / Mrs. Stevenson (PVM): Oh, my god.
George O'Malley / Mackie (PVM): I'm fine.
Cristina Yang / Mackie (PVM): No, isolate me first.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Whoever said winning wasn't everything
Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Bike Race Patient (PVM): Ooh, I'll take that guy.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Bike Race Patient (PVM): You'll have to beat me to it first.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Never held a scalpel.
Meredith Grey / Alex Karev (PVM): Nobody knows where they might end up Nobody knows Oh, oh, suppose
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Heads is mine.
Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Tails is yours.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Why do you get to be heads?
Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Oh, because I have a head.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): And honey, you are a tail.
Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Excuse me.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): How do you manage to make everything dirty?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Tails, there are plenty of other cases.
Alex Karev / Patient (Race Participant) (PVM): So go get one.
Cristina Yang / Bike Race Patient OR Patient (Race Participant) (PVM): I was here first.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I am not backing down so I can do sutures all day while you're up in the OR.
Intern 1 / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): This is a surgical case and you know it.
Intern 2 / Bike Race Patient (PVM): It's superficial.
Intern 2 / Bike Race Patient (PVM): I mean, it's cool, but it's superficial.
Intern 1 / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): How do you know those things didn't rupture his peritoneum?
Intern 2 / Bike Race Patient OR Patient (Race Participant) (PVM): Because he's sitting up and he's sitting there talking to us.
Bike Race Patient: Hello.
Bike Race Patient: Excuse me, I was wondering if you could take these out and sign me up so I could go and win my race.
Intern 1 / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Well, we can't just pull them out.
Intern 2 / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I mean, we have...
Bike Race Patient: Do some tests.
Bike Race Patient: Oh, wicked.
Intern 1 / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Are you out of your mind?
Intern 2 / Bike Race Patient (PVM): It's a superficial wound.
Intern 2 / Bike Race Patient OR Bike Race Patient (PVM): Sew him up and let him finish his race.
Bike Race Patient: You... Uh, good man.
Paramedic / Mackie (PVM): Unidentified John Doe, mid-30s pedestrian, hit by a motorist swerving to avoid a bike.
Paramedic / Mackie (PVM): GCS-3.
Paramedic / Mackie (PVM): Pupils fixed and dilated.
Paramedic / Mackie (PVM): Atropine given for a pulse in the 40s.
Paramedic / Mackie (PVM): BP 183 over 112.
Paramedic / Mackie (PVM): Pulse sucks 98%.
Paramedic / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mrs. Stevenson OR Mackie (PVM): Cheshire widened mediastinum and head CT revealed cerebral edema.
Paramedic / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): He's gotten 70 of mannitol, dexamethasone 10, and a gram of phenytoin.
Intern 1 / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Going to the OR?
Intern 2 / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Is he corked?
ER Attending / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Looks like.
Intern 1 / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): The bike race claims his first victim.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): I'll make my AAA repair after all.
Intern 1 / Mrs. Stevenson (PVM): Uh, Dr. Shepherd, he's not going to the OR?
Dr. Derek Shepherd: No.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: Do an EEG and confirmatory tests.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: If he doesn't respond, six hours.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: Declared.
George O'Malley: Sir, Dr. Bailey sent me to assist you.
George O'Malley: Should I scrub in?
Dr. Preston Burke: No.
George O'Malley: I'm stuck here all day.
Dr. Preston Burke: I need you on the floor monitoring my pre- and post-op patients.
George O'Malley: Oh.
Dr. Preston Burke: You got a problem with that, O'Malley?
George O'Malley: Oh, uh, no, sir.
Dr. Preston Burke: Uh, a buddy of mine in 4451, Lloyd Mackey.
Dr. Preston Burke: Give him whatever he needs.
George O'Malley: Mr. Mackey, no smoking.
George O'Malley: There's no smoking.
Lloyd Mackey: Why not?
George O'Malley: Oh, my god.
George O'Malley: You're in a hospital.
Lloyd Mackey: Your point being?
George O'Malley: I don't know if you've listened to the surgeon general lately say in the past 20 years, but smoking is bad.
George O'Malley: Smoking will kill you.
Lloyd Mackey: Liver cancer will kill me.
Lloyd Mackey: Smoking will just speed up the process.
George O'Malley: You're at the top of the donor list for a new liver.
George O'Malley: There's hope.
Lloyd Mackey: Sweetheart, I've been at the top of the list for eight months.
Lloyd Mackey: I'm not in a batter's cage.
Lloyd Mackey: I'm in the dugout about to be traded.
Lloyd Mackey: You like baseball?
George O'Malley: No.
Lloyd Mackey: Oh.
George O'Malley: Well, the chief wanted me to look in on you.
Lloyd Mackey: Richard's a dear old friend.
Lloyd Mackey: He's been my doctor for 30 years.
George O'Malley: Well, whatever you need, I'm your man.
George O'Malley: Just name it.
Mr. Mackey / Bike Race Patient (PVM): Oh.
Mr. Mackey / Lloyd Mackey (PVM): I'm sure I'll think of something.
Doctor (possibly George) / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Absent corneal reflexes.
Izzy / Mrs. Stevenson (PVM): It's been 55 minutes.
Izzy / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): If he doesn't respond to these tests in the next five hours, what, we're supposed to just stand here and watch him die?
George / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): If he doesn't respond to these tests, it's because he's already dead.
George / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Technically, legally.
George / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Actually, Izzy, actually dead.
Izzy / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): He's breathing.
Izzy / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): He has a heartbeat.
George / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Look at his EEG.
George / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): There's no higher brain function.
George / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): He'll never talk, move, or think again.
George / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): There's no one in there.
George / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Think like a doctor, Izzy.
Izzy / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): He could wake up.
Izzy / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): What about a miracle?
Izzy / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): There are medical miracles, you know.
George / Dr. Meredith Gray OR George O'Malley (PVM): I know.
George / George O'Malley OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You're right.
George / George O'Malley OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Miracles happen.
George / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): People do wake up.
George / George O'Malley (PVM): See, that's why we do a series of tests over a set number of hours.
George / George O'Malley OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): So when we call time of death, we know that we've done everything in our power to make sure it's actually his time of death.
George / Mackie (PVM): There isn't gonna be any miracles.
George / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): This is the hard part.
George / George O'Malley OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): To stand around as surgeons and not cut.
George / George O'Malley (PVM): But that's what do no harm means.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I should just go into the light already so I can get on another case.
Cristina Yang / Mackie (PVM): Oh, I'm the devil because I'd rather be in surgery instead of standing watch over the death squad?
Cristina Yang / Mackie (PVM): It's depressing.
Izzy / Mrs. Stevenson (PVM): Look at his sneakers.
Izzy / Mrs. Stevenson (PVM): They're brand new.
Izzie Stevens / Mrs. Stevenson (PVM): And somebody sewed this tear in his shirt.
George O'Malley / Mrs. Stevenson (PVM): And he has one of those electronic key cards.
Meredith Grey / Mrs. Stevenson (PVM): He belongs to someone.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mrs. Stevenson (PVM): An hour ago, he was out there alive.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): To simply stand here and wait for him to die.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): It would be a waste of life.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Exactly.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): It would be a waste of organs.
Alex Karev / Patient (Race Participant) (PVM): You got a nice touch.
Alex Karev / Patient (Race Participant) (PVM): And by the way, you are a rocking babe.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Seriously, do you actually think you have a shot here?
Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Patient (Race Participant) (PVM): I like to think I've got a shot anywhere.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Look, you really have to let me take you for some tests.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Run a CT.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You could have internal bleeding.
Patient (Race Participant) / Patient (Race Participant) (PVM): No, thank you.
Patient (Race Participant): I've got a race to get back to.
Izzie Stevens / Mackie (PVM): Why?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You can't win now anyway.
Patient (Race Participant): Doesn't mean I can't cross that finish line.
Patient (Race Participant): There's a party at the finish line.
Patient (Race Participant): Do you want to meet me there?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): One test, a CT.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Patient (Race Participant) (PVM): I'll have you out of here in an hour.
Patient (Race Participant): Can't do it.
Patient (Race Participant): Got to go.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): OK, well, you realize you're leaving up against medical advice, and then I strongly urge you to stay.
Patient (Race Participant): The frat guy said I could go.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): The frat guy is an ass.
Patient (Race Participant): Okay.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Well, you have to sign an AMA form.
Patient (Race Participant): Ellen, I will do anything you want me to.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Patient (Race Participant) (PVM): What is it with you guys and your need to dirty everything up?
Intern / Patient (Race Participant) (PVM): I don't know.
Patient / Patient (Race Participant) (PVM): Maybe it's the testosterone, hey?
Intern / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Maybe.
Intern / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You might want to see a doctor about that, too.
Patient: That was for good luck.
Patient: Don't worry, darling, you'll see me again.
Intern: For your sake, I hope not.
Intern / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): What do you want?
Supervisor/Another Doctor / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Do you make out with patients now?
Intern / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): What, are you jealous?
Supervisor/Another Doctor / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I don't get jealous.
Intern / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): We had sex once.
Supervisor/Another Doctor / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): And we kissed in an elevator.
Intern / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): And we kissed in an elevator once.
Supervisor/Another Doctor / George O'Malley (PVM): No, seriously.
Supervisor/Another Doctor / George O'Malley (PVM): Come on, go out with me.
Intern / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): No.
Supervisor/Another Doctor / George O'Malley (PVM): You know, I almost died today.
Intern / George O'Malley (PVM): Yeah, I came like this, Klaus.
Supervisor/Another Doctor / George O'Malley (PVM): How would you feel if I died and you didn't get a chance to go out with me?
Intern / Dr. Meredith Gray OR George O'Malley (PVM): Get over yourself already.
Supervisor/Another Doctor / Dr. Meredith Gray OR George O'Malley (PVM): Come on.
Intern / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): It's the chase, isn't it?
Supervisor/Another Doctor / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): What?
Intern / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): The thrill of the chase.
Intern / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I've been wondering to myself, why are you so hell-bent on getting me to go out with you?
Intern / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You know you're my boss.
Intern / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You know it's against the rules.
Intern / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You know I keep saying no.
Supervisor/Another Doctor / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): It's the chase.
Supervisor/Another Doctor / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Well, it's fun, isn't it?
Intern / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You see?
Intern / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): This is a game to you, but not to me.
Character A / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Because unlike you, I still have something to prove.
Character B / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I know you see me resecting this bowel.
Character B / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Do I strike you as someone who enjoys multitasking?
Character A / Mackie (PVM): We have a John Doe.
Character A / Mackie (PVM): In three hours, we have to declare him brain dead.
Character A / Mackie (PVM): We want to harvest his organs.
Character B / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Jill, why are you wasting time on this?
Character B / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You know how many patients we have downstairs.
Jill / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): If he dies, and he could still live, you know, his death should mean something.
Character B / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Then you want to harvest surgery.
Jill / Mackie (PVM): I want to save lives.
Character B / Mackie OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): OK, I want a harvest surgery.
Character B / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Getting organs from a John Doe is a long shot.
Character B / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Without ID, you can't contact the family.
Character B / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Without the family, you can't get consent to harvest the organs.
Character B / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Let's poor man die in peace.
Jill / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): What if we can find the family?
Character B / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Then get consent.
Jill / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): We could harvest the organs?
Character B / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): If you find the family.
Unknown Nurse/Doctor / George O'Malley OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Cardiac refusion is 4217.
Character C / Mackie OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): What are you doing?
Character D / George O'Malley (PVM): Hiding.
Character D / Bike Race Patient OR George O'Malley (PVM): There's this VIP patient.
Character D / Bike Race Patient (PVM): He likes me.
Character C / Bike Race Patient OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Let's go, right?
Character D / Bike Race Patient (PVM): He likes me, likes me.
Character C / Bike Race Patient (PVM): Go for it, man.
Character C / Bike Race Patient (PVM): Get yours.
Character C / Bike Race Patient (PVM): I'm down with the rainbow.
Character D / Bike Race Patient (PVM): Oh.
Character C / Bike Race Patient (PVM): Are you not gay?
Unknown / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): No.
Unknown / George O'Malley (PVM): Really?
Unknown / Bike Race Patient (PVM): Dude, sorry.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Gray OR George O'Malley (PVM): Uh, Christina?
George / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Does Meredith think I'm gay?
Cristina / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Are you?
George / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): No.
Cristina / George O'Malley (PVM): Really?
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Hey, we found the sign on John Doe.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): It's a hotel key card.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I've called the police, and they're going to send someone over.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Maybe they can figure out what hotel he was staying at, get his ID from there.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Could you make sure the police get it?
Unknown / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): OK.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): It's just, it's really important.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): We only have a few hours before we have to declare him, and I'd really like to find his family.
Unknown / Mrs. Stevenson (PVM): Do you want their permission for organ donation?
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Mrs. Stevenson (PVM): I just really want to find him.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You have a potential donor?
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): What's his blood type?
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mackie (PVM): Uh, oneg.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): OK.
Izzie / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Well, I know you probably can't hear me.
Izzie / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): And you're feeling this big push to go towards the light where everything's all halos and all-you-can-eat buffets and stuff.
Izzie / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): And I mean, sharing your organs is really great and all.
Izzie / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): But I think you have a family.
Izzie / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I can feel it.
Izzie / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): So I think it'd be really great if you could do me a favor and get better.
Izzie / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Just live.
Izzie / Dr. Meredith Gray OR George O'Malley (PVM): So you think you could give that a shot for me?
Unknown / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): No.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Meredith.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): What?
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): He's crashing.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Well, what the hell are you doing?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Call a coach.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I can't.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I'm not supposed to.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): He's brain dead.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Well, Izzy, if he's brain dead, you have to let him go.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): No.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): It's only been five hours and 33 minutes.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): He's supposed to get six hours.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Well, we can't do anything to help him live.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): It's not our place to make that call.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): He's a person.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): We're doctors.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): We should have every right to make that call.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): We can't just stand here and do nothing while he dies.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): He has a right to the next 27 minutes.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Screw it.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I'll get the dopamine.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You get the blood.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): We'll transfuse him.
Izzie Stevens / George O'Malley (PVM): Do you feel any pain here?
Patient (possibly Mackey or John Doe) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): No.
Izzie Stevens / Lloyd Mackey (PVM): You know, you really do have beautiful eyelashes.
Patient (possibly Mackey or John Doe) / George O'Malley (PVM): Um, thank you.
Izzie Stevens / George O'Malley (PVM): Uh, what about here?
Patient (possibly Mackey or John Doe) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): No.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): And nice eyes.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Kind.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I like a man with kind eyes.
Patient (possibly Mackey or John Doe) / George O'Malley (PVM): Really?
Patient (possibly Mackey or John Doe) / Dr. Meredith Gray OR George O'Malley (PVM): You think I have kind eyes?
Unknown (likely Kevin's wife or a doctor) / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Mm-mm.
Kevin's wife / Dr. Meredith Gray OR George O'Malley (PVM): I mean, uh, you can, uh... What are you examining me for?
Doctor (possibly Izzie or Meredith) / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Oh, you know, just routine medical stuff.
Doctor (possibly Izzie or Meredith) / Lloyd Mackey OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You're doing very well.
Kevin's wife / Lloyd Mackey (PVM): Because I'm enjoying the view.
Doctor (possibly Meredith or Cristina) / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): He's stable.
Doctor (possibly Cristina) / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): For now.
Doctor (possibly Cristina) / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I had a radiologist look at his chest films.
Doctor (possibly Cristina) / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): He has a traumatic aortic injury.
Doctor (possibly Cristina) / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mackie (PVM): He's going to rupture and bleed out.
Another doctor (possibly Meredith or Izzie) / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mackie (PVM): So he needs surgery.
Doctor (possibly Cristina) / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mackie (PVM): If he's going to remain a viable organ donor, yeah.
Another doctor (possibly Meredith or Izzie) / Mackie (PVM): If he's going to live.
Kevin's wife / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mackie (PVM): Is he?
Doctor (possibly Meredith) / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mrs. Stevenson OR Mackie (PVM): No, I'm not giving up on him.
Doctor (possibly Meredith or Cristina) / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): He has the surgery.
Doctor (possibly Cristina) / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): He lives longer.
Doctor (possibly Meredith) / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): That's the point.
Doctor (possibly Meredith) / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): So I'm going to help find the family.
Doctor (possibly Meredith) / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You guys find a way to get him into surgery.
Doctor (possibly Cristina) / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): She's the vice president of Fantasyland.
Doctor (possibly Meredith or Izzie) / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mrs. Stevenson (PVM): So who do we go to for the surgery?
Doctor (possibly Izzie) / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mrs. Stevenson (PVM): Bailey?
Doctor (possibly Cristina) / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): We need to go higher than Bailey.
Doctor (possibly Meredith or Izzie) / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Dr. Burke?
Dr. Burke / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Hello.
Doctor (possibly Meredith or Cristina) / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): OK.
Doctor (possibly Meredith) / Mackie (PVM): Um, I know you're busy, but our John Doe needs an aortic repair.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): The guy from this morning?
Dr. Burke / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Isn't he legally dead?
Doctor (possibly Meredith) / Mackie (PVM): Well, yeah.
Doctor (possibly Meredith) / Mackie (PVM): He's kind of still around.
Doctor (possibly Meredith) / Mackie (PVM): We gave him two units of PRBCs and put him on pressers.
Burke / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): On whose orders?
Mackey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Mine.
Burke / Dr. Meredith Gray OR George O'Malley OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): You get a brain-dead John Doe of blood transfusion without consulting anyone, and now you want me to repair his heart?
Mackey / Dr. Meredith Gray OR George O'Malley (PVM): Well, yes.
Burke / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): You do enjoy crossing our line, don't you?
Mackey / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): He is an excellent candidate for organ donation.
Burke / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): I am a surgeon.
Burke / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): I save lives.
Mackey / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): This guy is already dead.
Mackey / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Now, this is the men's room.
Mackey / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Either whip one out or close the door.
Burke / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): You're asking my advice?
Mackey / Unknown (PVM): Yes.
Mackey / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Now, who's chasing?
Burke / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Not funny.
Burke / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): This is important.
Mackey / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): OK.
Mackey / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): You want to get around Burke?
Mackey / Bike Race Patient OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): You got to find a way to get the chief involved.
Burke / Bike Race Patient (PVM): What'd I do?
Mackey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): How close a match for the liver is your guy to our John Doe?
George / Bike Race Patient (PVM): Very.
George / Bike Race Patient OR George O'Malley (PVM): Same type, same size.
George / George O'Malley (PVM): You knows couldn't find a better match.
Mackey / Mackie (PVM): Why?
Mackey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): He's the chief's VIP, right?
George / George O'Malley (PVM): Right.
Mackey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): How much would you kill to be in on a transplant surgery?
George / Bike Race Patient (PVM): You underestimate me.
George / Bike Race Patient (PVM): I'm not a baby.
George / Bike Race Patient (PVM): I'm your colleague.
George / Bike Race Patient (PVM): You don't have to manipulate me.
George / Bike Race Patient (PVM): If you want something, all you have to do is ask.
Intern (possibly Cristina or Izzie) / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mrs. Stevenson OR George O'Malley (PVM): We want you to go over Burke's head to the chief.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Ask me something easier.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Sir?
Dr. Richard Webber / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Oh, Mally.
Dr. Richard Webber / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): How's Mackie?
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Fine.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Sir, actually, that's what I want to talk to you about.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): I kind of think that me and the other interns, we think we're not.
Dr. Richard Webber / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Well, now I'm not getting any younger.
Intern (possibly Cristina or Izzie) / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): We found Mackie a liver.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): We are so going to hell.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Burke is sending us straight to hell.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): On an express train.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Alex Karev (PVM): It works.
Meredith Grey / Mackie OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): What are you doing?
Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Nothing.
Alex Karev / Unknown (PVM): Yes.
Intern (possibly Izzie or George) / Bike Race Patient OR Patient (Race Participant) (PVM): Dr. Burke!
Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Bike Race Patient (PVM): Excellent work, sir.
Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Excellent.
Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Flawless.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): It's a shame he's brain dead.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): If he wasn't, he would be on his feet in a few days.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I'm amazed at what skill your hands have.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): I seriously hate that guy.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Alex's vermin.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): That surgery is ours.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): At least Burke is doing the surgery.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I don't care about Alex.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): George, you did good.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I'm going to have to dodge Burke for the rest of my career.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mrs. Stevenson (PVM): He could kill me and make it look like an accident.
Nurse / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): The police call.
Nurse / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): They've identified your John Doe.
Nurse / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Alex Karev (PVM): His wife is on the way.
Mrs. Stevenson / Mrs. Stevenson (PVM): Oh, my god.
Mrs. Stevenson: Kevin.
Izzie Stevens / Mrs. Stevenson (PVM): It's OK.
Mrs. Stevenson: Oh, my god.
Dr. Isobel Stevens: Mrs. Stevenson, this is Dr. Stevens.
Izzie Stevens / Mrs. Stevenson OR George O'Malley OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Now, if you have any questions at all, please, please call me.
Mrs. Stevenson: Is there still a chance?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mrs. Stevenson (PVM): We can hold off till morning.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): But if there's still no change, we'd like to talk to you about organ donation.
Doctor / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Mackie.
Doctor / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): How are we treating you?
Mackie: Oh, fine.
Mackie: Except that beautiful boy won't let me smoke.
Mackie: You should reprimand him.
Mackie: Make him change bedpans.
Doctor / Mackie OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Mackie, that beautiful boy may have found you a liver.
Alex Karev / Lloyd Mackey (PVM): God, I smell good.
Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Alex Karev OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You know what it is?
Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Bike Race Patient (PVM): It's the smell of open-heart surgery.
Alex Karev / Bike Race Patient (PVM): It's awesome.
George O'Malley / Bike Race Patient (PVM): It is awesome.
Alex Karev / Bike Race Patient OR Bike Race Patient (PVM): You gotta smell me.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I don't want to smell you.
Alex Karev / Bike Race Patient (PVM): Oh, yes, you do.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You are good to be kidding me.
Dr. Meredith Gray: Okay, I have more important things to deal with than you.
Dr. Meredith Gray: I have roommates and boy problems and family problems.
Dr. Meredith Gray: You want to act like a little frat boy bitch, that's fine.
Dr. Meredith Gray: You want to take credit for your saves and everybody else's, that's fine too.
Dr. Meredith Gray: Just stay out of my face.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): And for the record, you smell like crap.
Meredith Grey / Bike Race Patient OR George O'Malley (PVM): She attacked me.
Izzie Stevens / George O'Malley (PVM): Meredith!
George O'Malley / George O'Malley (PVM): Meredith!
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): You know what?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): You might want to leave before I change my mind and let her beat you to a pulp with her tiny, ineffectual fists.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): What?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Nothing.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): It's just...
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Nothing.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Oh, this one is skin grafting.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Skin grafting?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): No way.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I've never seen that done before.
Dr. Meredith Gray: Are those my mother's surgical tapes?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Please watch the skin grafting one first.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Where did all this stuff come from?
Dr. Isobel Stevens: Oh, I unpacked some of your mother's things.
Dr. Isobel Stevens: I was upset.
Dr. Isobel Stevens: And when I'm upset, I like to nest.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Alex Karev (PVM): Oh, I have my palvectomy.
Izzie Stevens / Alex Karev (PVM): I think we should watch this one first.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): No.
Dr. Meredith Gray: We're not watching my mother's surgery tapes.
Dr. Meredith Gray: We're not unpacking boxes.
Dr. Meredith Gray: We're not having long conversations where we celebrate the moments of our lives.
Dr. Meredith Gray: And use a coaster.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray OR George O'Malley (PVM): I ordered Chinese food.
Dr. Meredith Gray: I hate Chinese food!
Dr. Meredith Gray: They're everywhere, all the time.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Izzy's all perky, and George does this thing where he's helpful and considerate.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): They share food, and they say things, and they move things, and they breathe.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): They're, like, happy.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Kick them out.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I can't kick them out.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): They just moved in.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I asked them to move in.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): So what?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mackie (PVM): You're just going to repress everything in some deep, dark, twisted place until one day you snap and kill them?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Yep.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mackie (PVM): This is why we are friends.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Alex Karev (PVM): Why is the Nazi making us stay in the pit two days in a row?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Alex Karev OR Bike Race Patient (PVM): Leftovers.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Alex Karev OR Bike Race Patient (PVM): Leftovers.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Got to get the cyclist who were too drunk or too stupid or too scared to get themselves to a hospital yesterday.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Patient (Race Participant) (PVM): Well, meanwhile, she gets to do a freaking organ harvest.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Patient (Race Participant) (PVM): That kills me, doesn't it?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): What?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Patient (Race Participant) (PVM): That two women caught the harvest.
Cristina Yang / Patient (Race Participant) (PVM): No, it kills me that anybody got the harvest but me.
Meredith Grey / Patient (Race Participant) OR Bike Race Patient (PVM): Boobs do not factor into this equation.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Bike Race Patient (PVM): Come on, son.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Alex Karev OR Dr. Meredith Gray OR Bike Race Patient (PVM): You want to show me yours?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I'm going to become a lesbian.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Me too.
Organ Procurement Coordinator / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Now, Mrs. Davidson, this form simply says you've consented the donation of your husband's major organs, heart, lungs, liver, and kidneys.
Organ Procurement Coordinator / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Now I need to ask you a few questions.
Organ Procurement Coordinator / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Are you willing to donate his corneas?
Mrs. Davidson: But you want his eyes?
Organ Procurement Coordinator / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Um, corneal transplants can give someone back their sight.
Mrs. Davidson: I suppose that's OK.
Organ Procurement Coordinator / Mackie (PVM): What about his skin?
Mrs. Davidson: What?
Doctor (possibly Meredith or Cristina) / Mackie (PVM): It's used to help burn victims.
Family Member (possibly patient's wife or daughter) / Mrs. Stevenson (PVM): You want to cut off his skin?
Family Member (possibly patient's wife or daughter) / Mrs. Stevenson (PVM): What about the funeral?
Family Member (possibly patient's wife or daughter) / Mrs. Stevenson (PVM): You want me to have a funeral and have people look at him?
Family Member (possibly patient's wife or daughter) / Mrs. Stevenson (PVM): Have his daughter look at her father and he doesn't have any skin?
Doctor (possibly Meredith or Cristina) / Mrs. Stevenson (PVM): It's his skin.
Cristina Yang / Mackie OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): What are you doing?
Cristina Yang / Mackie OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I'm not a people person.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mackie OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): No kidding.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mackie (PVM): I can't do that.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I can't talk to the families of patients.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I'm sorry.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): What's his name?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Who?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): The patient.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): What's his name?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Kevin Davidson.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Remember that.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Not Gorkt Guy.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Not John Doe.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Kevin Davidson.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): He's someone's husband.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Someone's son.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Not a collection of body parts for you to harvest.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): A person.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): No one said this was easy.
Mr. Mackey: I owe you, George.
George O'Malley: No, you don't owe me anything.
George O'Malley: I'm just happy we found a liver.
Mr. Mackey: Well, when I get out of here, how about I take you and my new liver out for a night on the town?
Mr. Mackey: What do you say?
George O'Malley: Uh, Mr. Mackey, no offense or anything.
Patient (possibly a female patient speaking to George) / Dr. Meredith Gray OR George O'Malley (PVM): You're very handsome, but I, um, I'm not, I mean, you're not my type, because you're a man, and... George, I never thought you were gay.
George / Lloyd Mackey OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You didn't?
Patient / Lloyd Mackey (PVM): Oh, Charles, please.
George / Lloyd Mackey (PVM): You?
Patient / Lloyd Mackey (PVM): Gay?
Patient / Lloyd Mackey (PVM): I'm sick, George, not blind.
George / Lloyd Mackey (PVM): Then why have you?
Patient / Lloyd Mackey OR Lloyd Mackey (PVM): Well, because dying is a get-out-of-jail-free card.
Patient / Lloyd Mackey (PVM): I can be as bold as I want, and there's nothing anybody can say about it.
Patient / Lloyd Mackey (PVM): So I flirt.
Patient / Lloyd Mackey (PVM): Haven't you ever been attracted to someone you know you couldn't have?
George / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Well, I'm...
George / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): No.
Patient / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): What's her name?
George / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Bike Race Patient OR George O'Malley (PVM): There's no... I'm not... You know, this is really not... Meredith.
Doctor (possibly Burke or Cristina) / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Let's go get that liver shot.
Doctor (possibly George or another surgeon) / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): No, I'm sorry.
Doctor (possibly George or another surgeon) / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): I didn't... I never liked harvesting.
Another Doctor (possibly Burke or Cristina) / Mackie (PVM): Why?
Doctor (possibly George or another surgeon) / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Like I said, I'm a surgeon.
Doctor (possibly George or another surgeon) / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): I save lives.
Another Doctor (possibly Burke or Cristina) / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): This ends well.
Doctor (possibly George or another surgeon) / Mrs. Stevenson (PVM): I know you tried, so no hard feelings, OK?
Doctor (possibly George or another surgeon) / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): I was just.
Another Doctor (possibly Burke or Cristina) / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): You were saying goodbye.
Doctor (possibly Meredith, Cristina, or another intern) / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): What's Viper doing here?
Doctor (possibly Cristina or Alex) / Bike Race Patient OR Bike Race Patient (PVM): Probably crashed his bike again.
Doctor (possibly Meredith, Cristina, or another intern) / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): How long has he been waiting?
Doctor (possibly Cristina or Alex) / Bike Race Patient (PVM): Don't know.
Doctor (possibly Cristina or Alex) / Bike Race Patient (PVM): Busy on real cases.
Doctor (possibly Cristina or Alex) / Patient (Race Participant) OR Bike Race Patient (PVM): He's all yours.
Doctor (possibly Meredith, Cristina, or another intern) / Alex Karev OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Viper.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Viper?
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Are you OK?
Doctor / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Call up to the OR and tell them we're coming in.
Doctor / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Page Dr. Bailey.
Nurse / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Right away.
Doctor / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Alex, let's go.
Doctor / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Alex, push the damn gurney.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Clear the way.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Patient (Race Participant) (PVM): Coming through.
Unknown / Patient (Race Participant) (PVM): Somebody get the elevator.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mrs. Stevenson (PVM): Hurry.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mrs. Stevenson (PVM): I don't know how long I can keep this room closed.
Doctor / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Move faster.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Damn it.
Unknown / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): This is a new one.
Doctor / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Somebody get her off my patient.
Doctor / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Alex Karev OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Meredith, go get cleaned up from scrubbing.
Doctor / Alex Karev OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Alex, get back downstairs.
Alex Karev: Yeah, but I help.
Doctor / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Help?
Alex Karev: Yeah, they tell me down in the pit you only want to take the hot kicks.
Doctor / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Every pack of interns, there's always one fool running around trying to show off.
Doctor / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): And Alex, this time that fool is you.
Doctor / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Get out.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Alex Karev OR Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You better give me something to stand on.
Unknown / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Lower this table.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Mountain's going to have to come to me.
Doctor / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Count backwards from 10 for me.
Unknown / Lloyd Mackey OR Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): You're a good friend.
Unknown / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): The best.
Doctor / Alex Karev OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Shut up and count backwards already, Mac.
Mac: Nine.
Unknown Friend / Unknown (PVM): Nine.
Friend of Viper / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I'm not going to stay.
Another Friend / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): It's your job.
Another Friend / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You have to.
Friend of Viper / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You're better at this part than me.
Friend of Viper / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I don't want to watch him get taken apart.
Doctor / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Look at the vultures waiting to pick him clean.
Doctor / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Every last one of them represents someone somewhere who's going to live because of Kevin.
Doctor / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Here, put it on.
Unknown / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): All right.
Doctor / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): I'll be waiting next door when you're ready.
Unknown / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Everyone's waiting.
Doctor / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Meredith Gray OR Lloyd Mackey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Okay, doctors, let's get this over with.
Unknown (possibly background singing or family) / Alex Karev (PVM): You are my joy.
Unknown (possibly family or friend) / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Meredith Gray OR Alex Karev (PVM): So don't be scared of all the hurtful words.
Unknown (possibly family or friend) / Alex Karev (PVM): Because in the end they'll hurt themselves much more.
Unknown (possibly background singing or family) / Alex Karev (PVM): You are my joy.
Doctor (possibly Alex Karev) / Dr. Meredith Gray OR George O'Malley (PVM): Izzy, I'm going to sew him up for his family.
Izzy / Mrs. Stevenson (PVM): You do it.
Doctor (possibly Alex Karev) / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): What?
Doctor or Nurse / Mrs. Stevenson (PVM): Mrs. Davidson?
Nurse / Mrs. Stevenson (PVM): He's ready if you'd like to see him.
Nurse / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): This lovely group's his friends.
Nurse / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Uh, you all belong to, what was his name?
Friend of Viper / Alex Karev OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Viper.
Nurse / Alex Karev OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Viper.
Friend of Viper / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Alex Karev (PVM): Yeah, we were in the race.
Friend of Viper / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): How is he?
Another Friend of Viper / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Is he OK?
Nurse / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Yeah.
Friend of Viper / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Is he OK?
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): No.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): No, he's not OK at all.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): He hurled his body down a concrete mountain at full speed for no good reason.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Hey, yeah, yeah, I know you all pierce yourselves and smoke up and generally treat your bodies like your grungy asses can't break down.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Hey, that's fine.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You want to kill yourselves flying down a concrete mountain?
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Go to it.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): But there are other people walking, people driving, people trying to live their lives on that concrete mountain, and one of them got his brain scrambled today because one of you little sniveling no-good snot rag.
Friend of Viper / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Dr. Bailey.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Yeah, so, OK, no.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Your friend Viper, as far as I'm concerned, is not OK.
Nurse / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): She's, um, really tired.
Doctor / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): But Viper's gonna make it.
Doctor / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Alex Karev (PVM): He's gonna live.
Friend of Viper / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Alex Karev OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Thanks.
Male Lead (e.g., Derek Shepherd) / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): It's not the chase.
Female Lead (e.g., Meredith Grey) / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): What?
Male Lead (e.g., Derek Shepherd) / George O'Malley (PVM): You and me.
Male Lead (e.g., Derek Shepherd) / George O'Malley OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): It is not the thrill of the chase.
Male Lead (e.g., Derek Shepherd) / George O'Malley (PVM): It's not a game.
Male Lead (e.g., Derek Shepherd) / George O'Malley OR Lloyd Mackey (PVM): It's... It's your tiny, ineffectual fists.
Male Lead (e.g., Derek Shepherd) / Lloyd Mackey OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): And your hair.
Derek Shepherd / Mrs. Stevenson (PVM): My hair?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): It smells good.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): And you're very, very bossy.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): It keeps me in line.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I'm still not going out with you.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Meredith Gray OR George O'Malley (PVM): Can you say that now?
Meredith Grey / Lloyd Mackey OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): How'd it go?
Chief Webber / Lloyd Mackey OR Mackie (PVM): Very smoothly.
Mr. Mackey / Mackie (PVM): Damn.
Mr. Mackey: That means I have to quit smoking?
Alex Karev / Lloyd Mackey OR Alex Karev OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Ah, the pretty ones always come falling back.
Dr. Meredith Gray: There's another way to survive this competition.
Dr. Meredith Gray: A way no one ever seems to tell you about.
Dr. Meredith Gray: One you have to learn for yourself.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Number five.
Dr. Meredith Gray: It's not about the race at all.
Dr. Meredith Gray: There are no winners or losers.
Dr. Meredith Gray: Victories are counted by the number of lives saved.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Oh, OK.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): This is the best part.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Watch.
Stage Directions: She pulls a black spinning down over her face.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): We were... Hi.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): We were just, uh... Christina made us.
Dr. Meredith Gray: And once in a while, if you're smart, a life you save could be your own.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): What are we watching?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Ooh.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): This is the one where my mother... Literally pulls this guy's face off.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Yeah.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Go, Barb!
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Go, Barb!
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Go, Barb!