Meredith Grey / Mrs. Davidson OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): We live out our lives on the surgical unit.
Meredith Grey / Mrs. Davidson OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Seven days a week, 14 hours a day.
Meredith Grey / Mrs. Davidson OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): We're together more than we're apart.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): George's room is bigger than mine.
Izzie Stevens / Mrs. Davidson OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): After a while... I have more clothes.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I should have the bigger room.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): ...the ways of residency... I got here first.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It's Meredith's house.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): She should decide.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): ...become the ways of life.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): My room is like two inches bigger than yours.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Number one.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You have a bigger closet.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): So why is everything a competition?
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Always keep score.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Number two, do whatever you can to outsmart the other guy.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Everywhere else is filled with Meredith's mom's boxes.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Meredith, when is your mom coming back to town anyway?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Because maybe we can put her boxes in storage.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Or unpack a few things, make this place a little more homey.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Some throw pillows, lamps, a few paintings.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Oh, paintings would be nice.
Izzie Stevens / Mrs. Davidson OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Yeah.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You have all this amazing stuff just packed away.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): In the back hall, I found this box with like 100 tapes of your mother performing these amazing medical procedures.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Really?
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): We should watch them, Meredith.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Do you want to watch?
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Meredith, you want some privacy?
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Number three, don't make friends with the enemy.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Morning, Dr. Bailey.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Shut up.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: You realize that I'm an attending and you're only a resident?
Dr. Miranda Bailey: You work for me, right?
George O'Malley / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): No, I've forgotten something.
George O'Malley / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Something is happening today.
George O'Malley / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I know I should know what it is, but I just can't.
George O'Malley / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): All right, nice talking with you, Dr. Bailey.
George O'Malley / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): It's right in front of my face.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Oh, doctor!
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Oh!
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Oh!
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Not enough.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Watch out, watch out.
Alex Karev / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Who's on bikes killing themselves?
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Natural selection is what it is.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): So what's up with the Nazis?
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): She offer meds?
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You're not heard of the race?
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Excellent board.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Well-timed, balanced, efficient.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): If all goes well, we'll have a early night.
Resident or Intern (possibly Cristina Yang) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Chief, dead baby bike race started 20 minutes ago.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): All right, people, dead baby bike race day.
Alex Karev / Mrs. Davidson OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Every year, this bar... The dead baby bar.
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Every year, they hold this underground bike race.
Izzie Stevens / Mrs. Davidson (PVM): Don't you wonder why someone would name a bar something so disgusting?
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley OR Mrs. Davidson OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Keep your panties on, Nancy Drew.
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): The race is completely illegal and crazy.
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): There's a bunch of bike messengers racing against traffic trying to beat each other for free shots of tequila.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): No holds barred competition sounds like fun.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Yeah, you would think that.
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): The race doesn't even have any rules, except eye gouging.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): No eye gouging.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): We're able to be trapped in the pit, bandaging up idiots when we can be up in the O.R.?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): What kind of people engage in a race that has as its only rule that you can't rip out the eyeballs of another human being?
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Men, Georgie, men.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: I need someone to get up to the O.R.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: floor.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: The chief needs a right hand.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Oh, and yeah, number four.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: George.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Everything, everything is a competition.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: OK, people, the rules of trauma.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Don't mingle with the ER interns.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): They don't know the ass from their esophagus.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): So fast, discharge fast to get bodies up to the OR yesterday.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): And don't let me catch you fighting over patients, got it?
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Come on, let's go.
Dr. Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Oh, it's like candy, but with blood, which is so much better.
Dr. Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Oh, my god.
Dr. Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): I'm fine.
Dr. Alex Karev / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): No, isolate me first.
Dr. Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Whoever said winning wasn't everything
Dr. Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Ooh, I'll take that guy.
Dr. Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You'll have to beat me to it first.
Dr. Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Never held a scalpel.
Dr. Meredith Gray: Nobody knows where they might end up Nobody knows Oh, oh, suppose
Dr. Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Heads is mine.
Dr. Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Tails is yours.
Dr. Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Why do you get to be heads?
Dr. Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Oh, because I have a head.
Dr. Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): And honey, you are a tail.
Dr. Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Excuse me.
Dr. Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): How do you manage to make everything dirty?
Dr. Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Tails, there are plenty of other cases.
Dr. Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): So go get one.
Dr. Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I was here first.
Dr. Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I am not backing down so I can do sutures all day while you're up in the OR.
Dr. Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): This is a surgical case and you know it.
Resident (likely George O'Malley or another intern) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It's superficial.
Resident (likely George O'Malley or another intern) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I mean, it's cool, but it's superficial.
Resident (likely Cristina Yang or another intern) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): How do you know those things didn't rupture his peritoneum?
Resident (likely George O'Malley or another intern) / Patient OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Because he's sitting up and he's sitting there talking to us.
Lloyd Mackey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Hello.
Lloyd Mackey / Patient (PVM): Excuse me, I was wondering if you could take these out and sign me up so I could go and win my race.
Resident (likely George O'Malley or another intern) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Well, we can't just pull them out.
Resident (likely George O'Malley or another intern) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I mean, we have...
Resident (likely Cristina Yang or another intern) / Patient OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Do some tests.
Lloyd Mackey / Patient OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Oh, wicked.
Resident (likely Cristina Yang) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Are you out of your mind?
Dr. Burke / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It's a superficial wound.
Dr. Burke / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Sew him up and let him finish his race.
Dr. Burke / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. Preston Burke OR Patient OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You... Uh, good man.
Resident (likely Cristina Yang or George O'Malley) / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Unidentified John Doe, mid-30s pedestrian, hit by a motorist swerving to avoid a bike.
Resident (likely Cristina Yang or George O'Malley) / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): GCS-3.
Resident (likely Cristina Yang or George O'Malley) / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Pupils fixed and dilated.
Resident (likely Cristina Yang or George O'Malley) / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Atropine given for a pulse in the 40s.
Resident (likely Cristina Yang or George O'Malley) / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): BP 183 over 112.
Resident (likely Cristina Yang or George O'Malley) / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Pulse sucks 98%.
Resident (likely Cristina Yang or George O'Malley) / Mrs. Davidson OR Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Cheshire widened mediastinum and head CT revealed cerebral edema.
Resident (likely Cristina Yang or George O'Malley) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He's gotten 70 of mannitol, dexamethasone 10, and a gram of phenytoin.
Dr. Burke / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Going to the OR?
Resident (likely Cristina Yang or George O'Malley) / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Is he corked?
Dr. Burke / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Looks like.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): The bike race claims his first victim.
Dr. Preston Burke / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I'll make my AAA repair after all.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Uh, Dr. Shepherd, he's not going to the OR?
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): No.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Do an EEG and confirmatory tests.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): If he doesn't respond, six hours.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Declared.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Sir, Dr. Bailey sent me to assist you.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Should I scrub in?
Dr. Richard Webber / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): No.
Dr. Richard Webber / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I'm stuck here all day.
Dr. Richard Webber / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I need you on the floor monitoring my pre- and post-op patients.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Oh.
Dr. Richard Webber / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You got a problem with that, O'Malley?
Dr. George O'Malley: Oh, uh, no, sir.
Dr. Richard Webber / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Uh, a buddy of mine in 4451, Lloyd Mackey.
Dr. Richard Webber / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Give him whatever he needs.
Dr. George O'Malley: Mr. Mackey, no smoking.
Dr. George O'Malley: There's no smoking.
Mr. Lloyd Mackey: Why not?
Dr. George O'Malley: Oh, my god.
Dr. George O'Malley: You're in a hospital.
Mr. Lloyd Mackey: Your point being?
Dr. George O'Malley: I don't know if you've listened to the surgeon general lately say in the past 20 years, but smoking is bad.
Dr. George O'Malley: Smoking will kill you.
Liver Cancer Patient / Mr. Lloyd Mackey (PVM): Liver cancer will kill me.
Liver Cancer Patient / Mr. Lloyd Mackey (PVM): Smoking will just speed up the process.
Izzy / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You're at the top of the donor list for a new liver.
Izzy / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): There's hope.
Liver Cancer Patient / Mr. Lloyd Mackey (PVM): Sweetheart, I've been at the top of the list for eight months.
Liver Cancer Patient / Mr. Lloyd Mackey (PVM): I'm not in a batter's cage.
Liver Cancer Patient / Mr. Lloyd Mackey (PVM): I'm in the dugout about to be traded.
Izzy / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You like baseball?
Liver Cancer Patient / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): No.
Izzy / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Oh.
Izzy / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Well, the chief wanted me to look in on you.
Liver Cancer Patient / Mr. Lloyd Mackey (PVM): Richard's a dear old friend.
Liver Cancer Patient / Mr. Lloyd Mackey (PVM): He's been my doctor for 30 years.
Izzy / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Well, whatever you need, I'm your man.
Izzy / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Just name it.
Liver Cancer Patient / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Oh.
Liver Cancer Patient / Mr. Lloyd Mackey (PVM): I'm sure I'll think of something.
Resident (possibly Izzy) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Absent corneal reflexes.
Resident (possibly Izzy) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It's been 55 minutes.
Izzy / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): If he doesn't respond to these tests in the next five hours, what, we're supposed to just stand here and watch him die?
Another Resident / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): If he doesn't respond to these tests, it's because he's already dead.
Another Resident / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Technically, legally.
Another Resident / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Actually, Izzy, actually dead.
Izzy / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He's breathing.
Izzy / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He has a heartbeat.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Look at his EEG.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): There's no higher brain function.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He'll never talk, move, or think again.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): There's no one in there.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Think like a doctor, Izzy.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He could wake up.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): What about a miracle?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): There are medical miracles, you know.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I know.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You're right.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Miracles happen.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): People do wake up.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): See, that's why we do a series of tests over a set number of hours.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): So when we call time of death, we know that we've done everything in our power to make sure it's actually his time of death.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): There isn't gonna be any miracles.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): This is the hard part.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): To stand around as surgeons and not cut.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): But that's what do no harm means.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I should just go into the light already so I can get on another case.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Oh, I'm the devil because I'd rather be in surgery instead of standing watch over the death squad?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): It's depressing.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Look at his sneakers.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): They're brand new.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): And somebody sewed this tear in his shirt.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): And he has one of those electronic key cards.
Resident / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He belongs to someone.
Resident / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): An hour ago, he was out there alive.
Resident / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): To simply stand here and wait for him to die.
Resident / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It would be a waste of life.
Another Doctor / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Exactly.
Another Doctor / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It would be a waste of organs.
Patient: You got a nice touch.
Patient: And by the way, you are a rocking babe.
Dr. George O'Malley: Seriously, do you actually think you have a shot here?
Patient: I like to think I've got a shot anywhere.
Dr. George O'Malley: Look, you really have to let me take you for some tests.
Dr. George O'Malley: Run a CT.
Dr. George O'Malley: You could have internal bleeding.
Patient: No, thank you.
Patient: I've got a race to get back to.
Dr. George O'Malley: Why?
Dr. George O'Malley: You can't win now anyway.
Patient: Doesn't mean I can't cross that finish line.
Patient: There's a party at the finish line.
Patient: Do you want to meet me there?
Dr. George O'Malley: One test, a CT.
Dr. George O'Malley: I'll have you out of here in an hour.
Patient: Can't do it.
Patient: Got to go.
Dr. George O'Malley: OK, well, you realize you're leaving up against medical advice, and then I strongly urge you to stay.
Patient / Patient (PVM): The frat guy said I could go.
Ellen / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): The frat guy is an ass.
Patient / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Okay.
Ellen / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Well, you have to sign an AMA form.
Patient / Patient (PVM): Ellen, I will do anything you want me to.
Ellen / Patient OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): What is it with you guys and your need to dirty everything up?
Patient / Patient (PVM): I don't know.
Ellen / Patient (PVM): Maybe it's the testosterone, hey?
Patient / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Maybe.
Ellen / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You might want to see a doctor about that, too.
Patient / Patient (PVM): That was for good luck.
Patient / Patient (PVM): Don't worry, darling, you'll see me again.
Ellen / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): For your sake, I hope not.
Ellen / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): What do you want?
Romantic Interest / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Do you make out with patients now?
Ellen / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): What, are you jealous?
Romantic Interest / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I don't get jealous.
Romantic Interest / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): We had sex once.
Ellen / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): And we kissed in an elevator.
Romantic Interest / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): And we kissed in an elevator once.
Ellen / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): No, seriously.
Romantic Interest / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Come on, go out with me.
Ellen / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): No.
Romantic Interest / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You know, I almost died today.
Resident / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Yeah, I came like this, Klaus.
Resident / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): How would you feel if I died and you didn't get a chance to go out with me?
Dr. Burke / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Get over yourself already.
Resident / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Come on.
Resident / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It's the chase, isn't it?
Dr. Burke / Mrs. Davidson (PVM): What?
Resident / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): The thrill of the chase.
Resident / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I've been wondering to myself, why are you so hell-bent on getting me to go out with you?
Resident / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You know you're my boss.
Resident / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You know it's against the rules.
Resident / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You know I keep saying no.
Dr. Burke / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It's the chase.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Well, it's fun, isn't it?
Dr. Burke / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You see?
Resident / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): This is a game to you, but not to me.
Resident / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Because unlike you, I still have something to prove.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I know you see me resecting this bowel.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Do I strike you as someone who enjoys multitasking?
Resident / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): We have a John Doe.
Resident / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): In three hours, we have to declare him brain dead.
Resident / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): We want to harvest his organs.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Jill, why are you wasting time on this?
Dr. Burke / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You know how many patients we have downstairs.
Resident / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): If he dies, and he could still live, you know, his death should mean something.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Then you want to harvest surgery.
Izzie Stevens / Mrs. Davidson (PVM): I want to save lives.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): OK, I want a harvest surgery.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Getting organs from a John Doe is a long shot.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Without ID, you can't contact the family.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Without the family, you can't get consent to harvest the organs.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Let's poor man die in peace.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): What if we can find the family?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Then get consent.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): We could harvest the organs?
Cristina Yang / Mrs. Davidson OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): If you find the family.
Nurse / Mrs. Davidson OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Cardiac refusion is 4217.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): What are you doing?
George O'Malley / Mrs. Davidson OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Hiding.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): There's this VIP patient.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He likes me.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Let's go, right?
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He likes me, likes me.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Go for it, man.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Get yours.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I'm down with the rainbow.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Oh.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Are you not gay?
Unknown (likely a resident, possibly George or Izzie) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): No.
Unknown (likely another resident, possibly Izzie or George) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Really?
Unknown (likely George O'Malley) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Dude, sorry.
Unknown (likely George O'Malley) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Uh, Christina?
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Does Meredith think I'm gay?
Cristina Yang / Mrs. Davidson OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Are you?
George O'Malley / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): No.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Really?
Unknown (likely Izzie Stevens) / Mrs. Davidson OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Hey, we found the sign on John Doe.
Unknown (likely George O'Malley) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It's a hotel key card.
Unknown (likely Izzie Stevens) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I've called the police, and they're going to send someone over.
Unknown (likely George O'Malley) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Maybe they can figure out what hotel he was staying at, get his ID from there.
Unknown (likely Izzie Stevens) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Could you make sure the police get it?
Unknown (likely George O'Malley) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): OK.
Unknown (likely Izzie Stevens) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It's just, it's really important.
Unknown (likely Izzie Stevens) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): We only have a few hours before we have to declare him, and I'd really like to find his family.
Unknown (likely Cristina Yang) / Mrs. Davidson (PVM): Do you want their permission for organ donation?
Unknown (likely Izzie Stevens) / Mrs. Davidson OR Mrs. Davidson OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I just really want to find him.
Unknown (likely Dr. Burke) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You have a potential donor?
Unknown (likely Miranda Bailey) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): What's his blood type?
Unknown (likely Izzie Stevens) / Mrs. Davidson OR Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Uh, oneg.
Unknown (likely Miranda Bailey) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): OK.
Unknown (likely Izzie Stevens) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Well, I know you probably can't hear me.
Unknown (likely Izzie Stevens) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): And you're feeling this big push to go towards the light where everything's all halos and all-you-can-eat buffets and stuff.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): And I mean, sharing your organs is really great and all.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): But I think you have a family.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I can feel it.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): So I think it'd be really great if you could do me a favor and get better.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Just live.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): So you think you could give that a shot for me?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): No.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Meredith.
Meredith Grey / Mrs. Davidson (PVM): What?
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He's crashing.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Well, what the hell are you doing?
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Call a coach.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I can't.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I'm not supposed to.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He's brain dead.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Well, Izzy, if he's brain dead, you have to let him go.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): No.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It's only been five hours and 33 minutes.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He's supposed to get six hours.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Well, we can't do anything to help him live.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It's not our place to make that call.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He's a person.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): We're doctors.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): We should have every right to make that call.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): We can't just stand here and do nothing while he dies.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He has a right to the next 27 minutes.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Screw it.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I'll get the dopamine.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You get the blood.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): We'll transfuse him.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Do you feel any pain here?
Mr. Lloyd Mackey: No.
Mr. Lloyd Mackey: You know, you really do have beautiful eyelashes.
Dr. George O'Malley: Um, thank you.
Dr. George O'Malley: Uh, what about here?
Mr. Lloyd Mackey: No.
Mr. Lloyd Mackey: And nice eyes.
Mr. Lloyd Mackey: Kind.
Mr. Lloyd Mackey: I like a man with kind eyes.
Dr. George O'Malley: Really?
Dr. George O'Malley: You think I have kind eyes?
Mr. Lloyd Mackey: Mm-mm.
Dr. George O'Malley: I mean, uh, you can, uh... What are you examining me for?
Dr. George O'Malley: Oh, you know, just routine medical stuff.
Dr. George O'Malley: You're doing very well.
Mr. Lloyd Mackey: Because I'm enjoying the view.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He's stable.
Unknown / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): For now.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I had a radiologist look at his chest films.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He has a traumatic aortic injury.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He's going to rupture and bleed out.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): So he needs surgery.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): If he's going to remain a viable organ donor, yeah.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): If he's going to live.
Izzie Stevens / Mrs. Davidson OR Mrs. Davidson OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Is he?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Preston Burke OR Mrs. Davidson OR Mrs. Davidson OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): No, I'm not giving up on him.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He has the surgery.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He lives longer.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): That's the point.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): So I'm going to help find the family.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You guys find a way to get him into surgery.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): She's the vice president of Fantasyland.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): So who do we go to for the surgery?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Bailey?
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): We need to go higher than Bailey.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Dr. Burke?
Dr. Preston Burke: Hello.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): OK.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Um, I know you're busy, but our John Doe needs an aortic repair.
Dr. Preston Burke: The guy from this morning?
Dr. Burke / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Isn't he legally dead?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Well, yeah.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): He's kind of still around.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): We gave him two units of PRBCs and put him on pressers.
Preston Burke / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): On whose orders?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Mine.
Preston Burke / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You get a brain-dead John Doe of blood transfusion without consulting anyone, and now you want me to repair his heart?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Well, yes.
Preston Burke / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You do enjoy crossing our line, don't you?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He is an excellent candidate for organ donation.
Preston Burke / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I am a surgeon.
Preston Burke / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I save lives.
Preston Burke / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): This guy is already dead.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Now, this is the men's room.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Either whip one out or close the door.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You're asking my advice?
Izzie Stevens / Unknown (PVM): Yes.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Now, who's chasing?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Not funny.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): This is important.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): OK.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You want to get around Burke?
Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You got to find a way to get the chief involved.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): What'd I do?
Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): How close a match for the liver is your guy to our John Doe?
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Very.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Same type, same size.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You knows couldn't find a better match.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Why?
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He's the chief's VIP, right?
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Right.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): How much would you kill to be in on a transplant surgery?
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You underestimate me.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I'm not a baby.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I'm your colleague.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You don't have to manipulate me.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): If you want something, all you have to do is ask.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley OR Mrs. Davidson OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): We want you to go over Burke's head to the chief.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Ask me something easier.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Sir?
Richard Webber / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Oh, Mally.
Richard Webber / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): How's Mackie?
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Fine.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Sir, actually, that's what I want to talk to you about.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I kind of think that me and the other interns, we think we're not.
Richard Webber / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Well, now I'm not getting any younger.
Izzy Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): We found Mackie a liver.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): We are so going to hell.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Burke is sending us straight to hell.
Unknown (possibly George or another intern) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): On an express train.
Unknown (possibly George or Cristina) / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It works.
Unknown (possibly Cristina or Izzie) / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): What are you doing?
Unknown (possibly George or Alex) / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Nothing.
Unknown (possibly George or Cristina) / Unknown (PVM): Yes.
Unknown (likely an intern, possibly George or Cristina) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Dr. Burke!
Unknown (possibly George or another intern) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Excellent work, sir.
Unknown (possibly George or Cristina) / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Excellent.
Unknown (possibly Cristina or Alex) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Flawless.
Unknown (possibly Cristina or Alex) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It's a shame he's brain dead.
Unknown (possibly Cristina or Alex) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): If he wasn't, he would be on his feet in a few days.
Unknown (possibly Cristina or George) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I'm amazed at what skill your hands have.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I seriously hate that guy.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Alex's vermin.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): That surgery is ours.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): At least Burke is doing the surgery.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I don't care about Alex.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): George, you did good.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I'm going to have to dodge Burke for the rest of my career.
George O'Malley / Mrs. Davidson OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He could kill me and make it look like an accident.
Unknown (possibly Nurse or Doctor) / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): The police call.
Unknown (possibly Nurse or Doctor) / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): They've identified your John Doe.
Unknown (possibly Nurse or Doctor) / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): His wife is on the way.
Mrs. Stevenson / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Oh, my god.
Mrs. Stevenson / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Kevin.
Dr. Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It's OK.
Mrs. Stevenson / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Oh, my god.
Dr. Isobel Stevens: Mrs. Stevenson, this is Dr. Stevens.
Dr. Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Mrs. Davidson (PVM): Now, if you have any questions at all, please, please call me.
Mrs. Stevenson / Mrs. Davidson (PVM): Is there still a chance?
Dr. Stevens / Mrs. Davidson OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): We can hold off till morning.
Dr. Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): But if there's still no change, we'd like to talk to you about organ donation.
Dr. Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Mackie.
Dr. Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): How are we treating you?
Mackie / Mr. Lloyd Mackey (PVM): Oh, fine.
Mackie / Mr. Lloyd Mackey (PVM): Except that beautiful boy won't let me smoke.
Mackie / Mr. Lloyd Mackey (PVM): You should reprimand him.
Mackie / Dr. George O'Malley OR Mr. Lloyd Mackey (PVM): Make him change bedpans.
Dr. Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Mackie, that beautiful boy may have found you a liver.
Mackie / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): God, I smell good.
Mackie / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You know what it is?
Mackie / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It's the smell of open-heart surgery.
Mackie / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It's awesome.
Another patient / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It is awesome.
Mackie / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You gotta smell me.
Another patient / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I don't want to smell you.
Mackie / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Oh, yes, you do.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You are good to be kidding me.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Okay, I have more important things to deal with than you.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I have roommates and boy problems and family problems.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You want to act like a little frat boy bitch, that's fine.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You want to take credit for your saves and everybody else's, that's fine too.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Just stay out of my face.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): And for the record, you smell like crap.
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): She attacked me.
Alex Karev / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Meredith!
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You know what?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You might want to leave before I change my mind and let her beat you to a pulp with her tiny, ineffectual fists.
Alex Karev / Mrs. Davidson (PVM): What?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Nothing.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It's just...
George O'Malley / Mrs. Davidson OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Oh, this one is skin grafting.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Skin grafting?
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): No way.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I've never seen that done before.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Are those my mother's surgical tapes?
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Please watch the skin grafting one first.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Where did all this stuff come from?
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Oh, I unpacked some of your mother's things.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I was upset.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): And when I'm upset, I like to nest.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Oh, I have my palvectomy.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I think we should watch this one first.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): No.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): We're not watching my mother's surgery tapes.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): We're not unpacking boxes.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): We're not having long conversations where we celebrate the moments of our lives.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): And use a coaster.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley OR Mrs. Davidson (PVM): I ordered Chinese food.
Meredith Grey / Mrs. Davidson (PVM): I hate Chinese food!
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): They're everywhere, all the time.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Izzy's all perky, and George does this thing where he's helpful and considerate.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): They share food, and they say things, and they move things, and they breathe.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): They're, like, happy.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Kick them out.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I can't kick them out.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): They just moved in.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I asked them to move in.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): So what?
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You're just going to repress everything in some deep, dark, twisted place until one day you snap and kill them?
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Yep.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): This is why we are friends.
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Why is the Nazi making us stay in the pit two days in a row?
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Leftovers.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Leftovers.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Got to get the cyclist who were too drunk or too stupid or too scared to get themselves to a hospital yesterday.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Well, meanwhile, she gets to do a freaking organ harvest.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): That kills me, doesn't it?
Izzie Stevens / Mrs. Davidson (PVM): What?
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): That two women caught the harvest.
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): No, it kills me that anybody got the harvest but me.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Boobs do not factor into this equation.
Dr. Richard Webber / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Come on, son.
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You want to show me yours?
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I'm going to become a lesbian.
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Me too.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Now, Mrs. Davidson, this form simply says you've consented the donation of your husband's major organs, heart, lungs, liver, and kidneys.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Now I need to ask you a few questions.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Are you willing to donate his corneas?
Mrs. Davidson: But you want his eyes?
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Um, corneal transplants can give someone back their sight.
Mrs. Davidson: I suppose that's OK.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): What about his skin?
Mrs. Davidson: What?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): It's used to help burn victims.
Alex Karev / Mrs. Davidson (PVM): You want to cut off his skin?
Family Member (possibly Mackey's relative) / Mrs. Davidson (PVM): What about the funeral?
Family Member (possibly Mackey's wife or daughter) / Mrs. Davidson (PVM): You want me to have a funeral and have people look at him?
Family Member (possibly Mackey's wife or daughter) / Mrs. Davidson (PVM): Have his daughter look at her father and he doesn't have any skin?
Alex Karev / Mrs. Davidson (PVM): It's his skin.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): What are you doing?
Alex Karev / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I'm not a people person.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): No kidding.
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I can't do that.
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I can't talk to the families of patients.
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I'm sorry.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): What's his name?
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Who?
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): The patient.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): What's his name?
Alex Karev / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Kevin Davidson.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Remember that.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Not Gorkt Guy.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Not John Doe.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Kevin Davidson.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): He's someone's husband.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Someone's son.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Not a collection of body parts for you to harvest.
Unknown Resident / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): A person.
Unknown Resident / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): No one said this was easy.
Mr. Mackey / Mr. Lloyd Mackey OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I owe you, George.
George / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): No, you don't owe me anything.
George / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I'm just happy we found a liver.
Mr. Mackey / Mr. Lloyd Mackey (PVM): Well, when I get out of here, how about I take you and my new liver out for a night on the town?
Mr. Mackey / Mr. Lloyd Mackey (PVM): What do you say?
George / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Uh, Mr. Mackey, no offense or anything.
Mr. Mackey / Dr. George O'Malley OR Mr. Lloyd Mackey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You're very handsome, but I, um, I'm not, I mean, you're not my type, because you're a man, and... George, I never thought you were gay.
George / Mr. Lloyd Mackey (PVM): You didn't?
Charles / Mr. Lloyd Mackey (PVM): Oh, Charles, please.
Unknown Resident / Mr. Lloyd Mackey (PVM): You?
Unknown Resident / Mr. Lloyd Mackey (PVM): Gay?
Mr. Mackey / Mr. Lloyd Mackey (PVM): I'm sick, George, not blind.
George / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Then why have you?
Mr. Mackey / Mr. Lloyd Mackey (PVM): Well, because dying is a get-out-of-jail-free card.
Mr. Mackey / Mr. Lloyd Mackey (PVM): I can be as bold as I want, and there's nothing anybody can say about it.
Mr. Mackey / Mr. Lloyd Mackey (PVM): So I flirt.
Mr. Mackey / Mr. Lloyd Mackey (PVM): Haven't you ever been attracted to someone you know you couldn't have?
George / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Well, I'm...
George / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): No.
Mr. Mackey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): What's her name?
George / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): There's no... I'm not... You know, this is really not... Meredith.
Unknown Resident / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Let's go get that liver shot.
Izzy Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): No, I'm sorry.
Izzy Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I didn't... I never liked harvesting.
Resident / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Why?
Izzy Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Like I said, I'm a surgeon.
Izzy Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I save lives.
Resident / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): This ends well.
Resident / Mrs. Davidson (PVM): I know you tried, so no hard feelings, OK?
Izzy Stevens / Mr. Lloyd Mackey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I was just.
Resident / Mr. Lloyd Mackey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You were saying goodbye.
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): What's Viper doing here?
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Probably crashed his bike again.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): How long has he been waiting?
Cristina Yang / Mr. Lloyd Mackey (PVM): Don't know.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Lloyd Mackey (PVM): Busy on real cases.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Lloyd Mackey (PVM): He's all yours.
Alex Karev / Mr. Lloyd Mackey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Viper.
Alex Karev / Mrs. Davidson (PVM): Viper?
Alex Karev / Mrs. Davidson (PVM): Are you OK?
Dr. Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Call up to the OR and tell them we're coming in.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Page Dr. Bailey.
Intern (likely Alex Karev) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Right away.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Alex, let's go.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Alex, push the damn gurney.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Clear the way.
Hospital Staff Member / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Coming through.
Hospital Staff Member / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Somebody get the elevator.
Hospital Staff Member / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Hurry.
Hospital Staff Member / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I don't know how long I can keep this room closed.
Hospital Staff Member / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Move faster.
Hospital Staff Member / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Damn it.
Doctor / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): This is a new one.
Doctor / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Somebody get her off my patient.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Mrs. Davidson OR Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Meredith, go get cleaned up from scrubbing.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Mrs. Davidson OR Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Alex, get back downstairs.
Alex Karev / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Yeah, but I help.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Help?
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley OR Mrs. Davidson OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Yeah, they tell me down in the pit you only want to take the hot kicks.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mrs. Davidson OR Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Every pack of interns, there's always one fool running around trying to show off.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): And Alex, this time that fool is you.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Get out.
Short Doctor or Surgeon / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You better give me something to stand on.
Short Doctor or Surgeon / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Lower this table.
Short Doctor or Surgeon / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Mountain's going to have to come to me.
Doctor or Anesthesiologist / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Count backwards from 10 for me.
Patient (Mac) / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You're a good friend.
Friend or Doctor / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): The best.
Doctor or Nurse / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Shut up and count backwards already, Mac.
Patient (Mac) / Unknown (PVM): Nine.
Viper's Friend / Unknown (PVM): Nine.
Viper's Friend / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I'm not going to stay.
Another Friend / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It's your job.
Another Friend / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You have to.
Viper's Friend / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You're better at this part than me.
Viper's Friend / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I don't want to watch him get taken apart.
Resident / Mrs. Davidson OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Look at the vultures waiting to pick him clean.
Resident / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Every last one of them represents someone somewhere who's going to live because of Kevin.
Resident / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Here, put it on.
Viper's Friend / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): All right.
Viper's Friend / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I'll be waiting next door when you're ready.
Viper's Friend / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Everyone's waiting.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Okay, doctors, let's get this over with.
Viper's Friend / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You are my joy.
Resident / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): So don't be scared of all the hurtful words.
Resident / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Because in the end they'll hurt themselves much more.
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You are my joy.
Denny Duquette / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You are my joy.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You are my joy.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Izzy, I'm going to sew him up for his family.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You do it.
Cristina Yang / Mrs. Davidson (PVM): What?
Cristina Yang / Mrs. Davidson (PVM): Mrs. Davidson?
Cristina Yang / Mrs. Davidson (PVM): He's ready if you'd like to see him.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): This lovely group's his friends.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Uh, you all belong to, what was his name?
Friend of Patient / Mr. Lloyd Mackey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Viper.
Another Friend / Mr. Lloyd Mackey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Viper.
Friend of Patient / Mr. Lloyd Mackey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Yeah, we were in the race.
Friend of Patient / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): How is he?
Another Friend / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Is he OK?
Izzie Stevens / Mrs. Davidson OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Yeah.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): No.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): No, he's not OK at all.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): He hurled his body down a concrete mountain at full speed for no good reason.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Hey, yeah, yeah, I know you all pierce yourselves and smoke up and generally treat your bodies like your grungy asses can't break down.
Friend of Patient / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Hey, that's fine.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You want to kill yourselves flying down a concrete mountain?
Unknown (likely a surgeon or nurse) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Go to it.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): But there are other people walking, people driving, people trying to live their lives on that concrete mountain, and one of them got his brain scrambled today because one of you little sniveling no-good snot rag.
Unknown (off-screen or on-screen character addressing Dr. Bailey) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Dr. Bailey.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Yeah, so, OK, no.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Your friend Viper, as far as I'm concerned, is not OK.
Unknown (possibly an intern or resident) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): She's, um, really tired.
Unknown (possibly Dr. Bailey or another doctor) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): But Viper's gonna make it.
Unknown (possibly Dr. Bailey or another doctor) / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He's gonna live.
Unknown (likely a patient or Viper's friend) / Dr. George O'Malley OR Mrs. Davidson OR Mrs. Davidson (PVM): Thanks.
Unknown (possibly Meredith Grey or Derek Shepherd) / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It's not the chase.
Unknown (possibly Meredith Grey or Derek Shepherd) / Mrs. Davidson (PVM): What?
Unknown (possibly Meredith Grey or Derek Shepherd) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You and me.
Unknown (possibly Meredith Grey or Derek Shepherd) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): It is not the thrill of the chase.
Unknown (possibly Meredith Grey or Derek Shepherd) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): It's not a game.
Unknown (possibly Meredith Grey or Derek Shepherd) / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): It's... It's your tiny, ineffectual fists.
Unknown (possibly Meredith Grey or Derek Shepherd) / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): And your hair.
Unknown (possibly Meredith Grey or Derek Shepherd) / Mrs. Davidson (PVM): My hair?
Unknown (possibly Meredith Grey or Derek Shepherd) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It smells good.
Unknown (possibly Meredith Grey or Derek Shepherd) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): And you're very, very bossy.
Unknown (possibly Meredith Grey or Derek Shepherd) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It keeps me in line.
Unknown (likely Meredith Grey) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I'm still not going out with you.
Unknown (possibly Derek Shepherd) / Dr. George O'Malley OR Mrs. Davidson (PVM): Can you say that now?
Unknown (possibly Dr. Bailey or Dr. Shepherd) / Mrs. Davidson OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): How'd it go?
Unknown (possibly Dr. Bailey or Dr. Shepherd) / Dr. George O'Malley OR Mr. Lloyd Mackey (PVM): Very smoothly.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Lloyd Mackey (PVM): Damn.
Alex Karev / Mr. Lloyd Mackey (PVM): That means I have to quit smoking?
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Mrs. Davidson OR Mr. Lloyd Mackey (PVM): Ah, the pretty ones always come falling back.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): There's another way to survive this competition.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): A way no one ever seems to tell you about.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): One you have to learn for yourself.
Ellis Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Number five.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It's not about the race at all.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): There are no winners or losers.
Meredith Grey / Mrs. Davidson OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Victories are counted by the number of lives saved.
Izzie Stevens / Mrs. Davidson (PVM): Oh, OK.
Cristina Yang / Mrs. Davidson OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): This is the best part.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Watch.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): She pulls a black spinning down over her face.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): We were... Hi.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): We were just, uh... Christina made us.
Dr. Meredith Gray: And once in a while, if you're smart, a life you save could be your own.
Richard Webber / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): What are we watching?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Ooh.
Dr. Meredith Gray: This is the one where my mother... Literally pulls this guy's face off.
Izzie Stevens / Mrs. Davidson OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Yeah.
Izzie Stevens / Mrs. Davidson (PVM): Go, Barb!
George O'Malley / Mrs. Davidson (PVM): Go, Barb!
Cristina Yang / Mrs. Davidson (PVM): Go, Barb!