Doctors spend a lot of
time focused on the future.
Planning it.
Working toward it.
But, at some point,
you start to realize
your life is happening now.
- Any changes overnight?
- No.
Not after med school, not
after residency. Right now.
This is it. It's here.
Blink, and you'll miss it.
That's the chief. Somebody
better make a coffee run.
You all look like hell.
I gotta be in surgery
in ten minutes. Um...
- Mer, will you let me know...
- Yeah.
We should go too. It's
probably gonna be a while.
Shepherd said she'd wake up.
What'd he tell you? Was that all crap?
- What did he say?
- He said it may be a while.
She's gonna wake up.
♪ That's just your way ♪
♪ It's true ♪
♪ It's all love All love ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ It's all of my stupid love ♪
♪ It's all love All love ♪
Stevens still isn't awake and
I'm having something of a day,
even aside from that, so
don't take my face personally.
- It's just my face today.
- Did you tell her?
Uh, you should tell her. And
don't take her face personally.
OK. Well, on behalf of the
Department of Pediatric Surgery,
welcome to the fellowship
program. You're in!
- We're gonna
get you wheelie sneaks!
- Congratulations.
All right, I know I didn't
support you during this process.
In any event, I am
behind you now.
I'm trying to be a big person here.
How about you meet me halfway?
Wake up, wake up, wake up.
I have a headache.
You're up.
You're up and you're talking.
You talked, right?
- Talk!
- Ow...
I said I have a
headache, stop yelling.
- Page Shepherd!
- Ow.
Sorry.
Hey. What's with
hugging O'Malley?
I slept, Cristina. Last night.
I slept for the first time...
- I slept.
- Hugging O'Malley
because you slept?
I hugged O'Malley because he's got
great news which I will let him tell you.
But yeah, I guess, yeah, maybe
I hugged him because I slept.
And that's because of you. You came
with me to see my mom, and then I slept.
And I slept without nightmares.
That's not a small thing, Cristina.
That... That is everything.
I can be a better man. I
can be a better man for you.
I hope, if you'll let me,
I can be a better man with you.
Don't say anything. Just
think about it. OK? OK.
- Bailey? I need
to tell you something.
- Not now, O'Malley.
It'll be quick. I got to get to
the OR to scrub in with the chief.
I think you're gonna be mad at first.
But I'm about to do something important,
and I'm very sure
about this decision.
And I think eventually you're gonna
be proud but, you know, before that,
you're probably gonna
be like "What did you do?"
- I don't mean to imitate.
- You call that quick?
I joined the Army to be a trauma
surgeon. I report for duty tomorrow.
- You did what?!
- That's where
I thought we'd start.
- Something's going on
with George.
- What?
Owen hugged him.
They were happy.
We don't hug when we're happy.
- Are you better?
- What?
You know, with your therapy or
whatever. You said you got well.
Well are you? Better?
Or are you just fake better?
- What do you mean?
- I'm asking you if people...
I mean, are you actually
different? Do you feel different?
I'm getting married today.
City Hall. No muss, no
fuss. Just quick and dirty.
- Uh... Do you want me to come?
- No, no. Just letting you know.
Wait. Uh... Uh...
OK. This is my
grocery list: it's old.
Uh, this is new. Um...
This is my favorite pen,
so I want it back. Borrowed.
All of it's blue,
so you're covered.
Now see, if we were George
and Owen, we would hug right now.
Dude!
Unidentified male, dragged by a bus.
Clamped down so we couldn't intubate.
- Didn't they stop?
- Bus driver didn't know
- till they got halfway
down the block.
- Is he gonna be OK?
OK, I'll take over CPR.
Push 20 of etomidate
and 100 of sux.
He saved my life. The bus was gonna
hit me, he threw me out of the way.
- Grey, get her out of here.
- Was supposed to be me
under the bus.
He's alone. They don't
even know who he is. Please!
Stand over there
and just don't move.
- He's back.
- Let's get a trauma series,
trauma labs and O-neg blood in
here. Severe injury to the left forearm.
- Skull's bashed in. Page Shepherd!
- And Sloan.
Start antibiotics and start
cleaning out those wounds.
Uh...
Now can you get her out of here?
Did you get the whole thing?
- Did you get
the whole tumor out?
- Just let me finish my exam.
- Can you tell me your name?
- My name is Isobel Stevens,
it's 2009
and I'm in the Neuro ICU
at Seattle Grace Hospital.
- Did you get
the damn thing out?
- Got the whole damn thing.
- You got it!
- Yeah.
Oh, God, you got
the whole thing.
And I can talk and I know
my name. And I'm not a turnip!
- Nope.
- No offense,
you are a great surgeon,
but I really thought I
was gonna be a turnip.
- This is so unbelievably great!
- Your kidneys are a little
sluggish,
so we're gonna keep an eye on
your electrolytes for a few hours.
- Your post-op crit was fine.
- OK, good.
Good.
How'd the surgery go?
Did you get the brain
tumor? Did you get it out?
Iz, you just asked him
that. We just talked about it.
No, no. It's OK. She's gonna be
foggy for a while. The tumor's out.
There was a little
bleeding during the post.
- You got it?
- Yeah.
All of it?
That's amazing!
Derek Shepherd, you are a hero!
And I know that that's Derek
Shepherd, and you're Alex.
And you should kiss me.
Alex, I don't have
a brain tumor.
- I'm tumor free.
- Yes, you are.
What's wrong?
- Why do you look weird?
- Nothing. Nothing.
Your kidneys are a little
slow. We're gonna watch them.
OK, you'll re-check my
electrolytes in an hour. OK.
How did the surgery go?
Did you get the tumor?
We did.
Tumor's gone.
There was a little bit of
bleeding and we took care of that.
- You got it?
- Mm-hm.
Oh, my God!
And I can talk and
you didn't kill me.
What's wrong with you people?
We should be celebrating.
She's like the woman who couldn't
remember her husband was dead.
- We had to keep telling her.
- Could be a normal haze.
Or the bleeding blitzed her short-term
retention. Did you screw up her brain?
Karev... I'll be back.
Try and stay calm.
Freaking her out
is not gonna help.
Wake up.
Whoa.
- Man versus bus.
- Bus won.
Check out the left arm.
- He's crashing again!
- What do we got?
- Roadkill.
- You mind?
Stepped in front of a bus to pull
a woman out of the way. Hero.
- Can you can fix the arm?
- If it's gonna happen,
- gotta be in the next few hours.
- - Pupil's blown.
Get me a cranial drill. Grey,
want to practice your burr holes?
Stabilize his neck, please.
Give me a ten-blade.
Give me the drill. Go in
slowly. Feel a grab, stop.
Otherwise, you'll hit brain.
Let's go, quickly.
- OK!
- That's it!
Nice work, Dr. Grey.
I'm gonna get some
Bacitracin for that face.
- Let's get his head rotated.
- Easy.
Welcome back, sir. You had
us worried there for a minute.
- You think he's gonna make it?
- I hope so.
He really has to make it.
- Dr. Sloan.
- There's gonna
be too much tension.
Start over and do
a layered closure.
Um...
Can I ask a question about that?
OK, you brought up moving in
together and marriage, and I put it off,
now you're embarrassed
and won't make eye contact
because you feel I
have all the power.
But I don't want all the
power. I'm happy to share it.
Can we just skip this part?
Get some 4-0 Vicryl so you
can redo your patient's sutures.
I'll totally pretend I
didn't hear any of that.
Women do this to
me. I don't do this.
- "Let's get a house."
- Sucks being the girl.
I'm not the girl.
What do girls do?
Well, we start with the cold
shoulder, so you're right on track.
Then we go to our
girlfriends and we bitch.
And our girlfriends say,
"You want to build a future,
build it yourself.
You don't need...
a man to give you that. You
want to buy a house? Buy a house."
Huh. You're good at this.
I ought to help someone get
a love life. I suck at my own.
He jumped in front
of a bus for me.
- What did you do to O'Malley?
- Excuse me?
Somebody else here likely to
convince someone to join the Army
- and be a trauma surgeon
in Iraq?
- What? Army?
What?
- V-fib!
- Charge the paddles to 360!
- Call who you have
to and undo this.
- Bailey, busy here.
- Clear!
- George O'Malley?
- It wasn't my idea!
- No change.
- Charge again.
- Clear!
I gave him a decent education in trauma.
I didn't know he was gonna go enlist.
- He keeps coding.
- Open-book pelvic fracture.
Too much bleeding. We take him
to an OR now, he'll die on the table.
He needs to go to Angio if
we're gonna stop the bleeding.
Sinus tach. We have a rhythm.
Barely there, but it's there.
Let's stabilize the pelvis.
I know what goes
on in this hospital.
I know you're messed up from
that war. And not in a small way.
Get him out of it.
Page me if you need
me. I've got other patients.
How'd you piss
off all the women?
- Let's get our guy to Angio.
- Angio? He's barely got
a pulse!
It's now or never, if we
want him to live. Move!
I know it's tough, but I'd be grateful
if you'd stay alive for a few minutes.
Maybe we're bouncier in
peds than general surgery,
but I thought there would be a
"Yay!" or some jumping around.
You look pretty dour for someone
about to start a highly prized fellowship.
You are about to start a
highly prized fellowship, right?
Hey, I've got a plan to
stop George. You in?
- Stop George from what?
- He joined the Army. Yes, I'm in.
Bailey! I'm talking to you...
- Why are you trying
to stop him?
- He joined the Army.
- And?
- And because he's my ex-husband
and I know his mom
and I love his mom.
And normally, Izzie would talk
sense into him, but she's got cancer
and kind of a bad mental
deficit, so it's on me to stop him.
- Why would you want to?
- He joined the Army.
- Don't you think
that's a problem?
- I think that's awesome.
Awesome?
- You gonna chew?
- My dragged under
a bus guy's in Angio.
They're gonna page me.
How's Izzie? Retaining anything?
- No.
- OK.
Uh, at 6pm, your idiotic
colleague George O'Malley
will finish his
surgery with the chief.
At 6pm, you will be standing beside
us in the OR hallway prepared to join
- in an intervention.
- - What polite company call
an intervention, though
I'm not sure interventions
involve whupping
people on the behinds
- with a belt.
- What? He's got
a drinking problem now?
- He joined the Army.
- What?
Double O Seven? He can't
go, he's the guy that gets killed.
Gets killed cleaning
his own gun.
Grey is going to coax
him back as a loving friend,
you're gonna use logic and reason
to point out the idiocy of his ways,
Stevens will make sad cancer
eyes, and if all of that doesn't work,
Karev, you pull out your "I was raised
out back with the trash cans" roots
- and just beat
the crap out of him.
- Six o'clock.
Six o'clock.
Hey, there.
I know this must be scary. If it's any
consolation, you're a hardcore hero.
You saved that woman's life.
Is he trying to write something?
Can you hold this?
OK. You'll be stronger tomorrow.
Call OR 1, tell them
to get ready for him.
OK.
Amanda, you can't be out here.
Would you want to be all
alone at a time like this?
We had 30 seconds of
interaction before he saved my life,
and I wasn't even nice.
I was standing on
a corner when this
ordinary-looking guy
stands next to me and smiles.
And... And I'm so busy
scoping for someone hotter,
that... I don't even
give him a second look.
Next thing I know, he throws
me out of the way of a bus
I'm about to walk in front of
and almost gets himself killed.
He literally... he
swept me off my feet.
That is my prince in that bed.
OK. You can stay until
they take him to surgery.
Not a good time.
Walk away from me again, I will
grab you by the hair and pull hard.
I grew up with the name
Arizona. I learned how to play dirty.
I stuck my neck out for
you. You were my pick.
And I appreciate that.
But it's a big decision.
It's not, it's the brass ring. It's the
most exclusive, most competitive
and we're as good as it gets.
Nobody lands this thing and says "no."
My husband informed me yesterday
that if I accept the peds fellowship,
if I sign on for another
two years of training
and the hours and
workload that come with it,
when I could be a general surgery
attending and make it home for dinner,
he will divorce me.
It's a big decision.
Gonna have a hard
time saving that arm.
I can get him back to full
function if I can get there in time.
- Thinking about buying a house.
- Good.
Meredith and I are gonna
go to City Hall this afternoon.
- Getting married.
- Really? That's great news.
- If I could
just save Stevens...
- You're allowed to be happy.
You're allowed to get married.
You've earned that right.
Congratulations, you lucky
bastard. Come here, give me a hug.
- Why is everyone hugging today?
- The blushing bride.
Here's the plan
for our John Doe.
Shepherd, evacuate the epidural,
Grey and I correct internal injuries.
Torres will place
the internal fixator.
Sloan should work on the arm if
the patient doesn't get too acidotic.
- You think he has a shot?
- I've seen people come back
from worse.
- Hey. I thought
you were in surgery.
- I'm on my way.
You talked to Bailey
about peds and Tucker?
No. I talked to Bailey about
the Army thing and George.
Are you upset with me?
No. I'm awesome.
- Calliope...
- No. Do not "Calliope" me.
You said it was awesome.
George, sweet, kind George,
who can't even kill a fly is
joining the Army to go to Iraq
- and you said awesome.
- It is. Awesome.
No, it is not awesome!
God! Who are you?
- How's the arm?
- Nerves are intact,
- just have to reattach these vessels.
- - You ready for me?
I'm almost done with the
major internal crush injuries.
Pelvis will be all yours.
Get me some more laps.
You think you could do it? Step in
front of a bus for a perfect stranger?
We'd all like to
think we would...
More or less what
Hunt's been doing
- every day
for the last couple years.
- No. The guys did.
I just came in behind them with a
dustpan and broom and swept up.
You sewed up soldiers
under fire. You didn't sweep up.
How do you think O'Malley's gonna
do over there? Think he can handle it?
- No, I don't.
- I think he's gonna
surprise us all.
He's coming back in a body bag.
I think you all
should just shut up.
Just shut the hell up.
Please, shut up.
"Shepherd got your whole
tumor out." Oh, my God!
Alex, why didn't you
tell me? Oh, my God!
- Oh.
- We're working on it.
Remember what time
you woke up this morning?
Um...
- Not exactly.
- 7:45.
7:45. "O'Malley
joined the Army?"
Gonna be a trauma
surgeon in Iraq.
- When'd you wake up?
- 7:45. He's gonna get killed.
- We're dealing with it.
- Did you know about this George thing?
Yup. Cannon fodder. I'm just
gonna take some more blood.
Last time we checked, your potassium
was 6.3. When'd you wake up?
- Um, early,
I can't quite remember.
- 7:45.6.3, 7:45.
- "O'Malley joined
the Army?" George?
- We're dealing with it.
- What's your potassium?
- I...
- Iz, what's your potassium?
- - Give her the chart to read
and try and memorize, OK? I can
talk to you about her hyperkalemia.
She had brain surgery, and an
incredibly aggressive course of IL-2.
- She needs rest.
- She needs to exercise memory
- before it all turns to mush.
- Not with you barking orders
at her.
- Butt out.
- I don't care
if you're her husband.
Want to see how fast I can get
your visiting hours down to zero?
She signed a DNR.
She signed a friggin' DNR
and made me promise she'd come out
of this with a life. Not in a hospital bed.
Not with no brain. I had to
promise she'd have a life.
You want to know what happens
if she can't make new memories?
Forget about being a doctor. She'll
need round the clock babysitters.
We get an apartment, she
can't find her way to the toilet!
Tracker on her ankle in case
she wanders out the front door!
Alex. You can handle
this. She will get better.
Maybe, maybe not.
It's on me. Her future is on me.
- Is he gonna be OK?
- We'll know more
in the morning.
Go ahead.
How's she doing? Any better?
- No.
- Damn.
Well, I'm going to City Hall
- to go do the thing.
- Seriously?
It doesn't seem
like the day for it.
Look at Alex. He's in there
working so hard all day.
And she doesn't know.
And if she stays like this,
she may never know how much
he loves her. And that girl Amanda?
She's in there loving a stranger.
She thinks that's her Prince Charming.
He's probably gonna
die today. Chances are.
So, yeah, I'm gonna go get
married. Because I think it's important
to take the time to tell the people
you love how much you love them
while they can hear you.
I love you, Cristina Yang.
- You have changed.
- Maybe I have.
- What?
- I'm gonna hug you.
Maybe I don't understand
people. I don't see things.
Maybe I just don't get what's
going on with you or why you're mad,
but I think it's awesome. George
joining the Army is awesome.
- Shut up!
- Um, no.
You asked me who I was.
I am a person who thinks
that what George is doing is
dangerous and terrifying and brave.
He's going to serve his country.
He's going to risk his life to save
the men and women who make it possible
for you and I to sleep in our beds.
I am a person who
thinks that that is brave.
And I am a person who
stood in an airplane hangar
and watched them unload
my brother's body in a coffin,
and all we got was a flag.
My brother died over there because
there weren't enough doctors.
So for my money, George
O'Malley is a patriot. He's a hero.
And I am grateful that he exists.
So, yeah, the word I use is "awesome."
That's who I am.
I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry...
- Wait!
I love... you.
- I... I love you too.
- No.
Just...
I love you.
I said I love you!
Me.
Cristina Yang!
- You traumatized me.
- I didn't know... I'm so sorry.
No, damn it, not about the choking.
You come here and you pull out my icicle
and you make me
love you and I can't...
I don't want to...
I can't breathe...
without you.
You can do this,
Cristina. We can do this.
All you have to do
is meet me halfway.
All you have to do is say "yes."
- What's your crit?
- Ugh.
This is disgusting. I can't
believe we serve it to the patients.
"You keep asking for
lime Jell-O and don't like it."
So stop giving it to me.
You get mad if I don't.
- OK. Now what's your crit?
- I don't know.
- I'm tired.
- What's O'Malley
doing tomorrow?
Joining the Army.
- I need a break.
- You don't think
I need a break?
- Suck it up.
- God!
Back off. I'm sorry
if this is hard for you,
but you are not the one with
the short-term memory of a carrot.
Hey, go ahead, get it off your chest.
It's not like I'm gonna remember.
I'm not the one with the carrot
brain, but I'm married to it.
Some wedding we walked into, because
we thought you'd be dead in a week.
You made me promise
you wouldn't live like this.
What am I supposed to do?
Smother you with a pillow?
Shoot you up with an overdose of
morphine? Not really psyched about that.
Leave you? Not psyched about that,
either. So I'm kind of screwed, right?
Not as bad as you, but not a
friggin' walk in the park either!
I'm sorry, Iz.
No, I told you to get it
off your chest. You did.
Did you forget yet?
Nope.
Not yet, give me a minute.
Um...
If there's still a spot for me in
general surgery, I'd like to take it.
I spent months trying to talk
you off peds, I finally get on board,
- and you change your mind?
- Tucker gave me an ultimatum.
The fellowship or our marriage.
- You chose your marriage.
- No, I'm leaving him.
Because a marriage that resorts
to ultimatums is not a marriage.
I mean what kind of
husband does that?
So I'm going to be a single mom.
It's not the time
for new specialties.
Damn!
I'm sorry. It's just the first
time I've said it out loud.
It kind of took the
wind out of me.
Miranda, are you sure about
this? He might come around.
- He's just scared.
- We're all scared!
If you're not scared,
you're not paying attention!
One of my residents just signed
up to go to war! That's scary!
Another one almost
lost her life to melanoma,
and doesn't know what
day it is! That's scary!
What Tucker's
facing isn't scary!
He's just weak!
A pat on the back
isn't gonna help, sir.
Should I go?
OK.
I'll just stand here with
you, if that's all right.
Yes, sir. That would be fine.
I thought you were
operating on John Doe.
I already did. I'm looking at houses.
One has a stone fireplace which I like.
This one has a backyard
the size of Montana.
- Uh-huh. You're buying a house?
- Yeah.
Right. OK.
I'm buying a house. Right now. It's a
buyers' market and I'm buying a house.
The only reason you're even talking
about a house is to make me feel bad.
You're trying to prove you're moving
on without me so I'll change my mind.
This what women are doing
when they say they're moving on?
Yeah. They don't usually
take out a home loan to do it.
Pathetic. Let me be
clear. I'm moving on.
I'm a better woman than you.
- Ready to go?
- I just got a page.
Our John Doe needs
to go back into surgery.
Post-op CT showed a re-bleed.
I'm gonna have Nelson take care of it.
- No. Really?
- I'd prefer to do it myself,
but I wanna check in on Izzie. We
can do that first then get married after?
- We have the George
intervention after.
- I'll have Nelson do it.
Tell them to prep.
We'll run to City Hall,
- we'll come back
and we'll do it.
- Meredith.
No. Let's go. We gotta go.
We gotta run to City Hall,
come back, check on
Izzie, we'll monitor John Doe,
- talk George out of the Army...
- We could do this another day.
There is no other day!
Every day is like this.
Every day there's a
crisis. There's no time.
- Meredith...
- I love you. I wanna marry you today.
But there is no time.
- You have a piece of paper?
- For what?
I wanna be with you forever,
and you wanna be with me forever.
And in order to do that,
we need to make vows,
a commitment, a contract.
- Give me a piece of paper.
- I don't... I don't.
I have Post-its.
OK.
What do we want to
promise each other?
♪ Seems to hide ♪
♪ Deep inside your mind ♪
That you'll love me
even when you hate me.
To love each other even
when we hate each other.
No running, ever. Nobody walks
out. No matter what happens.
- No running.
- What else?
That we'll take care of each other even
when we're old and smelly and senile.
If I get Alzheimer's
and forget you...
I will remind you
who I am every day.
To take care when
old, senile, smelly.
This... is forever.
Sign.
- This is our wedding? A Post-it?
- Mm-hm.
Well, if you sign it.
♪ Pictures come alive ♪
♪ You can dance
right through your life ♪
♪ What a feeling ♪
Now what?
Now I kiss the bride.
♪ What a feeling ♪
- Married?
- Married.
See that?
Plenty of time.
- Gotta do an EKG.
- I don't even get
any small talk?
- What's your problem?
- I'll tell you.
I know I'm supposed to be
grateful for my new lease on life.
But Alex marched in here and
basically told me that being married to me
was the worst thing that
ever happened to him. Yeah.
And that he was trying to decide
if smothering me with a pillow
was the best way to put
us both out of our misery.
- OK, where is it?
- Where's what?
Where's the note that says that?
- Did you write that down?
- No.
No!
I'll be right there.
Yes.
Yes!
- I've gotta go. I've gotta find Alex.
- Go.
Oh. Sorry. I was looking
for George. It's after six.
Uh, we scheduled an intervention
so we could give O'Malley a piece of
our minds about this idiotic Army business.
- Did he leave already?
- He never scrubbed in.
He told me he was enlisting, I
sent him home to spend the day
with his mom since he's leaving
so soon. He took off this morning.
- How's his ICP?
- Worse. OR's expecting us.
- I thought you were
getting married.
- We did.
Sure you want to start
your honeymoon in an OR?
We're sure.
You can't be in here. I'll come
get you in the waiting room.
Hold his hand until you put him
under. It does make him feel better.
OK.
Well, you made a
good friend there.
That happens when you
take a bus for somebody.
OK. I know this is scary. But
you do have a great team up there.
You wanna try to write again?
Can you hold the pen? No?
OK. O?
O.
Seven?
Double O... Seven.
Oh, God! Oh, God!
- You paged. What do you need?
- Way to go dipwad.
Telling your wife
you're trying to off her?
Mind your business... Wait.
- How did you know that?
- She told me.
You remember?
Pillow or morphine.
I got the whole thing.
- I didn't mean that.
- Of course you didn't.
You love me too much to shoot me
up with morphine even if I asked you to.
And my stupid gorked
brain is coming back.
Oh, my God, I was so scared.
I mean, I would have
loved you no matter what.
You're back. You're back.
Iz. Iz?
Izzie!
- Yang!
- It's George! It's George!
It's George! John Doe is George!
Izzie, look at me!
Open your eyes!
Page Shepherd,
the chief, Bailey.
We have you, you hear me?
We have you, we'll fix this.
- Just stay with us.
- - O'Malley, it's Shepherd.
- You're not going anywhere.
- BP's dropping.
Put him out now!
- What happened?
- Is it her brain?
- Hyperkalemia.
- Couldn't control
the arrhythmias.
- Pressure's dropping.
- Intubation tray.
- Alex, she signed a DNR.
- Shut up!
- She knew this might happen.
- I don't give a crap!
It's not what she wants.
Get a crash cart!
- Karev, if she didn't...
- Look at her! Get a crash cart!
- Screw the DNR! Hand me those paddles!
- Yang, take over compressions.
- I got it.
- One, two, three.
And down.
Charge to 300.
Did you say it?
I love you?
Clear.
I don't ever want
to live without you?
You changed my life.
Did you say it?
Make a plan.
Set a goal, work toward it.
But every now and
then, look around.
Come on.
Drink it in.
♪ But never tie us down ♪
♪ They never tie us down ♪
♪ Loose ends tangle down ♪
♪ And then take flight ♪
♪ But never tie us down ♪
♪ Off I go ♪
'Cause this is it.
We're losing him!
♪ Where I fall ♪
♪ Is where I land ♪
Come on, Stevens.
Come on.
V-fib! Clear!
It might all be gone tomorrow.