Previously on Grey's Anatomy:
There's nothing sexual
between you and Georgie?
Don't come to me for
forgiveness, you traitorous bitch.
Our marriage is falling
apart. You're never here.
- I have a thing for her.
- Going to end badly.
Cardio is my thing.
You are flirting with cardio.
I am married to cardio.
What if while I'm waiting,
I meet someone who is
ready to give me
what I want from you?
- Are we friends yet?
- I'm sorry?
I don't want you to
date other people.
date anybody but me.
In the beginning, God created
the heaven and the earth.
At least that's what they say.
He created the birds of the
air and the beasts of the field
and he looked at his creation
and he saw that it was good.
And then God created man
and it's been downhill ever since.
- The woman loves me.
- Erica Hahn?
I'm telling you.
We went out last night,
had a couple drinks...
- You and Erica?
- Just me and Hahn.
And Callie.
All right. So, it wasn't a date.
You're gonna tell me
where we're going?
Why does it have to be
about the destination?
Why can't it be
about the journey?
Because I'm wearing
300 dollar shoes.
Meredith doesn't want
me seeing other people.
She found out
about you and Rose?
No. It was just a kiss.
You're not the kind who makes
out with nurses in scrub rooms,
not that there's
anything wrong with it.
- What do you think?
- It was more than just a kiss.
- No, no, no, no. The view.
- Well, what am I looking at?
The view from my new house.
Huh?
The story goes on to say that
God created man in his own image,
but there's not
much proof of that.
After all, God made the
sun, the moon, and the stars.
And all man makes is trouble.
It's a classic Victorian
design with an open floor plan.
- What are you doing?
- I'm making an omelet.
What do you think of the house?
The house? I think
the house is great.
If you don't like it you can
tell me. It's your house, too.
Damn.
So why are you cooking, again?
Lexie was having a bad night,
and I thought I would do
something semi-sisterly.
- Really?
- Really.
Wow.
- You getting up?
- No.
Maybe. I don't know.
- What's that smell?
- Someone's cooking.
That's not cooking.
- You're going to be late.
- I hate work.
- Since when?
- Since I hate it.
I hate Cristina. I
hate Hahn. I hate it.
What is that smell?
That smells like sulfur.
- Breakfast.
- It's breakfast.
No!
- Don't go. Don't go.
- What? I have to go.
She made me breakfast.
I'm going. Now stop. Off.
No.
Hey.
Where's your girlfriend?
Back with her husband.
I don't have a girlfriend.
- Or a conscience, apparently.
- But you knew that going in.
Not saying we have to
build, but we have to plan.
Dude, what the hell is that?
Meredith cooked, to do
something nice for Lexie.
- You cooked for me?
- It's no big deal.
Just eggs and avocado
and whatever cheese
that was in the fridge.
I love avocados.
Is it OK?
OK.
OK. This little man has
been fed and changed.
There we go.
I put the building manager's
number on my desk.
Do not believe him when he
tells you that he can fix the sink.
Remind him he's
the one that broke it
when he tried to fix the pipes.
- OK.
- Miranda.
You're talking to me now?
Now that I'm on my
way out the door?
You're always on your way out.
Are you interested in
being part of this family?
I can't do this now.
I don't have time.
- Dr. Torres.
- Dr. Hahn,
anyone who can outdrink
me and still kick my ass
at the dartboard gets
to call me "Callie."
Last night was
actually fun, wasn't it?
Mmm-hmm.
- And I'm not a group person.
- Me, neither.
I think it's because I
generally don't like people.
Me, neither.
Morning, ladies.
Case in point.
What's so funny?
When man finds
himself in trouble,
which is most of the time,
he turns to something
bigger than himself,
to love or fate or religion
to make sense of it all.
SweeTart?
Do you ever eat anything that
remotely resembles real food?
You'll have to take
me to dinner to find out.
I can't do that.
That kiss was unexpected.
I like kissing you.
I enjoyed kissing you,
but I'm seeing somebody.
Meredith Grey.
Everybody knows about
you and Meredith Grey.
I have to see it
through. I'm sorry.
Don't be. It was just a kiss.
See you in surgery,
Dr. Shepherd.
But for a surgeon,
the only thing that makes
any kind of sense is medicine.
Yes.
Back off. Elizabeth
Archer is my patient.
Technically, she's Hahn's
patient, but whatever.
I'm scrubbing in on a major
coronary artery dissection with Hahn,
and you're not going
to fight me for it?
I'm not doing the cardio
thing anymore. I am over it.
You're over it?
Whoa, whoa.
- Why? What do you have?
- Nothing. I'm charting.
Stevens. Elizabeth
Archer's chart?
Yang has it. You two have fun.
She's not a cardiothoracic
surgeon. I am the rock star.
- Karev, are you a rock star?
- Always.
You're with me today.
Congratulations. Your life
just got more interesting.
Karev doesn't know anything
about Elizabeth Archer.
You can read,
can't you, Dr. Karev?
Yes. "Elizabeth Archer, 49, came
into the ER yesterday complaining of..."
An urgent cardiac cath
demonstrated dissection
of the proximal
two-thirds of the LAD.
She was admitted
for observation.
While I admire your preparation,
there is one thing about the
patient you've failed to notice.
She's gone.
- Dr. O'Dell to the...
- Callie!
Mrs. O'Malley. Hi.
- Hi.
- How've you been?
Well, I've been
worried, is how I've been.
I've called, I've left messages.
I know how busy you two are,
but you can't pick up the phone
once in a while? Never
mind water under the bridge.
I was in the neighborhood,
and I hope you don't mind,
but I just couldn't
wait to show you
some of the outfits
I've been making.
- Outfits?
- Don't get mad,
but Georgie told me
you were trying, so...
what do you think?
- It's yellow.
- I see that.
Dr. Bailey?
Whatever it is, I
don't have time.
I think I need some epinephrine.
- Tucker, now's not a good time.
- Epinephrine?
The cart's around the corner.
Can you give her the...?
- Thank you.
- No, I told you,
I put it on my desk.
- Code blue.
- I have to call you back.
You're going to have to step
back from the patient, ma'am.
- Ma'am?
- Just one second.
Ms. Archer? What
is she doing here?
I have no idea. Who is she?
It's Hahn's patient. Ms. Archer,
you need to get back to your bed.
There.
What'd did you do to him?
He was V-tach and now...
I healed him. I'm a healer.
Oh!
You're a faith healer?
I am a healer and I have faith.
But I'm not sure
the two are related.
Ms. Archer, you collapsed.
You could go into cardiac
arrest at any moment.
I'm less interested in
what you do for a living
than I am with
getting you into...
I want to know what
she did to Mr. Greenwald.
He's been in and out of V-tach
all day and now he's stable.
Maybe because of the
amiodarone he got two hours ago.
Really? Does amiodarone
usually take two hours to kick in?
Ms. Archer, you have a
coronary artery dissection.
Dr. Karev and I need
to get you into surgery
as soon as possible.
I appreciate that, but I
am not going into surgery
until we've exhausted
all other possibilities.
Ms. Archer, if you don't
have the surgery soon,
I can guarantee you
that the blood supply
to your heart will be cut off.
I'll have to open you up anyway.
All I'm asking for is that
you give me some time
and talk me through the
surgery you'd like to perform,
so that I may visualize
it while I do what I do.
And if it doesn't work, then
you can slice me open, OK?
Dr. Karev can work with you
doing whatever
it is that you do.
I'll check in soon.
Call me when she codes.
Pharmacy two-nine-four.
- What are you looking for?
- I need epinephrine.
Why?
- What happened to you?
- I'm an adult child
of an alcoholic. I
have boundary issues.
When Meredith made me
eggs, I couldn't not eat them.
I had to pretend I
wasn't allergic to eggs,
now I have a rash
covering my body.
- Give me your arm.
- I'm codependent,
my throat is closing up.
Ow... And now my
arm hurts. Thanks.
You're welcome.
Thank you for letting
me crash on your couch.
You didn't tell your
mom that we broke up?
Your mom thinks we're
still trying to get pregnant.
She thinks you're
the kind of person
who would never
cheat on his wife.
Hand-stitched,
unisex baby clothes!
They're yellow and green
and go up to toddler sizes.
And she's waiting
for you in the lobby.
- Hey.
You never told me what
you thought of the house.
- I have a house.
- That's your house.
I'm talking our house.
Between yesterday and
today you had plans drawn up?
No, I've had the
plans for months.
But I decided to
share them with you.
Why?
Nothing's really
changed, has it?
Everything's the same as it was.
No, it's just...
it's really a lot.
And it's fast.
- I'm trying to
take a step forward.
- OK.
There are about 100 steps
between where we are right now
and building our dream house.
And they'll be fun
steps and sexy steps.
And we'll try not to fall
down them together. OK?
OK.
- OK.
- Dr. Bailey!
- Chief?
- Yeah.
Rumor has it Dr. Hahn has a
patient who's wandering the halls.
She's back in her bed, sir.
And laying hands
on other patients.
- It was just one patient.
- And healing them.
For which there's a
reasonable medical explanation.
Of course. But I can't have
a hospital full of sick people
thinking there's a miracle
woman on the cardiac ward.
It creates panic and hysteria,
and frankly, it's
bad for business.
- Are you gonna answer that?
- No, I'm not.
Make sure this woman
keeps her hands to herself?
- Yes.
- Thank you, Dr. Bailey.
Dr. Sloan,
why are you endangering
the life of my patient?
Because your
patient had her hands
all over one of my patients.
I was trying to heal her.
Don't worry your pretty little
head about it, Sloan. Karev?
Even when you're insulting me,
you manage to tell
me how pretty I am?
It wasn't meant as a compliment.
Is this a gender reversal thing,
where you're the
big man on campus,
and I'm the blonde whose
ponytail you can't stop pulling?
Why don't you get
that I just don't like you?
That I think you are a crass,
predatory, ape of a man,
who happens to be
a decent surgeon?
You want to heal
someone? Heal her.
This is toxic in here.
Could somebody
take me to my room?
My healing team
should be arriving soon.
I'll take you.
Mrs. O'Malley?
- There she is! Come here.
- Hi!
What are you doing here?
Does George know you're here?
Callie said she'd find him for
me. How are you, dear? You OK?
- You talked to Callie?
- Poor thing. It's hard for her.
You try and you try,
but we're all human.
Nobody's perfect.
And in the end
it's nobody's fault.
I'm so happy to
hear you say that.
I have just felt so
terrible about it.
I know. Me, too.
You know, we just... We
didn't mean for it to happen.
I know how that
sounds, but it's true.
We were drunk.
It only happened one time and
I know that doesn't make it right,
but it was never my intention
to break up George's marriage.
I didn't know I was in love with
him. George was so distraught.
I think that's why he
failed the intern test, so...
- He failed?
- He didn't tell you that part?
- He didn't tell me any part.
- You said you talked to Callie.
About baby clothes. I thought she
was having trouble getting pregnant.
I made baby clothes.
- Oh, no.
- Mom.
- What?
- I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry. I'm sorry, I'm
sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Hey. I know I said I'd
call you right back...
Tucker, wait. I
can't do this now.
I'm being paged to the ER.
What do you mean
you're the one paging me?
I told you never to page
me at the hospital unless...
There was an accident.
All four limbs are moving.
Pupils are responsive
and dilating.
There's no neurological damage.
Get him on a monitor.
Where's the X-ray
for the trauma series?
Order a left forearm.
There's bruising and swelling.
Mama's right
here. I'm right here.
He was under a bookshelf?
The whole thing must
have fallen over on him,
And all those medical books.
He tried to climb up and pulled
it over. I heard him screaming.
I'm trying to
hear. Stop talking.
- Miranda, let me do that.
- No, no. I got it. I got it.
- Miranda.
- What?
This is why we put the
baby gate in the living room.
- The gate was open.
- You left the gate open?
- No, I didn't.
- I left the gate open?
Accidents happen.
Not if you take the time to
bolt the bookshelves to the wall.
I can't baby-proof and
watch him at the same time.
Weren't watching him,
otherwise we wouldn't be here.
Got decreased breath
sounds on the left
- and his abdomen's rigid.
- What does all this mean?
- There may be
internal injuries.
- What kind?
We don't have time. He
needs a full trauma work up.
Clear a CT and get me
an ultrasound machine.
This is not OK,
Georgie. This is not OK.
You're planning to marry Izzie?
You're planning an annulment?
- This is not about Izzie.
- What is it about? It isn't OK!
I raised you better than this.
I never should have gotten
married in the first place.
But you did. You got
married. You didn't invite me.
You didn't let me
plan a wedding.
I accepted it because you
were happy. I won't accept this.
- Mom.
- We're Catholic.
We don't believe in divorce.
And we certainly don't
believe in adultery.
- I'm sorry.
- Don't be sorry to me.
Be sorry to Father
Mike. You call him.
He'll hear your confession
and he'll get you and
Callie into counseling.
- It's too late for that.
- No, it's not too late.
You made a vow to
Callie and a vow to God.
You don't walk away from that.
This is your soul we're talking about.
- I have to go.
- No, you will not.
You will not walk away from me!
It's Dr. Bailey. I have to go.
- What happened?
- He got crushed under
a bookshelf.
- Rib fractures.
- Might have dropped a lung.
They're worried there may
be damage to the heart.
Get him to radiology for a
head, chest and abdominal CT.
O'Malley, tell the
lab to move fast.
Karev, clear out.
We'll keep you posted.
Dr. Bailey's worked up,
and I want to make sure
that doesn't get in the
way of the baby's care.
- I don't need a babysitter.
- I know you don't. Stay with her.
Sorry about that. There
was an emergency.
Dr. Karev, this is Dawn and Mai.
- Nice to meet you.
- He's a skeptic. Shouldn't be here.
- Is Dr. Hahn coming?
- Dr. Hahn's
been called into surgery.
She asked me to talk
you through the procedure.
Is she going to be long?
I'm hoping she's done
before your heart blows,
but I can't make promises.
I told you he shouldn't be here.
I need someone who knows what they're
doing to talk me through the surgery.
This? It's crap. You're
stalling. You're scared.
Of course, I'm
scared. Surgery is...
It's barbaric. You tear
flesh and spill blood.
I work with light. I work with
energy. I visualize healing.
If there's the slightest
chance what I do works,
isn't that preferable?
I don't believe in what you do.
I'm not asking you to. I'm
asking you to help me to do it.
Can you imagine how
horrible this is for her?
This is why people
should not have kids.
What's the matter with
you? It's Bailey's baby.
See, no, it's a trauma case.
If we are going to be
effective in saving that kid's life,
it can't be Bailey's baby.
He's a blunt trauma case.
You and Hahn are exactly
alike. You deserve each other.
- Thank you.
- I thought you loved cardio.
No, no. She's pretending
not to anymore.
- Can't take the pressure, Iz?
- You're right, Cristina.
In the contest to see who
can be the best robot, you win.
Ooh... Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh.
Tell me again how this happened?
- You didn't understand me?
- Just tell me again.
Somebody left
the baby gate open.
Somebody.
Did you...?
You're saying
you think I did this?
I'm saying that you were in such a
hurry to get out the house this morning,
that you were in such a hurry to
get to work and get away from me...
Doesn't have
anything to do with you.
Why do you think he
even went into that room?
You're the only one
who goes in there.
He went looking for his mama.
He went looking for his mama
and wound up in the hospital!
You made a bad
choice, huh, Tucker?
You picked a bad wife,
she made a bad mother, she
made you stay home, raise your son,
and she almost killed
him. Poor you, huh?
Dr. Mahoney to the ER.
I heard about Dr. Bailey's
son. How bad is it?
We're still waiting
on his studies.
Derek?
Remember before when I was cool
and let you off the hook
for making out with me?
- Well, now I'm angry.
- Why?
You're not making
eye contact with me.
Because we are talking
about Bailey's baby
and you won't look at me.
- Sorry.
- Better.
Now, it was one kiss, OK?
It was a good kiss,
maybe even a great one,
but are we going to let one
maybe great kiss get in the way
of what has been a great
professional relationship,
even if you didn't know
my name until recently?
No, we are not.
So, friends?
- Friends.
- Good.
Bailey wants to know if
Tuck's films are ready.
What? Is that...?
What's that shadow?
Where's his heart?
- You can't see it because...
- His stomach's in his chest.
Visceral herniation.
A positive collar sign.
Which indicates a
diaphragmatic hernia.
It's a ruptured diaphragm.
Which is the least
of his problems
because the force of the
trauma injured his thoracic aorta.
And you see this?
In the chest cavity next to
the stomach? That's colon.
And around the colon is fluid.
Which could mean
the colon has ruptured
and there's fecal
matter floating around
that could infect
the aortic repair.
And that complication
can be fatal.
What are you all standing around
for? Page Hahn and the Chief!
Book an OR!
They repaired the
hole in the diaphragm.
Dr. Hahn's about to
inspect the mediastinum.
Is she gonna repair with
sutures or prosthetic graft?
- Don't know.
- You don't know?
She didn't say.
- Dr. Bailey!
- Dr. Bailey? Are you kidding?
- I need to be with my son.
- Miranda.
I have no intention
of getting in the way.
I can't stand out there.
I can't. I need to
be with my son.
And what we need, Dr. Bailey,
is to not have our
patient's mother
watching us perform his surgery.
Dr. Grey, please escort
Dr. Bailey back outside.
There will be no escorting of
Dr. Bailey anywhere, Dr. Grey.
Now you can proceed.
I will not proceed
until you leave this OR.
Now, do you want me to
stand here talking to you
or do you want me to try
and save your baby's life?
Miranda.
I just want to hold
my son's hand.
his hand, please.
I'll hold his hand.
Dr. Grey can hold
this retractor, right?
Yes.
I'll hold Tuck's hand,
Dr. Bailey, if it's OK with you.
I'll hold his hand.
OK, go, go, go.
OK, everybody,
let's get back to work.
Mrs. O'Malley, what are you...?
I couldn't leave.
When Harold was
here, when he was sick,
Dr. Bailey took such
good care of him.
I couldn't leave knowing
her son was in trouble.
Knowing both our
sons are in trouble.
Mrs. O'Malley, I...
Look, I know you
think I'm old-fashioned
and maybe I am.
But it doesn't
matter what I think.
In God's eyes,
marriage is forever.
If it's any consolation, George
and I got married on the Vegas strip
at a 24 Hour Church of Elvis.
I'm not sure God was even there.
He's everywhere.
I used to believe in God.
And marriage. And
Heaven and Hell.
But you don't anymore?
I believe in love.
And second chances.
And that even though
George wasn't the one for me,
it was OK that I believed
that he was, because...
Well, for a little while at
least, I got to be an O'Malley.
And I really loved
being an O'Malley.
He's back.
I'm sorry to interrupt, but
your most recent echo shows
the dissection is extending.
You need to let me
prep you for surgery.
Oh, no. No, not yet. We
haven't finished our work.
You're going to die.
Do you know how Mai
knew you were back
even with her eyes closed?
- She heard me?
- She felt you.
It's like a pull,
like a darkness.
Right, I'm the
angel of death, got it.
No. You're not the
angel of death, Dr. Karev.
You're actually
a very sweet boy.
He's got a beautiful heart,
wouldn't you say, Mai?
- I would. But his gut
and his throat...
- They're blocked.
Second chakra's worse.
You're talking about "chakras?"
You've got a darkness at your throat
chakra where your voice should be.
Because whatever
happened to you was so ugly
and went on for so long
that you don't talk about it.
You were hurt so
badly that sometimes
you want to hurt other
people just to spread it around.
You were a good boy,
Dr. Karev. A good, sweet boy.
But you're not a very good
man. What happened to you?
Your artery is shredding.
You need surgery.
I'm not a very good
man, but I do tell the truth.
And the truth is, if you
don't get this surgery fast,
you're going to die.
I left it on the desk.
I walked to the office
door and I closed the gate.
I walked out of the
bedroom and wrote a note
to the building manager.
I left it on the desk.
I was in a hurry.
But I looked at the clock.
I walked out of the door.
- The gate was opened.
- Miranda, this isn't helping.
- Did I close the gate?
- Stop this. It's not helping.
I walked out of the bedroom,
into the office, wrote a note.
- This isn't helping. Stop this.
- I can't remember!
I can't remember
if I closed that gate.
- I can't remember
if I closed the gate.
- It doesn't matter.
It does matter
because I'm his mother
and I can't have
done this to him.
You didn't do this.
Things just happen.
No! They don't just happen!
Things don't just happen.
People make decisions!
People prioritize!
The world doesn't just happen,
OK? It's not on God, it's on me!
- Or it's on Tucker!
- Stop.
- It's on me or Tucker!
- Stop it, stop it.
Just stop it.
- Oh, no.
- You're a good mother.
Tucker is a good father.
You love your baby.
People make mistakes.
You didn't do this to your son
and neither did your husband.
He wants to build us a house.
With kids' bedrooms
and French doors
and that scares me to death.
Why?
Just because of the Rose thing?
Well, that shouldn't scare
you. It was just one kiss.
One kiss?
It wasn't like they were
being secretive about it.
It was just something
that happened.
You guys are back together,
it's not happening anymore, so...
- Derek kissed Rose?
- Yeah, but you knew that.
That I'm an idiot.
OK, the stomach's repaired.
There's no splenic laceration.
Now all I have to do is get the
chest tube in and we're done.
That's good.
You're in better
shape than we thought.
It means you're
almost out of here.
Dr. Yang, would you
like to do the honors?
I can trade places
with you, if you'd like.
No, I'm OK. I'm OK here.
His stomach
ruptured, not his colon.
Both of which we repaired,
so the surgery was a success.
However, there is a lot
of fluid in the chest cavity.
So, at this point, we
have no way of knowing
whether he'll be able
to breathe on his own.
I know that. You
don't think I know that?
We'll be moving him
to the pediatric ICU.
- We'll be watching him closely.
- Can I see my son now?
Absolutely.
You're new here.
You don't know me.
If what you did today ends up saving
my son's life, I'll thank you for it.
But if I never have to
look at you again after that,
that'll be all right with me.
♪ I went up to the mountain ♪
We never baptized him.
We kept putting it off, thinking
we were going to find time.
And now...
We will find the time.
When this is over
and Tuck is fine,
you and I are
going to find time,
and we are going
to baptize our baby.
♪ Everywhere ♪
♪ I could see all around me ♪
♪ Sometimes I feel like ♪
♪ I've never been
nothing but tired ♪
How's Tuck?
He's still not
breathing on his own.
You know, I wish I could help,
but I can't think of
anything I can do.
Cristina always
knows what to do.
What's your deal
with her? With Yang?
Nothing. There's no deal.
I'm crippled with envy.
Of Yang? Because
she's better at cardio?
She's not better than me.
She just...
She knows what she wants.
She has this faith in her skill and
herself and her future in cardio.
It's an unwavering faith.
She knows who
she is and I want that.
I was chasing cardio
because I want what she has.
- She's a robot.
- Not the robot part.
The faith part.
- ♪ Afraid I will fall ♪
- I want that.
♪ Just over the mountain ♪
♪ The peaceful valley ♪
♪ Few come to know ♪
There's probably a
thousand scientific reasons
why Mr. Greenwald's heart
rate suddenly stabilized.
Without question.
And why Miss McCaffrey's staph
infection suddenly disappeared.
Sloan's patient? She's fine?
I mean, don't get me
wrong. I have faith.
Now, I do.
But faith isn't medicine.
Faith can't heal you.
Well, that may be so.
But then again, it can't hurt.
- Hey.
How's Tuck?
He's intubated and we won't
know anything for a few hours.
- How are you holding up?
- Who's Rose?
Rose is a circulating
nurse. I kissed her once.
I'm sure you know that.
It's why you're asking me.
- When?
- When did you kiss her?
- Yesterday.
You were making out with nurses, and
today you're building our dream house?
- We were dating other people.
- Not the point.
That is the point. I told
you I wanted to marry you.
I wanted to build a life with
you and you weren't ready.
And Rose is? You don't
want to build a life with me.
You want someone. You want someone
who wants the same things that you want.
I knew the minute I
showed you those plans
- you'd find reason
to walk away.
- You called my bluff?
I did, because I
can't do this anymore.
I can't do the back
and forth. I can't.
Are we together or are we not?
We were together. I
was in love with you.
You didn't tell me
you were married.
We're gonna have that fight?
You didn't tell me
about your nurse.
You want to know why I'm not
ready to build a house with you?
- Because I cannot trust you.
- You can't trust anybody.
And no matter what I do...
you're always gonna look
for reasons not to trust me.
I can't do it anymore.
- I can't.
- Well, neither can I.
♪ The broken
clock is a comfort ♪
♪ It helps me sleep tonight ♪
♪ Maybe it can stop tomorrow ♪
♪ From stealing all my time ♪
♪ And I am here still waiting ♪
♪ Though I still
have my doubts ♪
I need you to hold hands.
♪ I am damaged at best ♪
Why?
Because the energy
in here, it's not healing.
So I need you to hold hands
and focus all of your
love on this child.
For a few minutes I want
you to try to forgive each other.
Can you try to do that?
♪ So I'm holding on ♪
♪ I'm holdin on ♪
♪ I'm barely holding on to you ♪
♪ The broken locks
were a warning ♪
♪ You got inside my head ♪
♪ I tried my best
to be guarded ♪
♪ I'm an open book instead ♪
♪ And I still see
your reflection ♪
♪ Inside of my eyes ♪
♪ That are looking for purpose ♪
♪ They're still
looking for life ♪
♪ I'm falling apart ♪
♪ I'm barely breathing ♪
♪ With a broken heart ♪
It's not for you.
It's for little Tuck.
- Is he better?
- We don't know yet.
I know I haven't
called you in a while.
And that there's a lot that I
haven't told you. I know I messed up.
But I didn't want to cause you any
more pain, I didn't want to disappoint you.
You disappointed yourself. You
should be disappointed in yourself.
I am.
I don't even recognize
myself anymore.
This isn't the guy
that I wanted to be.
Who do you want to be?
The guy Bailey
named her baby after.
I want to be that guy again.
You won't go to counseling?
That's just going to
hurt everyone more.
- I miss your dad.
- Me, too.
Move back home.
I'll take care of you.
Well, I think it's time that I
started taking care of myself.
♪ I tried to be
your light in love ♪
♪ I pray that is
enough for now ♪
♪ I tried to be
your light in love ♪
♪ And I pray that
is enough for now ♪
♪ I pray that is
enough for now ♪
It doesn't help me to have
you all clustered here watching.
It doesn't help me. I appreciate
that you care, that you're concerned.
But I don't need to be watched.
- Miranda, he's choking!
- He's choking?
OK! Oh, thank God!
- What are you talking about?
- It's good!
He's fighting the tube. It means
he can breathe on his own.
- There you go. Shh. Shh.
- There we go.
I need your help.
♪ How long you have traveled ♪
♪ In darkness weeping ♪
Hahn said you'd have a heart
attack this afternoon and you didn't.
So you think there might
be something to this?
No. But I'm going to help
you anyway, or she is.
- This is Dr. Stevens.
- Hello.
Hi.
I'm sorry. I'm not sure
what I'm doing here.
You're gonna talk her through a
coronary artery dissection repair.
- She's an expert?
- No, no, no.
She's a second year resident.
She's been focused on cardiothoracics
and she's seen the procedure done.
Well, I appreciate what
you're trying to do, but...
She's like a bright
yellow, right?
- What?
She's an optimist.
She's the opposite of me.
She's exactly the kind of person
you want helping you, right?
- She brightens you,
that's for sure.
- Shut up.
What are we talking about?
Just talk her through the surgery before
she croaks, all right? Can you do that?
You want me to
talk you through it?
Uh... In as much
detail as possible, yes.
OK.
Yang's got nothing on you.
OK. There are four
chambers in your heart,
and three major coronary arteries
that supply blood and oxygen.
As doctors, we know more
about the human body now
than at any other
point in our history.
They extubated him. His
blood pressure's up, too.
Good.
Do you know that his
middle name is George?
- Tuck's?
- After me.
I thought Dr. Bailey
didn't like interns.
Yeah, she doesn't.
Did you find an apartment yet?
Because I was thinking,
maybe, I'm going to get one and...
But the miracle of life itself,
why people live and die,
why they hurt or get
hurt, is still a mystery.
Here's the thing.
- You're too pretty.
- Oh, come on.
No. So pretty, in fact, that
if we didn't work together,
we would probably be...
But, the point is,
we do work together.
And, in order for
me to do my job,
I need to leave who I am
outside the doors of this hospital.
So...
- Hey. You ready?
- I am.
You going to Joe's?
I'll come meet you.
Good night, Dr. Sloan.
We want to know the reason,
the secret, the answer
at the back of the book.
Do you wanna go to
dinner with me tonight?
- I thought you weren't free.
- Turns out I am.
And I'd like to go out with you
tonight. Do you want to go out with me?
That'd be nice.
Because the thought
of our being all alone down here
is just too much for us to bear.
- How's he doing?
- Well, he's going
to be just fine.
Where's your husband?
Uh... He went home
to get some sleep.
And to pack his things because he's
getting himself a hotel room tonight.
I'm sorry.
For some reason, life just
seems to make a lot more sense
when you're looking at a baby.
But at the end of the day,
the fact that we show
up for each other,
in spite of our differences,
no matter what we believe,
is reason enough
to keep believing.