It's intense, what
happens in the OR...
when lives are on the line
and you're poking at
brains like they're Silly Putty.
You form a bond with the
surgeons right next to you.
An unbreakable,
indescribable bond.
It's intimate, being
tied together like that.
You up?
- No.
- Yes.
Whether you like it or not,
whether you like them
or not, you become family.
- The Wicked Witch is dead.
- Metaphorically dead,
or dead dead?
- Who are we talking about?
- Hahn.
Her name is off
the surgical board.
Her surgeries have
been canceled.
I don't know how or why,
but I do know Hahn is gone.
It's too bad. She
was really talented.
- You're not talking to me.
- Mm-mmm.
♪ But I'd rather be dead ♪
- ♪ My patience is fleeting ♪
- ♪ I'd rather be dead ♪
- Hi. Is Grey home?
- Hi.
Yes.
Death! Come on,
where are you, Death?
- Death!
- Die!
- Oh, my God, it's been...
- Forever.
- You look like...
Death!
The guy in the pajamas your
boyfriend? 'Cause if so, then hot.
- Right?
- Hey.
- Uh... Who are you?
- I'm Sadie. Who are you?
I'm Cristina.
Wow.
Apparently they went backpacking
around Europe or something.
Before med school.
That woman all but
kicked me out of the bed.
That's terrible.
And Death? Meredith's
name is not Death, it's Mer.
I really feel for you.
She's never even
mentioned this woman.
How good of a friend can she be?
Good enough to kick
us both out of bed.
Welcome to my world.
♪ Can we stop? ♪
This woman is the reason I went
to med school in the first place.
I figured if a slacker like Death could
handle slicing people open, I could too.
- Meredith's not a slacker.
- I could tell you some stories.
But you won't.
Sadie, you postponed your
residency to work in a morgue?
Yeah. All the fun
cutting, none of the rules.
But I got bored, started
craving blood that was flowing.
And now you're here. I
can't believe you're here.
Yay.
Iz, you coming?
- Yeah. I just need a minute.
- I get it.
Hahn's case brought up the Denny
thing, but Hahn's not even here anymore.
It's stuff from the past.
Stuff from the past, Iz.
- You don't understand.
- I might, if you talk to me.
Fine.
See you inside.
- I'm walking.
- Good morning.
- Walking straight ahead,
all by myself.
- You look good.
Tired, but good.
Did I mention I find the
short hair kind of sassy?
Now I'm turning this
corner. Again, all alone.
Ow!
Um... These are
scratches from my kitten.
He's a crazy scratchy scratcher.
- You're a cat person?
- I meant hairbrush.
I have a crazy
scratchy hairbrush.
Solo surgeries are
at stake here, Three.
I can't have you acting weird.
- Or wounded.
- I'm on top of my game, really.
I'm sending you to Plastics,
far, far away. Just go.
What do you know about
a heart guy named Dixon?
Dixon? No, not a guy.
I've heard of Virginia Dixon.
Got an incredible record,
really low mortality...
- Wait, is she coming here?
- Yeah, today.
Piggyback heart
transplant. I'm on the case.
What? Why am I not on the case?
So she's your
pre-Cristina Cristina?
You're gonna tell me
why she calls you Death?
The adventures of Death
and Die are better left untold.
Pedia's julienning
her little arms.
No word on what made H hitch
a ride with the flying monkeys.
- Translate that for me.
- Lexie may be a secret cutter.
- Still no word
on why Hahn quit.
- That true about Lexie?
- I don't know.
- What are you gonna do?
- Nothing.
- You can't do nothing.
- She's your sister.
- And?
- And your family.
- I'm not understanding.
Lexie's your family.
Forget it.
- Hello, Dr. Hunt.
- Dr. Yang.
Thank you.
- What do we got?
- Crush injuries.
- Couple minutes out.
- What do you know about Hahn?
- She's gone.
- Yeah, but why?
I don't know.
- You two are friends.
- I don't want to talk about it.
I want blood and guts
and mangled bones.
I want a guy so smashed
up it takes all day to fix.
I want to rock a surgery. I
don't want to talk about Hahn.
Unidentified man with
prolonged extrication time.
Had to fish him out of a garbage
truck. Multiple crush injuries,
open fractures, GCS
three, couldn't unhook him.
- Unhook him?
- His femur's broken in half
and is puncturing his
torso. He's impaled.
- Impaled on himself?
- Human pretzel.
That'll do.
- Wow.
- Check his popliteal pulse.
- I'm getting nothing.
- 'Cause his knee's over here.
Sleeping in the Dumpster and
they started crushing the trash?
- That's a bad day.
- I'm here. What did I miss?
Your first day. Stand
back and shut up.
Breath sounds are clear and
equal. Both sides. Unbelievable.
No punctured lung. We need a
portable X-ray and an ultrasound.
- Someone page us?
- I did.
- You did? That's a first.
- So's this.
I've seen guys cut in half,
amputations, eviscerations,
but I've never seen
anything like this.
I wondered if you could help.
You hire when you're
number one, not number 12.
But I need you to be
my ambassador today.
Show Dr. Dixon what
Seattle Grace is all about.
I've thrown a lot of money, big title
and a lot of research dollars at her,
- but...
- But what?
She's a little different.
She's a little off.
So we're wooing today, Bailey.
I can woo with the best of 'em.
- So, what, Dixon's a nutjob?
- Excuse me?
I've already had my
quota of crazy for the year.
I've had my off days.
Wanna judge me?
You never even met the woman.
Now you heard the chief, our
job is to impress Dr. Dixon today,
- so be impressive.
- I've got the chart
for Dr. Dixon.
I'm ready to work. I'm excited.
- Don't be. She's off.
- Karev.
- Are you OK?
- Yeah.
Heads up. Here she comes.
Dr. Dixon. Hi.
Welcome to Seattle Grace.
We're very happy to have you here.
- I'm Dr. Bailey.
- I brought
my own lab coat.
I'm here to perform a heart
transplant today. I do hearts.
A procedure invented by Christiaan
Barnard in 1967. I do hearts.
Uh... I'm Dr. Webber.
We spoke on the phone.
Karev, get Dr. Dixon
the latest labs.
Stevens, let's prep
the patient, please.
OK, then, she's a little off.
His femur's in pieces. Except
the part stuck in his torso.
No way I'm saving that leg.
Impaled piece is
lodged under his clavicle.
C-spine looks clear.
Without a CT, hard to be sure.
- Why can't we get a CT scan?
- Way he's impaled,
no clear reading.
A stupid question.
A limited window. With vitals
like these in a few hours...
Won't be able to
withstand surgery.
Good thing he's unconscious.
Can't do anything till we dislodge
the femur from his clavicle.
Let's un-impale him.
Yang, Grey, new kid, hold
his shoulders. Brace hard.
- I'll hold his C-spine.
- I got his torso.
I need to guide
posterior hip dislocation.
Second that leg is out be ready
to assert pressure, stop bleeding.
Better than working
on corpses, huh?
On the count of
three. One... two...
Three!
Femur's really wedged in...
OK, almost there. Steady.
Just a little bit further. Sloan, I need
you to rotate his knee to my right...
- Push ten of morphine now!
- Stop! Stop!
Corpses don't do that.
- I need you to calm down, sir.
- What are you doing to me?
Can you tell us your name?
Get out of my face and your
hands off! You're hurting me!
Do as he says.
Hands off, everybody.
Hands off!
Thank you.
- What's your name?
- Timothy Miller.
Mr. Miller, we need
to get you into surgery.
I'm gonna be
able to walk, right?
We're trying to keep you alive.
Our cardiac wing is extensive
and well-equipped with all...
The first successful heart transplant
was performed on September 7, 1896,
by Dr. Ludwig Rehn,
Frankfurt, Germany.
OK.
Excuse me, I don't
mean to interrupt.
Please... I mean, just...
Please update
Dr. Dixon on the patient.
Dr. Stevens is prepping your
transplant patient for surgery.
They scheduled a
transplant six years ago,
but the heart was too small.
They added a donor heart
to help his own heart function.
- They did a piggyback...
- Heterotopic transplant.
Piggyback is the colloquial
name for the procedure.
Don't do that.
How about we take
you to meet the patient?
They told me my heart belonged to a girl
hit by a car while she was hitchhiking.
And now when I'm driving, I
see hitchhikers all the time.
Always up ahead, just up ahead.
When I get up
ahead they're gone.
You're not buying this, are you?
I should never have
gotten the heart.
- I don't understand...
- Navajos, we don't
touch the dead,
don't touch their
bodies or belongings,
the spirit clings there.
So to have part of a dead
body sewed into my chest is...
My friends, who
follow the old ways,
they begged me not to do it.
- I should've listened.
- Sorry, I don't understand.
You think you're haunted by
your transplanted heart, but
you're here for
a new transplant.
No! That's what I'm trying
to tell you. I don't want it!
I don't want the new one. I
want you to take the old one out.
OK, that's just plain stupid. Take
the heart, man. Take it if they offer it.
Did he just say he doesn't
want the donor heart?
- Yes, ma'am.
- - Clay Bedonie, are you aware
without a new heart you'll live a
short life attached to a machine
before dying a sudden
and agonizing death?
See, that's what
I'm talking about.
Five parallel pulley
stitches per cut, then switch.
- Are you sure I'm numb?
- Toughen up.
When one of our residents
gets picked for the solo surgery,
one of us gets to scrub in.
We have a goal here.
Focus on the goal.
Solo surgeries,
totally worth it.
Hello. I need someone
to run these labs
and pull these X-rays, please.
Will do.
This looks like a cool place to
hang out. What are you doing?
This is for interns, it's our
hangout. Go find your own.
Sorry.
Solo surgeries.
Totally worth it.
I won't live if I can't walk.
- We'll do our best to save the leg.
- - I'm homeless.
Walking is how I survive, it's
how I get from one day to the next.
Marion Street's safe
from 2:00 to 6:00am,
and then I go over
to Hadley Bridge
and I hang there till
6:30 until the traffic hits.
And then I go over to Belltown,
and I hang out over
at the waterfront.
And then the
waterfront, if it's trouble,
then I go back to 4th Street.
I'm homeless. I can't not walk!
I... What am I gonna
do? What am I gonna do?
Your injuries are critical. If
we don't get you to surgery...
Will your surgery make me walk?
Huh?
Then I don't want it!
OK. All right.
You heard the man.
The surgery's off.
I appreciate you trying to advise
me to do what you think is best.
- These are facts, not opinions.
- What I'm saying is...
He's trying to say he'd rather
live a shorter life unhaunted
than a longer one that is.
I'm not saying I
agree, I'm just...
I'm just gonna stand over here.
That was a good idea.
The heart that you take out
of me, what happens to it?
It goes from the OR to
pathology to medical waste.
I need that heart
back, for a ritual.
We have laws. There
are rules. Rules are rules.
Maybe there's a
compromise to be made here.
We could, I don't know,
give him back the old
heart to do the ritual,
then give him a chance to
live by putting the new heart in.
- No.
- Doesn't work that way.
- I'd still be haunted.
Just by a new ghost.
There are rules. We have laws
and rules are rules and laws are laws.
No.
So that's it? No surgery,
you're just gonna walk away.
I'm respecting the
patient's wishes.
Patient's unstable
with an open wound.
Which we are packing.
- This guy's circling the drain.
- You cannot walk away.
Don't tell me how to
run things in my ER.
- Your ER?
- We save lives here.
We don't just patch up
patients and leave them to die.
If you can't handle that,
go back to the desert
and leave us
here to do our jobs.
Dr. Torres, please tell me...
you could figure out some
way to build this man some legs.
The right femur's toast. So's
the hip and half the pelvis,
but if I put some pins here,
and maybe a plate here...
I mean, there are some
viable bone fragments.
Not starting from nothing.
What do you think?
- I think it's wild.
- She wasn't talking to you.
It's her first day.
Could you not...
She needs to learn her place.
I think it's a lot of hardware.
What the guy needs
is a whole new leg.
Maybe I can do that.
Yeah, it's kind of a puzzle.
I just need to figure out what
equipment I need and how to pull it off.
- Like Lincoln Logs.
- A little more high-tech
than that.
It's exactly like Lincoln Logs.
I need you guys to grab every
piece of titanium we've got.
OK.
I need the hospital
rules to specify the fact
that we must respect all religious
and spiritual beliefs of our patients.
- The rules?
- I'm asking you
to declare a rule
of our department.
That we respect the
beliefs of our patients?
- Yes.
- Isn't that common courtesy?
- Then why am I declaring it?
Um... Dr. Dixon doesn't
do common courtesy,
but she understands rules.
So if it's a rule, we're golden.
If not, we have a
pissed off patient,
an apoplectic surgeon,
and none of those things
makes for a successful procedure
on a faulty heart.
Not to mention
the failure to woo.
You want me to
announce it as a rule?
I'm here as a witness. You
can raise your right hand,
put your left one on the
Physicians' Desk Reference.
- It's a rule.
- Thank you.
Dr. Dixon? I'm Cristina
Yang. I'm a resident.
Been focused on cardio
since I began my internship.
I'm certainly
looking forward to...
Were the other ones
taken off my case?
- What other ones?
- The black one, the male one,
the one with yellow hair.
- Not that I'm aware of.
- Then why are you
talking to me?
What happened to Hahn? Whatever
made Hahn leave it can be fixed.
Unless she was... She
wasn't fired, was she?
- Not coming back.
- You don't know that.
- She kind of does.
- How?
Because she doesn't...
Look, it's just too...
We had a fight.
Oh, please. Meredith
and I fight all the time.
We still work together.
It's not like Hahn was
your girlfriend or something.
Oh, my God. She
was your girlfriend?
We hadn't... figured it all out.
- So are you a lesbian now?
- I don't know.
Maybe you were a "oncebian?"
Or a "twicebian."
Whatever. It's over.
- Are you OK?
- She's fine. Leave her alone.
I hit the titanium mother lode.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Oh, come on, really?
Hey, Lexie. How are you?
- Is everything going OK?
- Did somebody say something?
- I was doing something?
- No, I'm asking as a person
who's sort of related to you if
there's anything bothering you.
This is not as a boss or resident or
superior who keeps an eye on what I do?
No, I'm a compassionate
person. I'm just wondering
if you're channeling your
tragic pain into self-mutilation.
- Are you a secret cutter?
- No!
Little Grey, Torres is
trying to set a world record
for most titanium rods
used in one patient. You in?
- Little Grey?
- Little Grey, Big Grey.
It's how I tell you two apart.
Yeah, I'm in. I'll
just be a minute.
Can't you people let
a guy die in peace?
Your vitals are slipping.
I'm not gonna lie to
you, that's not good.
- I've been through worse.
- Yeah. I imagine you have.
Oh... Don't get like that.
Don't look at me like
I'm some tragic hero...
with a secret past.
You have a story.
We all have a story.
I took a turn, with my
life, and I couldn't connect.
I lost.
I couldn't connect.
My life, it took a turn and...
I just couldn't turn it back.
Guys, we need to shut
down for a few days.
People are starting
to get suspicious.
I was accused of
being a secret cutter.
So wear long sleeves.
I didn't realize we were
inviting more people here.
Are you kidding? A
secret intern society?
I'm all over that.
Well, I still think we
need to take fewer risks.
Fewer risks? Come on,
you got a guard at the door.
You're using more local
anesthetic for three sutures
than you would
upstairs for a chest tube.
Look, I get that you're doing
all this to learn new skills,
but you'll only learn so
much by being careful.
Actually, I would disagree. I
think the only safe way to...
Ouch.
Who wants to stitch me up?
Oh, right here.
You gonna tell me
about Death and Die?
Nope, but I did
talk to Lexie for you.
- I need you to do
something for me.
- What?
Tell Mark to keep his Little
Sloan out of Little Grey.
- Is he hitting on you?
- No! Not my little Grey,
Lexie's.
The last thing she needs is
Sloan going man-whore on her.
So you need to tell him to
step away from Little Grey.
- I'll see what I can do.
- Little Grey, Derek. Little Grey.
Did she, uh...
- Did she say goodbye to you?
- Nope.
- You OK?
- Do I look OK?
You look great.
Then I'm OK.
So, there's a nine-day
ritual to undo a haunting?
It starts with a
nine-day ritual.
Are you really gonna
waste nine days on this?
- Dr. Stevens...
- Yes?
Why are you so
interested in my haunting?
Can ghosts do things?
I mean, can they make
things happen in your life?
I've had two cases,
two patients in a row
that have really reminded
me of my dead fiancé.
Heart transplants and LVADs.
Could he be doing that? Could
he be bringing them to me?
Izzie, come on.
Is he here right
now, your ghost?
I... I hate to ask, but...
Oh...
You don't want
me in your surgery.
Not that I think there's
something wrong with you,
it's just... I don't need extra
ghosts in my operating room.
- Mr. Miller...
- What does a guy have to do
to get a little peace
and quiet around here?
The fatigue you're feeling is from
blood loss, queasiness, dizziness.
You're slowly bleeding to death.
- What, you trying to scare him?
- No.
I'm trying to ascertain whether
he's suicidal or just defeated.
Mr. Miller, you
survive on the streets,
so I know you're a fighter.
That doesn't make me a
fighter. Makes me lucky.
How long have you been
out there, ten years, 20?
You're not in jail, not dead.
That's not luck. You're smart.
You gotta be smart to take
care of yourself on your own.
I guess.
This, what you're doing
right now, Mr. Miller,
refusing surgery,
it's not smart.
There's a rehab center
not too far from here.
Medicare takes care of
it. You could stay there.
Food, bed, long as you need.
Just let us operate.
Let us operate, and
we'll figure the rest out.
Wow. That's the fastest I've ever
seen anyone dissect through adhesions.
Dr. Dixon, there
is a rule regarding
giving medical
waste to the patient.
- Dr. Dixon?
- Huh... What?
I was just saying
there's a rule,
an official, very,
very specific rule,
that, in the event a
patient asks for their organ
or body part back,
for any reason
related to or involving
their cultural beliefs,
we must respect
that patient's wishes
and return that
organ to the patient.
That is the rule I
forgot to tell you about.
If I went down to
pathology right now,
would they know about the rule?
The chief would
know. It's his rule.
He declared it. Rule's a rule.
Dr. Karev, make sure that
we follow the chief's rule
and return the heart to
the patient after the surgery.
I'm going back to
work now. Clamp.
What the hell is that gooey
thing they're taking out of him?
Oh, the silent treatment.
OK, if you're gonna
be that way I'll just, uh...
I'll just stand
here and be quiet.
OK, that, that is disgusting.
I thought you were
gonna be quiet.
You know you're acting like
you don't want me to be here.
You know what I've wished
for every day since you died?
I've wished that I
could see you again.
I'd have given anything just
to see you one more time.
Looking at you and
knowing that I can't touch you,
it's hurting me.
- Izzie, you can touch me.
- You're not real.
You can't be real, so
that means that I'm sick
or something is wrong with
me and I can't hope for that.
I can't hope...
You're not real.
Izzie, I am as real as you
or that gooey, disgusting
thing down there.
Touch me.
Izzie... touch me.
- I'll prove it to you.
- No!
Why are you here? Why?
I am here for
you, Izzie Stevens.
Clamp.
OK, that's it. The
donor heart is separated.
We have the cannulas
ready for bypass.
Next step is the LVAD.
Wait, what is that?
That's not right. That
can't be happening.
Heart's beating. How's his
heart beating on its own?
It can't be happening. It
shouldn't be happening.
The heart is beating.
Heart is beating, it
shouldn't be beating.
It shouldn't be beating.
I've never seen a
reconstruction like this.
Never done one like this.
Here's hoping it works.
Ready for the rod. How
are you guys doing?
Hemorrhaging bleeding
through the packing.
- Try the fibrin sealant.
- Good call.
- How are you doing?
- - Good, moving to the next lac.
Finished already? Let me see.
Wow.
- Pulley stitches. Nicely done.
- Thank you, Dr. Sloan.
- So my heart?
- - Started beating by itself.
If it continues to
function like this
you won't need an LVAD
or any kind of machinery.
It's wonderful news.
- It's very atypical.
- Not for me. I'm finally free.
I'm not haunted anymore.
Your heart had
six years to rest,
probably enough time
for it to repair itself,
which is why it started beating
again. Never seen this before.
Read about it but
never seen it before.
You have your
beliefs, I have mine.
I don't have beliefs,
I have science.
Science is a belief,
a belief in only what
you can see and touch.
I believe in more.
Just thought I'd stop in to
see how everything's going.
I'm still several hours
away, but I may pull this off.
Rebuilding a man's
skeleton from scratch.
And we just found out that Dr. Grey
here can out-pulley stitch Shepherd.
I wouldn't go so
far as to say that.
Excellent job, Dr. Grey.
- Excellent job of teaching,
Dr. Yang.
- Sir?
Taking time to teach your interns
and they retain the knowledge.
Haven't made my decision
yet on the solo surgery,
but keep teaching like that
and you're my one to watch.
Thank you, sir.
- V-fib.
- Start CPR.
Push one of epi and
charge the paddles to 360.
Clear.
- ♪ 'Cause what I need to say ♪
- Thank you.
Thank you so much.
So what do you do now with
the haunted piece? Bury it or...?
Burn it. Actually, my tribe's
medicine man will burn it.
I'm not allowed to
even touch the smoke.
So the not-touching thing, does
that apply to just the flesh or...?
No, we don't touch
their belongings.
We can cleanse jewelry, metals,
but fabric, bedding, clothes,
books that were owned by
the dead, we burn all of it.
The spirit can
cling to any of it.
Oh, no. Your ghost.
You still don't have
anything of his, do you?
♪ I hope this song
brings you back to life ♪
Time of death, 19:22.
♪ 'Cause I can see the fear ♪
♪ In those eyes ♪
♪ I promise you if we just try ♪
I built his bones.
You tried. We all tried.
No, I didn't try, I did it.
I did my part, I
built his bones.
I built his bones from scratch,
and you, all of you, you were
supposed to keep him alive.
That is all you people
had to do. You just had to...
keep his body breathing.
You just had to keep him
safe and breathing and living
until I made his bones. I
made... I made his bones.
Until I made his bones.
I made his bones.
Why don't you guys go ahead
and I'll help
Dr. Torres clean up.
- Go call the morgue.
- We've got it. Go.
Everyone, clear out.
♪ My heart found a home ♪
♪ Yeah, when I found you ♪
♪ My heart ♪
♪ Found a home ♪
Uh... Excellent job
today, Dr. Dixon.
Excellent rule following.
I only have one
real area of interest.
The human heart. I love it.
I like its regularity.
I know everything
there is to know about it.
I like its predictability.
It has rules.
Every chamber has a function,
every function has a movement.
I like the color.
It's comforting.
Are you familiar with
Asperger's syndrome, Dr. Bailey?
Um... Of course. Significant
impairment during social situations...
I'm not good at cues like
sarcasm or condescension,
but I do know when I'm being
manipulated and made fun of.
I don't think I like this
hospital very much.
I don't think I like
this hospital at all.
Lexie Grey sure knows how
to wrap herself around a suture.
- Meredith had some concerns.
- That's not news.
About Lexie. Apparently
Lexie is fragile,
and getting involved
with a superior
might make her more fragile.
I was talking about her sutures.
Keep Little Sloan
out of Little Grey.
- What?
- Little Sloan
does not enter Little
Grey. Are we clear?
- Did you just say...?
- Hmm-hmm.
OK, that's just
creepy... and inaccurate.
Big Sloan.
You heading home?
I love you.
I will always love you.
You own a piece of me.
So even though you'll be gone...
you will never be
forgotten. Not by me.
I'm sorry we never
got our chance.
got to get married,
have children or
grow old together.
I wanted that so much.
I wanted to be your
wife more than anything.
Why are you telling me this?
I'm trying to let you go
so that your soul
could be at peace.
I have peace, Izzie.
I'm here for you.
Goodbye, Denny.
I love you, but goodbye.
I can explain.
I did not teach you
the parallel pulley stitch.
I can barely do it myself.
Whatever you guys
are doing, shut it down.
Do not practice on
yourself. That is insane.
Shut it down.
Iz?
♪ Trouble will find you
no matter where you go ♪
I see you.
I've seen you all day.
I see you struggling.
And I know you don't want
my help, but let me help you.
Whatever it is, I can help you.
So let me.
♪ You're fine for a while
but you start to lose control ♪
Will you burn this for me?
♪ He's there in the dark
He's there in my heart ♪
♪ He waits in the wings
He's gotta play a part ♪
I hate how hard it is.
It's just like... You get
attached to someone,
they work their way into your
life and you wake up one day...
Suddenly all you can
think about is their little...
- Another round?
- Oh, I'll get it.
♪ Trouble is a friend
but trouble is a foe ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ And no matter what I feed
him He always seems to grow ♪
- Tell me the stories.
- What stories?
The ones you won't
let Sadie tell me.
They're ancient history.
Humiliating and ridiculous.
Ridiculous is a grown man
telling another grown man
- to stay out of
a woman's little...
- You did it?
I did. Those exact
words. I did it because...
it was nice to see you
sticking up for your sister.
I did it for you.
So now, you owe me...
a story.
♪ Trouble is a friend of mine ♪
OK, fine.
But you can never
tell anyone ever.
♪ So don't be alarmed if
he takes you by the arm ♪
♪ I roll down the window
I'm a sucker for his charm ♪
Hey.
♪ Trouble is a friend, yeah ♪
♪ Trouble is a friend of mine ♪
I'm sorry we lost him,
the patient. I'm sorry.
I don't need you to be sorry.
- OK.
- I don't need you to be sorry.
I don't need you.
OK. All right. All right.
♪ How I hate the way
he makes me feel ♪
♪ And how I try ♪
♪ To make him leave ♪
♪ I try ♪
♪ Oh, oh, I try ♪
♪ But he's there in the
dark He's there in my heart ♪
♪ He waits in the wings
He's gotta play a part ♪
♪ Trouble is a friend, yeah ♪
♪ Trouble is a friend of mine ♪
The ties that bind us are
sometimes impossible to explain.
♪ So don't be alarmed if
he takes you by the arm ♪
♪ I roll down the window
I'm a sucker for his charm ♪
They connect us,
even after it seems like
the ties should be broken.
♪ Oh, oh ♪
Some bonds defy distance.
And time. And logic.
Oh, God. I said goodbye.
I burned the sweater.
Yeah, thanks for that, by
the way. I loved that sweater.
- You made me that sweater.
- Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
- Izzie!
- Oh, my God, oh, my God.
- Stop freaking out.
- You're not real.
Hey, I told you,
I'm here for you.
You're not real,
you're not real.
- You're not real.
- Izzie, look at me.
Touch me.
You see? I told you I was real.
Oh, my God.
Because some ties are simply...
meant to be.