Previously on "Grey's Anatomy"...
I want Seattle Grace
to open a free clinic.
Why ?
I need something to hold on to.
You still need funding.
I have $8 million.
The Denny Duquette memorial clinic.
What's all this about?
They all want to be chief.
She's in a nursing home
Alzheimer's.
I gave up everything for him.
I should never have had a kid.
Marry me, Cristina Yang.
Marry me.
As surgeons, we live in a world
of worst-case scenarios.
We cut ourselves off
from hoping for the best
because too many times,
the best doesn't happen.
But every now and then,
something extraordinary occurs...
and suddenly...
best-case scenarios seem possible.
- 8 days, $8 million...
- and we're open for business.
And every now and then,
something amazing happens...
She woke up this morning
completely aware.
She's her old self. It happens.
Medically, we don't know why.
It's just a random gift.
So she's lucid? She remembers?
Pretty much everything,
except the last five years. And, of course,
she doesn't realize she has Alzheimer's.
We thought she should hear it from you.
So she'll know me?
I'm gonna walk in there,
and she'll know who I am?
She's been asking for you.
And against our better judgment...
We start to have hope.
Hey, chief. I need a signature.
I'd like to use the helicopter to
transport a patient from Denver.
Good morning, chief.
I found a way to fund
a stereotactic robot.
I want to make sure you're
on board before I move forward.
It's a little early in the morning
for you two to be chasing me down.
I'm going to be doing a bloodless pulmonary
valve translocation on this patient.
This machine is an excellent source
of revenue for...
Aren't you gonna get in there?
You want to be chief, you gotta fight
with the big boys.
Oh, I intend to fight like a girl.
I'll let them kill each other, and then
I'll be the only one left standing.
And then there's me.
There you go, underestimating me again.
Oh, it's not that I underestimate you.
It's just that I don't think about you...
at all.
Well, you should.
I was, uh, heading down to the clinic.
It's opening today, and I
thought it might be nice to show
Dr. Bailey a little support.
Very thoughtful, Dr. Sloan.
I think I'll join you.
Gentlemen, if you'll excuse me.
Certainly.
Nicely done.
Mm-hmm.
Meredith, what is going on?
When did you get back from Europe?
I went to Europe for two months,
but that was...
I've been sitting here thinking
about the fight we had,
the things I said.
I... I said some terrible things.
It's fine.
No, it's not.
After you left, I... I was upset.
Did I... did I have a breakdown?
I must have had a nervous breakdown.
I'm in a... is it a hospital?
Because I can't remember anything
for the past two months, Meredith.
The last thing I remember
is the fight we had.
And listen, if you don't want to
go to medical school, that is fine.
It is your life. Just take me home.
I went to medical school.
I... I want to go home, Meredith.
I... I need to go home.
You are home.
I  went to Europe five years ago.
You got sick.
You have Alzheimer's.
This is your home.
You live here now.
No.
No!
Mom.
Mom?
Mom! Somebody call 9-1-1.
- She had substernal chest...
- Chest pain and syncope.
My pulse was in the 200s, but the
rate has resolved on its own.
She's completely lucid.
She's what?
She's aware.
She's herself again.
Oh, my god. Is this...
Are we at Seattle Grace?
Yes, mom. This is where
I'm doing my residency.
Your daughter is one of
our finest interns,
following in your very big footsteps.
Do you know Richard Webber?
Is he still a doctor here?
What, the chief?
Richard Webber is the chief?
Of surgery?
Okay, welcome to the
Denny Duquette Memorial Clinic.
Barring any surgical emergencies,
you will be working here today.
Working on what?
Right now,
Olivia will be familiarizing you with
the protocol for the flu vaccine.
Oh, no, no, no. Don't... don't...
don't touch that.
That was $79.
Oh, my god.
I have got to get out of here.
Burke has a bloodless
pulmonary valve translocation
fly in from Denver tomorrow.
I should be preparing.
You don't get to scrub in
on the valve translocation.
How do you know?
Because I am.
He picked you?
You guys ready?
Where is everybody?
Uh,  Grey will be late.
O'Malley should be back from vacation.
No, no, no, the patients...
the underserved, uninsured population
that we're supposed to be helping.
The underserved uninsured will come.
You'll see. Just watch the door.
They will come through it.
I can't wait for the first patient.
It's gonna be amazing.
It's gonna be amazing what
Denny's money can do, right?
Just watch the doors, Stevens.
Dr. Bailey,
congratulations on the
opening of the clinic.
It is open, isn't it?
Is Stevens all right?
She's watching the door, sir.
Okay then.
Someone's coming.
Damn it!
O'Malley, welcome back. You're late.
Is O'Malley all right?
We got married in Vegas!
We're married!
Dude, she... she's Callie O'Malley.
It's... it's fast.
You know, it seems really very fast.
Are...are you even happy ?
We're incredibly happy.
Oh, yay. Well, great.
Yay.
Show her the ring.
Oh.
That's so great.
Tiny diamonds are great because you know
no one will every try to steal it.
Oh.
Okay, that's it.
Yang, Burke needs you in cardio.
O'Malley, the chief has a surgical
patient coming into the pit.
Stevens, Karev, go find me
some patients.
I don't care where you get them,
just get them.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Okay, we've been out of our Vegas hotel
room bubble for six hours,
and I don't like it.
It's gonna be fine.
We're married.
All right.
So, chief,
we're a couple of married men.
Uh,
Adele and I are getting a divorce.
No...
um...
I didn't... I didn't know.
That's life, O'Malley.
That's  life.
Now this patient...
I removed a large tumor from her colon
eight months ago.
Since then, she's been undergoing
chemo and radiation.
We thought she had it beat.
Excuse me.
Are you the doctors for Marina Wagner?
Yes. You brought her in?
I woke up this morning,
she was barely breathing.
You think this could be food poisoning?
Cause we had sushi yesterday,
but I... I feel fine.
Could be complications from the radiation.
What do you mean, radiation?
From her cancer treatment.
She doesn't have cancer.
I'm her boyfriend. I'd know.
O'Malley, get a C.B.C., A chem 19 and
a triple contrast abdominal C.T.
Excuse me.
Yes, sir.
Wait.
Is she all right?
She's... Richard Webber.
My god, you've aged.
Ellis.
I was having arrhythmias.
They wanted to do tests.
And I hear you're the chief
of surgery now.
That's wonderful.
Yes,  I'm...
but I'm stepping down soon.
Stepping down?
Well, I can only assume
that was Adele's idea.
Meredith.
I'll be right there, mom.
Go ahead.
She's lucid.
She woke up this morning
with her memory back.
They say it's temporary.
My god.
Well, obviously, don't...
don't worry about work today.
You need to be with her.
I mean, this time...
it's a gift.
It's a gift.
Right.
Meredith's mother had some runs of
S.V.T. I'm ordering an echo.
And she's lucid.
What?
It happens, but it won't last.
I...is Meredith okay?
She seems fine, but her mother's going
to need the best care we have to offer.
And  you, dr. Yang,
are the best.
You're still not wearing the ring.
I would like an answer.
It's been over a week.
I told you,
it's under advisement.
Well, do you not like the ring?
It's a ring.
It's 3-carat, diamond-cut platinum...
it's... it's the ring.
Then what?
Are you using the surgery tomorrow to
pressure me into giving you an answer?
Is that why I'm not scrubbing in?
I need to give the other
interns a chance.
Why?
The echo, please, Dr. Yang.
- Hey.
- Hi.
You been waiting long?
Almost an hour.
Mm.
Are you my doctor?
I can be.
We have a clinic right
outside those doors.
So wait.
What's wrong?
It hurts when I pee.
Oh.
We can help with that.
Yeah, that's easy.
It's nothing.
We can have you out of here
in less than an hour.
Are you hitting on me?
we need patients.
You need doctors.
And we just happen to be surgeons.
You think I need surgery?
You never know.
It's free.
A free clinic.
My co-pay is only 10 bucks.
That's lunch.
sounds like T.B.
Yeah
Very contagious.
You and Meredith are good friends.
I can tell...
Because you're afraid to look at me...
as if I might ask you some personal
question about her,
and you'll accidentally slip.
But you don't do anything
accidentally, do you?
Has Meredith chosen a specialty?
That's a personal question.
For a surgeon, it's the most personal
question you can ask.
It tells you who they are.
My mother would want to know
whether I had a boyfriend.
Your mother sounds like
a frivolous woman.
If I chose cardiothoracics,
what would that say about me?
Heart surgeons are the know-it-alls.
They're the most ambitious,
the most driven.
They want it all, and they want it now.
And they don't want anything
getting in their way.
Meredith says I'm part of
an Alzheimer's research study.
I want a neuro consult
with the doctor who put me in the trial.
Hey, Mer.
I've been looking for you.
Burke has me on your mom.
Are you okay?
I'm avoiding her.
I'm avoiding the gift.
Yeah, well, uh, your gift
wants to meet Derek.
What? What did you say?
Oh, no, no, no, not Derek,
your boyfriend.
Dr. Shepherd, the neurosurgeon.
But she's gonna know that
he's your boyfriend anyway.
She has ways.
I'm kind of in love with her,
by the way.
She has that affect on people
who aren't her daughter.
Hey, I heard about your mother.
That's unbelievable.
Yeah, it's a gift.
She's avoiding her.
Mer, she's your mother,
and she's really here.
This is your chance.
You should talk to her.
You should spend some time with her.
She has a very long history
of being disappointed in me.
You're a doctor now.
Parental disappointment ends
with a medical degree.
Can we get moving?
It hurts when I pee.
Are you stealing patients from the E.R.?
Yes, but only because I have to know
that I didn't spend my entire inheritance
on an empty room with empty beds.
Because if I did that,
I might go crazy, and George called dibs
on all the crazy this week.
Do you think Callie's pregnant?
I'm going back to the E.R.
Okay, just keep your pants on.
We're going. We're going.
What...what...what's going on?
Oh, yeah.
Bambi got married.
Psst.
I'm sorry. One second.
Everything okay?
Are...are you off today?
You got married?
Yeah,
I did.
It was a... I know it was impulsive.
Well, was it "good" impulsive,
or was it "Meredith" impulsive?
Because if it was Meredith impulsive,
maybe I can help get you out of it.
No.
no, it was a...
it's a good thing.
Good.
It's good.
Um, but, uh,
thanks for the backup.
You're welcome.
Congratulations, Georges.
Thank you.
Are you planning on coming
to talk to me anytime soon?
Excuse me.
Uh, you know those cartoons where there's
a bear or whatever and it's starving,
and it looks at a table, and the table
turns into this delicious cooked turkey,
with, like, lines of
deliciousness coming off it?
I  was not looking at him like that,
because he is the help,
and I am not going to be
sleeping with the help.
I married the help.
What?
We went to Vegas.
My idea.
I embrace the trashy.
That's...
not that I'm not happy for you,
But why married so... fast?
You know those cartoons where there's
a bear and it's starving,
and it looks at a cute intern?
Well...
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Oh, it's small.
I know, it's small.
It's beautiful.
You think so?
Yes.
So tell me about yourself.
Well...
What's your life like?
I...
really do want to know you, Meredith.
Well, I have a boyfriend.
Does he understand the demands of
your career?
Because not all men do. They
say they do upfront, but they...
He's great.
He's a doctor, too, so he gets it.
Good.
He's actually...
have you chosen a specialty?
No, it's still early.
Cristina's already chosen cardiothacics.
Yeah.
Well, I guess I'm...
Just waiting to be inspired.
I'm happy now.
You know, I feel like I know who I am.
Plus, I think when you have someone
in your life that you love...
you really love... I think that's...
I don't know. I just...
I'm really happy.
What happened to you?
What do you mean?
You're happy?
You're happy now?
The Meredith I knew was a force of
nature, passionate, focused, a fighter.
What happed to you?
You've gone soft.
Stammering about a boyfriend and...
and saying that you're waiting
to be inspired?
You're waiting for inspiration?
Are you kidding me?
I have a disease for which there
is no cure.
I think that would be
inspiration enough.
Listen to me, Meredith,
anyone can fall in love
and be blindly happy,
but not everyone can pick up a scalpel
and save a life.
I raised you to be an extraordinary
human being.
So imagine my disappointment
when I wake up after five years
and discover that you're
no more than ordinary.
What happened to you?!
We are living in the same building so
I'd see her in the laundry room and uh
She's really sexy when she
folds clothes.
Once we started dating, it was
just like, boom, you know?
We got really serious really fast.
Now I'm just kinda like...
I don't even know her middle name.
I'm trying to fill out these forms, and
I'm stumped on the first question.
Rose.
That's her middle name.
She's charming, she's fabulous, and then
suddenly, she's the enemy.
I'm meeting the enemy?
Just don't get personal.
You're being ridiculous.
I am not being ridiculous.
Okay. It's gonna be fine.
Just be careful. She has ways.
- Hey, George.
- Hey
Are you okay?
Yeah.
You seem kin shaky
and sweaty and pale.
Is it the marriage?
Are you totally regretting it?
No, the marriage is fine.
Uh, do you mind, uh, taking that to, uh
sorry, taking the blood work
to the lab for me?
Sure.
Thanks.
I think I need to sit down.
George, if you need to talk...
Thanks.
Hey.
Are you okay?
You're sweating.
Yeah, I'm good.
What's your...what's your middle name?
It's bad.
I don't tell anyone.
Come on. We're married,
and I don't even know your middle name.
Okay, I knew it.
It's your weird and judgy friends.
You let them get to you.
No, it's... I don't... I don't know...
your middle name. God, I can... I can...
I can barely breathe.
You know what? You didn't know
my middle name last week,
and you could breathe just fine.
What?
What about a functional M.R.I.
Now, while I'm lucid?
Mm.
An M.R.I.'s not gonna show
us anything new.
No test is gonna help us understand
what's going on.
So in five years, you've made
no advances,
and there is nothing else
you can do for me.
I don't know how you do it,
day in and day out, work with people
with this awful disease.
Oh, I... well, see...
actually, I'm not an Alzheimer's
specialist.
I just took a special interest
in this case
because of Meredith.
You're what happened to her.
- I'm sorry?
- I thought you were here for me,
to offer me some hope,
to tell me about some new treatment.
But you're here for her.
Dr. Grey...
an attending? A neurosurgeon?
No wonder she's so unfocused.
I don't think you understand.
- I'm...
- Oh, I understand.
I understand perfectly.
I've seen men like you before,
threatened by a woman who's their equal.
You just want someone to admire you.
And you don't care about the damage
you do to her along the way.
I need to lie down.
Whoa. No, no, no. Hey, hey, hey, Buster,
do you know how much it costs
to have these linens laundered?
I'm sick. I'm shaky and sweaty
and my mouth is dry
and my body aches.
Fine.
Uh, Karev, replace O'Malley in the O.R.
Yes.
So this is Marina Wagner,
your colon cancer patient?
Karev, where the hell's OMalley?
Curled up in a ball in the clinic.
Is he okay?
Well, he's married.
Right.
Okay,
boki, 10-blade.
Stolen, nonemergent E.R. Cases
and sick hospital staff...
this is what $8 million buys you.
Dr. Stevens, I swear on my life,
if I hear you say "$8 million"
on more time...
It's not about the money.
It's...
It's Denny.
It's his legacy. It's...
I was looking for meaning.
This was supposed to be meaningful.
It will be meaningful.
$8 million worth?
Uh, excuse me. Are... are you, uh,
can I...are...are you the doctors?
Yes, we are.
Are you a patient?
Like an actual free-clinic patient?
Not me. My... my daughter.
Oh, is your daughter sick?
I'm not sick.
Can we please go?
Kelley finds suddenly she has a need
for these products.
And, uh, and we were hoping you might
show her how to use them.
George, you're married.
You should be happy.
You don't look happy.
I'm sick, Olivia.
All right, you could...
uh, you should go home, O'Malley.
Clearly whatever you have is contagious.
Aren't you from the lab?
Yeah, I feel like crap.
Is that the lady you gave,
uh, Marina's blood to?
Uh, yeah.
And you all feel shaky and nauseous?
It's awful.
She's toxic.
Callie? Yeah.
A lot of us feel that way.
No, the patient's blood is toxic.
It's making us sick.
Has the chief started, uh,
Marina's operation?
They were wheeling her up
as I came down.
What's the extension for O.R. One?
The patient's blood is apparently highly
toxic. Any contact is dangerous.
Nobody goes in there until we figure
out what the hell is going on.
How's he doing?
He's tachypneic, but his B.P.
Is starting to stabilize.
He's doing better on oxygen.
It's a good thing he got
out of there when he did.
- Yeah.
- Dr. Shepherd.
- What is it?
- Can you sign this?
I just heard. How can I help?
You're off duty.
You should be with your mother.
I don't want to spend time
with my mother.
The chief is down. Alex is down.
I would like to help.
Dr. Grey...
you want to help?
Talk to your resident.
What do you got?
They found an herbal supplement
in her purse.
The lab guys think it combined
with the chemo chemicals
and turned her blood into some
kind of neurotoxin.
We're lucky they're not all dead.
The only reason she's alive
is because she's intubated.
Who got them out of there?
O'Malley.
George.
Callie, she was toxic.
Her blood was toxic, not our marriage.
You thought our marriage was toxic?
Okay, all our people are being treated.
Now what do we do about her?
Dr. Grey,
your holter monitor shows you're having
multiple runs of tachycardia every hour,
so Dr. Burke would like
to do a radioablation.
Why would he recommend surgery when
medication can keep it under control?
Because Alzheimer's patients aren't
always compliant with their meds.
And apparently, Meredith says...
you are particularly difficult.
I could elect not to treat it at all.
Your stress test shows coronary
artery disease.
That coupled with the tachyarrhythmia
could cause too much stress on your
heart, which would
eventually...
what would you do
if the thing that defines who you are
was taken away?
Tell Dr. Burke...
I don't want the surgery.
I'm...
I'm s... I'm very sorry, Dr. Grey,
but technically, that
decision isn't yours.
It's Meredith's.
This is a maxi pad... heavy flow day.
Mini pad... pretty self-explanatory...
just peel the label and stick it.
And the tampon we've already gone over.
So
are we clear on everything?
Kelley...
I understand
that you're a little mortified that your
dad dragged you in here,
but can you just talk or nod
or something?
I get it, okay?
How's it going with our very
first patient?
Kelley's a woman.
Can I just go to the gallery and learn
something, if that's okay with you?
Okay.
Uh, Mr. Hanson, if you could go to the
front desk and fill out some paperwork,
I can get you outta here.
Of course, of course.
Uh... thank you.
Since my wife died, I... I've been in
the woods a little with Kelley.
Okay.
Yeah.
Are you okay, Kelley? Any cramps?
'Cause a heating pad...
Could I be pregnant if I had sex last
week ?
Like, before the period thing started?
'Cause I did,
and it would really suck if I was pregnant
'cause now the guy's being a real jerk,
and he's totally ignoring me at school.
So I really hope I can't be pregnant.
I can't, right?
Any way you could, like, answer me
before my dad gets back?
I'm not sure refusing treatment
is what you want to do.
Apparently what I want doesn't matter.
It isn't even legally binding.
So it's really about what you want,
Meredith. You're in charge.
You think I like making
these decisions for you?
Do you think it's fun to get
calls from the nursing home
asking whether I was planning
on giving the nurse
who changes you every morning
a Christmas tip?
But I do it, because you have managed
to alienate everybody else in your life.
And I am the only one,
so I have to step up and do it.
You want to know why I'm so unfocused,
so ordinary?
You want to know what happened to me?
You. You happened to me.
- Then let me refuse the heart surgery.
- No.
- Why not?
- Because killing my mother
is not gonna be another thing
that happens to me.
These suits are airtight.
These packs recirculate the air
trapped inside.
These batteries haven't been
charging long.
I'm guessing you got about 30 minutes
before they die and you have to come out.
Oh, my god. The anesthesia's
wearing off. She's waking up.
30 minutes starting now.
She's fighting intubation.
We go inside before
these seals are secure,
we wouldn't last five minutes,
and she will die.
These guys are two minutes out.
- She doesn't have two minutes.
- Addison!
Get the hell outta there!
She's awake, Mark. She's awake
and open on the table.
I need to know her weight so I can
dose her with the propofol.
She looks about 60 kilos.
you're okay.
It's okay.
Got it.
I got you. I got you. It's okay.
Looks like S.V.T.
Push 10 of adenosine
and page Dr. Burke.
He's already gone into surgery.
I'll get the adenosine.
Carotid massage.
Carotid massage can reboot the heart
and stop the S.V.T. Okay, okay, hold on.
Oh, hold on, please. Hold on, please.
Hold on. Hold on.
Okay.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
oh.
You're good.
Sharp under pressure.
You'll make an extraordinary surgeon.
Dr. Grey, I need to ask you...
will it get in my way?
Can I have both?
Can I be a great surgeon
and have a life?
Because there is this man
who just asked me to marry him,
and I know you tried to have both,
but you split up with
Meredith's dad and...
- I know this is none of my business.
- It is none of your business.
And I didn't try hard enough.
Thank you.
Are you feeling better?
Oh, I will be once my patient's
off the table.
Look at these two...
a heart surgeon and a neurosurgeon
performing a bowel resection.
You think the world stops when you stop,
but it keeps on going.
People perform your surgeries
better than you could.
The next generation comes up, and
you're scared you'll be forgotten.
Your mother stopped for five years,
and you became someone.
According to her, I didn't.
According to her, I'm a disappointment.
Well, in a perfect world she'd be able
to tell you she was proud of you.
But it's not a perfect world,
and your mother's not a perfect woman.
I think the person she'd most like to
see right now is you.
The only thing your mother wants to hear
from me is that I regret staying with Adele.
That's the only gift I could give her.
And I can't tell her that.
That's not true.
They won't fit.
Stop right there.
The bowel swelled.
You won't have any room.
- How much time do you have?
- Eight minutes.
Okay,
now listen to me
and do everything I say.
Kelley, your pregnancy test is negative,
and you're clean for S.T.D.S.
- Oh, thank god.
- Great.
Thanks to you, I'm also grounded
for the rest of my life.
Kelley, be polite.
I'm sorry, Sir, but polite doesn't seem
to be getting you two very far.
Kelley, your dad told me you lost your
mother a few years ago,
and I want to say how sorry I am. You
probably have a million of questions.
And if your mother were here,
I'm sure she would have more eloquent
answers than I do.
But I think that she and I would
actually be saying the same thing,
which is if you keep going
the way you're going,
you will get an S.T.D.,
You will get pregnant,
you will increase your chances
of getting cervical cancer.
You're not being smart.
And you're too young for anyone to
expect you to be smart
the way you need to be
when you're having sex,
which means you shouldn't be having it.
I thought he liked me.
Oh. Oh, honey, I know you did.
I know you did.
okay, you're gonna live.
Callie, wait.
I was a little bit heroic in there.
Mm.
I thought you'd be proud of me.
Proud? You were poisoned, and you
thought it was about me.
- It felt like an anxiety attack.
- About me.
You see, we...we were fine when we
were in our Vegas bubble, when it was
just room service and pay cable and us,
it was bliss, but then you get around
your weird and judgy friends for one day
and suddenly you're racked with
uncertainty, toxic-gas-level uncertainty.
I guess it was too much to hope
you'd just stand up for me.
- Cal
- and middle name is Iphegenia.
Okay?
I can't wait to hear what your pals
have to say about that.
So that was pretty cool, what you just
did. Going in and putting her back under.
Cool or stupid...
Take your pick.
Huh.
Okay.
All right. I gotta...
go.
What's going on?
The chief figured out the anesthesiologist
didn't have time to drop an N.G. Tube.
So now they have to place one
and decompress
and repack her intestines and close.
And they're about to run out of air.
Holy crap.
This so beats tampon training.
Preston, you'll need to milk the bowel
to get out the excess fluid.
Pack her and wrap her and get
her stable for transport.
- How's Georges?
- Medically he's fine.
Emotionally? He's a little
stunted if you ask me.
You don't marry the rebound girl.
Am I right?
You don't marry anyone on a whim.
- Well, he needs our support.
- He doesn't need us.
He's got his Vegas show-wife.
Oh.
Chief, they're at 32 minutes.
You gotta pull'em out.
How you doin' on air?
- I'm out.
- You go.
- I'll wrap it.
- Alone?
You can't.
Burke?
Burke!
Burke.
That's not good.
Okay, damage control.
We still have to pack her and wrap her
so that she's stable for transport.
We work in shifts...
one doctor at a time, no one stays in
for more than 20 seconds.
Dr. Sloan, do you want to go first?
I'm not going in there.
What?
It would be irresponsible for the
remaining healthy attending
to expose himself to the neurotoxin,
a neurotoxin whose long-term effects we're
still unaware of. So I'm staying in here.
I can swim 3 lengths of my
parents pool underwater.
You're up, Dr. Yang.
All right, let's get her a mask.
Sloan, give her the lap pads.
You're gonna wet them
and pack the cavity.
If you feel faint, get out.
Come on Yang. Hurry.
- I... oh, I... I've packed the wound.
- Dr Stevens.
I couldn't get...
I couldn't wrap it.
Remove the drape and secure the plastic
along her sides. It's gotta be tight.
Hurry.
Come on, Stevens.
Come on.
I couldn't, um...
it...it it...it twisted.
Okay, the seal needs to be as close to
vacuum-tight as possible.
It'll inflate, and then
you'll know it's secure.
Come on, Grey.
Come on.
Is she still toxic?
She's on C.R.R.T.
It's type of dialysis to remove
the toxin from the blood.
You should be able to go in
in a few hours.
You woke up.
You're gonna be okay.
I was hoping you'd never have to know
about any of this.
I thought all the bad stuff in my life
was over when I met you.
It is...
Marina Rose.
That's my name.
Heroic work, all of you.
Heroic.
Dr. Sloan, let's check
on our patient now.
How come we do all the work
and he gets all the glory?
Because he's Mark.
I'm sorry I left.
I... It was...
I got to do damage control
on the toxic woman.
Good for you.
Did you ever get any patients?
Just that one.
$8-million worth of one.
Lock up for me.
I heard you're having surgery tomorrow.
Do you...
Do I know who Meredith is?
Do I at least recognize Meredith?
You know she's someone important,
someone who loves you.
You'll look out for her?
Because she's got so much more to learn,
and I won't be able to teach her.
I'll look out for her.
I wish I could go back.
I'd do everything so differently.
I'd fight harder for you.
I think it...
If I'd fought harder for you, maybe...
We would've had a wonderful life
together, Ellis.
- You think so?
- I do.
We would've done our fellowship here,
and then you would've fought me for
chief, and probably won.
And...
I wouldn't have minded
because we'd have the kids at home.
We have kids?
Meredith would've needed
a brother and sister.
Kids need family.
We would've been a family.
Probably bought that big house on
Parker. The one with the barn?
Yeah, that's a good place for a family.
And I would've been happy,
Just like Meredith says she's happy.
And that would've...
Changed everything.
Maybe...
I would be fine, and we could
grow old together.
and life would be so perfectly ordinary.
Yes.
My life is so unfinished.
It's unfinished, and I'm not finished.
No. No, Ellis.
Don't think that.
Just close your eyes...
And think of the family,
of the house...
and you there every night
to come home to.
And me there.
I'm there.
I am super scrubbed.
I'm minus my epidermis.
- I still feel all fumey.
- Oh.
Hey.
it's the little woman.
So what are your plans now?
You're not moving in, are you?
Nice.
- Wait, Callie.
- Forget it. Just...
- No.
Unbelievable.
You people... you're supposed to be
my friends... my closest friends.
Callie's a big... she's the most
important part of my life now.
If you want to drive her away... and
you're masters at it... you'll do it,
but if she's gone, I'm gone.
She's my wife.
Calliope Iphegenia Torres is my wife.
- Ipheg...
- Don't you dare.
- Okay
As doctors, we're trained to give
our patients just the facts.
But what our patients
really want to know is,
Will the pain ever go away?
Will I feel better?
Am I cured?
I thought you said you didn't
think about me.
I don't.
I am actively not thinking about you...
Right...
Now.
What our patients really want to
know is... Is there hope?
I don't do rings.
Don't expect me to suddenly change.
I'm a surgeon, just like you.
And we'll have money.
We can hire a wife.
Are you saying yes?
Yeah.
- I'm not letting you scrub in tomorrow.
- Well, I'm not wearing a ring.
- Okay.
- Okay, then.
Yes!
oh! Okay, okay, okay, okay!
But inevitably, there are times
when you find yourself
In the worst-case scenario...
- Meredith...
- I just have to say this...
the reason I want you to have
the surgery
is because I have this hope
that in a year or two years or five,
They're gonna have a breakthrough
They're gonna find a cure for Alzeihmers
and you and I will have another chance
to get to know each other
You'll have a chance
to get to know me
to see
that I am not even remotely ordinary
So, I wish you would have the surgery.
But it's up to you mom. It's your life!
You remind me of my daughter
About an hour ago
One minute she was here, the next...
I'm so sorry
Me too
When the patient's body
has betrayed them
And all the science we have to offer
has failed them.
When the worst-case scenario comes true.
Clinging to hope
is all we've got left.
Transcript : Raceman
Synchro : ChipounetteF /Mickeyte
www.forom.com
http://experts.heberg-forum.net/