My mother called it the greatest
and most terrifying
moment in her life.
He said Karev.
Standing at the head
of the surgical table,
knowing that the patient's life
depends on you and you alone.
- He said Karev!
- Yes!
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
You're "sure" sure?
Huh.
It's what we all dream about.
Because the first person
that gets to fly solo in the OR?
Kind of a badass.
- Stevens! He said Stevens!
- Which is it, moron?
- Stevens or Karev?
- This is stupid.
Trust imbeciles to tell you
who's getting solo surgery?
Is this hard for you, being
banned from the solo surgery?
- It must be
really hard for you.
- A mean streak. I like it.
He may change his mind.
He's been known to change.
Don't do that. Go ahead and
will yourselves to be voted in.
- Use the Secret.
- Grey!
The Chief said Grey.
- What?! This is bogus.
- You just figuring that out?
Steve is not a lip reader. None
of the interns are lip readers.
You have to wait for the attendings
to vote, just like we did when I won.
- You won your solo surgery?
- I'm gonna pretend you didn't
feel the need to ask me that,
Yang. Of course I won. I was good.
I didn't cut LVAD wires or put
my hand in bomb-y body cavities
or have my interns operating
on themselves. I was special.
I was young, gifted and
black, and everybody knew it.
The attendings knew
it, the Chief knew it.
I didn't have to act
like I could read lips.
Just go about my work calmly,
waiting for my
name to get called.
It's done!
- Whatever, Helen Keller.
- No, I'm serious.
The Chief sent me.
They made their choice.
Who is it?
It's you.
I am happy to announce that the
first solo surgery will take place tonight.
A below-the-knee
amputation, bone cancer...
- Poor bastard.
- No appy?
- Saw action, sweet.
- Choosing who gets
first solo surgery
isn't just about who has
the best surgical skills
or who's logged the
most hours in the OR.
It's about the
highest form of trust.
The trust to put a patient's life
into one of our resident's hands.
And for the first
time that I can recall,
every single attending
picked the same person:
Dr. Yang.
However, Dr. Yang is out of the running.
She is going to pick the winner instead.
Dr. Yang will post her decision
on the OR board at 4:00pm.
Also, since your interns
are still banned from the OR,
the winner will pick a fellow resident
to scrub in with them. Good luck.
This is torture for me.
I'm not even done.
- Sir?
- Dr. Dixon is back.
You'll be spending the day
with her. You will impress her.
You will make sure this
hospital impresses her.
By end of the day, I want that
woman to be my next head of Cardio.
If she's not, I'll know
who to blame. Good luck.
We held a retractor
for 12 hours together.
You said I had small hands.
Good for surgery. Remember?
No. Go away.
I operated on a
heart in an elevator.
Over a year ago. O'Malley's 007.
Think how poor your decision
would look if you gave it to him.
Your turn.
I don't know why you
are even bothering.
- We know who she's gonna pick.
- She's not gonna pick me
because I'm her best friend.
She'll pick me because I'm the best.
Stop! Are you guys kidding me?
Fine. I'll think about it.
Just... go and
do surgical things.
Are you coming? We gotta
go do clinic. Flu season fun.
Yeah.
I... will catch up with you.
- Me, too.
- Shut up.
Not you.
My head. Shut up!
When I win, you
can scrub in for me.
Alex, she's not...
not gonna pick you.
I'll scrub in for you, too, if you
win, which you won't. 'Cause I will.
- Enough!
- I... I gotta go.
Cristina still hasn't talked to me.
Which is normal. Except it's worse.
Two weeks suspension and
she hasn't said one mean thing.
Karev called me a
moron. Which is good.
- Residents don't look at me.
- Least they could do
is hate us.
I'm gonna get some sex.
- Sex always
makes me feel better.
- Don't look at me.
- Me, neither.
- That makes three of us.
Hi.
I get it.
I organized a crazy cabal
of secret cutter interns.
The thing is, I've been
advised to seek out sex
as a way out of my sad predicament,
but I'd rather just learn today, so...
what do you say? You, me...
Why are you talking about sex?
Inappropriate. I'm your teacher.
I have things to teach.
Double board-certified things.
That's... That's what I was
talking about. For you to teach me.
Medicine. The sex...
That was a joke.
Dr. Sloan, I heard you're performing
a hypopharynx reconstruction today.
- I'm gonna make a woman speak.
- Let's hope.
- I read up on the surgery...
- You read up on my surgery?
Since it's your first time performing
what is a cutting-edge surgery,
I was hoping you might
need an extra set of hands.
Fine. You can join
Dr. Grey and me.
Dr. Grey who is
banned from the OR?
She's on cappuccino duty.
- Which I'm still waiting for.
- Right away. Thank you.
Dr. Virginia Dixon. It says she
arrived over half an hour ago!
- Where is she?
- Nervous?
What are you doing here? This is
cardio wing. Only cardio gods allowed.
I know. I'm looking around, getting
to know other parts of the hospital.
What else is there? The OR,
the ER and the place with the food.
Somebody's got a lot to learn.
Kathleen Patterson. Laryngectomy
five years ago resulted in loss
of her ability to speak.
Undergone surgical attempts
to restore her voice in the
past. None have been successful.
This time, though, this time we
have a good feeling about this.
Right, honey?
As discussed, I'll get blood supply
from your arm, cartilage from...
from your...
Kathleen?
Honey?
Honey.
You can talk to me.
I'll get skin and blood from
her arm, cartilage from her nose
to construct a speaking tube
which will become her new voicebox.
You should be aware there's a
chance the procedure might not work.
- He's clear on that.
- I'm just reminding him
not to get his hopes up.
Any other questions
I can answer?
Kathleen? Honey?
Tell me everything
to know about Karev.
- Why?
- I'm his intern.
He seems cool
enough at your house.
Whatever he's got going with the
girl who masturbates all the time...
I don't like to judge.
Still, officially, I'm his
intern, so what's his deal?
Sadie, I can't be your friend in
here. I'm a resident, you're an intern.
You have to figure out how not
to piss off Alex Karev yourself.
- OK. I get it.
- Good.
And ugly! It wasn't my fault!
I had to tell those
guys where to meet us!
I said I'd do it that way
you could drive! I'm telling!
- I'll kill you!
- You need to calm down.
- Tell her!
- Shut up!
- What happened?
- Sisters, 16 and 15,
crashed dad's car.
All we know since they won't stop
screaming. We need your names.
- Don't tell her. Don't say a word.
- Her name is Holly Anderson.
She was driving. And
texting. While driving!
Is there an officer? I
want to press charges.
- You suck-up! Suck-up assface!
- We need your number
- so we can call your parents.
- Here. I speed-dialed my dad.
- You are such a bitch!
- No, you are!
- Make it stop.
- Shut up!
You are dead when Mom and Dad
show up. The doctors will save you again.
- I hate you!
- I hate you more!
- I hate you both.
- All the time!
- So easy, OK?
- Come on!
I know you still see me as
007, but that was day one.
I've grown a lot since
then, and learned a lot.
Anyone can have brains,
or anyone can have talent,
but the key is to grow.
So, sure, I had a rough start and I
had to re-do some of my intern year,
but I came out the other side,
smarter, better.
The important point
is I never gave up.
Because I'm a fighter.
Thank you.
I have to check your X-rays,
I think your leg is broken.
- You'll be off it for a while.
- No. No!
I can't miss my Future Leaders
of America conference! Holly!
Emma, I'm gonna be
grounded till graduation.
I was going to D.C.! I've
been waiting for this for a year!
Mom and Dad spent two grand,
they've now wasted two grand!
- You stupid baby!
- I'm separating you two.
Listen, I've been here. Lots.
Your dad won't be pissed.
He'll be happy you're safe.
He'll kill me. He'll
take away everything.
How long have her
eyes been like that?
- Her eyes?
- Page Shepherd.
She might have a basilar skull
fracture. Get her up to CT now!
- I didn't see...
- Do scut.
I'll call you when she
needs another pep talk.
- Where's she going?
- Just to run a few tests.
Good, get her out of
here. Take her away!
I hope you die!
- Oh, crap.
- Somebody's in big trouble.
- Did you forget
to open it or staff it?
- Both.
I'm sorry, everybody. I'll
be right back with the keys.
Might want to get
nurses while you're at it.
This happen a lot? If it does,
you're giving my clinic a bad name.
You're mocking me
now? Sweet, very sweet.
Dr. Dixon, there
you are. I'm Dr. Yang.
We... I've been assigned to work
with you today. I was in the cardio lab.
- Sorry it took me so long.
- There's a blank spot
on this board.
There's a surgery but no
surgeon. I would like to do a surgery,
but that's an amputation and I haven't
done an amputation since residency.
Well...
that's... really
hard to... That...
Is your stuttering
pathological and persistent
or is it occasional
and stress-related?
- I don't stutter.
- I had pathological stuttering
as a child, but it can be treated
with rigorous speech therapy.
Yes, ma'am. Thank you.
Why is this slot
on the board blank?
I need to select one of my
fellow residents for that slot.
It's the first solo
surgery of my class.
The Chief asked you to
choose from your peers?
Yes, ma'am.
Mr. Patterson, I have some
forms for your wife to fill out.
- Is now a good time?
- She's a blogger.
About cancer and voicelessness.
She's famous in
certain Internet circles.
It seems like you two have
a great system going here.
- You've learned to communicate.
- You mean the Post-its?
You think that's a
pretty great system?
I... it's...
- convenient?
- Yes. No. Hello. I love you.
You read the words long enough,
they begin to lose their meaning.
Mid-shaft transverse tibia
fracture? Hi. Sorry to barge in.
I was just walking by,
and I saw broken bones.
I love broken bones.
Less than five degrees
of angulation, right?
Yeah, it...
We can treat it with closed
reduction and casting.
Flexion/extension views
of the cervical spine?
Yes.
I should go see my patient.
Chair.
She's got a hemopericardium.
Let Cardio know.
- Hey. I've got a Future Leader
outside, she needs a CT.
- Hey.
I'm not mad for not voting for me.
It would look like playing favorites.
You deserve it. Cristina knows,
- even if you two are fighting.
- You and Yang are fighting?
We're not fighting.
Fought. Past tense.
How bad is it? Real bad?
She's crashing.
Code blue, fourth floor.
Brain matter in her blood.
Let OR know we're coming.
What happened
to her? Holly? Holly!
Holly! What did
you do to my sister?
Holly! Holly! What
did you do to her?
Hey. So you know I deserve this.
You know I'm the most qualified.
But I don't want it to
be a big awkward thing.
I don't. So, just, you
do what you have to do.
OK.
I'll see you later.
Almost done here, Emma.
Holly will be all right, right?
- She's gonna be OK?
- She got into surgery quick.
- That's good.
- Are my parents here?
- They're coming. Your dad...
- Holly's gonna be all right?
She's not in, like...
She won't die?
- Emma, you didn't mean it.
- I said, "I hope you die."
That can't be the last thing
she heard me say. It can't.
Just don't let her die. Please.
All right, I'll go to the OR
and get an update for you. OK?
OK.
Be objective, Dr. Yang.
Consider accomplishments,
achievements, look for the stand-outs.
Let's see what kind of stand-out
Karev proves himself to be
- when I ask him
to sew the graft.
- Really?
Absolutely. Dr. Yang, watch
Karev to see if his skills are up to par
- for the solo.
- A system! Devise a system.
Rank everyone
accordingly. That's all.
Thank you.
- Out of the way.
- What happened?
Her brain's changing color.
She's hemorrhaging.
100 of mannitol.
What did I do? What did I do?
OK, OK. So the new
intern, Meredith's friend?
- Psycho with no appendix?
- Yeah. We talked.
She came to talk to me. But it
was more than that, you know?
A guy looks at you a certain way,
eyes wander when he talks to you.
Bam, you know. This
girl thing, it's confusing.
- Was there touching?
- No.
- Was there playing
with the hair?
- No.
- Was there licking of the lips?
- Oh, my God.
I made it up because I'm lonely
and depressed and desperate
for attention from
the hot new intern.
- Crazy new intern.
- Crazy hot.
No. The hot ones are the
ones that cause trouble,
ones that distract you from
realizing your true potential.
You need to focus on the medicine.
Take that pent up sexual energy
you waste thinking
about hot, naked interns
and put it back into your
genius, your godliness.
Build someone an
organ. That's hot.
She smiled. Did I
mention she smiled?
No hot interns!
Then we'll insert the newly
constructed tube in between her trachea
and esophagus just... like...
that.
So this valve flips
open when she has air...
You're in my space! Back
up! Just back the hell up!
Dr. Bailey, will you please
find Dr. Grey something to do
- other than interfere?
- Dr. Grey?
Finish prepping Mrs.
Patterson for surgery.
She was in my space.
George, can you
cover for me for a while?
- We're swamped.
- There's something
I need to do.
- It's pressing.
- She doesn't want
to miss hot sex.
- Izzie!
- It's the clinic.
You can handle the clinic.
You're lucky she even showed
up. She hasn't been here all week.
- Dr. Shepherd...
- It wasn't you.
She had a carotid dissection.
Nothing we could have done.
- So we can't...
- She had a massive CVA.
Blood to her brain was cut
off and cannot be restored.
So even though Dr. Shepherd
was able to fix the hole
in her brain that allowed
tissue to leak through her nose,
the subsequent carotid dissection
has caused loss of her cerebral function.
- You do understand that?
- She's brain dead. I get it.
She's only 16.
That's good news. She'll be an
excellent candidate for organ donation.
Excellent candidate.
Excellent organs. Young.
Dude.
You were robbed. You
got screwed by politics.
The Chief, he needed a
scapegoat. It's so unfair.
I'm sorry. I can't do this. I
can kiss ass when I have to.
But not yours.
Below-knee amputation:
incision at mid shaft of the tibia.
Elevate the periosteum
and cut the tibia with saw.
Ligate bundles and
release tourniquet.
I've done four: one on a
cadaver, three on Stan.
- Know who you're gonna pick?
- I'm ranking them.
According to a system.
Surgical skills, hours in the OR,
published papers,
academic accomplishments.
You know them, their
capabilities. Go with your gut.
My gut? I'm not putting a patient's
life in the hands of a novice surgeon
- based on my gut.
- Well, it worked for me.
Your gut?
It's what told me to choose you.
- Hey.
- Beautiful.
- What?
- Your necklace.
- Oh, right. Um...
- I have to go.
- See ya.
I hope you didn't page me
to help pass out cough drops.
- Ain't gonna happen.
- Where's Izzie?
- I thought she was here.
- She's avoiding me.
- What do you want me to do?
- You are together now?
Talk to her. Find out why she
couldn't care about her clinic.
You're pissed 'cause
you can't handle the flu.
Something's wrong, Alex.
You need to talk to her.
- She won't talk to me.
- Don't talk to me
about Izzie again.
It's just George.
Your friends, they're out
there fighting for a chance
to chop of that guy's
leg. What is that, anyway?
It's how we learn. By doing.
I lost my shot at the solo
surgery as soon as the Chief
made it Cristina's decision.
Anyway, there'll
always be surgeries.
There won't always be fiancés
who come back from the dead.
Good point.
Aren't you going to
deepithelialize here
to connect it to the trachea?
You're a very eager
student, Dr. Bailey.
- Very thorough.
- Any way I can be of service.
- I'm not sorry.
- What?
For what we did. It was
extreme. Maybe even stupid.
But this program, you
should be down in that OR,
not up here in the nosebleeds.
I shouldn't be spending my day
transcribing Karev's
illegible handwriting.
How is that teaching? They call me crazy
Sadie and God knows what other names,
but that doesn't change
that this program is broken.
The only time they bother with us
is if they think they can get us in bed.
That's not true. Dr. Sloan
took the time to teach me,
- and that wasn't about sex.
- He likes you.
Who? Dr. Sloan?
Don't tell me you haven't
noticed his eyes on your ass.
- You are delusional.
- Is he cutting into her throat?
Bloody hell.
So I suppose
you'll use a strip test
to confirm flow across
the anastomosis?
It can damage the endothelium.
- But don't you need to...
- Dr. Bailey,
would you rather do
Patterson's surgery? I can leave.
Dr. Sloan, I wasn't...
questioning your surgical skills.
I was just trying to learn.
Something exciting. Something new.
Residents are fighting tooth and
nail for a chance to cut off a leg.
What you've done here, you made
something where there was nothing.
And... it's thrilling.
I was just trying to learn.
Thank you, Dr. Bailey.
Would you take the flap veins
and join them to the internal jugular?
♪ The spartan mule
and the crippled cow ♪
She looks like she's
sleeping. Can I touch her?
Yes, of course.
Can she hear me?
She can come out
of it, right? The coma?
- People can do that?
- No, she can't.
I'm very sorry for your loss. But
tests confirm that, although your sister's
bodily functions are
fine, her brain is dead.
She has no thoughts,
no emotions, no senses.
I'm Dr. Dixon. I will be
harvesting your sister's organs
- if your parents agree.
- Please, she's our baby.
- We need time.
- I'm sorry for your loss.
But her organs are young and
vital. They could save many lives.
Wake up, Holly.
Wake up, come on, wake up.
I'm very sorry for your loss,
but your sister can't wake up.
Her basic functions are
gone. Her brain is dead.
Her body is alive but, unfortunately,
unfortunately, she is dead.
Get out! You cannot have her.
- And you cannot take her.
- Dr. Dixon, I think,
I think they understand.
I think you should go now.
I have offended you, but
we are running out of time.
Get out!
Holly, wake up!
Wake up, Holly!
Holly, wake up, please!
Have you ever had mind-blowing sex?
The kind of sex that makes you want to die?
Just fall on the floor
and give up and die?
'Cause this sex I'm
having, it's that good.
It's the best sex I've ever had. It's
the best sex anybody's ever had.
I don't know why anybody who's had
this sex would do anything but have sex.
Izzie...
You're gonna give the solo surgery
to Mer, which is typical and boring
and slightly corrupt, but at
least I'm having really, really,
really good sex.
Just thought you should know.
I know you're nervous. It
may feel strange at first,
- but just give it a shot.
- You haven't forgotten.
You can do it.
No! No! No more!
No more typing!
No more Post-its!
No!
Talk to me. Talk to me, damn it!
Talk to me!
Maybe we should
give her a little time.
Maybe you should go, too.
Just go for a walk or a drive.
- Just give her some space.
- I've given her
five years of space.
- It was my fault.
- Excuse me?
What happened, the appy, it was
my fault. I knew what I was doing.
So if you want to punish
someone, punish me, not Dr. Yang.
You know who your father is
and he's why you're still here.
So if I were you, I'd stop worrying
about whose fault the appy was
and start figuring out what I
was gonna do to make up for it.
Yes, sir. Thank you, sir.
There are people dying right
now. There are people dying.
- It's inappropriate.
- I'm sorry, it's almost 4:00.
- I have to make this decision.
- I'm not talking about
your system.
I approve of your system. I was
talking about the brain dead girl.
Can't hear her sister,
can't feel her hands.
There are patients dying and
those organs would keep them alive.
Leave feelings out of it.
Leave them out of the science.
Leave them out of the decision-making
because people are dying as we speak.
♪ All along the way
Listen what I say ♪
♪ If I whisper to you
Would you keep it ♪
♪ All around the world
Every boy and girl ♪
♪ Looking for exactly
what they're needing ♪
♪ They need you ♪
- Is she kidding?
- Congratulations.
Whatever.
- Interesting choice, Yang.
- He made the best case.
♪ A secret ♪
♪ They all love
you It's a secret ♪
Iz, I won.
Hey. What time is it?
Yang, she picked me
for the solo surgery!
She did? That's amazing.
I love you.
- What?
- I love you.
I friggin' love you.
I just got the solo surgery and
the first thing I did is look for you.
And you weren't there.
You're never there anymore.
I've been thinking about it and it
might be 'cause you love me, too.
And you're scared of that.
'Cause I screwed it up last time.
- And 'cause Denny died and...
- Alex.
Just listen. You
had that heart patient
and it reminded you of how bad
you felt lying on that bathroom floor.
I get that. I get
that you're scared.
But you're not gonna
have to feel like that again.
'Cause I'm not gonna die, Iz.
And I'm not gonna cheat on you.
I'm not gonna go anywhere.
'Cause...
I think you're
my best shot at...
I think with you,
you make me better.
You make me wanna be better.
You make me wanna be good.
And I think I can.
With you, I think I can.
I'm not going anywhere.
You can stop hiding.
And if you want to be scared,
that's OK. Just be scared with me.
Be scared while you scrub in
with me for my first solo surgery.
- OK?
- You love me.
Shut up.
♪ Every boy and girl ♪
♪ Looking for exactly
what they're needing ♪
Solo surgery.
♪ They need you ♪
I'm really starting
to not like that guy.
I never should have
said it. I didn't mean it.
I never should have said it.
Tell her that.
Tell her the last thing
you'd want her to hear.
You have to believe if
it were you in this bed
and Holly was with you, feeling
bad, you would forgive her.
Tell her.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I love you.
She loved you, too.
No matter what you said.
No matter what happened
between the two of you,
she loved you.
She loves you.
So you were right.
- Cristina and I are fighting.
- Go, talk to her.
She's your best
friend. It's important.
Derek?
They don't tell you when you
become a doctor it's gonna be like this.
They don't tell you that you...
lose more patients
than you save.
Sixteen.
I'm sick of the death.
I'm sorry.
- I'll see you at home.
- OK.
It's OK. Nobody else
is here. It's just me.
And I'm just an
intern. I'm nobody.
So you can try, and if
it doesn't work, it's OK.
Just... just try.
Hi.
Dr. Dixon, how's your day been?
Feel like you may have
a home at Seattle Grace?
Dr. Yang, you tortured her,
making her choose among her peers.
Some kind of emotional
torture. Was that your intention?
Yes.
Have your board
make me a better offer.
We're fighting, and
I don't want to be.
Let's just put this past us.
What happened with the Chief
and interns, it doesn't matter.
That's why you didn't choose
me, why you made it personal.
So let's just move on.
You made it personal.
This, here, is you making it personal.
You told me to do what I had to do.
So I chose Alex. He's the most
prepared. That's why I didn't choose you.
Not because we're fighting.
Because, unlike you, I can
separate my personal life from my job.
You made it personal.
None of you said anything.
Those were all our interns.
But I won this.
They picked me.
If I don't deserve this solo
surgery, then none of us do.
I don't know if I'm more jealous
of Alex or worried about Izzie.
I think something's
wrong with her, Mer.
Something's wrong
with all of us, George.
It's Alex.
Not here.
Here.
- Hi. You paged?
- I need you
to scrub in with me.
- Where's Izzie?
- I'm freaking out.
I'm freaking out! I
told her I love her.
I told her I love her before the
solo surgery. I can't believe that.
She's not gonna
show, I'm freaking out.
Stop freaking out. If you screw this up
and kill this guy, I'm gonna be pissed.
Then I'll know I should have won it.
You have to kick ass in there, Alex.
You have no choice.
Big night, Karev. You ready?
You ready?
He's ready.
♪ Do I still got time to grow? ♪
♪ Things ain't
always set in stone ♪
- Where are we going?
- Don't worry. You'll like it.
Come on.
Wait. Just wait.
Wait.
It's OK.
It's good. Right, right?
It's the vent. It clears your
head. You feel better, right?
Yes, yeah!
It's out of time, out of space.
Anything can happen on the vent.
Anything.
Like what?
Just wait.
♪ I know my destination ♪
♪ But I'm just not there ♪
♪ In the streets ♪
♪ I'm just not there
in the streets ♪
You made her speak. Mrs.
Patterson. She said "hi".
She spoke. You made her speak.
I respect you.
As a man, as a surgeon,
as a teacher, I respect you.
So... teach me.
What are you doing?
- Don't do that. Stop.
- Teach me.
- Stop.
We can't do this. You're
Little Grey. And I promised.
- And I'm your teacher.
- So teach me.
Lexie.
Teach me.
Come on, am I really so bad?
No.
I am.
♪ I'm just not there
in the streets ♪
♪ I'm just not there ♪
We enter the world alone,
and we leave it alone.
And everything that
happens in between?
We owe it to ourselves
to find a little company.
Fifty says he calls the
Chief in ten minutes.
A hundred he chokes
before they turn on the saw.
That's one of us down
there. Show some respect.
We need help. We need support.
Otherwise, we're
in it by ourselves.
Strangers.
Cut off from each other.
And we forget...
just how connected we all are.
♪ But I'm just not there ♪
♪ All the street
lights glowing ♪
♪ Happened to be
just like moments ♪
So instead, we choose love.
We choose life.
And, for a moment, we feel
just a little bit less alone.
Ten-blade.
♪ In the streets ♪
♪ I'm just not there
in the streets ♪
♪ I'm just not there ♪
♪ Life's just not fair ♪