Previously on Grey's Anatomy:
The chief's under the spell
of some insane
man in camouflage.
Major Owen Hunt.
I'm a trauma surgeon.
You're reading your mom's diary?
I'm not half the
surgeon my mother was.
Chief wants us to give
George one of our interns?
You didn't even think to ask
for me? Screw you, Dr. O'Malley.
We can take it slow.
Maybe just... first base.
Meredith.
- I'm only opening one box.
- Plan was not to open any.
The plan was to take
the boxes to the attic.
Look, it's Anatomy Jane.
For a surgeon, every
patient is a battlefield.
- I'll never have my own office.
- They're our terrain,
where we advance, retreat,
try to remove all the landmines.
- And she still has
her little twosh.
- Her what?
Anatomy Jane had
detachable organs.
I could never remember the
real names, so I made up names.
Like the twosh was
next to the chubbel.
And that was
connected to the slivvy.
Oh, and look, it's
the jelly pouch.
Jelly pouch, my favorite.
Still can't get enough
of the jelly pouch.
Just when you think
you won the battle,
made the world safe again...
along comes another landmine.
- So are we screwing
other people or not?
- What?
I want to know if you're gonna go
screw O'Malley or some other loser.
Then I don't cancel my
plans with the chick from Peds.
You're an ass.
What?
- That was amazing.
- Yay.
It was for me, too.
- I mean, that was amazing.
- For me too!
My whole life,
my whole adult life, I
have been with men,
and it always felt,
you know, fine, good.
But I never...
I mean, I did, but not...
Not like this.
This is like... needing glasses.
- I blinded you?
- No. When I was a kid,
I would get these headaches
and I went to the doctor,
and they said that
I needed glasses.
I didn't understand that.
It didn't make sense to me
because I could see fine,
and then I get the glasses
and I put them on and I'm
in the car on the way home,
and, suddenly, I yell...
because the big green blobs
I'd been staring at my whole life,
they weren't big green blobs!
They were leaves... on trees.
I could see the leaves.
And I didn't even know I
was missing the leaves,
I didn't even know that leaves
existed, and then... leaves.
You are glasses.
I am so gay.
I am so, so, so gay.
I am extremely gay.
Um...
I have to go.
Gentlemen, I want you to meet the
new head of trauma at Seattle Grace,
Major Owen Hunt. You remember
Derek Shepherd, Mark Sloan?
- He stole my patient.
- Mine too.
- Now you'll get
a chance to steal mine.
- Looking forward to it.
I talked to a friend
of mine at the DOH.
Now that we have Owen,
we are being reclassified
as a level-one trauma unit
by the end of the month.
That explains it.
My mom bought it
for me when I was five,
which was a super creepy gift
for a five-year-old, but I liked it.
Run!
- OK, what was that all about?
- I just saw Owen. Major Owen Hunt.
The guy who pulled
the icicle from my chest.
- I thought he was in Iraq.
- Now he's here, in my hospital.
- OK, so?
- So... So we kissed.
He kissed me. It was stupid,
it was nothing. Stupid nothing.
But you don't think he
thinks it was a stupid nothing.
He obviously likes me,
he's back. What's he doing?
Don't think he quit the military for
you? That'd be severely stalkery,
but very romantic.
I'm not getting involved
with another attending.
Coast clear?
- You paged me, chief?
- Yes, I did.
'Cause generally, when I'm paged to
the helipad, there's something landing.
Yeah. You pulled off a 12-person
domino surgery last week.
That's the kind of thing
we need every week.
It's the kind of thing that shows me
you'll be a great surgeon someday.
- Well, thank you, sir.
- It's not enough.
I don't want you to be just
great. I want you to be the best.
If you're gonna succeed me as the
best general surgeon in this hospital,
you need to start now, today,
which means you need to be me.
You want to take point
on a surgery, take point.
Problem comes up, solve
it. Don't talk to me, just do it.
- Be me.
- Be you?
Be me.
I can do that.
I don't know why you had to
bring me all the way up here to...
That's why. Lake Washington
Med is sending over a 10-year-old girl
with an abdominal
leiomyosarcoma. It's inoperable.
You're gonna have to put together a
team and come up with a plan to save her.
Save a girl with an
inoperable tumor?
It isn't easy being me.
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong with me?
We've been sleeping
together for a week
and already you're bored.
I'm hot and great in bed,
so what's wrong with you?
I didn't say I was bored. I asked if I
should keep sleeping with Michelle.
I'm asking if you're all
in. What's wrong with that?
You're a barbarian. How can I
be all in with an actual barbarian?
Fine. Claudia in Radiology thinks
I have a hot ass. I'll tap that next.
You do that.
Would you mind picking
up... Lexie, I'm your roommate.
- You'll eventually
have to talk to me.
- I reject that supposition.
- I reject your rejection.
- I ignore your rejection
of my rejection.
- I don't reject you, George.
- Thank you.
OK, two things. You all
have a skills lab this morning.
It is mandatory. Don't
think about trying to get out.
Second, one of you will not
have to go to the mandatory lab
because you will be assisting me
in my efforts to remove an
inoperable tumor from a 10-year-old girl.
- I'll do it.
- You won't.
You have a hundred
delinquent charts.
You will do those after the lab.
Slacker.
How can you operate
on an inoperable tumor?
- Karev is also out. You doubted me.
- What did I say?
- I don't doubt you.
- Yang is out too.
You weren't supportive
of a fellow resident
who couldn't get his
paperwork under control.
What is that? Grey,
is that Anatomy Jane?
- Yes.
- With the 24 removable organs
and the optional parts
to simulate pregnancy?
- Yes. Does that mean
I'm out too?
- No, that means you're in.
- Yes!
- Not fair.
Next time you'll know
to bring in an ugly doll.
Dr. Yang, what exactly
happens in a skills lab?
- Who are you?
- I'm your new intern. Ryan Spalding.
I'm never gonna
remember that. You're... 4.2.
Three, Three.
- Is everything OK?
- Shut up. Don't move.
I'm Dr. Hunt. Over
the next few months
I'll be teaching you how to
work quickly and efficiently
to keep someone alive
in the circumstances
where the safe bet is they're
dead by the end of the hour.
Anyone have a problem
working with live tissue?
- Live tissue?
- Anyone?
Speak now. In fact, leave now.
If not, I own you for
the rest of the day.
Good. Here we go.
Each resident gets
a pig, interns assist.
Hang on.
Go ahead.
Save their lives.
You're a monster.
They're under, they
didn't feel any pain.
- You stabbed them!
- Yeah, so we can save them.
We can practice on surgical mannequins.
We can learn to do the same stuff.
- Does that mean you're out?
- Yeah, I'm out!
In that case, who
wants two pigs?
Tori Begler, age 10. Tori has
an abdominal leiomyosarcoma.
The tumor is wrapped around
her celiac artery, her splenic artery
and her left gastric artery. It
is considered unresectable.
Did you understand
a word of that, Tori?
Not really.
Grey.
This is Anatomy Jane.
She's kinda funny-looking.
She is funny-looking,
but she's very helpful.
So the tumor... is way
down here in your belly.
Hard to get at because it's
underneath all these organs.
Hard but not impossible, right?
We're gonna try
everything we can.
Everything you can should
include your cardiothoracic gal.
Dr. Stewart at Seattle Pres said
the vasculature is the problem,
and you stole the best
cardiovascular surgeon he's ever had.
If she's not on Tori's team we're
leaving, going to San Francisco.
Fudge? It's homemade.
- I love this hospital.
- Yeah, no small talk. Come on.
- More lessons?
- No lessons, just sex.
Nothing fancy, just plain
missionary, boy/girl, penis/vagina sex.
I mean it. No dirty talk, no Erica talk.
No talk. Just grunting and grinding.
- Now who's talking dirty?
- Shut up!
- What's this about?
- I'm testing a theory.
Good. That looks good.
Are you petting the pig?
Stop petting the pig.
Spending a lot of time on that
anastomosis. What's your name again?
Yang. Cristina Yang.
Right. Come take a
look at this guy's pig.
- O'Malley?
- This is gonna be good.
- Make way for Dr. Yang.
- See what he did?
He stopped the bleeding, then
moved on to his liver laceration.
But sloppy work can
lead to complications.
Two days from now when
this pig starts vomiting blood
O'Malley'll wish
he'd been thorough.
He can come back later, make
things pretty when his pig is stable.
Meanwhile your pig is getting
acidotic and hypothermic.
If this was a scrawny
kid, he'd be dead by now.
- Quick and dirty, Cristine.
- "A." Cristina.
Let's guide the catheter
into the celiac axis.
Turning on the fluoro.
What? Excuse me a sec.
Hello, you can't be in here.
That's my Uncle
Pat and Aunt Jean.
They like to make
sure I don't get lonely.
She's not lonely. Dr. Grey
and I are very entertaining.
OK, fine. They have to stay in
there. There's radiation in here.
All right, let's inject dye.
Is everything OK?
Uh... It's fine.
Owen Hunt is a
murdering, sadistic bastard.
Let me guess,
your first wet lab?
He's stabbing pigs,
defenseless pigs,
or as he likes to call
them, "live tissue,"
God forbid you should
call them animals.
He is the new head
of trauma, Stevens.
May not be ideal, but if that's
how he does things, roll with it.
We don't need live subjects. What
happened to "first do no harm"?
That's about all living things.
Actually, I think it's
just about humans.
I'm saying this to you as my
roommate and not my attending.
Uh-huh.
You disgust me.
- Damn it!
- What, it wasn't good for you?
- Impossible.
- It's not that it wasn't good.
It's that it was.
- A "thank you"
would've been nice.
- You paged me?
Got a 10-year-old girl with a
tumor wrapped around her aorta.
- I'm putting together a team.
- This is her angio?
Thing is wrapped
around five major arteries.
- It's bad, but I've got ideas.
- Try them on someone
who might actually live.
I admit it doesn't look great,
but her family
mentioned you by name.
That's nice, but I
really don't care.
Well, I do.
Don't get emotional, Bailey. No
one likes a girl who gets emotional.
Still, I'd like you on my team.
I'm sorry about this, little
guy. It must've been awful.
One day you're at some
beautiful farm out in the country,
breathing in the fresh air, lounging
in the mud with your friends.
Next thing you
know you're sedated
- and stabbed in
some skills lab.
- Get it together.
Heads up.
Take your interns
down to ER. I'll meet you.
Multiple MVC. Six incoming.
You, lab's over. Do your charts.
- What about my pig?
- She's got it.
- What?
- You're staying here.
With a half dozen
crash victims into the pit?
You have four struggling
victims here. Keep them alive.
Karev gets to work on people
and I have 300 pounds of bacon?
Live bacon. They better
be that way when I get back.
Thirty-five-year-old backseat passenger,
forehead versus window, the window won.
Second-degree burns on the
left side. Vitals stable en route.
- Trauma one. What do you got?
- Charles Hiott, 46.
Positive ecchymosis over
abdomen. Last BP 96 over 68.
Know how to do a
trauma ultrasound?
- Yes.
- In that case he's yours.
- Can I help you?
- Dr. Karev paged us.
Got it covered.
A head injury and burns.
Don't think you have it covered.
- Karev, are you a doctor?
- Yes, sir.
You capable of assessing
a patient's injuries?
- Yep.
- Like I said, got it covered.
- Let us dive in.
- Appreciate the offer,
but I want my residents to
learn to deal with trauma.
They won't learn
as much or as fast
if they watch attendings do
it unless that attending is me.
Three other hospitals have
already sent them away.
And if we were smart, we
would do the same thing.
What is the matter with you?
We can try and cut
around the stomach.
No. The only way to
do that is to take it out.
- They've done ex-vivo
autotransplants.
- With livers and kidneys.
Why don't we take out
the stomach and kidneys?
That'd be great, if
you wanted to kill her.
We're talking about two completely
different blood supplies here.
So no, not a good idea, Grey.
Who are those people?
Uh, that's Tori's dad,
Randy, and his brother, Pat,
and Pat's wife, Jean,
and Tori's brother David...
- Why are they staring at us?
- I don't think they're staring.
I think they're just waiting...
seeing if we have any news.
Try and come up with
something before I get back.
Close the blinds, Grey.
- You paged me?
- Rambo's completely
out of control.
- Excuse me?
- Hunt. He kicked me
out of my own ER.
- Did he kill somebody?
- Not yet.
Call me when he does.
I don't have time for it.
I have a dying 10-year-old and doctors who can't
stop bickering long enough to solve a problem,
except for your girlfriend who's
more interested in playing with a doll.
She dragged that thing all around
the hospital when she was five,
and let me tell you,
it was cuter in a child.
- Any luck?
- What do you think?
I know you want
to be number one,
but we can't take in every
charity case that comes along.
It is a huge waste of resources.
It's your call, Dr. Bailey.
Grey, put that away.
This isn't playtime.
I'm not playing, I'm thinking. What
if we took out each of the organs
where the tumor interferes
with the blood supply?
By the time you clamp off the aorta
you risk damaging the other organs.
- Even if you
take them out one by one?
- You don't have the time.
What about if we made the time?
Dr. Bailey, let's throw
some stuff up on the board.
CT showed a subdural
hematoma. Should I book an OR?
First thing's first. The scalp
is bleeding. What do you do?
- I page Shepherd.
- Shepherd's not here.
What do you do to
stop the bleeding?
Suture laceration,
tie off bleeders.
That'll take two hours. What would
you use in this room to take care of this?
- Staples?
- It's his forehead.
Want this guy to look like
Frankenstein the rest of his life?
- Skin glue.
- Excellent.
Clean it, close it, stick a
pressure dressing over it.
- How are you feeling,
Mr. Hiott?
- Not too good.
How'll we make
Mr. Hiott feel better?
Ultrasound showed free fluid.
We'll get him to a CT to confirm.
- Pretty much OR bound.
- Excellent. Is that tetanus?
Know who we have to thank for
the invention of the tetanus shot?
Horses. First experiments
were done on horses.
Want to take out her
abdominal organs?
- Intestines, stomach, everything?
- - All at once?
That's right.
We'll put the organs on ice
while we dissect out the tumor,
then reconnect the vessels
using synthetic grafts
and put the organs back in.
Why didn't Graham or Fleisher
over at Lake Washington suggest this?
They're a couple of smarties.
Probably because it's
never been done before.
It is extremely risky. There are any
number of things that could go wrong.
I don't know, Randy. Maybe
we should try more chemo.
With all due respect, Mrs. Begler,
I don't think there's time for that.
Is it going to save her life?
It's your best shot.
Your only shot.
- Then do it.
- OK.
Dr. Bailey, I'm not a vet,
and while I can appreciate the value
of practicing technique on live tissue,
there's a multiple
MVC in the pit
and my education will be far
better served practicing on humans.
- Who's babysitting
the pigs now?
- My interns.
Major Hunt order the interns
to baby-sit the pigs or you?
- Not the point.
- Make it the point.
I don't have time. I'm taking
six organs out of a person.
See, that's not fair.
I'm not Dr. Doolittle.
The zebras and the elephants
are thanking their lucky stars for that.
I have a question.
Why aren't we taking out the kidney
since the left renal artery is involved?
We can remove the tumor
without doing that, so why bother?
- I have another question.
- Yes?
Why can't you look at me?
- What?
- You can't look at me.
You haven't been able
to look at me all day.
I think you're imagining things.
Oh, I don't think I am.
But, hey, if you say so.
I do. I say so. Instead of worrying
about whether or not I'm looking at you,
concentrate on saving a 10-year-old
girl that we're about to eviscerate.
Dr. Grey, why do we
dissect down in quadrants?
So we can look at the vessels to
make sure we have reconstruction.
- Very good.
- - Suction in here, please.
Tori's dad is on the phone.
OR desk wants to know
- if they can put him through.
- No.
- He's insistent.
- I'm busy.
I think... Hold this up a
little bit higher, Dr. Grey.
I want to make
sure to avoid... that!
Let's get some clamps.
Another clamp, please.
- Right there.
- Let's hang another bag of blood.
Better hope the
aorta's not that friable.
Otherwise all the blood in
the world won't save this girl.
- Ryan, what's Reggie's pulse?
- Sixty-nine.
Really? 'Cause Wilbur's at
102. I'm pretty sure that's bad.
- Babe's like an ox. Hers is 52.
- Hey, no cute names!
They're not pets,
they're subjects.
It's not our job to
get affectionate.
It's our job to keep them alive,
so the attending who thinks we're incapable
can choke on his words at the end of the day.
So I don't want to
hear Wilbur or Babe.
You want to call them something,
call them sausage or prosciutto.
Wilbur's crashing.
- What? What did you do?
- I don't... I don't...
I gotta re-open that thoracotomy.
Pull that chest tray back.
- Dr. Bailey?
- Removing the organs on three.
Ready? One... two...
three.
Let me have it.
Wow.
I'll need medium
and large vessel loops
to dissect out the tumor.
Mr. Begler again. He wants to
talk to you about his daughter.
- I'm pretty busy.
- I already told him that.
- Tell him again.
- I've told him 18 times.
Chief, you need
to go talk to them.
Hey, you did put me in charge.
I'll be back.
What the hell?
Look at this crap.
Is that glue? You
used skin glue?
Dr. Hunt wanted to get
him out of there pretty quick.
Because Dr. Hunt didn't
have you revise the wound,
he could lose half his face.
You can't rotate a flap,
you call someone who can.
He says the ER's like being in
the field. Use what's available.
What qualifies us as a war zone,
Karev? Our undermanned gift shop?
The lukewarm drinks
from the coffee cart?
Guy's a meatballer.
What do you expect?
- Meatballer?
- Trauma guys slap it together.
- Dr. Webber, how's Tori?
- Stable.
We're removing the tumor.
I should be in there to help,
- but I'm out here instead.
- I just needed an update.
Not important you get
an update right now.
The best doctors we have
are focused on your daughter.
Calls and interruptions
don't help us focus.
I'm sorry. I know we have
been underfoot sometimes,
but we have been
to a lot of hospitals,
and hospitals are not easy
places to get information.
A lot of times it's impossible
to get a doctor to talk to you
or to get the doctors
to talk to each other.
And I don't know if it's neglect
or their egos getting in the way,
I don't care. We're just trying
to take care of our little girl.
She's 10, she's
scared and she's sick.
We're doing whatever we can.
Don't ever stop taking
care of her like that.
♪ I've tried, but I couldn't
find any warning of you ♪
Stevens, have you
ever used a GIA stapler?
No, but I'm ready,
I can handle it.
Answer me three
questions and I'll let you.
- OK.
- Question one:
The polio vaccine, which animal
do we have to thank for that?
- This really necessary?
- Only if you want
to use that stapler.
- Flipper babies.
- What?
Flipper babies. Ten thousand
babies were born with birth defects
in the 1950s because their
pregnant mothers took Thalidomide.
First developed on guinea pigs.
Guinea pigs didn't have side effects.
- And your point?
- My point is that
humans and animals
have different physiologies,
- different reactions.
- They can have
different reactions.
- Doesn't mean they will.
- Tell that to those
10,000 babies and moms.
So the polio vaccine, developed
using mice and monkeys.
You can keep your
stapler. It's not worth it.
Give me the status
on Reggie and Paddy.
Reggie's fine. Paddy's
pulse ox is low but stable.
- Babe?
- Holding steady.
Thought we weren't
supposed to give them names.
I could give them numbers
but then I'd tell you
Three needs antibiotics
and find you shoving
a needle in Grey's ass.
His vitals are getting
worse, damn it.
- Uh, did you check his lung?
- I took out an entire lobe.
- His descending aorta?
- I've tried everything.
Pulseless.
That's it. We need to
give him more exposure.
- You're opening him up more?
- I need everyone's help,
stem to stern.
What if he can't take
it? You could kill him.
Don't get emotional. Get ready to
start massaging his heart. Scalpel.
Bailey, can you
dissect any more?
There's nothing to dissect.
There's barely any artery left.
What about if we extend
the Gore-Tex graft?
What's left is too friable.
We can't reconnect the
organs to the vessels?
- Not at this moment. No.
- But if
we can't reconnect,
they won't reperfuse
and they'll die.
- Yes, they will.
- - Too late for a transplant?
Well, we'd have to find six
good organs in about eight hours.
- It's too late
for a transplant.
- And a gold star for Grey.
We could put in more Gore-Tex.
Oh, put even more
synthetic material in?
- What about
a saphenous vein graft?
- She's getting acidotic.
- That has to be pre-planned.
- What's your idea?
- Excuse me?
- You're good at shooting down
every idea we come
up with. What's yours?
It was my idea not to do this
in the first place, Dr. Bailey.
Yeah, and you made that
very clear every chance you got.
Shut up! I don't care
who had what idea when.
Get over yourselves. Shut
up and talk to each other.
What about using
human umbilical vein?
- Ready to go,
already heparinized.
- OK. I like it.
- Erica, what do you think?
- It could work.
It's Dr. Bailey's call,
if she wants to do it.
- I do.
- OK, in that case, let's do it.
Nice work on the valve.
First developed in pigs,
but more recently in cows.
Are you done beating me up for
the day because I'd like to go home.
- I was trying to teach you.
- You want to teach us?
Take us to the Simulab with the
plastic guys who have heart rates
and blood pressure and
croak when you nick an artery.
Until you apply scalpel to skin
you're just going through motions.
That attitude?
That's from before.
We have technology. We
don't have to torture creatures.
You don't get to accuse me of
torture. Those animals felt no pain.
You don't know that.
You don't know what they felt, you
don't know how scared they were.
Animals are sensitive
and intelligent creatures.
And that is not me being
emotional, that is simply the truth.
Want me to learn from your methods?
Want me to learn anything from you?
Then don't stab pigs in front of
me and tell me the sky isn't blue.
You are torturing God's creatures in
an age where we have the technology
that no longer requires us to. If
you want to do that, go ahead,
but don't tell me I'm less
of a doctor for walking away.
Come on, Wilbur, don't do this.
His heart's not
filling. You know...
Massage it with both
hands, like a heart sandwich.
Good. Good.
There! Right there.
Stupid. Look at that.
The knife went through his
diaphragm into his spleen. OK.
Hand me those clamps.
We've got blood pooling
the lower left quadrant.
Anybody see where
it's coming from?
Here. This graft.
Satinsky clamps.
- And four-0 Prolene.
- Scissors.
Waiting, Dr. Bailey.
OK, this thing's coming out.
We're still waiting, Dr. Bailey.
OK. Suction. Clear it out.
OK, release clamps.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
- Right in here.
- Still nothing.
No pulsation.
Come on, come on.
Reperfusion complete!
The heart's beating on its own.
All right!
All right.
Everyone, hell of a job.
I've known women to be upset because
they couldn't make it to the big finish.
Never had anything
to do with me.
Usually something to
do with their anatomy.
Point is, I've never known
a woman to be upset
because she could take a curtain
call. You're a conundrum, Torres.
Erica cried this morning.
In bed. After sex.
That was a compliment, for you.
- The crying was a compliment.
- It wasn't a compliment for me.
She was having a
revelation. She was having...
The sex is awesome with Erica.
We've reached
awesome, which is...
- Awesome.
- Yes, but it's also
awesome with you.
So, what's the problem?
Guess I thought there
should be a difference...
between you and Erica.
If I'm... There should
be a difference.
The difference
between me and Erica
is that I know you had
sex with her 12 hours ago.
She doesn't know you had sex with
me, and that makes you a cheater.
Do you want to be a
cheater? 'Cause I'm fine with it.
The question is, are you?
Gonna yell at the major
general. Wanna come?
- Hell yeah. Be right there.
- Hey, Torres.
Hey.
- Hunt, can I talk to you?
- Sure.
- Karev?
- No, no, he can stay.
Want Karev to hear how you screwed
up the flap of my head trauma, fine.
My job's to keep him
alive. It's what I did.
What you did was almost
maim a guy for the rest of his life.
You're lucky I saved
the blood supply.
- What would you have done?
- A man with a deep scalp wound,
and two of the best surgeons in
the country standing ten feet away.
I would've asked those two surgeons
to step in. That's what I would've done.
I mean, medically. What would you
have done medically so I can do better?
I recognize there's different ways
of doing things, even the basics.
Here, someone appears
dead, you go to them first.
In Iraq someone appears dead
you don't. This is day one for me.
You think there's a better
way then tell me, and I'll listen.
- Again, both of you, great job.
- Thank you.
Is there a problem, Dr. Bailey?
Just find it hard to believe
you're accepting congratulations,
considering you didn't
want to do this operation.
When you finally did do it, you
fought me every step of the way.
And yet you still had a world-class
heart surgeon by your side.
You may be a fine surgeon, God
knows I know that, but not today.
Today you were
a pain in the ass.
A naysaying, bullying,
consistently negative pain in the ass.
At no point did you encourage me
or do anything to make me think this
surgery could be anything but a failure.
And it wasn't just me. You made it as
hard as humanly possible for all of us.
So, yeah, we did do a nice job
today. We did a great job today.
But that wasn't thanks to you,
that was thanks to me and the chief.
And Meredith Grey.
And Anatomy Jane.
Babe is indestructible.
She lost a part of her liver and
small bowel but she's doing fine.
We had to cross-clamp Wilbur's
aorta and massage his heart.
I couldn't locate the
source of his bleeding
until I found a hole in his diaphragm,
realized he had a splenic laceration.
He's a fighter,
he's pulling through.
Reggie had some oozing
after his colon resection,
but we packed it and he's
been stable ever since.
Paddy almost bled out because
his carotid was sliced right through.
We put in a graft. He's
been stable ever since.
- He's good as new.
- That's good.
That's great work, all of you.
So put them out and make
sure you write up all your work.
- What do you mean
"put them out?"
- Terminate them. Kill 'em.
I'm not killing those pigs. I spent
the day trying to keep them alive.
Want them dead, do it yourself.
You resected half
of a liver today.
You repaired a diaphragm, did a
splenectomy, grafted a severed artery
and repaired a lacerated
bladder, performed a lobectomy.
And I understand you
even removed a tumor.
On Paddy, his thyroid.
You have any idea how
much you just learned?
They'd be in pain. Those are
massive injuries, months of recovery.
To keep them alive after
all that, it's not humane.
Seriously, you don't
remember my name?
I remember your name,
but that was before.
This last tour, I was on
a forward surgical team.
We... treated combat
casualties in the field.
You're mostly looking
to do damage control:
Sedate 'em, ventilate 'em, airlift
'em to Baghdad, get out of there.
Only this one time we
didn't get out fast enough
'cause we ended up in the
middle of an RPG ambush.
There were 20 people in my
unit, including me, and 19 died.
And then I got discharged.
So... I'm not there
anymore, in the before.
I knew your name in the before.
Now I'm living in the after.
- Erica.
- You want to apologize
to someone,
apologize to Bailey. Thanks to
you, I made her life a living hell.
I slept with Mark Sloan.
If that's your idea of an
apology, you seriously...
Shut up!
You were crying
and seeing leaves.
And I wasn't.
OK? I may never see leaves.
Or maybe I will see leaves,
but I'll also see flowers.
I might be a whole
forest girl, I don't know,
but I do know that I
want to be with you
and... to do that I have to
at least tell you the truth,
and the truth is I slept
with Mark Sloan today.
OK.
Twice, actually.
- You paged?
- Yeah. How's Tori?
She's good, stable.
You weren't imagining things.
You used to run around
here with that doll all the time.
Took her everywhere. The
cafeteria, the old art gallery.
Tori's got a whole army.
You didn't have anyone.
Seeing Anatomy Jane
reminded me of how
much I was to blame for that.
You're a living reminder
of every failure in my life.
That's not your fault.
And if I thought "I'm sorry" would hold
any meaning for you at all, I'd say it.
I'd say it a thousand
times a day.
Some wars are never over.
Some end in an uneasy truce.
I can't do it.
I know I'm supposed to, but...
They'll suffer.
Don't let them suffer.
♪ From the valley to the stars ♪
- So no more on-call room, huh?
- Afraid not.
That's too bad.
Guess I'll, uh, see you around.
Hey.
Wanna get a drink?
Really?
Just 'cause we're
not sleeping together
doesn't mean we can't
hang out, be friends.
You're good for
more than sex, Mark.
I would love to get a drink.
- She's not gonna
cry every time, right?
- No. That passes.
Some wars result in
complete and total victory.
Sit.
Mac and cheese, from
the box, not the freezer.
Some wars end
with a peace offering.
I named the pigs today.
I'm sorry, but I don't
know what that means.
I take things personally.
I get too emotional.
There's no place for it at work,
not with the pigs and not with you.
I'm sorry.
This is so much better
than the freezer kind.
Thought you were sleeping with
Michelle tonight, or was it Jackie?
- Iz.
- I've had a hard day, Alex.
And a sad night. Please
just leave me alone.
- Izzie.
- What?
I'm not good at this, all right?
I'm not good at relationships
or talking about stupid feelings
and you are, so maybe you could
teach me or something, you know?
Tell me what I did wrong.
You don't want us
to see other people.
You don't want us to see other people
and that's how you tried to tell me...
by asking if it was cool
if you screwed Michelle.
- Laughing's not helping.
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
- So you want lessons, huh?
- I want lessons.
OK. You start with,
"Isobel Stevens,
you are staggeringly
good in bed.
You're amazingly
smart, wonderfully funny,
- and you care about animals."
- That's where I start?
Yeah. And then you say,
"You want to go steady with me?"
That's what I'd
say if it was 1952.
- Alex.
- Yeah?
You want to go steady with me?
If that's what you want.
I mean, yeah, whatever.
And some wars...
end in hope.
Oh, look!
I wore this every day
to elementary school.
Nice. Your mom
make that for you?
Yeah, right. She probably got it at
the lost and found at the hospital.
- Mer, you should do this one.
- Is it more ugly hats?
- Another diary?
- More than one.
But all these
wars are nothing...
Oh, my God.
Compared to the most
frightening war of all.
♪ All the love we need ♪
♪ Feel it coming in ♪
♪ Like a memory ♪
The one you have yet to fight.