There's this thing that happens
when people find out you're a doctor.
Good morning.
Did you...
- patter?
- Propose? No. Not yet.
You'll be the first to know.
They stop seeing you as a person
and begin to see you as something
- bigger than you are.
- How's she doing?
She's, uh... OK.
She's OK.
They have to see
us that way, as gods.
Otherwise we're just
like everyone else.
Unsure, flawed, normal.
- How's she doing?
- No change. This is
the MCA Doppler?
Yeah. Can I get you
anything? Coffee?
I'm fine, thanks.
So we act strong, remain stoic.
We hide the fact that
we're all too human.
He still beating himself up? Addison
thinks he's still beating himself up.
- Alex...
- The head of Neuro hasn't left
- his patient's bedside
for three days.
- He's fine.
- I thought Addison left.
- She put her brother on
a plane last night.
Admit it, her hanging
around your guy, it bugs.
It doesn't bug. You bug.
Karev, page Addison.
Tell her I need her to stay.
OK, it bugs a little.
Lack of blood flow is causing
the mini-strokes and aphasia.
We can't put the surgery off any longer.
I'll do a repair called an EC-IC bypass.
And that will fix the strokes?
She'll be better after this?
- I'm hoping it will work, yes.
- But, uh...
They wouldn't operate unless it were
safe for the baby. Dr. Montgomery?
Your blood pressure's high, but I'll
be there to monitor you and the baby.
Get some rest.
We'll see you soon.
- Thank you for staying.
- Least I could do for saving
Archie.
Um...
I know what we said
before about the baby,
but if something should happen, if it
comes down to a choice, save my wife.
We can make another baby.
We can't make another her.
Fifty-two-year-old
male, fell down stairs.
Five days post-op from a cholecystectomy
which looks to have caused the fall.
Why would having your
gallbladder removed cause a fall?
A non-laparoscopic cholie?
Sir, what hospital did you
have your operation at?
- Here. My surgeon
was Dr. Campbell.
- That explains it.
Excuse us for a moment.
All right, what?
Campbell was Seattle
Grace's first female surgeon.
She just sits in her office
and spreads prestige around.
She still does the routine
surgery now and then.
Botches routine
surgery. I'll page the chief.
- No, page Campbell. It's her patient.
- Let her maim the guy again?
Page someone who
knows how to operate,
instead of some dinosaur
who refuses to retire her scalpel
and go join her friends in Boca.
The dinosaur is here.
No need to page me.
- So did you scope her out yet?
- Who?
- Arizona.
- Oh, right.
I haven't had a chance to swing by
Peds and ask the nurse to point out
the attending who kissed
my friend in a bar bathroom.
- At least you're
still good for coffee.
- That's not for you.
- Coffee. Why, thank you, Mark.
- That's not for you either.
- Good morning, Dr. Grey.
- Keep your secret coffee.
Until you tell Derek, our
relationship continues to consist
of you hiding in the attic and
me smuggling snacks past Mer.
- Know what that makes you?
- Your boyfriend?
Anne Frank. I'm dating
Anne Frank, and I'm tired of it.
I want to go downstairs. I wanna
tell the Germans to kiss my ass.
I'm gonna tell him. Soon.
When I do, you'll be
my date to the wedding.
- Derek proposed?
- Not yet. But when he does.
This is the first step
in the start of a new life.
How are we feeling?
Positive? Confident?
I am good. Great.
You take care of
your own feelings.
Peds Surgery is
super competitive.
That's why I'm armed with
letters of recommendation
to put the competition to shame.
Shepherd says I'm talented.
Sloan finds it an
honor to work with me...
- What does the chief think?
- I'm still working on that.
Chief's recommendation matters.
Everyone on the committee...
I know! You calm down.
I've got it under control.
Good. Because
speaking on behalf of me,
we couldn't be more
excited to have you. Yay.
Chief? Just a friendly nudge.
Your recommendation is
due by the end of the day.
- I'll remind Patricia.
- You have written it?
You'll get your recommendation.
- I need more time.
- No.
Don't get me wrong. I am
honored that you asked me
over all the other residents,
but it's not easy distilling a doctor
of your stature to 500 words or less.
I chose you because you're the only one
to do this without screwing up. So don't.
Make sure he planes the patio...
- Plates the...
- We'll get him piano lessons. Yes.
Only puddle shell... uh.
Only public...
Public school so he doesn't
become a snob, I know.
But I don't have to.
You're gonna be there
to make sure I don't
turn him into a jerk.
We're here.
I love just...
I know. You love me.
And I love you. I'll
see you in a few.
Thank you.
Her blood pressure's
higher than it was yesterday.
- We can't wait.
- I know...
You want me to be aware.
You're a good doctor. So am I.
Let's just be good together.
Your guy and my
guy work well together.
My guy works well with everyone.
- Dr. Stevens?
- Yes.
Think we'll get to
scrub in on a surgery?
You losers think you're capable of
holding someone's life in your hands
when you could barely
finish the intern bowl? Really?
- Dr. Stevens, remember me?
- Yes.
I was here a couple of days ago,
you told me I might have cancer.
You sent me to an oncologist,
who sent me to an immunologist,
who then sent me to some
other ologist I never heard of
before I set foot in this deathtrap.
80 thousand dollars in tests later,
the only thing wrong
with me is that I'm anemic!
- Anemic?
- My lawyer seems to think
that someone here
mislabeled the blood.
Switched it with someone
else's. I was told not to come here,
but my conscience wanted to
make sure you went through the files
of everybody who was
here at the clinic that day.
Of course we will. I'm so sorry.
Don't apologize to
me. I'm just anemic.
You apologize to
that dying person.
Middle cerebral artery?
Yes, after I connect the STA,
- we will close.
- Baby's having spontaneous
decels.
Mom's hypotensive. I don't
know how much they can handle.
MCA's bleeding a bit.
It shouldn't contribute.
Pressure's dropping. The
baby's gonna need to come out.
- Almost done. Wait.
- Not me that can't wait.
- The decels are getting
more frequent.
- A fetus can't handle
three surgeries in four days.
We have to get the baby out.
- He's too young to come out.
- Last decel lasted 30 seconds.
Let's go. I'm taking him out.
- Ten-blade.
- Leave the baby in.
Done. I'm done.
I'm done.
You've got a minor fracture
so you won't need surgery.
You should on your
feet within a few weeks.
I don't know what I was thinking.
The wound wasn't healing as fast...
Next time, you call me, John.
Dr. Yang, explain to my patient
what you feel I should
have done differently
in order to avoid this
complication. Don't be shy.
OK. Well, patients status post
minimally invasive procedures
have been shown to have
decreased post-surgical discomfort...
In human please, Dr. Yang.
This surgery should have
been done laparoscopically.
Dr. Hunt, perhaps you
can explain to Dr. Yang
why I chose to do
the surgery this way.
Although some doctors prefer
to use the new technology,
there are others who
believe it's more risky
since we can't see or move
around as much during the surgery.
It's half a dozen either way.
Bravo, Dr. Hunt.
- Do you understand, John?
- Yes.
I have no doubt you
did the right thing by me.
Wonderful. Now, Dr. Yang,
please take our patient to CT.
Maybe you'll learn
something in the process.
While I confer with Dr. Hunt
about our course of treatment.
- I'm on a deadline.
- Sadie Harris mislabeled
a patient's blood sample.
The clinic's getting sued.
- Good thing Sadie no longer
works here.
- No, it's not.
Because it isn't just her.
The interns, all of them,
they're capable of the same mistake.
They are dangerous and they are bad.
Don't tell me I'm overly
emotional and it isn't personal!
Because it is personal! I've
worked so hard to teach them,
- and... and it is personal.
- Stevens.
I thought the same
thing about you every day
the first year you worked here.
Know what the chief told me?
Get out.
You don't get much rest,
do you, Dr. Shepherd?
- Did you hear yourself?
- Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! I can talk!
I know! Listen to you!
And the baby? How's the baby?
The baby's stable. However,
your new labs show
that you're pre-eclamptic.
We hoped to keep it from progressing
to this stage, but stress of surgery
- was a lot on your body.
- So do we need to be worried?
Come on! Dr. Shepherd, tell
me we're done being worried.
First moment of hope
they've had in a week.
Pre-eclampsia is serious.
You're too close to this patient.
Stop fighting me on this. We
had a victory. Focus on that.
We give the family all the
information. That's our job.
- My guy won that round.
- Meredith?
Karev, can you go get
Jen's blood test results?
Give me a reason why I
shouldn't go to the chief.
- The surgery was a success.
- He made a mistake in her
first surgery.
He caused complications.
He feels responsible.
So tell me why I
shouldn't go to the chief.
During the trial, he lost
patients. It affected him.
For the better, I think. He
cares more, if that's possible.
You just have to trust him.
OK.
- Hey.
- Calliope.
- I haven't seen you around.
- Well, I've been avoiding you.
I know, it's so weird.
You share a kiss with a
woman you've never seen...
This is a new adventure,
one I'm so ready to take,
for the second
time, and... Anyway.
Do you want to go
on a date with me?
Wait, Erica and you.
She was your first?
- Yeah.
- Oh.
OK. So then I guess
my answer is no.
- I'm sorry.
- Wait. What?
Uh... Um...
You kissed me, out of
nowhere, in a bathroom.
OK, this is what I try to avoid.
You're all exploring
and experimenting and...
Yay! This is a really
exciting time for you.
But I work in Peds. I spend
my entire day around newborns.
So I try not to in
my personal life.
Thanks for asking,
though. I'm super flattered.
Super.
- As discussed.
- Thank you.
Newborn. I'm not a newborn.
I'm a senior resident.
I'm a great surgeon.
I'm a divorcee, for God's sake.
I'm...
I'm, uh... looking for you to
agree with me here, Bailey.
- Bailey?
- The chief,
he wrote me a form
letter of recommendation.
That's insane. He's
chief, you're Bailey.
"Pleasant in the OR and
enjoyed by the nurses.
She's completed a
serviceable amount of research.
A fine addition to any program."
Fine! He used the word "fine."
A blank page would mean more. I
pulled off a 12-person domino surgery.
I took out and put back
six of a dying girl's organs!
I am Dr. Bailey. I
am better than fine!
At least he didn't
call you a baby.
Just a minute more, Mr. Terzian.
Oh... Done tending
to Her Highness?
You're tough on people.
It's good to hold such high
standards, but this is medicine.
- No one's perfect.
- She's stubborn and
out of touch.
Forty years experience
means nothing?
Not if you don't
use them correctly.
She wants to be old
and keep operating? Fine.
- Just keep up with medicine.
- Cristina, this is one case.
You can't judge someone
based on one case.
That patient deserves
to know his doctor,
no matter whose
feelings it happens to hurt.
Laparoscopic or open, none of
us should have made that mistake.
You realize you're
charging one of our hospital's
most respected
surgeons with negligence.
Yes, sir.
Dr. Hunt, do you agree
with Dr. Yang's assessment?
- This is Dr. Yang's call.
- I'm asking you, Dr. Hunt.
Campbell outranks me, sir.
I think it would be best for you
to discuss it with her directly.
Very well. Page Dr. Campbell.
I want to speak to that
patient before surgery.
Yes, sir.
Way to take a stand.
There he is, the legend himself.
How are you, legend?
Are you drunk? Should
I be worried about you?
He's got his sense of humor
back. How's your patient?
She's good, stable. Today's
the first day in a long time
I remember what it feels
like to be good at my job.
You? Come on, you're like
the Dalai Lama of surgery.
People from all over the world come to
let you cut into them. Know what else?
You look good doing it. I
like the facial hair, by the way.
- Keep it that length. No more, no less.
- All right, stop.
Derek, there's something
we need to discuss.
- Go ahead and have sex
with Addison.
- Addison?
- Go for it.
- I don't want to.
Really? What did
you want to discuss?
Nothing.
OK.
- How's my mother?
- Bitter.
Angry. Genius.
What's so wrong is how much
the chief and your mother fought.
- Sex must have been great.
- Saying that, that's wrong.
What's wrong? Our entire
healthcare system? I agree.
Here it is. "March 3, 1979.
Assisted Margaret
Campbell on a splenectomy.
Impressive resume, adequate
technique." Hack! Even then.
You're working with
Margaret Campbell?
Yeah. Ye Oldy Timey thinks
she's sane enough to do surgery.
That's what I like
about your mom.
She wasn't Alzheimer-y
and still operating.
Do me a favor and shoot me if I
start making mistakes on patients
- and think it's kosher to cut.
- Sounds like Shepherd.
- Alex.
- Please, my guy's right.
Your guy nicked an aneurysm
and is trying to cover his ass.
Your guy needs to shut up.
- What happened?
- Bypass must have blown.
- Page Addison, meet in the OR!
- I told them everything was OK.
I don't understand. He said
the surgery was a success.
I'll give you an update
as soon as we can, OK?
The swelling's not going down.
Maybe the
ventriculostomy is plugged.
No. Damn it!
Derek?
I have to take out
the temporal lobe.
- Won't that kill her?
- No.
She could lose some speech,
memory and vocal pattern.
The brain can rewire. I've
done it before to stop seizures.
Have you done
it before for this?
- I'm doing it now.
- Baby's got decels.
What are we doing here, Derek?
Bayonet forceps.
What are we supposed to say?
"Shepherd's cutting out parts
of your wife's brain.
She'll pull through?"
Tell him the truth. Dr. Shepherd
is doing everything he can
- to save your wife and child.
- The guy's life ended as he
knew it. Tell him that.
Alex, just be...
The baby's having
heart fluctuations,
but Dr. Montgomery is taking every
precaution to avoid an early delivery.
- And my wife?
- Dr. Shepherd is trying to get
the bleeding under control, but we won't
know more until the surgery's finished.
But she won't die?
Please tell me she won't die.
Shepherd is doing everything
to make sure your wife lives.
She'll live?
Dr. Shepherd is doing
absolutely everything he can.
We should get back.
Right. Of course. Thanks.
- Thank you.
- Your guy sucks.
Mr. Terzian, your scans show a change
from Dr. Campbell's original assessment.
There was a complication
from the surgery,
a lacerated bile duct and artery.
You'll need another surgery to repair it.
- Is that all?
- Yes, that's all.
Oh, thank God!
I thought when they told me
the chief of surgery was coming,
I was a goner for sure.
We wanted to make you aware that it's within
your rights to request a change of surgeon.
- Dr. Campbell's not available?
- She's available.
No, thank you. I
choose Dr. Campbell.
- Very well. Dr. Campbell.
- Richard.
Sir, with all due respect, I don't think
the patient's clear on what happened.
You heard the patient.
He wants his doctor.
- But sir...
- Back down, Yang.
I just need you to tell me
if it's worthy of Dr. Bailey.
Bailey's an ass. She
doesn't listen to residents
when they have important
information about interns.
You're missing the
point of the exercise,
which is to say nice
and impressive things.
You still hang out here?
Just say she's dependable.
Say she's selfless.
Everything she was
until she wasn't. Just...
You should probably go.
Dependably selfless.
- Thank you.
- Hm.
Isobel Stevens?
It's been years since I've
had you in my OR, chief.
I seem to remember an incident
with a clamp being dropped
into an open body cavity.
You're never gonna let
me live that one down.
A good teacher never lets
up on her students. Although,
I've often wondered how the
upcoming classes learn anything
with the way we
teach these days.
Attendings seem more concerned
with inspiring their students,
using encouragement
and validation and so forth,
instead of instilling them
with the fear and shame
that causes one to remember
anything in the first place.
Dr. Hunt, you come
from the military.
Wouldn't you say the rigid aspects
of your training helped you become
- the doctor you are today?
- Yes. Very much so.
Dr. Yang, on the other
hand, something tells me fear
is not something you
have often faced in the OR.
I'd appreciate any
opportunity to learn.
Wonderful. Let us begin then.
Tell me how you'd do a
pulmonary embolectomy.
I'd insert a steerable
catheter into the femoral vein
and position a fluoroscope
adjacent to the embolus.
What would you do if the
power should suddenly go out?
Or if you had to operate in a hospital
that couldn't afford a fluoroscope?
It's like a calculator. Just because
there's a machine to do it for them,
children shouldn't have
to learn simple arithmetic?
If it would help them
avoid mistakes like this one.
Out of my OR!
I said get out! Out!
This is still my OR!
She's bleeding into the frontal
lobe. If I can stop the bleed,
save the rest of the
brain, she'll have a chance.
Decels are getting longer.
- I have to
deliver the baby.
- No. Just...
If you cut her, she'll
bleed out. I can save her.
How?
- I have to cut out
the frontal lobe.
- What?
Derek, no. Stop. Derek.
You've done enough.
Can she live without
frontal and temporal?
- Yes.
- No, she can't.
This baby isn't
getting any oxygen.
You want to save Jen, you
feel you have to, but not this way.
I can save them
both. She will live.
Not as the person her husband
and child need her to be.
She'll lose everything about
her that makes her human.
- Meredith.
- Are you sure you can do this?
- I have no choice. Bipolars.
- Baby's heart is bottoming out.
Damn it, Derek!
This has gone too far.
Taking the frontal lobe out, even if
she lives, you're creating a monster.
You don't get to play God here!
Jen is gone, but this baby
has a chance. Let her go.
Let it go. Please, let...
- I'm taking the baby out.
- Put down the scalpel, Addison!
You put down the scalpel.
- Addison, put the scalpel down.
- You put it down!
Get off the scalpel,
Addison! Take it off!
- Meredith...
- Do not go anywhere.
Karev, go!
- Derek, don't do this.
- Do not touch my patient.
Meredith.
Derek, look at me. You
don't have to do this.
Jen's gone. It's too late. You
can't save her. She's gone.
We can save the baby.
Derek, look at me.
Certain surgeries get
the best of all of us.
I made a mistake.
A careless mistake.
And for that, I am sorry.
But I am only human,
as human as any of us.
And for that, I
do not apologize.
- Margaret, you don't have...
- No need to discuss it further.
No need at all.
- Chief, we need you in OR 1!
- Karev?
Right now, sir!
I was fired. From the Army.
They call it an
honorable discharge,
but they knew it was my
time, even though I didn't.
I'm grateful to them for that.
The baby's still in distress.
I need to take it out.
Wait. Just wait. The
bleeding could stop.
The baby could stabilize. If we
do a C-section now, she'll die.
- She is dead, Derek.
- Please, just wait.
Most of her brain is gone. For all
intents and purposes, she's dead.
Karev, page Dr. Friedman's team.
Tell her we have a preemie on the way.
Stop cutting.
Why are you cutting?
Meredith, get some more
blood. She needs more blood.
Get more blood.
- She needs more blood.
- No more blood, Derek.
No more blood.
You're smart to get it looked at, but
it doesn't look too suspicious to me.
- Even combined with
high LDH levels?
- Oh.
That could be caused by
anything, mono, exercise even.
Coupled with neurological
episodes? Hallucinations?
There we go. All done.
You and I both see
patients do this everyday.
They find something and
convince themselves they're sick.
But as doctors,
you and I both know
that it's our job to
remain worry-free
until we have proof
that says otherwise.
That's what you should do.
Relax. By this time tomorrow,
you'll be laughing at the fact
you thought anything was wrong.
OK. Ready?
He looks strong.
He definitely has a chance.
Let's get him intubated.
Placenta.
The steroids we gave your wife
allowed your baby's lungs to mature.
That, combined with the extra
days that Dr. Shepherd took
to do the surgery, makes us
very hopeful that he'll survive.
I don't understand.
She just died?
I'm sorry.
Yeah, I know.
You said that. Um...
I'm asking how she died.
Your wife's high blood pressure
caused the bypass to fail.
That caused the bleeding
and swelling in the brain.
Dr. Shepherd did everything he could to save
her. There was too much damage to her brain.
That's when Dr. Montgomery
stepped in to deliver the baby.
You said it was a routine
procedure, she would be fine.
Then there was a complication.
And you said you fixed that.
But then the baby got sick,
and that made Jen sick.
But then you said
you fixed that, too.
And now she's dead.
- I'm sorry.
- Stop saying you're sorry!
You killed her!
You're a murderer! A murderer!
Where's my wife?
I want my wife!
I want...
I know it's bad. But I tried.
You're just very complex,
and word-defying.
Chief!
That is a letter of
recommendation!
O'Malley? You want me to
take pointers from O'Malley?
You'd be hard-pressed to find a
better person to take pointers from.
- Chief? Chief!
- Exactly!
I am the chief of surgery. I don't have
time to write letters to pump your ego.
My head of Neuro is
being called a murderer,
I have to fire my general
surgeon 'cause she won't retire,
interns are mixing up
blood samples in your clinic,
and you want me to write a
recommendation so you can leave?
Leave you? Sir, I am
applying for a fellowship
in pediatric surgery.
Which is not what we discussed! Do you
know how much of my time you wasted?
The amount of work it
takes to groom someone?
You were supposed
to become the next me!
You wanted me to
become the next you.
I am not your son
or your daughter.
You don't pin all your
hopes and dreams on me, sir!
I'm seeing Lexie.
Sleeping with her too, but it's
more than that. We're happy.
I'm happy.
OK, that's... Maybe
I deserved that.
You know what? I didn't.
You have no right to tell
me who I can sleep with.
You're worried
about your legacy.
But I am not your legacy!
And me applying to...
You are not listening to me.
What the...?
Oh, my goodness!
Come on. Come on!
Come on, stop. Come on!
Come on.
It's done.
That's her guy.
I'd do a pulmonary arteriotomy,
directly visualize the clot
and use forceps to extract it.
That's how I'd do a pulmonary
embolectomy without a fluoroscope.
The fact that you felt the
need to come tell me that
tells me you're a much better
surgeon than I first thought.
I've decided today's
surgery was my last.
You look at me like you won't wake
up one day not that far from now,
so much faster than
you can imagine,
and find that you are me.
When you can't cut anymore,
what will you have?
I was a god.
In this OR. Holding a scalpel.
And now...
What will you have?
I don't see anyone
burning the place down.
That's how they do it.
Do everything right. As soon as
you look away, they screw it up.
Hey, I'm sorry. I
was busy earlier.
With myself, I was
busy, so I'm sorry.
Don't be.
I called you an ass.
And you were right.
I think I just needed to vent.
I'm sick of this place.
Hell, I just watched
Derek Shepherd
beat up a man because he's
sick of it. That's the way it works.
The patients we lose, the mistakes
we make, that's how we learn.
It's the only way
it's ever been done.
Figure out a better way, and
you will be a better doctor than us.
Patients see us as gods.
- Izzie?
- Or they see us as monsters.
But the fact is,
we're just people.
Hi.
OK, well, it's not broken.
But you should ice it. Lots
and lots of ice. Goodbye.
- I'm so sorry.
- It was worth it.
No. It wasn't.
Maybe a little.
Thank you.
We screw up.
We lose our way.
- I have experience to give.
- Calliope?
Life experience. Like I was
married. Did you know that?
Or that I was in the
Peace Corps. Botswana.
It convinced me to
go to med school.
And I've experienced
the joy of cooking.
I make an excellent chicken piccata, in
addition to many other delicious meals
you'd be lucky to experience.
That you can't open your eyes
to see that makes you
a little inexperienced.
- Um... Calliope, this is Julie.
- Hi.
My date.
Even the best of
us have our off days.
Letter of recommendation. Callie
told me about the chief's letter.
I figured it was the least I can
do before getting back to LA.
- Addison Montgomery, thank you!
- Don't thank me. Just kick ass.
Don't make me regret writing that you
are the most promising young Peds surgeon
I've ever had the
pleasure of working with.
Still, we move forward.
Today, you were a teacher to
someone who needed to learn,
but you were also a bully to someone
who needed compassion. You were both.
I wasn't a bully.
And... I was right.
Right.
You're a lot like her.
Stubborn, opinionated, smart.
Forty years from now I'll have to
pry that scalpel out of your hand, too.
From my cold dead hands.
You're missing the point.
I wanna be around
40 years from now.
We don't rest on our laurels or
celebrate lives we've saved in the past.
Because there's always some
other patient that needs help.
So we force ourselves to
keep trying, to keep learning.
You're unmotivated,
careless, selfish, distracted,
and pretty much the people in this
hospital I'd least trust with my life.
But that's the way it's supposed
to be. You're interns. You're babies.
And you're lucky to work here.
We're all lucky because
we get to save lives.
Every day, we get to save
lives. That's our job, and...
It's not something a lot
of people get to do, so...
- In the hope that...
-  Let's begin.
- Maybe...
- New game.
- Someday...
- This is Patient X.
She's a 29-year-old female
we misdiagnosed with anemia
the first time she came to us.
Let's not make the
same mistake again.
We'll come just a little bit closer to
the gods our patients need us to be.