Previously on "Grey's Anatomy"...
We just received word of
a mass-casualty incident nearby.
You cannot tell Shepherd
until I've told Meredith.
Cristina and I are engaged.
Immediate! Immediate!
I need help down here!
My buddy's trapped.
He's trapped under a car.
Dr. O'Malley and I made a deal.
He's gonna find my son
before I go into surgery.
I just have to bandage him up,
we're gonna find someone
to take him to the hospital,
and then we're gonna find your mommy.
- I gotta get outta here!
- No, sir, don't move!
Like I said...
disappearances
happen...
Pains
go phantom...
blood
stops running...
and people...
people fade away.
There's more I have to say...
So much more.
But...
I've disappeared.
Did you check on Kramer in 2309?
Because his x-rays are done,
and I don't know what to do.
Higgins in 2312 needs diet orders
before he can eat.
Done and done.
Um, I need you to monitor
Collins in 2323.
Page me if his systolic drops below 90.
I gave him a loading dose
of dig to lower his heart rate now.
Have either of you seen Dr. Grey?
Uh, I checked on her earlier, but
she's a little sedate today so...
Not Dr. Ellis Grey.
Dr. Meredith Grey.
- No.
- Not since this morning.
Fine.
Um, if there's anything emergent,
page me in the pit.
Georges...
Did you find him?
Is Chris okay? Is he awake? Is he...
Answer Mrs. Heit, O'Malley.
Chris is fine.
He's glad you're okay, and he'll be
waiting for you after surgery.
He's being very brave.
That's my Chris. That's my boy.
Thank you, Dr. O'Malley, so much.
Dr. O'Malley.
Hold up a second.
So what happens when the happy mother
in there wakes up after surgery
and her son isn't there to greet her?
What then?
How you gonna explain that, O'Malley?
If she wakes up after surgery because
my lie helped to save her life,
I'm okay with that, Dr. Bailey.
Find that child.
Yes, ma'am.
Her echo showed cardiac tamponade.
Hmm. So our first priority is stabilize
the traumatic pericardial effusion.
Well, keeping mom alive means keeping
baby alive. I'll monitor the surgery
while he operates.
I'll notify the O.R.
Chief, we got a mob scene in the clinic of
people looking for missing family members
and nothing but a 2-hour-old
list of patients.
No one has any more
information than you do.
The police are asking us questions.
Search and Rescue can't track it.
- We'll have to do it ourselves.
- Is there some kind of system that...
You're the system, Karev.
Figure it out.
How's she doing?
Well, we won't know until
we get her up to the O.R.
Is she still a Jane Doe?
Yeah.
Oh, to be in that condition and have
no one who knows you even know...
What?
I mean, she's all alone.
It makes you think.
You know, if I went missing, would
anyone notice I was gone?
Do something.
He's  still seizing.
There's nothing more I can do.
You're supposed to put something in his
mouth so he doesn't bite his tongue,
aren't you?
Nobody's putting anything in his mouth.
We just have to let him ride it out.
Wh... what are you gonna do?
You just can't let him die.
Th... they're gonna come soon... in a
little while... and they'll get him out.
You said we don't got much time.
- What if they don't get him out
from there before he...
I don't know.
I don't know, okay? I don't know.
Please, you can't quit on us now.
You just...
you just gotta try something else.
I'm out of practice.
I've been watching.
For weeks, I've just been watching.
I...
I'm sorry.
You stopped the bleeding. That was good.
Come... come on. Please, Doc.
I know this guy. I believe in him.
I believe he can make it.
You gotta believe in it, too.
You gotta believe you can do this.
Please.
Don't stop now.
Who's got a cell phone?
You guys good?
You okay?
Yeah, what do you got?
Nearly severed leg, but he had his
artery tied off, so that's something.
Yeah. Who tied off the artery?
Was it dr. Grey? This is her jacket.
We found him like this.
She must have moved on.
Yeah, okay.
Doc.
Yeah.
What is it?
Yeah, just stabilize the fracture and get
him to the hospital as soon as possible.
Hey.
You okay?
Hey, did...did the Doctor bring you
here? Huh? Meredith?
Is Meredith okay?
Hi, my name's Georges.
Is your name Chris?
Is he yours?
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
-  Do you have a new list?
- Uh, not yet.
Nothing? How can there be no new
information?
Isn't there someone you can call?
Someone who knows something?
Uh, nobody knows anything right now,
- We've been here for hours waiting!
I mean, what are we supposed to do?
- Quiet!
All right, that list is all I have for
you, and it sucks, but that's it.
I can't believe you don't have some kind
of a system. I mean...
Give me a minute to think.
I'll come up with a damn system.
I just want you to know that I understand
you're under a lot of pressure.
If you... if you just need
to sit for a minute...
or if you need a hand...
or a hug...
- Chief Webber.
- Oh, Chief, I got a guy here, and...
and we... we can't extricate him.
- Hold on.
- And I've tried everything.
- Hold... hold on.
- Who's this?
- It's Izzie Stevens. I'm at the dock.
I've got a patient with a
depressed skull fracture
and probably an intracranial bleed.
Is he showing signs of
increased pressure?
Yes. His left pupil is blown.
He's gone limp.
He's seizing, and now his
right pupil is dilating.
He could be herniating. What's
your E.T.A. to the hospital?
That's what I'm saying.
We can't get him out.
He's stuck under a car,
and we can't get him out.
- Okay, first you've got to stay calm.
- I can't stay calm.
Calm was over minutes ago. Calm is gone.
Calm is impossibility.
I've got his best friends here,
and I can't let him die.
So please just tell me
what I need to do.
You need to do some burr holes.
Burr holes?
I can't do burr holes out here.
Do you want to save his life, Stevens?
- Yes.
- All right.
I need a minute to check
something out in the book,
and then I'll talk you through it.
You're looking it up in a book?
I'm not a neurosurgeon, Stevens, and
I want to make sure we get this right.
Somebody find me a copy
of Boardman's neurosurgery!
Everything okay?
You know anything about making
burr holes?
Done it a couple of times.
Good.
Don't go anywhere.
Stevens, listen to me.
I'm gonna need a drill.
- There's one in my truck.
- What do you need a drill for?
I've gotta drill holes
in your friend's head.
Watch your back... Coming through
Uh, hello. I'm suturing here.
- Sorry. I'm... What are you...
- Oh, wait... oh, you just got back?
Yeah, I'm looking...
- Have you, uh, seen any lost children
down here?
- Is...
Is Meredith back, too?
'Cause I need her.
It's really important.
Yeah, this is important. This kid's
missing. His mom's in surgery.
- What kind of surgery?
- This kid's lost.
You didn't see it today, Cristina.
You  weren't out there.
I know.
Have you seen any lost kids
down here or not?
- Not.
- Okay.
- Do you know where, uh, Meredith is?
- I'm leaving.
Yeah, I know.
All right, if you can
identify the patient,
- please write their name on the picture.
- I've got markers.
These patients are in surgery, and
these patients are in the I.C.U.
This is Fatima!
Is she okay?
Uh, yeah. She's in...
she's in the O.R. stable.
Okay, all these people have been
transferred from other hospitals.
Oh, and I have the details.
If it's okay...
I got... I got a case
I need to check on.
My husband's not on that board.
- Kelly Winter... she's not either.
- What does that mean?
It's, uh, it's, uh, they could be
in shock or...
- walked away from the site or...
- Just say it.
A lot of people died. They're dead.
W... we don't know that.
So how can we know?
My wife,
she wasn't in these photos either.
But she's pregnant.
Is...is it possible you just
didn't see her?
She's pregnant?
W hat?
It's okay.
Just think. Where is she
Which way she come?
It's okay take your time.
Take all the time you need,
you're doing great.
Where is it?
Good.
Okay.
Use your words.
Where exactly is Meredith?
Hmm. The leak in the heart is coming
from the right atrium.
Are you gonna put her on bypass?
'Cause that could compromise the baby.
No, I can fix her heart
while it's still beating.
Push 40 milligrams of esmolol.
I found her husband.
I found him.
She's not a Jane Doe.
Her name's Casey.
Casey Clark.
What?
How do you know?
How  do you know it's Casey Clark?
Well, she's pregnant and...
there were hundreds
of people on that ferry,
Alex, hundreds, and chances are that
more than one was pregnant.
Now do not give that man hope unless
you are certain. Do not give him hope
until you've checked every
last body in the morgue.
Dr. Burke, can I, uh...
Yes, make it fast.
I gotta tell you,
this group of interns...
Emotional.
Headstrong.
Hot-headed, stubborn.
They think they know everything.
You can only give them so much rope
before they hang themselves with it.
It's like they lose all rationality,
don't want to listen to reason.
Jeez, Preston. Don't hold back.
She's getting hypotensive.
I'm seeing some late decels on
the fetal heart monitor. The baby
is not getting enough blood.
Almost...
just got... one more stitch.
Got it.
Turn on the echo.
Baby's heart rate is stabilized.
Good.
Then we've seen the worst of it.
What's the deal?
Do you know how massive
this hospital is?
How many people...
not just sick people...
Not to mention, if I'm a little kid, how
many places can I hide? He's little.
A little kid can hide anywhere.
What, you're looking for a kid?
Yeah.
His mom's in surgery, and I, um...
if I don't find him, Bailey will...
Well, to start, she'll change her son's
middle name to...
Elvis or...
Tupperware or...
I'm not kidding. Anything will be
better than Georges.
I know a place a kid might be.
Really?
You could have warned me.
Well, you didn't check
down here, right?
No.
So stop whining and tell me
if you find a pregnant chick.
You know, you're not the only one
with a detail that sucks.
You know, I'm supposed to deal
with these freaked-out families.
I'm not good with people. They should
just let me stick to patients.
Patients are people, especially kids.
- You know what I mean.
- He's face down.
How does that...
Come here and help me turn
his body right.
Dude... don't tell me it doesn't matter.
- God, I swear to...
- Dramatic much?
This doesn't bother you?
Any of this?
All this death, it doesn't
mean anything to you?
I'm working. Why would it?
Yeah, well, there's working and then...
Caucasian female, about 30 years old.
She's...
She's pretty.
She looks about seven months pregnant.
Now remember, Stevens,
that drill isn't just gonna stop
like a neurosurgical drill,
so as soon
as you feel a release in pressure, stop
the drill or you'll pierce his brain.
Even if I don't see blood?
Trust your instincts, Stevens.
Trust the feel of it.
I'm ready.
No, wait. I need to clean the drill off
one more time.
You've cleaned it a dozen times, Stevens.
It's as clean as it's gonna get.
You're ready?
Yes.
Okay.
Place three fingers above the ear
and two or three fingers in front of that
on the side where the first pupil blew.
Got it.
All right. Now use a scalpel to make a
vertical scalp incision down to the skull.
Jeez.
I see a lot of blood, a lot.
Superficial bleeders.
Nothing to worry about.
Are you at the skull?
Yes.
Drill a hole in the middle
of the incision.
Oh, God.
Okay, that can't happen.
Do you understand me?
Sounds can't happen.
Freaking out can't happen. Because
if you freak out, I'm gonna freak out.
And I'm the one holding a power
tool to your friend's brain.
So if you're gonna vomit, if you're
gonna make sounds, step away.
If you're gonna stay here,
you have to pull it together.
Okay?
We're good, Doc.
Okay. I'm ready.
The temporal bone's only gonna be
a couple of millimetres thick.
Okay, I'm in.
But the dura looks fine.
You're gonna have to go in again.
Frontal lobe, right?
That's right.
Just behind the hairline, a few
centimetres off the midline.
This bone will be thicker,
about five times as thick
as the temporal bone.
Okay.
Got it.
Second hole done.
What do you see?
I think I see blood.
I... I see some blood.
Okay, now this is important.
Drill around the hole
to expand the opening.
You have to try and
relieve the pressure.
Okay.
Uh, the hole is about
2 centimetres around now.
I see blood. I definitely see blood.
Try to evacuate as much
of the clot as you can.
With what? I don't have suction.
Use your finger, gauze, anything.
I see clotted blood.
- No arterial?
- No.
Good. Now how does the dura look?
Is it bulging or does it look lax?
It looks like it's...
pulsating regularly with the heartbeat.
That's another good, right?
That's great, Stevens.
If  it's pulsating, that means
blood and oxygen are entering the brain.
Now pack it with gauze so
you can minimize the bleeding.
O... Okay.
Now get that rescue right in here.
Nicely done, Stevens.
- Is that it?
- Is he... Is he gonna be okay?
We've relieved the pressure
on his brain,
but he's still got a lot
of other injuries.
Hey.
His eyes are open.
Hey, kid.
Kid.
You okay?
You need to come with me.
Kid?
E.T.A. is five minutes.
How is she doing?
Good. No intestinal damage.
Missed all her vital organs. She's
almost done here. You find her son?
I've looked everywhere.
I've been in contact with the scene,
with Mercy West, with Seattle
Presbyterian. I've checked in,
he's lost
or...
- or, uh...
- He's in the water.
So when she wakes up, I get to inform
her that she's not going to die,
she's just gonna want to die.
I'm sorry. I will... Okay,
I'm gonna keep looking.
Yeah, you do that.
His right pupil's not dilated anymore,
and he's normotensive
but his pulse is still up in the 130s.
- Okay, what's his neurological status?
- G.C.S. is 8.
I'm sorry. I ran out of sterile drapes.
I had to use some guy's t-shirt.
It wasn't sweaty or anything.
He was a clean guy, but--
Okay, call the O.R.
Tell'em we're coming up.
I also dropped the scalpel in the field,
and by that time, I had used all the
alcohol swabs on the drill bit, so
I think we should load him up on
antibiotics, lots and lots of antibiotics.
Stevens you put a drill
through a man's skull
and didn't hit his brain.
You saved his life.
Get cleaned up and get to the O.R.
You got work to do.
The O.R.?
Yes, the O.R.
You're officially off probation.
Oh, Cristina!
Oh, my god. You are not gonna
believe what I just did.
I'm gonna tell you,
but you're not gonna believe it. You're
gonna think I made the whole thing up.
You're back?
Is Meredith back?
- I drilled a hole into this guy's skull
- What?
Several holes, actually,
with a drill I borrowed
from a guy named Vince,
patched the hole with freakin'tissue,
then brought him back here, and now I
get to scrub in on his craniotomy.
So you haven't seen Meredith?
It was like a ride,
this crazy roller coaster ride
with adrenalin shooting out of my ears.
You'd think that my hands would be shaking,
but they weren't. There was no shaking.
- Did I mention the drill?
- Okay, Izzie,
I get it. You are a hero.
I am jealous. But I need to know
where the hell Meredith is.
Okay.
I don't know where the hell Meredith is.
But she should be back here.
I didn't see her at the scene...
The scene where I was a rock star,
by the way.
Did I mention I'm off probation?
Rock star.
These photos are fatalities.
I know it's difficult,
but please try to I.D. who you can.
We've agreed to let you do the honors...
A few more burr holes
to start the craniotomy.
Really?
You saved his life. You might as well
help finish what you started.
After I strip off the periosteum,
you can see what a high-speed pneumatic
neurosurgical drill feels like.
Drill, please.
I, uh, we have two pregnant women. One
of'em is... she's in bad shape. She's...
pretty beat up.
She might be hard to recognize.
I... I don't know.
- What color is her hair?
- Brown. Reddish.
My wife my wife is blonde.
Brownish, but blonde.
Oh, yeah. Sometimes the blood makes
it look darker like that, you know, red.
I know you can't tell from the photo,
but her eyes are...
they're pretty distinctive.
Casey's eyes are very distinctive.
Yeah, brown,
but not that really dark, dark brown.
More golden and... and really warm.
That's not her.
Casey's eyes are blue, very, very blue.
I'm sorry.
I thought you...
You said you had two pregnant women.
Yeah, we, um...
the other one is, um...
she's...
oh, god. Oh, no. Oh, god.
Oh, Casey.
What do we got?
Jane Doe, hypothermic drowning...
She is not a Jane Doe.
It's Meredith Grey. It's Meredith.
Derek.
- Derek, how long has she been down?
- I don't know.
She's alive.
- One, two, three...
- Derek.
She's alive.
Okay, look, I need you
to help me get her inside.
Clear a trauma bay, stat!
Move it!
How was your surgery, dr. Burke?
Well, the patient is out of
the woods now, dr. Yang.
Thanks for asking.
Ow!
You're numbed.
Whatever. It looked harsh.
Fran, finish this, please.
- What is your problem?
- You know, everyone's back.
Everyone's back except her.
And I listen to her every day
about her McLove life
McDreamy and McCrap, and, and on the
one day, the one day I have a thing...
she disappears.
Meredith?
This is about Meredith?
- She doesn't know yet.
- Meredith?
She's my person.
Right.
And if Meredith doesn't approve,
then what?
No, no, no. This is not about getting
her approval. It's about...
What?
Telling her makes it...
makes it...
if I murdered someone,
she's the person I'd call to help me drag
the corpse across the living room floor.
Okay. See, now you're likening
someone here to a corpse.
I'm done.
She's my person.
Removing the bone flap.
Ready with suction.
Looking good.
Yes.
Yes, it is.
Dr. Stevens, it's your pager.
That's okay. It can wait.
I think you want to take this page.
How's she doing?
She's holding steady for now.
Anybody claim her yet?
No.
She's still a Jane Doe.
I'd notice.
What?
If you went missing...
I'd notice.
- Okay, I need a little more suction, please.
- Callie.
O'Malley, I'm working. What do you want?
I read on the board you're doing an
internal fixation of the lumbar spine
on a John Doe from
the ferry crash, age 7.
That's right.
Can I see his face?
- I'm in the middle of surgery.
- I know.
Is this boy your patient?
I... I know the picture's half smeared
and hard to see, but...
please tell me it's him.
Tell me he has been right here
under my nose, open on
your table all day and not...
drifting along the
bottom of the ocean.
Just... please tell me that.
Put the photo under the light
so I can get a better look.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah, that's my kid.
I could spot those goofy ears anywhere.
- Really?
- Really.
Callie O'Malley...
I can't kiss you right now because
you're scrubbed in, but tonight...
when you get home,
- I am going to...
- Okay,
Okay. All right. You know what,
people? Let's focus here.
George, I'm working.
Yeah.
I'm...
I'm working.
Okay.
So... yeah.
Bye.
Oh, my god!
Oh, you're safe.
You're safe.
Oh, honey, mommy's sorry
she got lost.
Oh, Lisa.
They could only put a 20-guage
I.V. in, but I think it blew.
I'll start a central line, but you
have to get out of the way.
- We... We put, uh, 3 milligram
of epi down the E.T. tube...
- Derek!
The last dose was three minutes
ago. We should push...
Shepherd, get out.
I think we should push
just 1 at... atropine.
I think I saw some reactivity
in her pupils
before the atropine, and I think
she might have actually had some
- cardiac activity...
- Shepherd, get out.
we need to put an external pacer
on just to make sure.
We need to save her life.
You can't do this.
We need to do this.
Now go.
One, two...
Go.
Three, four, five.
Okay, she has a new 18-guage in her
left A.C. push 1 of epi through it.
The chief is working on her, man.
He threw me out.
What do you need?
I need you to go in there.
Give me a new warm blanket.
Her temp's still only at 80 degrees.
What can I do?
She needs an A.B.G.
Whoa.
Was that v-fib?
Charge to 300.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Okay.
Clear.
Back to asystole.
Keep compressions going.
Oh, my god.
She's hypothermic.
Uh...
Have you tried a warm peritoneal lavage
or even a continuous
bladder lavage with warm fluids?
You could do a thoracotomy.
Get back the A.B.G.
Okay, now let's go, people.
How's her temp?
- Only up to 81 now.
- Come on Meredith. Don't do this.
- It's Meredith?
- Yeah.
- Are you sure? Did you see her?
Because it could be anybody.
- It's Meredith
Oh.
- Uh... She will come through this.
- You don't know that.
She will come through this.
People die.
I know people die.
People die in front of us every day.
But I believe Meredith will survive this.
I believe...
I believe... I...
I... I believe in the good.
I believe that it's been
a hell of a year.
And I believe that in the face of
overwhelming evidence to the contrary,
we will all be okay.
I believe a lot of things.
I believe that...
I believe that Denny
is always with me.
And I believe
that if I eat a tub of butter and no
one sees me, the calories don't count.
And I believe that surgeons who prefer
staples over stitches are just lazy.
And I believe that you are a man who
made a terrible mistake marrying Callie.
And I believe that because
I'm your best friend,
I can tell you this,
and we can be okay.
I believe even though
you made this mistake,
you will be okay.
I believe we survive, George.
I believe that believing we survive
is what makes us survive.
She's gonna be okay.
Push another epi.
How many is that?
This is her fourth round, Sir.
We've been here
20 minutes.
Still in asystole.
We're losing her.
Hey.
Am I...
dead?
Damn right, you are.
Holy...
Transcript : Raceman
Synchro : ChipounetteF et Mickeyte
Traduction : Chryssie, Tbdb
Relecture : Cookie
Pour
www.forom.com et
http ://experts.heberg-forum.net/