Previously on Grey's Anatomy:
Derek's married.
- Why are you here?
- You had a life in Manhattan.
Had.
It was a business decision.
Not personal.
It is personal to me.
I'll only be your boss for a few days.
- I have a girlfriend.
- Olivia.
You and Alex?
- You gave me syphilis!
- George!
- It's best to make a clean break.
- Oh, you're ending this.
I'm pregnant.
Have you even told Burke
about the baby?
I've had a thing for my roommate since
day one. And I just can't tell her.
My husband didn't cheat on me.
I cheated on him.
- I was drowning and you saved me.
- It's not enough.
I have an aunt who,
whenever she poured anything for you,
would say, "Say when."
It's not us. It's them.
Them and their stupid boy penises.
They didn't tell me they had a wife.
They gave absolutely no warning that
they were going to break up with you.
It's not that Burke broke up with me.
It's how he broke up with me.
Like it was business. Like a business...
Like he's the boss of me.
- He is the boss of you.
- And what's worse is that I care.
I'm going to throw up again.
My aunt would say, "Say when,"
and of course we never did.
No. Wait.
False alarm.
- Look, the problem is estrogen.
- No, the problem is tequila.
I used to be all business,
then he gets me pregnant.
- With the stupid boy penis.
- Now I'm having hormone surges.
He ruined me. I'm ruined.
He turned me into this fat,
stupid, pregnant girl,
who cares.
- Estrogen.
- Penises.
- Penises, Izzie!
- Estrogen, George.
OK. What did I miss?
Came home to full vomit drama.
She dumped Derek. And her.
- She's been sleeping with Burke.
- I know.
We don't say "when" because there's
something about the possibility of more.
So you really broke up with Shepherd?
I feel empty.
Two hours of vomiting
will do that to you.
More tequila. More love. More anything.
More is better.
No, I feel empty.
You're lucky. I feel pissed off.
Stop.
- What?
- You're stalking me. Stop it.
Did we not communicate last night?
- Yes.
- Did you hear what I said?
Your wife screwed your best friend.
Then from that point on,
she no longer existed to me.
- You had marital amnesia.
- I bared my soul to you last night.
- It's not enough.
- Why?
When you waited two months to tell me
and I had to find out by her showing up,
all leggy and fabulous, and telling me
herself, you pulled the plug.
I'm a sink with an open drain.
Anything you say runs right out.
There is no enough.
- She could've picked a better metaphor.
- Give her a break. She has a hangover.
- Dr. Shepherd.
- Dr. Burke.
We have an organ donor coming in
from Wilkeson General.
- We're doing a harvest.
- Commendable, but...
- In OR One at four.
- I'm in OR One at four.
Yours is non-critical.
- You can't bump me.
- As chief, I can.
- Interim. Bump somebody else.
- You're in the OR we need.
- Why don't they harvest at Wilkeson?
- Small facility in the boonies.
We have the location,
the airport nearby and the staff.
Your surgery is rescheduled.
-  Cardiologist to the cath lab.
- "Mine's bigger than yours."
- Whip it out. I'll measure.
- Shut up, Alex.
Male, 55, victim of a head-on collision.
GCS is three. Depressed skull fracture.
Multiple internal injuries. ACLS
protocol started, but his veins blew.
We've pushed meds down the tube.
PEA on arrival.
- How long?
- We've been doing CPR for 20 minutes.
It took Fire 20 minutes to get him out.
He's pretty much gone.
He's not gone until we say he's gone.
O'Malley, get him into a bay
and save him.
- But he's dead.
- Did you not hear me?
He's not dead until we say he's dead.
You know what to do, so do it.
Grey? You on this too. Move.
We've got three more victims
from the other car coming in!
- Come on.
- But he's dead.
Olivia.
- Pulseless V-tach.
- Line's in.
OK! Charge to 200.
- 200.
- Clear.
Push one of epi. Let's go again.
Charge to 300.
Seriously?
I think that's what Dr. Bailey
wants you to do, George.
You...
Dr. O'Malley.
It's what she wants, Dr. O'Malley.
OK then. Let's charge to 300.
- 300.
- Clear.
Male, 46, unrestrained driver
of the car that jumped lanes.
BP 80 over palp.
Tachycardic. Last pulse 1:38.
Got two liters LR running wide open.
Abdominal tenderness.
- Any history?
- He's got a bad liver.
- He's on the transplant list.
- Abdomen's rigid. Hands off!
We need to page Burke and Domner.
Who wants it?
- I do!
- I do.
- Too late. Stevens, take it.
- Yes.
Karev! Take the boy.
Yang, you take the mom.
I want to be looking at their films
in 15 minutes.
- We've got one more for you.
- What? In there? Oh, OK.
What is it?
- That guy.
- He was in the accident?
No. Bowel obstruction. He won't say what
he ingested. Films suggest he's packing.
Can't people figure out
a better way to move drugs?
Grey!
Pericardiocentesis. Good.
Any response?
- OK, all right, you guys can...
- Should I call it?
- What would you do next, O'Malley?
- I would call it.
To save him.
Oh... Uh...
- A pericardial window.
- Excellent. Do it.
Grey, you're done here.
I got a bowel obstruction for you.
- Fun.
- At least your patient's still alive.
What next, doctor?
- Stop it!
- OK. Stop. OK? That's it.
- That is not it.
- Come on, stop it. That's it.
- It's not. Hold still.
- How can I with you poking me?
I have to poke you to discharge you.
What makes you think
he wants to be discharged?
Derek, don't you know that this hospital
will crumble unless Richard's here?
Adele. You're meant to be
in the Virgin Islands.
You are in five kinds of trouble,
mister man.
You had brain surgery
and didn't tell me?
- It was a small procedure.
- It was brain surgery.
- Didn't want to ruin your vacation.
- You don't know what one is.
How would you know how to ruin it?
Well, anyway...
How did you find...
- You called my wife?
- You called mine.
Having someone at home with you is
the only way I'm letting you out today.
- Fine.
- I thought I saw a great-Iooking woman.
Addison! Yes, see?
Hi.
I told Richard, I knew you and Derek
would get back together.
- I'm here on a case.
- Addison and I are over, Adele.
- It's not like we're divorced.
- Practically.
- You've had counseling?
- We had adultery. That was enough.
I'll call you later, OK?
You should give her a chance, Derek.
It's good to see you.
Keep him in line.
- My mom's OK, right?
- Yeah, yeah, I think so.
They'd been fighting at breakfast.
Dad... It's ugly when it gets like that.
He ran three stop lights
before we even got on the freeway.
- My husband Bob is a good driver.
- Some guy in a pickup cuts us off.
Safe. I think he saw something
in the middle of the road and...
- My dad just lost it.
...and swerved to avoid it.
- Started chasing the guy.
- The crash just came out of nowhere.
Blasting through traffic.
We'd been having a really nice morning.
One minute everything's fine
and the next...
- Screaming at him.
- I saw his face before we hit.
Then we're upside down
across the freeway.
Do the surgeons know
Bob has a bad liver?
- They know.
- How's Scotty?
Your son's next door getting X-rayed.
- My dad, he...
- He's in surgery. It's pretty serious.
Yeah? Well.
I guess the son of a bitch
got what he deserved.
Here you go.
What makes people think
they don't need seatbelts?
My end is done.
Well, the bowel's a mess,
but it's repairable.
It's a lot of work, but I don't see
the point with this liver.
Forceps.
- What do you see, Dr. Stevens?
- Deep laceration, bleeding.
- What else?
- It's hard and pale. Cirrhotic.
- He's on the transplant list.
- Does he have family here?
A wife and son.
I'm just going to roll you over. Gently.
Oh. This looks pretty bad.
How'd you get this?
Well, we hit so hard...
I don't think it's from the collision.
It looks a couple of weeks old.
Where are you?
I can see his heart.
His heart that's not beating.
OK, open the pericardium and aspirate.
If the heart's still not beating,
close and call it.
What? You think
we're defiling this man's body?
Well, we're certainly doing more than...
Than what?
If they're dead or dying when they
come in you hump and hump hard. Why?
- For the experience.
- No. What else? There's something more.
You think on that. It'll come to you.
Mr. Hubble, you might make things
a little easier on yourself
if you would just tell us
what you've ingested.
We'll know anyway,
once we see your films.
You have the most beautiful features.
They're delicate. Almost porcelain.
Mr. Hubble, whatever you've ingested
could kill you.
Are you sure you don't want to tell me
what's got you blocked up inside?
- It might offend you.
- Is it drugs?
- It's not drugs.
- Mr. Hubble...
I promise. It's not drugs.
OK. Well, good.
I'm glad it's not drugs.
It's drugs. Looks like at least
ten balloons in his bowel.
My guess, cocaine.
Scott Seibert, 18. No fractures
or internal bleeding. Got pretty lucky.
- Recommendation?
- Overnight for observation.
- Damn!
- Lea Seibert, 43.
Multiple healed fractures on clavicle
and humerus. Third and fourth rib.
She's either a bull rider
or she's abused.
Kid said the accident was road rage.
His old man got cut off in traffic.
That's not the story I got.
She has a large yellowing bruise over
her right kidney, tender to palpation.
Said she got it from a fall last week.
She's bleeding.
Perinephric hematoma. What do you do?
It should take care of itself.
We'll watch it.
She needs bed rest. And a shrink.
- It's drugs.
- Stupid. Stupid, stupid.
One bursts and he's dead
in five minutes.
- OK, what do we do?
- Run his bowel?
And what does that mean? Yang?
Running the bowel entails
removing all 36 feet of the intestine
from the body cavity, searching
for the balloons then cutting them out.
Grey, book an OR. Yang, Karev, you're
in. I need all the hands I can get.
You sure they're balloons?
You have reason to believe they're not?
This one here's got a face.
So does that one.
They all do.
I'll be damned. They're Judys.
Judys?
He's swallowed the heads
of ten Judy dolls.
Eugh.
My mother used to buy me Judy dolls.
Manhattan Judy,
Surfer Judy, Disco Judy.
- I wanted one.
- I dissected them.
Cut off their arms
and shaved their heads.
Sounds like a sick and twisted story.
They're sexist, distorted devil toys
that create unrealistic expectations
catering to the porn-driven minds
of men.
You swallow a bitter pill
this morning, Yang? They're dolls.
Grey, call for a Psych consult,
then see if he has family.
- Do I still book the OR?
- Blocked bowels become necrotic bowels.
Check with Dr. Burke.
See if we can bump someone.
Those Judys got to come out today.
- Hanging another B neg.
- Using a lot of blood.
- Noted.
- What's the word from UNOS?
He's on the list,
but they don't have a liver.
The list won't help him now.
This liver won't stop bleeding.
It won't support his recovery.
What about the donor
that's coming in?
That liver's already been committed.
His only hope is a family donor.
Maybe we should call it. No use tying up
an OR if it's postponing the inevitable.
How much work do you have
to complete, Dr. Domner?
- Five, maybe six hours.
- That's how long we have to find one.
You're the chief.
- Any family members waiting?
- Trying to reach them.
Good. I mean, not good that
we haven't reached them.
- It's just good I don't have to...
- It's always hard.
Yeah.
I'm sorry about Alex.
That's fine. It's good, you know.
No need to talk about it.
You do understand that I had sex
with him before you. Not during.
Because when
you and I were having sex...
- I understand.
- Just wanted to clear the air.
It's clear.
- Perfectly clear. OK.
- OK.
- And about the syphilis...
- We don't have to talk about this.
I mean, I didn't know I had it.
I should have. I'm a nurse.
I mean, there was the sore
and I was all itchy.
OK. You know, I uh... got it.
You know, things happen.
They really do.
Things you wish you could change.
Yeah.
It's the chief. I got to take this.
Sure. George?
- You have to call it.
- Call it?
- Him.
- Oh. Um...
Time of death 1:48.
I got it.
This guy came in this morning with
ten Judy doll heads in his abdomen.
Is that some kind of sick or what?
I mean, when you think about it, those
things can't be that easy to swallow.
They still got their hair on them.
That's some bad spaghetti.
Dude's crapping toys.
You know, when you're little,
you can hide.
Ignore the shouting, the screaming.
Pretend like you're someplace else.
Then when you get older... bigger...
you feel like you should be
doing something.
Something to stop it.
You know, to protect her.
And when you can't,
you don't know who to be angrier at,
your old man or yourself.
Usually it's yourself.
- Did she tell you?
- She didn't have to.
It's all over her films.
He's not beating you, is he?
No. Just her.
So what do you do? About the anger?
Me? I think about the guy
who eats doll heads.
He's got problems.
Hey. I've been looking for you guys.
It's my father.
Bob liked his beers. His liver
started to fail a couple of years ago.
He quit drinking and we put him
on the transplant list,
- but his blood type...
- B negative.
There just aren't that many available.
They suggested a family member.
Any luck?
My son.
They say Scotty's a good match.
He's 18...
Family members shouldn't do it
out of obligation. It's risky.
Scotty's had counseling.
You know, they just don't let you do it.
He hasn't made his mind up yet,
you know.
We actually have a date set
for the surgery.
It's just... I just don't...
I don't want to pressure him.
Well, then you shouldn't.
Oh, God...
God, I don't want to lose Bob.
We'll give your son as much time
as we can to make a decision.
- Would you care to explain?
- Seibert is a wife beater.
- Her films show abuse.
- I didn't know that.
Multiple fractures. She has a kidney
bleed from a beating last week.
Plus, it was his road rage
that caused the accident.
- The guy in the other car died.
- And that means what?
No heroic measures?
We leave him on the table?
- If it were up to me...
- Think like a surgeon.
We have a dying patient
and a liver match.
- This is more complicated.
- For social workers, yes.
For the family. Not for you.
It isn't up to you.
Yeah, you've made that perfectly clear.
- I'm glad we have an understanding.
- I'm sure you are.
- The donor from Wilkeson?
- Should be here at three.
Harvest team's on their way in.
I need to contact the transplant center
about Seibert getting his son's liver.
Dr. Burke? Dr. Bailey needs an OR
and they're all booked.
- For?
- An emergent bowel obstruction.
- Drugs?
- Ten Judy doll heads.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
I can see their little faces.
"Help. Let me out."
Bump Warner's hernia in one,
but don't tell him what we're removing.
Thank you.
If he can't be here obsessing,
he wants stuff to obsess with at home.
I'll be done and out of your way
in a moment.
Intern time cards. Sign.
It's always something, isn't it?
Some emergency surgery,
some annoying administrative problem.
Being chief is a lot like being
an intern, the work never stops.
When I found out Richard had a tumor,
you know what I felt?
Relieved. I was hoping
he would finally be forced to retire.
Ah.
That has your attention, doesn't it?
How we both would like
for that to happen.
I could finally book a vacation for two.
You know,
you're perfect for this job, Preston.
Unattached. Obsessive.
This hospital, this job,
it's enough for you, isn't it?
It has to be today?
Thanks. He won't make it off the table
with his own liver. He's bleeding a lot.
When you get counseling,
they tell you not to force it.
A decision, you know.
One day, one moment,
you'll just know the right thing to do.
This should be easy, right?
He's my father.
Well, it's a tough operation.
It'll be a big change in your life.
The upside is the liver's
the only organ that regenerates.
They'll only take half of yours.
It'll be back to normal in two months.
- You won't be running marathons, but...
- Dr. Stevens, can I see you a moment?
- What is your problem?
- You're doing a sales pitch.
The recipient is your patient.
You shouldn't be talking to the donor.
The recipient is his father
who he's going to lose.
And he understands that, all right?
Believe me. He understands that.
You have no idea
what's going on in that kid's head.
None.
- Call three times a day.
- Do not call.
- If my wife doesn't put you through...
- I won't put you through.
...keep calling.
- Yes, sir.
He's not talking. It could be pica.
Doubtful for a man his age.
Maybe an Oedipal complex
or idolization of the dolls as partners.
Or it could be that he simply enjoys it.
I've seen strange things in strange
places, but how does he enjoy this?
He'd enjoy them when they came out.
I didn't need to hear that.
Dr. Grey?
May I speak with you for a moment?
Don't look at me for help.
I assume he told you why he left me?
Dr. Shepherd, with all due respect,
this has nothing to do with me.
Really? So you didn't take him back?
Good girl.
In future, I'd appreciate it if we kept
our relationship strictly professional.
Meredith?
Sometimes people do desperate things
to get someone's attention.
There are two sides to every story.
He's an alcoholic
wife beater. Shouldn't be a question.
If you didn't save him,
wouldn't it be like murder?
Like when he crashed into George's DOA?
He's the killer, not the son.
- That is sick.
- Who would do that?
Oh.
Look! See Judy fly.
- Hey, George?
- Hey.
What?
George. She was trying to make up
with you. You should go eat with her.
No. No, I shouldn't.
She likes you.
Don't let the syph get in the way.
- It's not the syph.
- So the syph.
- It is not the syph.
- Then what is it?
Oh.
What?
What is it?
- Say.
- There's another girl.
- Izzie!
- You have another girl?
- He hasn't told her yet.
- It's not high school.
- George has a little crush.
- I do not.
It is a thing.
A thing that is very personal.
One day I'd like to build on this thing
with this other girl... woman.
She's all woman.
- What are you doing?
- I was playing with...
No, George, with Olivia.
What are you doing with Olivia?
- Nothing.
- She thinks you're available.
She thinks she has a chance.
There is nothing worse in the world
than thinking you have a chance
when you really don't.
Meredith is right. Tell her there's
someone else. Tell her why.
At least give her the chance to have
some feelings about it for God's sake!
- Why are you yelling at me?
- Because of the estrogen, George!
So, new subject.
- It's a mess.
- No, it isn't.
I think I know a mess when I see a mess.
You got the harvest tying up OR One,
Seibert tying up OR Two...
It's simply a bit crowded.
Your "crowded"
is my "seriously overbooked."
And in my book,
seriously overbooked is a mess.
Is there any word on the Seibert liver?
- How much work do they have left?
- Couple of hours.
- Tell them I'll be in to see them.
- You bumped me for a bowel obstruction?
Uneasy lies the head
that wears the chief's cap.
Code white, code white...
Was it an act of desperation?
- Not at all.
- Something to attract attention?
Of course not.
I'm just trying to understand here,
Mr. Hubble. Why ten doll heads?
Well, because eleven
would have been too much.
What's up, Dick?
I think it has something to do
with his mother.
Maybe she wanted a girl
and gave him Judy dolls as presents.
I got another one.
Doyen clamps to Yang.
Grey, push the head to the incision.
Mother looked like Judy
and he's into voodoo.
Instead of sticking pins in...
Yep. Ah.
Black Judy.
Before they gave her long hair.
Back when she had the Afro.
She came with go-go boots
and a leather jacket.
- Shame. It's a real collector's item.
- Collectible dolls. New twist.
Seriously? You can
identify these dolls by their heads?
You got a problem with that, Yang?
I like Judy dolls. I own Judy dolls.
The only problem I have with Judy dolls
is they're in the bowel of this man.
Bailey? I need an intern in the E. R.
to meet the harvest donor.
- O'Malley.
- See you, trooper.
- You good here?
- Couple more to go.
Karev, Stevens, Yang, scrub out.
We need to get an answer
from Seibert's son.
Ah, yes. Mod Judy.
She came with a yellow Vespa.
- Wait. You know what's strange?
- We haven't had enough strange?
She looks a little like you.
This is the donor from Wilkeson.
Put her in here until the
harvest team comes down. Thanks.
Well, this...
this one's heart is still beating.
I think Bailey would want me to...
We reached the family
of the dead motorist. Live in Portland.
Should be here in a few hours.
Want me to page you?
- Yeah. Do they know?
- Only that we were working on him.
I think it's always better
to hear bad news first hand.
I know I'd like to talk
to the doctor who called it.
Get some answers.
So that I could get on with my life.
George?
Did you... Did you see that?
She's decerebrate. Her brain's...
Her brain stem's still alive.
- OK. We'll take it from here. Thanks.
- Did you look at this?
She's decerebrate. OK.
Yeah, she can't really be
declared brain dead...
They probably just missed it. The cortex
is dead, the brain stem will follow.
Death is imminent.
We just have to wait.
- But don't you think...
- She'll be dead when we get to the OR.
But she's alive now.
It smells like a hospital in here.
What are we doing with this guy?
Is this an exercise?
- I don't need the practice.
- Transplant committee gave the OK.
We need an answer from the son.
He's using blood
like there's no tomorrow. Literally.
- How much work is still left?
- An hour and a half.
But, without a liver, I don't think
this guy's going to last that long.
I need to speak to Scotty. I can talk
to him. I need to talk to him.
I think they want him
to make the decision on his own.
You think I'm sick for wanting
to save my husband, don't you?
I think you're feeling very emotional.
And when we're feeling emotional,
sometimes it's hard to keep a level head
and to consider all the facts.
Your husband killed a man
on the highway today.
He almost killed you and your son.
Those are the facts.
Have you ever been in love, doctor?
Have you?
Love has its limits.
- Dr. Shepherd.
- Dr. O'Malley.
I was just in ICU
with the harvest donor.
Dr. Bailey has us do procedures and
exams on patients even if they're dead.
- What did you find?
- She's decerebrate.
The donor. Her brain stem's still alive.
Excuse me.
Derek Shepherd, head of neurosurgery.
Do you mind if I take a look?
OK. Yeah, she's still posturing.
We have every intention
of waiting until she's dead.
She's in an irreversible coma.
Hines, at Wilkeson, ran the protocol.
Missed decerebration.
What else did they miss?
She has a tumor
on her uh... brain stem, right?
I don't see an MRI. Did you do an EEG
to confirm brain death?
- Yeah. According to Hines.
- I don't know Hines.
Six patients in three states
are waiting for organs.
They'd be happy to know the organs were
from somebody who is brain dead.
No one will touch her while she's alive.
To imply otherwise...
Is there a problem here?
This donor is still decerebrate.
I want to do an EEG and an MRI.
- An expensive waste of time.
- I insist on it.
- You insist on it?
- I do.
If my head of neurosurgery
says he needs an EEG and an MRI,
he needs an EEG and an MRI.
We have six patients waiting.
That is not my call, Dr. Orsen.
Who gets the organs is up to UNOS.
Who donates them
is up to the families.
Hell, I got a guy waiting for a liver
that may not deserve to be saved.
Again, that's not my call.
Do you want to know what my call is?
Everything else.
- The patient is yours, Dr. Shepherd.
- Thank you, Dr. Burke.
Dr. O'Malley,
want to assist with this MRI?
Can you carry this for me?
First thing we'll do is the EEG.
George, you with me?
What if he goes back to hitting her?
You can't make that call.
But you can't make the decision
out of anger.
- Alex!
- So what do you do with it?
- What did you do with yours?
- Alex! Hey!
- You shouldn't be out here.
- Can you just back off? Please.
My anger had a life of its own.
I became a wrestler and the next time
he laid a hand on my mother,
I beat the living crap out of him.
When he got out of the hospital,
he took off.
Just took off and never came back.
You know, he was a cold, mean-tempered
bastard, but he was still my old man.
And now I can't stop wishing
that I'd never laid a hand on him.
That we somehow
could've worked it through.
What is it?
Sorry. I didn't mean to interrupt you.
What? What does Burke want?
I'm sorry, Scott.
He needs a decision now.
When would it happen?
We would take Scotty
to pre-op immediately.
The transplant surgeon is on call
and waiting. There isn't much time.
Scotty?
Scotty.
Yeah. OK. I want to do it.
- Let's get him to pre-op.
- But I have a couple of conditions.
You're going tell the cops the truth
about what happened in this accident.
And as soon as we get back home,
you and I are moving out.
Enough is enough.
18-year-old male, liver donor,
no malignancy or transmittable diseases.
ETA about ten minutes.
You know she's going to go back to him.
- I don't know that. And it's not my...
- This is not our call.
Well, Cristina...
I was wondering...
I mean, I was hoping that we can...
- I know we didn't...
- You're asking me...
Are you OK?
Can I scrub in?
Then, yes, Dr. Burke. I'm OK.
Karev. Let's get him to pre-op.
You see the tumor
on her brain stem here?
Looks pretty bad.
You ever had a crappy day, O'Malley?
I mean, really, really crappy.
I've had many crappy days.
This one just got better.
You should go home, gentlemen.
I will be the only one of us
performing surgery today.
My friend here has a viable brain.
OK.
Do you really think she'll be OK?
I get the tumor out,
she's got a good shot of recovery.
Look out for her.
Meredith?
Yeah.
Oh.
Um...
- Is it the family of the dead guy?
- Yeah.
Look. Maybe I'm not over
the Alex thing or the syph thing yet.
That's not really the problem.
There's a girl who I...
And it doesn't matter
that there's this other guy.
And, frankly, I wouldn't care
if she gave me the Ebola virus.
I like you, Olivia.
But... I just don't like you enough.
I gave it a shot, right?
And you were honest.
That's good.
You know what you're going to tell them?
Why do we hump on every dead or dying
patient that comes through those doors?
Experience?
So we can tell their family
that we did everything we could.
Are you Ted's family?
- Just when the day was improving.
- You told Meredith what happened?
I did. What did you tell her?
People do desperate things
to attract attention.
What? Wow. That's your side of this?
That I didn't pay you enough attention?
You thought that
when you got naked with my friend?
No. By that point,
I wasn't thinking at all.
I was just scratching an itch.
We got successful, you and me.
We got busy and we got lazy.
We didn't even bother to fight anymore.
And Mark was there, and I missed you.
And now I'm sorry. I'm more sorry
than you can possibly imagine,
but at least I'm talking to you
about it. Derek...
I'm a sink with an open drain, Addie.
- Did you get them all?
- Yes.
It wasn't easy or very pleasant.
How do you feel?
Empty. I feel empty now.
Yeah, I've been feeling
a little bit of that myself lately.
I could see that.
Mr. Hubble. Why does eating doll heads
fill you up? What's the satisfaction?
Do you really want to know?
Would it be too much information?
It might.
Maybe I'm better left in the dark.
There's something to be said
about a glass half full.
About knowing when to say "when."
I think it's a floating line.
A barometer of need and desire.
It's entirely up to the individual...
and depends on what's being poured.
Sometimes, all we want is a taste.
Other times,
there's no such thing as enough.
The glass is bottomless.
And all we want...
is more.
www.tvsubtitles.net