I believe in heaven.
I also believe in hell.
I've never seen either,
but I believe they exist.
They have to exist.
Because without a heaven...
without a hell...
we're all just headed for limbo.
You coming?
If it's bad, the nurses
will come get us.
Dr. Grey, he's seizing!
How about now? Now can we go?
Sadie, go find something
else to do. Now.
That's an order.
Why are you still here?
I'm here for you, Izzie Stevens.
No, you're not,
because I broke up with you.
So you are not here for me.
I'm sorry, but...
you have to go.
- I can't go. I'm here for...
- Me. Yeah. Right.
- I am. I'm here for...
- Stop saying that!
Dr. Bailey, I just called UNOS.
Jackson's at the top of the
list for a liver and small bowel.
They can't come soon enough.
His ammonia
level's starting to rise.
I thought the shunt was
supposed to buy us 24 hours.
Isn't that what you said, that
it should give us 24 hours?
We're doing everything we can.
I know. I know you are.
Excuse me.
- Oh, my God - He had a seizure.
- I gave him lorazepam.
- You page Shepherd?
- I paged you.
- Page Shepherd.
- The patient doesn't want that.
- He tell you that?
Yes. Don't page him.
He's terribly unpleasant.
Mr. Dunn is a match
for your kid who
needs the transplant.
He's a match.
Uh-huh.
All of this wasn't
caused from the seizure,
but I'm sure you
know that already.
Oh, no.
This is my project.
Dr. Grey does
not get the credit.
You probably have a brain bleed,
which is why we need
to get Shepherd in here.
Dr. Bailey, he's
gonna die anyway.
The boy who needs organs,
I presume, wants to live.
And me?
I have organs...
and I'm ready to die.
- Dr. Sloan.
- Dr. Grey.
- After you, Dr. Grey.
- Thank you, Dr. Sloan.
It feels wrong on so many
levels I can't even count them.
But there is no case
in any medical book
that tells you how
to deal with this.
I don't need a book. I do
what's best for my patient.
I suggest you do the same.
- I am.
- Really? You page Shepherd yet?
Are you gonna page him?
I'm gonna do my best to
keep that beautiful boy alive
long enough to find
him some organs.
I suggest you do everything
you can to keep your patient alive.
Because we're doctors,
Grey. We're not... executioners.
- Don't even tell me.
- Locked.
People sleeping or...?
Why do I bother asking?
This is ridiculous.
I need sleep.
Oh, my God!
- That's not a good noise.
- That's a bad noise.
That's a really bad noise.
- Oh, my God! Are you OK?
- No!
It's bent. In the
middle. I think I broke it!
- Get Torres! Go!
- Um! Oh, OK.
I'm getting a 911 page
and I have a
casserole in the oven
I spent half the night baking...
- Hey.
- Whoa. I'm so sorry.
- Is Cristina a... a... around?
- No.
OK, then. OK, then.
Yep.
There's casserole in
the oven if you're hungry.
Thank you.
Has there been a change?
Has Matthew improved?
I'm sorry. Still
no brain activity.
- What are you doing to him?
- Blood test.
It's standard. Excuse us.
You two are on
Jackson all day today.
He doesn't have
a liver or intestines,
toxins will build,
his brain will swell.
We can't stop it,
we can slow it down.
You don't have time for this,
to think about anyone else.
Stevens, I need a nod. A
yawn. Maybe even a little burp.
Something that lets me know
you're capable of
keeping this boy alive.
Yes. Sorry. I'm all yours.
Way to listen. Thanks for that.
Dr. Bailey, how much
time do we have left?
Sixteen hours, at the most.
There's a liver
dialysis machine.
GI is using it
for a clinical trial.
- Liver dialysis?
- It's new. Completely
experimental.
It could help get
rid of the toxins.
It may give Jackson a
few more hours... maybe.
All right, Stevens,
put in the ICP monitor.
Start tracking his
intracranial pressures.
Karev, go get the machine.
What if it's hooked
up to somebody?
If that somebody has
more than 16 hours to live,
then we'll unhook them.
- I want off this case.
- Dr. Bailey?
Oh, God, I want off
this case. I want off...
This little boy is gonna die.
And I don't wanna be
there to see it. I just don't...
I can't see it... I want off.
I want off this
case. I want off.
When was the
last time you slept?
No, no, I'm OK.
You need one or
two hours of rest.
I'm good.
I'm fine. Just go.
OK...
I'm good, I'm good, I'm good.
Mmm.
- Mmm. You're very happy.
- I am happy.
I'm happy to see
you. You're not happy.
No, I've just been
here all night.
How is our resident
psychopath? Is he gone yet?
Yeah, yeah, soon.
Good. Sooner he
gets out, the better.
Mm-hm.
By the way, Mom likes you.
She thinks you're good for me.
Oh! Dr. Torres!
Thank God you're here.
I'm headed to the
pit, got a 911 page.
It was me. I paged
you 911 for Dr. Sloan.
He's the emergency.
Himself. It's on his person.
- Mark's hurt?
- Yes. No. Yes. Badly injured.
In a bad way, that is bad
for anyone who is a man,
but for Dr. Sloan in particular.
He may have broken a bone.
- A bone?
- He broke a bone.
I broke his bone.
You're kidding, right?
You're not kidding.
Cristina, I wanted to
apologize for last night.
It was not my intention
to arrive in that state.
You don't have to say anything.
As a rule, if I'm
showering with a woman
I do it without my clothes.
And if I get in her bed naked,
I don't pass out, and if I...
It's OK.
- It's not.
But you don't
have to talk about it.
It's getting a little
harder to breathe.
You can stop
doing this, William.
You can stop at any time.
I know.
Do you want me to
page Dr. Shepherd?
He's your boyfriend, isn't he?
Yes. I had a feeling.
Yes.
I had a feeling.
The man has very good taste.
Right now all I think
about are lemons.
Lemons?
When my grandfather was
dying, he said he smelled lemons.
It's all he could talk about for
three days, the smell of lemons.
I keep waiting to
smell them, and I don't.
Of course, he
was a big liar, so...
Are you sure you don't want
me to page Dr. Shepherd?
I'm sure.
OK.
O'Malley, whatever you're
doing, I need you to drop it.
- I was going home.
- Not anymore.
I need you to
talk to the nurses.
Find out if any
patients on life support
are O positive or brain dead.
Then cross-match those
folks against Jackson Prescott.
- Kid's running out of time.
- OK.
And O'Malley...
Be sensitive to their families.
We need organs for this
boy, but we can only ask.
We can't pressure. We
can't coerce. Understood?
Of course, sir.
- Um, Cristina?
- Oh, Shepherd.
- It's a ring.
- It's from my mother.
It's from me. It
was my mother's,
I'm gonna give it
to Meredith soon.
I'm looking for an opinion
on whether she's gonna like it,
or I should have the
setting redone more modern.
That's really not my job.
I know you two
are still fighting.
Isn't it about time
you wrap that up?
I ask, because when I propose,
she's gonna need
somebody to freak out to.
She misses you.
A lot.
You must miss her. I don't
know what's going on in your life,
but you must have something
you need to freak
out to her about.
I'm sorry. You should
ask someone else.
Ms. Prescott? Have you
had anything to eat today?
You should keep
your strength up.
Get a cup of
coffee or some food.
I'll stay here with Jackson.
He's stable for now.
Go on. I'll stay.
You are like the guy who
graduated from high school
and still hangs out
on the football field.
- Do you believe in heaven?
- What?
Heaven.
I don't know. I guess.
Because I thought that,
maybe, this was heaven.
Getting to be here with you.
But now... Now I'm
not so sure. I think this...
I think this may be hell, or...
What are you talking about?
- I'm here for you.
- For me, I know.
I got it, I hear you...
a thousand times.
I chose Alex. I'm sorry. I am.
I'm really sorry about that...
And I'm still here.
You broke up with
me and I'm still here.
Doesn't that tell you anything?
It tells me that you're jealous.
That you don't want
me to be happy,
you don't want me
to choose Alex...
Damn it, listen!
You can't pick Alex.
- I'm here for you!
- Denny...
I want you to be happy, Izzie.
I do. And I would
leave, if I could.
You think I want to stay here
while you tell me you
want another man?
I can't go because
you won't listen to me.
- I am here for you.
- What does that even mean?
- What does it mean?
- You're a doctor, Izzie.
Figure it out.
Thank you.
What?
Did... What?
Nothing.
How's your serial killer? Did
you monitor him last night?
Yeah. I got it covered.
Cristina, I said
I've got it covered.
Tell me you paged Shepherd.
- He wants to die.
- Meredith!
He's gonna die anyway, in
a few days. If he dies here,
we can donate organs to
the ten-year-old down the hall.
Derek won't allow it.
I didn't page him. I
hope you won't, either.
I know you think this is
wrong. Just let me do this.
Please... please help.
Help me.
I don't want to die.
- I don't want to die.
- Page Shepherd right now!
Code blue, 3rd floor.
- Should I thread the catheter?
- I want to see
the Grand Canyon.
- Visualize it on the ultrasound.
- - I wanna hike it.
Look out over Dead Man's Drop.
Not because I'm
dead. Just 'cause,
- you know, the view.
- Shut up.
- What was that?
- Nothing.
- Should I be able
to see the needle?
- Yeah.
That shadow within
the lumen is the catheter.
Have we heard anything from
UNOS? Have we heard anything?
I'll call them back.
I'd also like to see the
Great Wall of China.
I did a lot of
traveling in my life
but never made it
to Asia. I regret that.
My point, you unbelievably
stubborn woman,
is that there are other things
I would like to do and see.
Things that I would
like to, but I can't.
I can't go to heaven
or hell or to Asia.
I can't do anything but
this until you figure it out.
Would you just tell me already?!
I'm sorry.
Why don't you take a
little break, Dr. Stevens.
Does your sister talk to you
anymore or just boss you around?
She used to talk to me.
Now she tells me to get
lost, like we aren't friends.
- You hear Sloan
broke his goods?
- What?
- On-call room. I heard him scream.
- With Torres?
Maybe. Whoever it was,
whoever rode him and broke him?
That's a girl I want on me.
Was it Torres?
- What?
- Those two are off and on.
Think she's the
one who broke it?
How should I know?
It's not my business.
It's nobody's business.
It's definitely not yours...
Not that I know.
If I did know who broke
Mark's penis, I wouldn't tell you.
We're not friends.
I took out your appendix,
almost ended my career.
That doesn't make us close.
I want him prepped and
in the OR in 20 minutes.
Yes, sir.
Should have paged
me a long time ago.
Better yet, when I asked how
he was, you should have told me.
I was following the
patient's wishes.
He doesn't get wishes.
- He killed five women.
- You believe you're right,
I think I'm right.
If I said something
there'd have been a debate.
He's been manipulating you since
he got here. He preys on women.
I made a decision as his doctor.
A bad decision.
It was the wrong decision.
You're gonna scrub
in on his surgery
and watch while I try like
hell to undo what you did.
- His ICP's not going under 25.
- Is the catheter occluded?
- Looks fine.
- All right.
Try adjusting the height
of the drip chamber.
Raise his bed 10 degrees.
- What'll that do?
- Not much.
Jackson. Jackson,
listen to Mommy.
It's not time. You
do not get to go yet.
You have to stay here with me.
You hear me? You
stay with Mommy.
It is not time,
baby. I love you.
And I need you to fight. I
need you to fight, Jackson.
Come on, come on.
You fight to stay alive.
Yeah, that's a penile fracture.
Oh, I'm gonna kill myself.
We should operate,
then kill yourself.
Oh, God!
- Can you do it?
- Him? No! He's a meatballer.
He is meticulous and he
will keep his mouth shut.
Mainly because I've seen you
naked in a resident's bedroom.
I've done this before.
It's not complicated.
Guys run into this
on the battlefield?
Don't think we should talk
about how guys run into this.
Line up an OR.
We need to get in fast or
you risk permanent damage.
Oh, God! No permanent
damage, please.
- Hey...
- Little Grey, go away.
I don't want you
to see me like this.
I made you like this.
I'm saying "please," here.
Please.
Uh...
Talk to me, O'Malley.
- My God.
- The guy's not a donor.
They're about to unplug him.
- Dr. Shepherd!
- Dr. Bailey?
I need you to stop.
I need you to put
down the scalpel.
This man is trying
to kill himself.
God forgive me, I
need you to let him.
You need to leave
my OR, Dr. Bailey.
In five days... In five days
this man is going to die,
and his organs are
gonna go with him.
They'll be buried with his body,
and they'll rot in the ground,
and that is a crime.
It's a crime against life.
It's only five days. That's it.
That's all we're
taking from him,
and he doesn't want them anyway.
- We took an oath, Miranda.
- I know... that.
I know we took an oath, but...
right now, that oath
makes no sense.
It makes no sense. It doesn't.
Just stop. Don't do
anything else for this man.
If I stop this surgery,
it's the same as me sticking
this scalpel into his brain.
Is that what you want?
Yes. That's what I want.
- I'm sorry, what do you want?
- I'm sorry.
I know this is excruciating.
But what I want...
what I need...
are your husband's organs.
His liver and his bowels.
- He's a match for...
- Go away.
- I'm sorry?
- Please, go away.
I don't want anyone
cutting into him anymore.
I can't.
I can't take any more.
He was healthy.
He was healthy two days ago.
He's my love.
And he put his head
through a windshield.
And I have to unplug him.
He is the person who is supposed
to hold my hand
when things go bad.
He is supposed
to be here to help.
But he gets to go to heaven.
I can't take any more.
I can barely do this.
So, please, go away.
I don't want anyone
cutting into him.
Thanks for doing this, by the
way. I know you didn't have to.
Apparently I did, or you would
blackmail me to keep me quiet.
I wasn't gonna
actually do anything.
I wasn't gonna say anything.
Uh, it wasn't me, by
the way. With Mark.
- In case you were wondering.
- Wondering what?
Who broke him.
We're just friends.
I mean, we also...
We don't really,
actually, anymore.
He got involved
with somebody else
plus I'm a lesbian now, maybe.
Sort of. I don't know.
Anyway, he took up
with somebody else.
That's cool,
'cause I'm celibate.
I cook now, which
is totally great.
I roasted a chicken.
I'm happy for him,
that he's got somebody who can,
you know, shake and break him.
I guess I'd be lying if I said
I didn't miss having
a backup penis,
just in case I'm not a lesbian.
And he was my friend,
too. I guess he still is,
but it's never the same
when somebody's getting
all into somebody new,
so it's kind of like I've
lost both those things,
the penis and the friend.
I hate to lose one good
thing, never mind two.
Sometimes I get started talking
and I... say more than I should.
Picked up on that.
Cristina can seem cold, but...
that's just a lid,
a lid on a jar that
holds her feelings.
But... it's a big jar.
So don't give up too easy.
Torres, I hope you
find your backup penis
or a great lesbian to cook for.
- Whichever.
- Thank you.
How's he doing?
Intercranial pressure's
through the roof.
Where the hell have you been?
I... had some stuff.
Dead man talking stuff?
Yeah, I... I don't know.
This kid is dying
in front of his mom.
It's so bad
Dr. Bailey, Dr. Bailey
can't stay in here and watch.
But we're busting
our asses to save him,
and you're talking
to a dead guy.
You want to do that
crap at home, fine.
But not here. Here
you're a doctor.
Start acting like one.
ICP's too high.
I just gave him
hypertonic saline.
When was his last lorazepam?
Gave him a bolus 20 minutes ago.
Put him on a drip with Vec.
And put him on a BIS monitor.
Check with UNOS again.
I know it's a long
shot. Just go.
Uh-huh.
Whatever Bailey's doing,
I hope she's having
better luck than we are.
He's hemorrhaging
through his craniectomy.
Should I put in a drain?
That's up to Dr. Bailey.
Dr. Bailey?
- Dr. Bailey? Should
I put in a drain?
- No.
There's a lot of bleeding...
- I'm aware of that, Dr. Yang.
- Sir, really soon.
It's your call, Dr. Bailey.
It's up to you.
Am I an executioner
or am I a surgeon?
It's up to you. It's your call.
Pick up the scalpel.
He can't take his
liver to heaven,
can't take his
bowels or kidneys.
His brain is gone, but those
organs are probably good
because he's a young man.
And I know this is not
what you want to think about.
It's more than anyone should
ever have to think about.
But he can't take
his organs with him.
I heard it was this
physical therapist
from the rehab floor who
does this fancy yoga thing,
where she turns herself into a
pretzel while she's on top of a guy.
- She quit two weeks ago.
- I thought it was Torres.
Whoever it was is going
down in Seattle Grace history.
Sloan is a legend.
Can you imagine the kind of muscle
it takes to break a man like that?
Shut up! Just shut up about it!
You know something.
I know that it's
nobody's business.
She knows something.
Did you see somebody
come out of the room?
Maybe it was her.
What?
It was me. OK? Can we drop it?
It was me.
I do this twist and shout thing
that blows most guys' minds,
and I guess I
twisted a little too far,
and almost took the
whole thing off. OK?
I can feel you.
I can smell you.
If you're dead, how come
I can smell your skin?
So I'm thinking,
maybe, you're not dead.
Maybe that was the
part of me that was crazy.
Maybe this is the not
crazy part. You're still alive.
Right? That's it?
I'm sorry. No.
Then how come I
can feel your heart?
Because I'm real... to you.
Are you a ghost
or a dream or...?
You're a doctor,
Izzie, a scientist.
- Think like a scientist.
- I am.
I am!
Scientists believe
what they can see.
What they can feel. Facts.
Hard facts.
I slapped you. That is a fact.
I felt your face
on my hand. Fact.
We made love. That's a fact.
I can feel your breath
against my skin. Fact.
Fact. Fact.
Izzie. Izzie, Izzie.
What's happening?
You tell me.
I'm scared.
ICP's still going up.
- Are you
hyperventilating him enough?
- Yes.
Raise him all the way up.
Jackson, you have
to hold on. OK, baby?
Melinda, step back. You're in
the way. You need to step back.
Hold on for Mommy, OK?
Please, Jackson. Please!
Ms. Prescott.
- No. No, no, no, no, no, no!
- You have to let
them work on him.
I can't leave my son. I can't.
I can't leave him. Please.
- Let me stay, please!
- We'll be outside.
- You see any bleeders?
- Field looks clear.
Nice work, Dr. Yang.
Go ahead and close up.
- Thank you, sir.
- What a waste.
He's alive, Dr. Grey.
We saved a life.
That's never a waste.
He's just a little boy.
He's never had a sleepover.
He's never learned
to ride a bike.
Melinda, listen to me.
Miracles happen. Medical
miracles happen every day.
People live.
Even when they shouldn't.
I need to be with him. He's
never been anywhere without me.
He can't go alone. I
need to be with him.
You are here with him.
You're here for him even
though you aren't in the room.
You are. You are here for him.
You're...
I'm here for you, Izzie Stevens.
- I'm here for you.
- You're not real.
- I told you, I'm here for you.
- You are not real.
Izzie, I told you,
I'm here for you.
Dr. Bailey says you
need to come now.
♪ See the sun come rising ♪
♪ And white wings start to fly ♪
It's time to hold him.
He's going, Melinda.
Hold him and help him go.
♪ I don't want to
close my eyes ♪
♪ Don't want to
leave the stage now ♪
It's OK, baby. You can go.
It's OK. You can go.
It's OK, Mommy won't be mad.
You can go, Jackson. It's OK.
It's OK, Jackson. You can go.
We have organs!
Get him to OR 3 now!
- Starting CPR!
- Push .35 of epi.
Fifty of bicarb.
♪ Down to the downtown ♪
♪ Down to the lockdown ♪
♪ Boards, nails lie around ♪
♪ I crouch like a crow ♪
Finishing the vena cava.
Releasing the clamps.
Do we have any black spots?
Looks clean.
He's coding.
Start CPR! Get the
crash cart over here!
- Heaven or hell.
- Yes.
You're here for me.
- No.
You're not here for me.
You're here for me.
You came to get me.
I didn't know what heaven was.
I thought you were my heaven.
I loved you so much.
I loved you so much that when
I got to come back for you...
I thought...
♪ Peek in ♪
you are my heaven.
But, maybe...
♪ Into the peer in ♪
maybe I'm your hell.
♪ I'm not really like this ♪
- I'm sick.
- ♪ I'm probably plightless ♪
I'm sick, aren't I?
And instead of telling me...
Instead of telling
me to save my life...
You son of a bitch! You
selfish son of bitch! I hate you!
I didn't know there was a
chance. Miracles happen!
Medical miracles happen every
day. You said it. You said that.
Leave! Leave.
♪ I am ♪
♪ Blindsided ♪
I can go now...
because you know.
But it's your choice.
You get to choose.
But, Iz, if I go...
I don't know. I don't know
if I can come back. If I go...
In the choice between
heaven and hell,
I choose heaven! I choose life!
Go! Get out of here!
Go.
- I really hope this is heaven.
- Go.
Yeah...
What are you waiting for?
♪ Taut line ♪
-  This.
- ♪ Down to the shoreline ♪
♪ The end of a blood line ♪
♪ The Moon is a cold light ♪
I'm alive.
Yes, you are.
I was playing you.
Your boyfriend was right.
I wanted to destroy your career.
I was playing you the
whole time, Dr. Grey.
And I wanted to be
here to see the fallout.
You were scared, William.
Death is scary. I
would've been scared, too.
It'd be good to have a
friendly face in the crowd...
when they kill me.
I planned a whole evening...
last night. A real date.
It was a clear night, one of
the five Seattle gets all year.
I was going to take you to
the West Point Lighthouse,
and we were gonna watch
the Northern Lights together.
I had a planned date.
I'd like another chance.
I want you to give
me another chance.
You've got some problems.
You've got some big problems.
Yeah.
Yeah... Yeah. I do.
Will you go out with me, anyway?
Yes.
- Hey.
- Please go away.
- No.
- Little Grey...
It's not Little
Grey. It's Lexie.
And I'm sorry
that I broke your...
I'm sorry that I hurt you.
And I'm sorry that
you're humiliated.
But I'm not going anywhere.
I've got a friend who
is guarding the door.
A good friend. And since no
one is going to be coming in,
I am now going to climb into
bed with you and stroke your hair.
Because that's what I like to
have done for me when I'm hurt.
How is he?
We were so late
getting those organs in.
Between the cerebral edema
and the reperfusion coding,
we don't know what kind of
damage was done to his brain.
We don't even know if
he's going to wake up.
I crossed a line today.
I endangered my medical license
I crossed a line.
So did I.
♪ Don't go too deep ♪
♪ Into the flood ♪
♪ Don't stare too long ♪
♪ You'll poison my love ♪
♪ Don't shut me out ♪
♪ Don't hold it all in ♪
♪ Don't let my venom
get under your skin ♪
♪ 'Cause every
word and every turn ♪
♪ And every sign
points to your hurt ♪
Heaven. Hell. Limbo.
♪ You're drifting further away ♪
No one really knows
where we're going...
♪ Come make your peace ♪
♪ Come find your way ♪
♪ Come lay your wreath
at the altar of change ♪
♪ Don't lose your step ♪
♪ Don't break the bones ♪
♪ Don't shoulder your burden ♪
♪ Out there on your own ♪
♪ 'Cause every
word and every turn ♪
♪ And every sign
points to your hurt ♪
♪ With every word
and every turn ♪
♪ And every sign
points to your hurt ♪
♪ With every hour ♪
♪ You're drifting further away ♪
♪ Don't banish me
then bid me home ♪
♪ Don't tell me where
I came undone ♪
♪ Don't harbor love
like it's all your own ♪
Lemons.
♪ Don't linger over
what you've done ♪
My grandfather
wasn't lying after all.
Or what's waiting for
us when we get there.
♪ When you're trying
to carry way too much ♪
♪ You never should have let go ♪
♪ You could have
joined the whole show ♪
♪ I never should have let go ♪
But the one thing
we can say, for sure,
with absolute certainty...
♪ 'Cause every
word and every turn ♪
- ♪ Every sign ♪
- Jackson?
♪ Points to your hurt ♪
♪ With every hour ♪
Can I have some water?
♪ You're drifting further away ♪
Oh!
Is that there are moments
that take us to another place...
♪ Don't tell me where
I came undone ♪
♪ Don't harbor love
like it's all your own ♪
♪ Don't linger over
what you've done ♪
♪ Don't sink underneath
the weight of ♪
♪ When you're trying
to carry way too much ♪
♪ You never should have let go ♪
I know you don't understand me.
I don't understand me.
I wanted to show him compassion.
That's why I went.
That's the reason.
And it was horrible.
It was horrible.
It's OK.
She's in the car and
she won't stop crying.
- Did you propose?
- No. She went to
William's execution.
Moments of heaven on Earth.
♪ Points to your hurt ♪
♪ With every hour ♪
♪ You're drifting further away ♪
♪ Now you're
drifting further away ♪
And maybe, for now,
that's all we need to know.