Previously on Grey's Anatomy:
You're not attracted to me.
You think you are, you're not.
You are nowhere near hardcore
enough to commit to cardio.
- Why isn't this easier?
- I don't know.
Well, I want my
best friend back.
You deserve the job. I
should have given it to you.
Things are gonna
be different here.
Your love lives, your
hopes and dreams,
the joys and tragedies that make you
who you are have no place in my hospital.
- This is our son.
- He's beautiful.
We go into medicine
because we want to save lives.
because we want to do good.
We go into medicine
for the rush...
for the high...
for the ride.
- You're not dancing.
- I'm too tense.
- Which is why we're dancing!
- My problem is,
I'm sleeping with a man who's
dating. I don't care if he dates Sydney.
It's the woman he dates after
Sydney. That's my problem.
If I had any sense, I would
break up with the breakup sex.
There would be no more breakup
sex-ing. If I had any sense...
Shut up! Dance it out.
But what we remember,
at the end of most days,
are the losses.
What we lay awake
at night replaying
is the pain we caused
or failed to cure.
The lives we ruined
or failed to save.
You know, I'm gonna tell him.
- I don't want him
seeing other people.
- Fine. Whatever.
I'm gonna tell him.
And I feel good about it.
Dancing makes you brave.
So the experience
of practicing medicine
rarely resembles the goal.
The experience, too often,
is ass-backwards
and upside down.
- Hey.
- I'm so sick
of Meredith and Cristina
and their stupid love affair that
they have to rub in everyone's faces.
It's stupid dancing. Frigging
Bobbsey Twins. It's stupid!
You're ranting. It's early
in the morning for ranting.
We're supposed to be the happy ones.
We should be dancing. Why aren't we?
You want to dance?
Whatever. I'm gonna go in early.
I'm gonna get on hardcore Erica
Hahn cardio, and I'm gonna kick ass at it.
When I kick ass, it's
gonna piss Cristina off.
But it won't matter because
I'll be a kick-ass cardio god.
- I'm just saying,
you're never here.
- Hold on, hold on.
I mess up the rotation schedule,
the residents are
gonna dog me all week.
- OK.
- You're never here.
I'm here in the mornings.
I'm here at night.
- Between midnight and 6am.
- I'm chief resident now.
And I'm loading the dishwasher!
Hi.
You volunteered
to stay home with T-U-C-K.
Who else was gonna
take care of T-U-C-K?
I'm late for work.
- Hey, honey.
- We need to talk.
OK, take the baby by your
mom and meet me for lunch. OK?
- We'll talk then.
- Well, why can't we
talk here?
I'm only here between the
hours of midnight and 6am.
Come on. Now, just meet me
for lunch, Tucker. Come on, now.
- Lunch.
- Yes, lunch.
Thatcher's not my problem. He can
get drunk all he wants. I don't care.
- Right.
- I don't care
about Lexie, either.
She's a big girl, she
can take care of herself.
You talk about them an awful
lot for someone who doesn't care.
You care because you're you.
You're gonna make me late
for my meeting with Sloan.
Well, OK then, go.
What?
Nothing. I'm gonna be late.
- Hey.
- I'm late
for Sloan's meeting.
- Yeah, so am I.
- Also, I'm not
speaking to you.
- I'm still not
- You don't have to speak.
Late for Sloan.
OK, ladies and gentlemen,
this is Nick Hanscomb.
- Hi.
- Nick was lucky enough
to have me remove a large
carotid body tumor from his neck.
That I was able to get clean
boundaries is pretty darn impressive,
- even for me.
- Congratulations.
Don't interrupt.
Now, despite the fact that it
was a wildly successful surgery,
we had to dissect out deep
lymph nodes in his neck.
There is now only a
delicate flap of skin
between his carotid artery
and the outside world.
That said, what
am I worried about?
I'd think given the
friability of the skin,
that there's a great possibility
that the artery could blow.
Right.
Don't worry, I've
heard this before.
If that happens,
whoever's in the room,
I don't care if it's a
doctor, a nurse, an orderly,
your job is to
stop the bleeding,
then page me, in that order.
Are we clear? Any questions?
- They look scared.
- They're professionals.
A healthy level of
fear is encouraged.
OK, then.
If I do die, it will have
been lovely meeting you all.
See? The patient is confident,
you should be confident. That's it.
- What do we got?
- Jacob Nolston, 47,
status post his double
bypass surgery two weeks ago,
febrile with tenderness
in his surgical incisions.
We got a ten car
pileup, mind taking him?
- You got it.
- I need a gurney.
I'll page Hahn.
We all agree. Get
him inside and flip for it.
- You're in good hands.
- Thank you.
One, two, three.
- You're in over your head.
- You don't own
the cardio department.
- He's my patient. First dibs.
- Hey, you guys.
- You can't call dibs.
- I think you should move!
- Let go of the gurney.
- You let go!
Move!
- My leg!
- Are you OK?
I'm good. Let's go.
Coming through!
Call the fire department.
Get some gurneys out here.
Ray? Ray, can you hear me?
Stan?
- Oh, my God.
- Stan? Open your eyes, man.
Oh, man. Don't
scare me like that.
Let's get you guys out of there.
No! Stop! Stop.
Don't touch anything.
Don't touch anything until Fire
stabilizes. Doors aren't gonna budge.
Torres! I need your
help here! Get the driver!
On my way! All right, just page somebody
to help you and keep them talking.
- You got this?
- Yeah.
- Don't leave. Don't.
- OK.
Somebody page the chief!
- Hey, you OK?
- No.
But I'm not as
bad off as this guy.
He started coding
after we picked him up.
And Mary had
some kind of seizure.
Mary? Mary, come
on girl, wake up!
- I need help.
- There's no pulse.
- Call the coroner. Let me check you.
- No. Is she dead?
- I'll go around.
- No, but she looks postictal.
A bad elbow dislocation and
weak pulse. Can you grab this?
She was driving, talking to
me. She started convulsing,
- and then we slammed
into that rig.
- Can you move?
Yeah.
You know I need to stabilize
you. You know the drill.
My c-spine's clear. I can walk.
Well, come on.
Where are you injured?
My gut. Upper abdomen.
I know this is going
to sound weird,
but think you could
get me a guy doctor?
- How am I doing?
- Strong and stable.
Strong and stable.
Two words that have never
been used to describe me. Ever.
You're a pretty girl. I hope
you don't think that's rude.
I'm just... I haven't
been allowed to notice
that kind of thing for a while.
- Now I'm allowed.
- You're allowed
to notice prettiness?
Well, I'm allowed to
notice other women.
Women other than my girlfriend.
- My now ex-girlfriend.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
Yeah, giant neck
tumors weren't her thing.
- She left because
of the tumor?
- No.
No. She left me because I
didn't make her laugh anymore.
And she had just
lost that loving feeling.
She left you because
of the tumor. That sucks.
Yep.
You seeing anyone? I'm
just making conversation.
My artery is exposed,
which kind of limits my game.
OK... yes.
Well, kind of. I am.
- Nice guy?
- Yeah, he is.
Well, he's kind of...
he's kind of a nice guy
- disguised as a jerk.
- Oh, yeah,
I know that type.
My girlfriend was a nice girl
disguised as a vapid narcissist.
But then it turned out
she really was just
a vapid narcissist.
- Ouch.
- Yeah.
So you really like this guy?
Even though he doesn't have
a super-cool exposed
carotid artery?
Yeah. I do.
What's going on in the
pit? They wiped the board.
A couple of ambulances
crashed into each other.
I'm canceling electives
to free ORs for
emergent surgeries.
- Are we friends yet?
- I'm sorry?
Friends. Are we friends?
I know I just learned
your name and all, Rose.
But I'd like to think I
could call you a friend.
- Why?
- Because,
if I'm your friend,
I'd tell you about
licorice in your teeth,
where as an acquaintance, I'd smile
politely and pretend it wasn't there.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
- Jacob!
- Dad!
- Daddy, are you OK?
- Hey, guys.
- You OK?
- What happened to your leg?
There was a...
a little accident,
but I'm OK. It doesn't hurt.
- What kind of an accident?
- The ambulances crashed.
The ambulances crashed?
Sandra, tell your
mother not to panic.
Stop panicking, Mom.
- Is his heart OK?
- What's your name?
- Lucy.
- Lucy, I'm Izzie.
Your dad's heart is hurt,
but we're gonna work
hard to make it better.
- I was paged? Dr. Yang?
- Jacob Nolston,
two weeks post-op from a CABG.
My exam suggests
a sternal infection.
- Our initial exam.
- He also sustained
injuries to his leg
- from an accident
outside the ER.
- OK, Stevens,
when you can tear yourself away,
page Torres about
the shrapnel in this leg.
And you can work with
her today. I only need one.
- No.
- You have
to let me examine you.
I can wait. I'll wait for a guy.
You're shy. OK, I get
that. This is no time for shy.
Now, my hands may be smaller than
a man's, but my brain is much larger,
I assure you. Now, you're
just going to have let me...
- No! Do not... Do not touch me!
- For the love of...
Dr. Bailey. An
emergent situation?
Says he wants a male doctor. He
doesn't want female hands to touch him.
Let me see his chart.
Um, Shane, I'm Dr. Webber.
- I'm going to palpate
your abdomen...
- No, no.
- You said he wanted
a male doctor.
- He did.
I just... I meant
I want another...
I want a different doctor.
I'll wait for a different doctor.
A different doctor?
You mean you
want a white doctor.
I have paramedics
hanging upside down.
Can you handle... this?
Yes, sir. I can.
- Dr. Torres.
- This is Mary Daltry.
She lost consciousness
behind the wheel.
- You're the neuro guy?
- Yes, I'm Dr. Shepherd.
- Why did I have a seizure?
- I don't know.
I've never had a seizure
before. I mean, I'm fine.
Except, apparently, I
caused this accident.
Call Radiology, let's
get her in for an MRI.
- Yes, sir.
- How's Shane? My partner?
- Does anybody know?
- He's with Dr. Bailey.
- That's good.
- Ready to fix the arm. Are you ready?
- Is it gonna hurt?
- Yes, but...
George.
But Dr. Torres is very good.
- OK, Dr. Shepherd,
are you good?
- Yeah, I'm good.
Soon as I get some more
information, I'll let you know. OK?
- OK.
- All right.
Ow!
How's it going in there, fellas?
I think... I think that they
better get us out of here.
Yeah. If we're
putting it to a vote,
I think we better
get out of here fast.
I'm afraid "keep still" is
the best we can do for now.
Don't want to make
anything worse.
We'll get you some pain
meds as soon as possible.
- Sir?
- Call me Richard.
Richard, can you tell me...
My legs, are they broken?
- I... I can't see your legs.
- How come?
Well, your body is trapped
in the door. You can't feel...
- I can't...
- You can't feel that?
I can't.
I can't feel anything.
- His ears are bleeding!
- I see, Ray.
Can you get my wife?
She works here.
She's an x-ray tech.
- You bet.
- Stan, don't die on me. You hear me?
- I'll be so pissed
if you die on me.
- I'm doing my best, man.
- Get Stan's wife here now.
- What do we... How do we...?
We don't.
- We have a whole hospital...
- The moment we move him,
he's gonna bleed out.
All the medicine in the
world won't save him.
His wife has to get here soon if
she wants to see her husband alive.
Now, move.
Everything's clear! Just a
couple more minutes, guys.
- Thanks.
- - Go ahead and secure that line.
I'm just checking on you guys.
- Ray, talk to me.
- What?
Talk to me. I need you to help
me hold on until Sara gets here.
I'm not helping you hold
on, because you're not dying.
Ray.
Talk to him. Help him.
Remember the night you met Sara?
At Joe's?
You used that
stupid line about...
The one about the
bet over the song lyrics.
Right. Right. What
was that song?
It was... It was...
"I can see clearly now,
the rain is gone."
♪ I can see all
obstacles in my way ♪
♪ It's gonna be a bright ♪
♪ Bright, sun-shiny day ♪
- What comes next?
- I don't know.
"I think I can make it
now, the pain is gone."
I can't believe
Sara fell for that line.
Listen, when you
get out of here,
you're gonna have
a great story to tell.
You tell it in the bar.
You tell them
how you got into this accident
and your best friend died.
Chicks love that stuff.
Ray, don't tell Sara that I was
talking about you getting tail
right before I died.
OK.
She should be here any
minute. Just hold on, Stan.
Dr. Sloan, I have a patient
13 days status post CABG
- with a sternal infection.
- Remove sternum?
And I need you to manipulate
the pectoral muscles
so we don't leave a hole in
the chest. Can you make time?
Make time for a drink with me?
Did I mention time is a factor here?
I'm looking for a yes or no answer.
- As am I.
- This may be
enjoyable to you,
but I have a patient
in serious condition.
I came to you. Legend has
it you're the best in plastics.
But if bad jokes and sleazy come-ons
are what I'm in for all afternoon,
- I'll page whoever's
second best.
- Dr. Hahn.
I apologize.
- And I'll clear my schedule.
- Thank you. OR One.
Why don't you clean this up
here and clear up my schedule
- and you can scrub in.
- Thank you.
Sorry about that.
I'm sorry. I'll be right back.
- So... coffee?
- I can't.
You can't? When I was your
patient, you made time for me.
- Because you were my patient.
- I thought it was
because you liked me.
Look, I'm really sorry.
I got to finish up and then
I'm scrubbing in on a surgery.
- It's one I've
never seen before.
- Can I watch?
- What?
- Can I watch
the surgery? Can I...?
- Can you sneak me in?
- No.
Know how much
trouble I'd get in?
Since when are
you a rule follower?
There's a dozen people in the
back of the OR and there's a gallery.
- Ava.
- Please?
- We're ready to go.
- Hold off a moment.
His wife's arriving.
Stan, Sara's here.
Stan.
Stan, wake up man,
Sara's here! Wake up!
That's good.
- That's good.
- Baby?
Baby! Hey.
Your x-ray shows the metal's
embedded in your femur.
I'm gonna go in and remove it
while Dr. Hahn and Dr. Sloan
repair the damage
caused by the infection.
Repair the damage?
- Mm-hm.
- They're removing
my chest bone.
Why is this all happening?
My kids shouldn't
have to see me this way.
It's a dad's job to worry.
You worry about your kids.
You worry about them
every day of their lives.
But they aren't supposed to have to
worry about dad, to comfort their mom.
- Why am I back here? My kids...
- Your kids are fine.
They're taking care of
each other and they're fine.
Lucy and the others were hungry,
your wife took them to the cafeteria.
The point is, they're fine. They
just want their dad to get better.
You'll keep an eye on
them, when I'm in surgery?
You'll keep them updated?
Because my wife, she...
She gets panicky if she
doesn't know what's going on.
I will keep her updated.
Uh, I would like to borrow Dr. Yang.
It's important. Can you spare her?
Torres! Can I steal
Stevens off your service?
- I'll give her away for free.
- Yang's all yours, Dr. Bailey.
Thank you.
Yang! Stevens!
Dr. Yang, Dr. Bailey has
requested your capable hands.
Dr. Stevens, take over
prepping Mr. Nolston for surgery.
- Wait...
- Just take it up
with Dr. Bailey, Yang.
- Hey.
- Mary's scans come up yet?
- Not yet.
What's going on
with you and Stevens?
Just 'cause I don't sleep in your
house, doesn't mean I don't hear gossip.
Why are we talking
about this? We don't talk.
Oh, you're... You miss
Meredith and you're clinging.
- I'm not clinging.
- A little bit,
you're clinging.
- I'm just making small talk.
- OK. Cool.
Here we go.
Tumor.
Look, I'm hurt.
I'm really hurt here.
You just try not to die.
Someone will be here soon
to save the master
race from extinction.
Can I talk to you for a
minute? I mean no disrespect.
But can you tell me you have an
amazingly good reason for pulling me off
of Dr. Hahn's service
when I have been fighting
- to get into her good graces.
- You're not black.
But you're not white either.
Dr. Yang will be examining you.
Oh, come on. Are you kidding?
OK, you have medical training.
How long do you think you have
to live if you have internal injuries?
Exactly. I seriously recommend
you let this fine doctor examine you.
Dr. Yang, give him the best medical
treatment possible. It's the law.
Sir, I need you to
move your hands.
I just didn't want her to see.
I thought she might
take offense, you know?
I'm not gonna
leave you. I'm not.
I'm not leaving here right
now without you, OK? Please?
- I've never seen her before.
- - What?
I've never seen her before. I've
worked in this hospital all this time.
Before today, she was a
complete stranger to me.
It happens. It's a big hospital.
I love you.
I've never met her before,
and yet I'm the person who
handed her the worst day of her life.
In her story, that's who I am.
That's who I'll always be.
That's the job.
That's the job. I know.
Look at me.
This day...
This day you feel helpless.
This day makes
all those other days
when you fight to
save a life and lose,
this day makes you grateful you
have a chance to do anything at all.
You take it in.
Ma'am.
It's time.
♪ And I don't know if I
could stand another... ♪
- Go easy. I'm injured.
- You've had plenty
of morphine.
You'll be fine. Not like you're in
a concentration camp or anything.
When people are young
or drunk, they get tattoos,
- they wake up,
they regret it.
- So you regret it?
You got to treat me like anyone
else. That's the beauty of this country.
Yes, it is.
So you're gonna
drill into my skull?
O'Malley?
Dr. Shepherd's gonna
do a cookie craniotomy.
He's gonna drill a very, very small
hole and then, with a computer,
he guides the scope through your brain.
It's as minimally invasive as possible.
It's just... It's
weird, you know,
to be on the other
side of all this.
How are Stan and Ray?
And Shane? Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, how did this happen?
She's seizing!
I always knew you were
an ass, but seriously?
You brought Jane Doe? Are you
trying to get yourself kicked out?
- She wanted to see what I do.
- I thought you were
seeing Lexie.
- I'm a popular guy.
- - Whatever you're talking about
is endlessly
fascinating, Dr. Karev,
but I kind of had my heart
set on saving a life today.
- Sorry.
- So... let's begin.
Hey, Nurse Olivia said you
needed to see me. Are you OK?
My book is bad. And I
hate daytime television.
- And all my friends
are at work.
- I'm at work too.
I'm an intern.
Supposed to be learning.
You can learn about my artery.
You can never know
too much about arteries.
- Come on. I have
no one to talk to.
- Fine.
- But I'm taking
your vitals again.
- OK.
So you want to help
me plot my revenge?
- The girlfriend?
- Uh-huh. Here's
what I'm thinking.
I page her here.
And then, you
know, I'm all like,
"I'm dying. And I just need to
gaze at your beauty one last time."
And when she gets
here... I flash her the artery.
- It's mean.
- Right?
- I like it.
- Can you get me a phone?
The moment they pull apart the rig,
we're gonna come in and grab you.
- You take Stan first.
- Once we get in there
and assess,
- then we'll see who goes first.
- No. You take Stan first.
You take Stan first.
Ray, I think I'm gonna be OK.
- I'm starting to feel better.
- Don't screw with me.
No. No. I'm probably
not as bad as I think.
I'm probably just paralyzed.
Richard, you think, maybe,
that I can get out of
here just paralyzed, right?
It's possible. It happens.
- Really?
- See?
OK. OK.
Is my wife inside? She
won't see any of this?
Nope.
You'll be where I
can look at you?
I'm right here, where
you can look at me.
Then let's do this.
Try to live, man.
You too.
♪ 'Cause I really
wanna know now ♪
♪ Before I begin ♪
♪ To let you go ♪
Stop! Stop!
Stop! Stop! Make them stop!
- Stop! Stop!
- What are you doing?
Stan!
Ray. Ray... Ray's back.
It's in deep. He'll bleed
out if you move us.
It's the oxygen regulator.
It's embedded in his back.
Ray! Ray! You still with us?
I'm here, chief.
I'm still here, but
my pulse is weak.
He's sweaty and breathing fast.
And with the angle
of that regulator...
It's cardiac tamponade.
If that regulator caused a tear
in his heart and we move him,
- the regulator could move.
- It makes the tear bigger.
Please let's don't
flood my heart. Please.
We'll stabilize him
in the ambulance.
Stan, you're a hero, man.
You saved Ray's life.
Stan?
Stan? Damn it, Stan! Stan.
Go get the ultrasound
so we can be sure.
And bring in a crash
cart, just in case.
And go find where Hahn is.
- OK.
- The films are up.
- Intraperitoneal bleeding.
- His liver looks
completely ruptured.
He is gonna need a laparotomy.
Maybe it'll be straightforward.
So I can get back
to Hahn's service?
- Or not?
- If I have to work
on this man,
- so do you.
- Why? You don't need me.
He has a swastika
on his abdomen.
A giant black swastika.
My stepfather's parents
died in Auschwitz.
You and I will do this.
We will do this and we will consider
ourselves having risen above.
We'll rise. Above.
You're busted.
- Save it.
- Mm.
You're using a cable
instead of wires, Dr. Sloan.
I've never seen
it done that way.
Tension banding. I
learned it back in New York.
I moved there after Columbia
to study under John Seever.
He was a great surgeon.
He died last year.
I was wrecked.
Couldn't sleep for weeks.
- It was like losing
my own father.
- What are we, on a date?
I was complimenting
your surgical skills,
not looking for a window into
your wounded soul. Clamp, please.
You can't operate. I won't
sign the consent form.
You need this surgery. You
will die without the surgery.
You may die with this surgery.
Your chance of living is
increased if you let me operate.
- It's just gonna be
you two in there?
- Yes.
No. I need to have at least one
white doctor in that operating room,
so you don't kill me on
the table. No offense.
No offense? Did he
just say, "No offense"?
- Shepherd. I need O'Malley.
- Yeah?
- We're going into surgery.
- O'Malley.
- You OK?
- Don't cross me.
- I wasn't crossing you.
- I'm rising above.
I'm rising above, and do not want
to be crossed while I'm busy rising.
I have to operate on
a white supremacist
and he has requested
a white doctor
to watch me to make sure that I
don't kill his crazy white behind.
I need O'Malley. Can I have him?
- O'Malley,
go with Dr. Bailey.
- Yes, sir.
Get him to sign the consent, then
have him anesthetized and ready.
Dr. Bailey, you are within your
rights to pass this on to somebody.
Well, that would make me
like him. And I'm not like him.
Sorry, Dr. Shepherd.
I'm running behind today.
- I'll be out of
your way in a second.
- Actually, I'm early,
- so technically
I'm in your way.
- Don't let it happen again.
- You're staring at my chest.
- What?
I think, maybe, you're
intending to admire my ring,
- but you're staring
at my chest.
- Sorry, it's just that...
you wear your engagement
ring on your necklace.
When I was engaged,
I wore it on my finger.
Now, necklace. The stone was my
grandmother's. I don't want to lose it.
- I'm sorry.
- Sorry why?
Your engagement.
Call it off recently?
- That's a pretty
personal question.
- We're friends now.
I saved you hours of potential
licorice humiliation. I think you can...
It ended a year ago.
Nothing to be sorry about.
- It was never gonna work out.
- How come?
Because I was always very clear
about what I wanted and he... wasn't.
And there's no way
to build a future on that.
Yeah.
- I can't be in here!
- Ray! Ray! Ray,
you can't do that!
You have to stay perfectly
still! You cannot move.
Ray, look at me.
Don't look at Stan. Look at me.
You are not gonna
die today. OK? Say it.
- I am not gonna die.
- You are not going
to die today.
He'll need a pericardiocentesis
if it's a tamponade,
but we need to
get an ultrasound.
- I can do it. I can get in.
- Meredith.
I can fit.
♪ Forgive what I have done ♪
♪ It means my
soul's survival, oh ♪
♪ I need you so, it's sin ♪
♪ Put an end to
my suffering... ♪
Dr. Bailey?
I'm calling on Jesus this time.
Don't bother me when I'm calling
on Jesus. I don't do it very often,
he might not hear me.
♪ Why am I so blind ♪
♪ With my eyes wide open... ♪
Scalpel.
♪ Trying to get my hands ♪
♪ Clean in dirty water ♪
♪ Mmm ♪
Respiratory, 2162.
It's amazing, isn't it? How
technical it all is? How impersonal?
They're, basically,
just mechanics.
Like God's mechanics,
because what they're doing
down there is saving a life.
So you're a surgeon?
Surgical intern. First
year. What about you?
Oh, um...
I'm not actually
supposed to be here.
The guy that I'm... you know...
Your husband?
No. No, no. The...
Not my husband.
The guy that... Anyways, I'm
just... I wanted to see him operate.
Oh, Dr. Sloan. Oh, I get
it. No, no. I'm not judging.
- I mean, he's kind
of insanely hot.
- Well, he is.
But I'm not with
him. I'm with... him.
- Do you know him?
- No. No, I don't
know him at all.
Supposed to be having lunch
with my husband, O'Malley.
Yes, ma'am.
Supposed to be having
lunch with my husband,
and instead I am elbow
deep in a Nazi's gut.
Yes, ma'am.
No one better ever
call me "Nazi" again.
Yes, ma'am.
All right, can I get a little
suction right there, please?
That's good. Good.
OK. All right, I should be
able to access the tumor now.
Did we lose power?
No, the other monitors are fine.
It must be the
stereotactic computer.
- Nothing. It's dead.
- You kidding?
I'm in the woman's brain. The
navigational system's dead?
- Should we get another machine?
- I remove the probe,
it won't be the machine that's
dead. Tell the company to get here.
- Tell them we need
somebody here, now.
- Take it slow, Grey.
There's glass all around you.
I'm sorry, Stan. I'm so sorry.
Here.
He's OK. He doesn't mind.
- We're losing him!
- OK, get in there!
Just get in there!
- Hey.
- Hi.
- You checking in on me again?
- Yep.
Will you call me strong
and stable again?
Let's hope.
What's wrong with you?
What makes you think
something's wrong?
Well, your cheeks are all
flushed, which they weren't earlier.
Is it creeping you out how
observant I am? I'm sorry.
It's the boredom,
I'm telling you.
Remember your girlfriend who just
turned out to be a vapid narcissist?
Your boyfriend turned
out to just be a jerk.
Jerk. Ass. And many dirtier
words that are inappropriate
for me to use in
front of a patient.
- I'm sorry.
- Yeah, me too.
Well, you want me to
help you plot your revenge?
- OK.
Here's what I'm thinking.
You go out with me.
Just like that, bam.
New boyfriend.
He'll be all, "What's he
got that I don't have?"
And you'll be all,
"Carotid artery. Exposed!
Top that, loser."
And he'll be all, "I can't.
- I can't top that. I'm a loser."
- No.