Previously on Grey's Anatomy.
The seven years you spend here as a surgical resident will be the best and worst of your life.
You will be pushed to the breaking point.
Eight of you will switch to an easier specialty.
Five of you will crack under the pressure.
Two of you will be asked to leave.
Dr. Shepherd, we should pretend it never happened.
What never happened?
You sleeping with me last night?
Or are you throwing me out this morning?
You're an attending, and I'm your intern.
Stop looking at me like that.
Like what?
Like you've seen me naked.
Your first shift starts now and lasts 48 hours.
You're interns, grunts, nobodies, bottom of the surgical food chain.
What are you doing here?
You and I are going to have so much fun together.
You know Meredith is inbred?
Like it's uncommon around here to be a doctor's parent.
No, royally inbred.
Her mother is Alice Gray.
Shut up, the Alice Gray.
She's a living ledger.
What's your name?
It's me, Mom.
Meredith.
All right.
We're gonna survive this, right?
It's all about lines.
The finish line at the end of residency...
Waiting in line for a chance at the operating table.
And then there's the most important line.
A line separating you from the people you work with.
It doesn't help to get too familiar.
To make friends.
You need boundaries between you and the rest of the world.
Other people are far too messy.
It's all about lines.
Drawing lines in the sand.
And praying like hell no one crosses them.
Look, I'm sure you're very nice, but I'm very particular about who lives in my house and you're just not right.
Why?
Look, I'm quiet.
No loud music, no parties.
Where were you when the Challenger exploded?
The what?
The space shuttle.
Challenger.
Uh, I think I was in kindergarten.
Exactly.
No.
Why do you put up posters for roommates if you don't want roommates?
I do want roommates.
We're together 100 hours a week.
You want to live together, too?
Oh, yeah.
See, you bring bribes down, huh?
I need a place to live.
My mom irons my scrubs.
I have to get out of there.
It's not a bribe.
I don't think it's a good idea.
I can put down last, first, and deposit.
It's totally a bribe.
I can cook.
And I'm an obsessive cleaner.
No.
I just want two total strangers who I don't have to talk to or be nice to.
And it's not a bribe.
It's a mocha latte.
George, you're running the code team.
Meredith, take the trauma pager.
Christina, deliver the weekend labs to the patients.
Izzy, you're on sutures.
Dr. Bailey, I was hoping to assist you in the OR today, maybe do a minor procedure.
I think I'm ready.
Mocha latte?
If she gets a cut, I want a cut too.
Yeah, me too.
I wouldn't mind another shot.
I mean, if everybody else is.
Stop talking.
Every intern wants to perform their first surgery.
That's not your job.
Do you know what your job is?
To make your resident happy.
Do I look happy?
No.
Why?
Because my interns are whiny.
You know what will make me look happy?
Having the code team staffed, having the trauma pages answered, having the weekend labs delivered, and having someone down in the pit doing the sutures.
No one holds a scalpel till I'm so happy I'm Mary freakin' Poppins.
Mogulotting my ass.
Why are you all standing there?
Move!
Seattle has ferry boats.
Yes.
I didn't know that.
I've been living here six weeks.
I didn't know there were ferry boats.
Seattle is surrounded by water on three sides.
Hence the fairy boats.
Now I have to like it here.
I wasn't planning on liking it here.
I'm from New York.
Genetically engineered to dislike everywhere, except Manhattan.
I have a thing for fairy boats.
I'm not going out with you.
Did I ask you to go out with me?
Do you want to go out with me?
I'm not dating you, and I'm definitely not sleeping with you again.
You're my boss.
I'm your boss's boss.
You're my teacher, and my teacher's teacher, and you're my teacher.
I'm your sister.
I'm your daughter.
You're sexually harassing me.
I'm riding an elevator.
Look, I'm drawing a line.
The line is drawn.
There's a big line.
So this line, is it imaginary, or do I need to get you a marker?
We'll talk later.
You the surgeon?
Yeah.
We've got a rape victim.
You better get in there.
25-year-old female found down at the park, status post-trauma.
She came in with a GCS of 6, BP 80 over 60.
Exam is significant for blood head trauma, unequal breath sounds, right pupil is dilated, and she's ready for x-ray.
You ready to roll?
Hey.
Yeah.
Call ahead to clear CT.
Let them know I'm coming.
Load up the portable monitor.
Call respiratory for a ventilator.
I'll get x-rays while I'm down there.
She's going to spend a hell of a long time in recovery and rehab.
She survives.
What is she, like 5'2", 100 pounds?
She's still breathing after what this guy did to her?
Catch the guy?
They should castrate him.
See how shitty her hands are?
She tried to fight back.
Tried to?
Rape kid came back negative.
She kicked his ass.
Oh, so we have a warrior among us, huh?
Allison.
Her name is Allison.
I think I've met her.
on the cause of our rupture.
What is this?
Does anyone know what this is?
Oh, my god.
What?
Spit it out, Gray.
She bit it off.
Bit off what?
That's his penis.
She bit off his penis.
Ouch.
If she can fight the infection, she'll be fine.
It's all gonna depend on whether or not she wakes up in the next 72 hours.
Yeah, we should get a drink later and tell me the long story of what makes a hot shot doc leave the Big Apple for Seattle.
It's a short story, actually.
Your chief of surgery made me an offer I couldn't refuse.
Richard asked you to come?
Yeah.
Why?
Oh, nothing.
See you later.
Do you know what the code team does?
Saves lives.
Eyes shock a heart, and someone lives to see another day.
That's upbeat.
It's, um, glass half full.
Bambi, don't say another word till after the hunter shoots your mother.
I don't like you.
I have a B.A.
from Smith, a Ph.D.
from Berkeley, and an M.D.
from Stanford, and I'm delivering lab results.
It's gonna take me all day to get through these.
Then get started.
Oh, I wasn't complaining.
I don't complain.
Intern was reassigned, so he's mine now.
Have him shadow you for the day.
You show him how I do things.
Alex Kreb.
Nice to meet you.
The figure who called Meredith a nurse.
Yeah.
I hate you on principle.
And you're the pushy, overbearing kiss-ass.
I, uh, I hate you too.
Oh, it should be fun then.
I'm Dr. O'Malley.
I'll be running this code.
What do we got?
We have a 57-year-old male.
See you, sisterly.
We're charging you 200, please.
We're charged.
Cleared.
All right, Mrs. Liu, I'm Dr. Stevens.
I'm gonna sew up your wound.
You're gonna need, yeah, about six stitches.
Are you allergic to any medication?
Oh, I'm sorry, I don't, I don't, um... Do you speak English?
I'll find, um... Does anybody here speak Chinese?
Hi.
Is the chief in?
He's on his way.
Is that it?
Yeah.
Can I see it?
No.
Forget I asked.
Meredith, it's good to see you.
Hey, I heard your mother was leaving the mail.
She going back with the UN?
She's taking time off.
Writing another book, I suppose.
Listen, so they said to bring this to you, so?
Yes, for the police.
Right.
When did the police say they were coming?
You know how slow they are, so she'd better take it with her.
What?
You have to take it with you.
Chain of custody rules.
All medical matter in a rape must stay with the person who collected it until it's placed into police custody.
You collected the specimen, so you have custody.
Custody of a penis?
Yes, until the cops come for it.
OK.
Well, what am I supposed to do with a penis?
You have a disorder called multinucleic cell angio-histiocytoma.
It's not a cancer or sarcoma.
It's a very rare but minor.
You'll be discharged today, OK?
I don't need a surgery?
No.
I'm not going to die.
I'm fine.
Fit as a fiddle or whatever.
What's that?
Don't ask.
You don't want to know.
I do want to know.
Really.
You really want to know?
It's a severed penis.
OK.
Well, I didn't really want to know.
Why do I have to be the one who gets hugged?
Because I don't do that.
Besides, you're the ovarian sister here.
Did you just call me an ovarian?
An ovarian?
Because when does that possession of ovaries become an insult?
Married is carrying a penis around in a jar.
Oh, from the rape surgery?
Yeah, and it's not a jar.
It's a cooler.
Talk about taking a bite out of crime.
You OK?
Yeah.
Allison's shoes are.
What?
The rape victim, Allison, her shoes.
I have the same ones in my locker.
And I normally never wear them because they're not comfortable.
But today I did.
And she was wearing the same shoes.
And it's just stupid.
And I'm tired.
And forget it.
You know what you need?
No.
It's sick and twisted.
We said last time was the last time.
You've been doing it without me?
Nancy Reagan lied.
You can't just say no.
Come on.
Do you know what would happen if anyone knew?
I'm doing it.
You can come with me, or you can stay here and be miserable.
You are such a woman.
That's a code.
Yeah, I got it.
You are really cute.
What are you doing in here?
The, uh, there were no tests ordered, and the baby has a murmur.
I know.
He turned blue.
Your surgery, you're not authorized to be in here.
Do you know how much trouble you can get into for this?
Are you going to do any tests?
It's a benign systolic ejection murmur.
It goes away with age.
So you're not going to do tests?
He's not your patient.
He's not even on your service.
Are you sure it's benign?
I'm a doctor, too, you know.
You should get out of here.
Dr. Palmer, agent of the pharmacy.
You get a good kiss?
No, her.
She won't let me sew her up.
I wouldn't have called you, but I can't get hold of the translator.
Can you just ask her what's wrong?
No.
Why not?
Because I grew up in Beverly Hills.
The only Chinese I know is from a Mr. Chow's menu.
Besides, I'm Korean.
Chief, so you asked Shepherd to come to Grace?
He's an old student of mine.
Oh.
Well, he left a Manhattan private practice because you asked.
Yes.
No other reason?
Just a favor for an old professor?
It'll be years before I retire.
Chief, the surgery is mine.
It was yours.
Now I'm not so sure.
I am the best surgeon at Grace with the lowest mortality rate.
You can't just bring some guy here for me.
Now ask me why I'm not so sure about you.
Ask me what?
OB nurse to labor and delivery.
Available over the doorstep.
Don't people get sick anymore?
I mean, how are we supposed to get any of our time if everyone's gonna just live?
Look, I'll take ten, you take ten.
Get in, get out.
No smiling, no hugging, no letting them cry.
Just be quick about it.
You're the one that's slow.
I am not slow.
You are slow.
You want to bet?
Yeah, you are.
A comprehensive workup.
Did not reveal any vascular abnormalities.
Your Doppler was negative.
For deep venous thrombosis, so there's no need for chronic anticoagulation or an IBC filter.
Your biopsy was, however, positive.
For a mixed anaerobics.
Non-group-based streptococci infection.
Your BUN and creatinine elevations had us worried.
About rapidly progressive glomerulonephritis.
Which could have signaled an autoimmune disease.
What does that mean?
We're not going to amputate your leg.
Huh?
You get to keep your kidneys.
Congratulations.
You can go home today.
Yeah, yeah.
Congratulations.
Whatever.
There's nothing wrong with you.
You're going to be fine.
Congratulations.
What's your favorite age group?
Queen.
No.
Twisted Sister.
Oh.
Not like there's a right or wrong answer to that question.
Yeah, the Go-Go's, Duran Duran, Eurythmics.
Have a nice day.
You can go home today.
Time of death, 1545.
Remember, call every hospital in the county.
Sooner or later, the guy that did this is gonna seek medical attention, and when he does, that penis you're carrying around's gonna nail it.
Where is her family?
Doesn't have any.
No siblings?
No.
Both parents are dead.
She just moved to Seattle three weeks ago.
Welcome to the city.
Meredith, you OK?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I just have to do something.
I have to go.
All right, I'm going to sit with her.
Dr. Burke, there's a baby up in Peds.
I saw him have his head fell, and I think I hear a murmur.
Did Peds call us for a consult?
Actually, no.
They're not doing anything about it.
So you want me to what?
If you could just go up and look at him.
Not without a Peds consultant.
I'm a busy man, Gray, and there are rules.
Look, it's not like I'm the chief or something.
Dr. Palmer, page the box.
You're hot.
You're drunk.
Hold still.
Wait, you're that girl from the magazine, that red bikini?
Yeah, it was Pink.
I'm done.
You can see the nurse outside now.
Is she crazy or something?
No, I don't think so.
Okay.
Please, please sit down.
I really need to look at your arm.
Okay.
When I left her, she was very young.
It wasn't a good place, but we got the money.
What are you doing down here?
Just sitting here with my penis.
What about you?
Hiding from Alex.
I kissed Eric.
You kissed Eric?
In the elevator.
Well, you kissed him in the elevator.
I was having a bad day.
I am having a bad day.
So what do you do on your bad days?
Make out with Dr. McDreamy?
You know, that and carrying around a penis just makes everything seem so shiny and happy.
George said Allison was wearing your shoes.
Yeah.
It's weird, right?
It's weird that you care.
I think it's weird.
Can I have security, please?
What do we got?
Take a look.
Let's get them to OR1.
Meredith, you call the chief and let him know we got the rapist.
I saw Allison.
You can't believe the beating that she took.
And then to see this.
It's like that old saying, you should see the other guy.
Why are we not attempting to reattach the severed penis?
Teeth don't slice, they tear.
You can only reattach with a clean cut.
She wanted to slice him off with a knife.
Besides, the digestive juices didn't leave much of the flesh to work with.
Right.
So what do we do?
Sew him up minus a large part of the family jewels.
And his outlook?
He'll be urinating out of a bag for a very, very long time.
Not to mention he'll never be able to have sex again.
Oh, too bad.
Shane.
Let's all take a moment to grieve.
Clamp.
Richard.
We got the rapist.
He stumbled right into the hospital.
Yeah, I heard.
Listen, Bert.
Why?
You really want to know?
I want to know when you stop thinking of me as your number one.
Richard, I do more in this hospital than any other surgeon you have.
You do only exactly as much as is necessary.
You never take an extra step.
You never give an extra minute.
You're comfortable and arrogant, and it doesn't impress me.
You want to be chief?
Earn it.
I'm sorry.
I have patients lined up.
I don't have time.
I don't understand you.
I'm sorry.
Dr. Bailey to ortho staff.
My head hurts.
Maybe it's a tumor.
You wish I had a tumor.
Look, I'd rip your face off if it meant I got to scrub in.
I've been suturing all day.
My hands are numb.
At least you're helping people.
At least you get to practice freaking medicine.
I had to send my Chinese lady away.
She was, like, camped out down there.
Oh, poor Izzy, turning away a patient.
Boo hoo.
So the police say they can't send a crime scene guy down for hours.
So I have to spend the night with a penis.
Alex, don't say it.
Oh, it's too easy anyway.
Who here feels like they have no idea what they're doing?
I mean, are we supposed to be learning something?
Because I don't feel like I'm learning anything.
Except how not to sleep.
You know, it's like there's this wall, and the attendings and the residents are over there being surgeons, and we're over here being... Suturing, code running, lab delivering, penis minders.
I hate being an intern.
Hi.
Is he yours?
Yeah.
He's adorable.
Thanks.
Oh, please.
You are so out of line.
She says the murmur might not be benign.
I think we should do an echo to check.
This is your career.
There really is no reason to get along.
What's the problem?
If our baby is sick, we want him treated now.
Who said your baby was sick?
Her, the surgical intern who has no business on our service.
Who authorized you being here?
I was just actually... Hey, dude.
Could you excuse me for a second?
Are you messing with my intern, Dr. K?
No, sir.
Give me the check.
There's nothing wrong with him.
I checked.
Are you sure?
Yes.
You can guarantee that he's fine.
You're 100% sure.
How sure are you?
I don't know, 75%.
Not good enough.
He's my patient now.
That okay with you, Dr. K?
Absolutely.
We can take our patient.
He's an attending.
Which means I can do whatever I want.
Mr. and Mrs. Johnson, I'm Dr. Burke, head of cardio.
We're going to run some tests and get you an answer within the hour.
Great.
Excuse me.
I want an EKG, chest x-ray, and an echo.
I don't have all day.
You're a busy man.
I'm a busy man.
Anybody else?
No.
No more.
Then I need a bed.
Ms.
Liu?
Dr. Cutlin, thoracic surgery.
Dr. Frank Cutlin, thoracic surgery.
Ms.
Liu!
Liu, wait!
Ms.
Liu!
What is it?
It's okay.
I'll help.
It's deep.
I need to clean it out.
Clean it.
Machine is broken in the factory.
It's gone.
Can you speak English?
Just, if you could come inside.
No, no, not inside.
No, no, no.
Jail.
Jail?
She came inside.
No.
She been caught.
Me, no.
You're illegal.
That's okay.
We don't have to tell them that.
I just need to get you inside.
I have to sew that up.
No, no inside.
Please, I promise.
I promise you won't go to jail.
It's raining.
Please, come inside.
Okay, okay, okay.
Not inside.
Wait here, okay?
Wait.
I'll come back.
I'll be back.
Well?
It's a birth defect.
Tetralogy of a lower pulmonary atresia.
You were right.
Book an OR for tomorrow.
Thank you for backing me up on this.
No, no, no, wait.
You were right.
But if you ever pull a stunt like that again, going to the parents behind a doctor's back, trying to steal a patient from another service, I will make your residency here hell on earth.
I came home in the morning and everything was gone.
Oh, what have I done?
I dropped dead in the hallway, cursing the dawn.
Oh, come on, son, why must I burn?
I'm just trying to learn.
Okay, you're all sewn up.
That's pretty good.
I could have done a better job if I'd had more light.
You might have a scar.
It's good.
You're gonna need to come back in five days, okay?
I'm gonna need to check the wound and remove the stitches, okay?
Here's my pager number on this card.
Right here.
Okay?
We'll meet right back here.
You have to come back.
But you can't tell anybody that I helped you outside of the hospital or I might lose my job.
Understand?
Yes.
Come back and don't tell.
Okay.
That's it.
I'm done.
You can go.
I'll see you in five days.
Yes, Eel.
She is my only family here.
You are a good person and a good doctor.
Thank you.
Do you think I'm too confident?
No.
Don't lie.
You are my boss.
All right, then.
Anything you say in the next 30 seconds is free, starting now.
I think you're cocky.
Arrogant, bossy, and pushy.
You also have a God complex.
You never think about anybody but your damn self.
But I... But what?
I still have 22 more seconds.
I'm not done.
I need a drink, a man, or a massage.
I've already drunk a massage by a man.
What's wrong with you?
I lost five patients on the code team today.
I feel like the angel of death.
George, 95% of all code patients can't be revived.
Most of them are seriously dead before you can get there.
What?
Why didn't you tell me that when I was going on and on about how great it was gonna be?
Because.
His heart surgery is scheduled for the morning.
I really did think I was right, you know?
I know.
We almost never are.
We're interns.
We're not supposed to be right.
And when we are, it's completely shocking.
Are you... I mean, being an intern, do you feel...
Terrified, 100% of the time.
Good.
It's not just me.
No.
How is she?
No change.
Have you been here all night?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
You know I have four sisters?
Very girly, tons of kids.
If I was in a coma, they'd all be here.
I'd want them here.
Not having no one?
Can't imagine that.
I can.
What are you talking about?
What about your mother?
She'd be here ordering all the surgeons around.
She'd fly these cowboys in from Prague to do these amazing medical procedures.
That's true.
I do have my mother.
So we're kissing, but we're not dating?
I knew that was gonna come up.
Don't get me wrong, I like the kissing.
I'm all for the kissing.
Or kissing, I say.
I have no idea what that was about.
It's gonna happen again, because if it is, I need to bring breath mints.
But I can't in a moment.
Shut up now.
There's this baby up in the nursery.
He's brand new.
No one's neglected him or damaged him yet.
How did we get from there to here?
She's wearing my shoes, and someone's beat the crap out of her.
And she's got nobody.
Your ICP's double.
Get O.R.
Perfect for craniotomy.
Let's hang a medical.
Uh, take a blood gas.
Dr. Cutler to thoracic surgery.
Dr. Frank Cutler to thoracic surgery.
I, uh...
Had to leave her skull flap off until the pressure in her brain goes down.
She's not going to make it, is she?
She's going to be fine.
If she ever wakes up.
Dr. Burke, I'm off at 6.
Want to get that drink we talked about?
I don't think so.
Well, what about tomorrow night?
Shepard, you should know that Richard promised Chief to both of us.
But you knew that already.
Keep your friends close and your enemies closer.
You're not the enemy.
You're just a competition.
So here is where you have the signature, and down here, the initials.
It just says that the, um, the... Penis.
I'm a doctor.
I mean, it shouldn't be weird to say this.
It's just that I used to change her diapers.
I get it.
It just says that it was never on his side.
There you go.
It wasn't a penis.
Officer.
We'll be using a median approach for a transventricular repair with a right ventriculotomy.
Let's open him up.
Moki, 15 blade, please.
Gray.
Yes, sir.
Go scrub in.
When we're finished cracking the baby's chest, I'll let you hold the clamp.
Seriously?
Don't make me change my mind.
I'm going.
Good news and bad news.
The good news is Dr. Bailey stops your bleeding.
The bad news is we're giving your penis to the cops.
Have a nice life.
The results of your labs are clean.
The tumor is benign.
You can go home today.
At some point, you have to make a decision.
Boundaries don't keep other people out.
They fence you in.
Life is messy.
That's how we're made.
Okay, fine, George and Izzy, you can move into the house.
Yes!
I can't believe it!
Thank you.
Yes!
I can't believe I caved.
I blame the babies.
They make you toxic.
So, you can waste your life drawing lines,
Or you can live your life crossing them.
Welcome back.
But there are some lines... So... It's intense.
This thing I have for fairy boats, I mean.
...that are way too dangerous to cross.
I'm so taking the stairs this time.
No self-control.
It's sad.
Really.
Here's what I know.
If you're willing to take the chance, the view from the other side is spectacular.