Narrator (Meredith Grey) / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Previously on Grey's Anatomy.
Dr. Richard Webber / Dr. Richard Webber (PVM): The seven years you spend here as a surgical resident will be the best and worst of your life.
Dr. Richard Webber / Dr. Richard Webber (PVM): You will be pushed to the breaking point.
Dr. Richard Webber / Dr. Richard Webber (PVM): Eight of you will switch to an easier specialty.
Dr. Richard Webber / Dr. Richard Webber (PVM): Five of you will crack under the pressure.
Dr. Richard Webber / Dr. Richard Webber (PVM): Two of you will be asked to leave.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Dr. Shepherd, we should pretend it never happened.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: What never happened?
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): You sleeping with me last night?
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Or are you throwing me out this morning?
Meredith Grey: You're an attending, and I'm your intern.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Stop looking at me like that.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: Like what?
Meredith Grey: Like you've seen me naked.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Your first shift starts now and lasts 48 hours.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You're interns, grunts, nobodies, bottom of the surgical food chain.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): What are you doing here?
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Preston Burke OR Patient (PVM): You and I are going to have so much fun together.
Alex Karev / Meredith Grey (PVM): You know Meredith is inbred?
Cristina Yang / Patient OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Like it's uncommon around here to be a doctor's parent.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR Patient (PVM): No, royally inbred.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Her mother is Alice Gray.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): Shut up, the Alice Gray.
Alex Karev / Meredith Grey (PVM): She's a living ledger.
Ellis Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): What's your name?
Meredith Grey: It's me, Mom.
Meredith Grey: Meredith.
Ellis Grey / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): All right.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): We're gonna survive this, right?
Meredith Grey: It's all about lines.
Meredith Grey: The finish line at the end of residency...
Meredith Grey: Waiting in line for a chance at the operating table.
Meredith Grey: And then there's the most important line.
Meredith Grey: A line separating you from the people you work with.
Meredith Grey: It doesn't help to get too familiar.
Meredith Grey: To make friends.
Meredith Grey: You need boundaries between you and the rest of the world.
Meredith Grey: Other people are far too messy.
Meredith Grey: It's all about lines.
Meredith Grey: Drawing lines in the sand.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): And praying like hell no one crosses them.
Meredith Grey: Look, I'm sure you're very nice, but I'm very particular about who lives in my house and you're just not right.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Why?
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Look, I'm quiet.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): No loud music, no parties.
Meredith Grey: Where were you when the Challenger exploded?
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): The what?
Meredith Grey: The space shuttle.
Meredith Grey: Challenger.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Uh, I think I was in kindergarten.
Meredith Grey: Exactly.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey OR Alex Kreb (PVM): No.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Why do you put up posters for roommates if you don't want roommates?
Meredith Grey: I do want roommates.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): We're together 100 hours a week.
Meredith Grey: You want to live together, too?
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, yeah.
Meredith Grey: See, you bring bribes down, huh?
Izzie Stevens / Patient OR Meredith Grey (PVM): I need a place to live.
George O'Malley: My mom irons my scrubs.
Meredith Grey / Patient (PVM): I have to get out of there.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): It's not a bribe.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey OR Patient (PVM): I don't think it's a good idea.
Izzie Stevens / Patient OR Meredith Grey (PVM): I can put down last, first, and deposit.
Meredith Grey / Patient OR Meredith Grey (PVM): It's totally a bribe.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I can cook.
George O'Malley / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): And I'm an obsessive cleaner.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey OR Alex Kreb (PVM): No.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): I just want two total strangers who I don't have to talk to or be nice to.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): And it's not a bribe.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): It's a mocha latte.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: George, you're running the code team.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Meredith, take the trauma pager.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Christina, deliver the weekend labs to the patients.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Izzy, you're on sutures.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Dr. Bailey, I was hoping to assist you in the OR today, maybe do a minor procedure.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): I think I'm ready.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Mocha latte?
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): If she gets a cut, I want a cut too.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey OR George O'Malley (PVM): Yeah, me too.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey OR George O'Malley (PVM): I wouldn't mind another shot.
George O'Malley / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Meredith Grey OR George O'Malley (PVM): I mean, if everybody else is.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR George O'Malley (PVM): Stop talking.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Every intern wants to perform their first surgery.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: That's not your job.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Do you know what your job is?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): To make your resident happy.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Do I look happy?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey OR Alex Kreb (PVM): No.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Why?
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Because my interns are whiny.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: You know what will make me look happy?
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Having the code team staffed, having the trauma pages answered, having the weekend labs delivered, and having someone down in the pit doing the sutures.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: No one holds a scalpel till I'm so happy I'm Mary freakin' Poppins.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Mogulotting my ass.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Why are you all standing there?
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Move!
Meredith Grey / Hospital Intercom OR Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Seattle has ferry boats.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Yes.
Cristina Yang / Hospital Intercom (PVM): I didn't know that.
Meredith Grey / Hospital Intercom (PVM): I've been living here six weeks.
Meredith Grey / Hospital Intercom (PVM): I didn't know there were ferry boats.
Derek Shepherd / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Seattle is surrounded by water on three sides.
Derek Shepherd / Hospital Intercom (PVM): Hence the fairy boats.
Meredith Grey / Hospital Intercom (PVM): Now I have to like it here.
Meredith Grey / Hospital Intercom (PVM): I wasn't planning on liking it here.
Cristina Yang / Hospital Intercom (PVM): I'm from New York.
Cristina Yang / Hospital Intercom (PVM): Genetically engineered to dislike everywhere, except Manhattan.
Derek Shepherd / Hospital Intercom (PVM): I have a thing for fairy boats.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm not going out with you.
Derek Shepherd / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Did I ask you to go out with me?
Derek Shepherd / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Do you want to go out with me?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm not dating you, and I'm definitely not sleeping with you again.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Meredith Grey (PVM): You're my boss.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Meredith Grey OR Alex Kreb (PVM): I'm your boss's boss.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): You're my teacher, and my teacher's teacher, and you're my teacher.
Unknown / Hospital Intercom (PVM): I'm your sister.
Unknown / Hospital Intercom (PVM): I'm your daughter.
Meredith Grey / Hospital Intercom OR Meredith Grey (PVM): You're sexually harassing me.
Meredith Grey / Hospital Intercom OR Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm riding an elevator.
Alex Karev / Meredith Grey (PVM): Look, I'm drawing a line.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): The line is drawn.
Izzie Stevens / Alex Kreb OR Meredith Grey (PVM): There's a big line.
George O'Malley / Hospital Intercom OR Alex Kreb (PVM): So this line, is it imaginary, or do I need to get you a marker?
Miranda Bailey / Hospital Intercom (PVM): We'll talk later.
Nurse / Hospital Intercom OR Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): You the surgeon?
Derek Shepherd / Alex Kreb (PVM): Yeah.
Nurse / Hospital Intercom OR Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): We've got a rape victim.
Nurse / Hospital Intercom OR Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): You better get in there.
Nurse / Hospital Intercom OR George O'Malley OR Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): 25-year-old female found down at the park, status post-trauma.
Nurse / George O'Malley OR Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): She came in with a GCS of 6, BP 80 over 60.
Nurse / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Exam is significant for blood head trauma, unequal breath sounds, right pupil is dilated, and she's ready for x-ray.
Derek Shepherd / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): You ready to roll?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Hey.
Derek Shepherd / Alex Kreb (PVM): Yeah.
Derek Shepherd / Meredith Grey (PVM): Call ahead to clear CT.
Derek Shepherd / Meredith Grey (PVM): Let them know I'm coming.
Derek Shepherd / Patient OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Load up the portable monitor.
Derek Shepherd / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Call respiratory for a ventilator.
Derek Shepherd / Meredith Grey (PVM): I'll get x-rays while I'm down there.
Cristina Yang / Hospital Intercom OR Alex Kreb (PVM): She's going to spend a hell of a long time in recovery and rehab.
George O'Malley / Alex Kreb (PVM): She survives.
Alex Karev / Hospital Intercom OR Alex Kreb (PVM): What is she, like 5'2", 100 pounds?
Alex Karev / Alex Kreb (PVM): She's still breathing after what this guy did to her?
George O'Malley / Alex Kreb (PVM): Catch the guy?
Cristina Yang / Alex Kreb OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): They should castrate him.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): See how shitty her hands are?
George O'Malley / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): She tried to fight back.
Alex Karev / Alex Kreb OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Tried to?
Cristina Yang / Alex Kreb (PVM): Rape kid came back negative.
Alex Karev / Alex Kreb (PVM): She kicked his ass.
George O'Malley / Alex Kreb OR Dr. Preston Burke OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, so we have a warrior among us, huh?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Allison.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Her name is Allison.
George O'Malley / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Allison.
Alex Karev / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): I think I've met her.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): on the cause of our rupture.
George O'Malley / Hospital Intercom OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): What is this?
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Does anyone know what this is?
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, my god.
Unknown / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): What?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Spit it out, Gray.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): She bit it off.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Bit off what?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): That's his penis.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Cutlin OR Meredith Grey (PVM): She bit off his penis.
Cristina Yang / Hospital PA System OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Ouch.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Cutlin OR Dr. Preston Burke OR Meredith Grey OR Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): If she can fight the infection, she'll be fine.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): It's all gonna depend on whether or not she wakes up in the next 72 hours.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Yeah, we should get a drink later and tell me the long story of what makes a hot shot doc leave the Big Apple for Seattle.
Addison Montgomery / Alex Kreb (PVM): It's a short story, actually.
Addison Montgomery / Alex Kreb (PVM): Your chief of surgery made me an offer I couldn't refuse.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Richard asked you to come?
Addison Montgomery / Alex Kreb (PVM): Yeah.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Why?
Addison Montgomery / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Oh, nothing.
Addison Montgomery / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): See you later.
Miranda Bailey / George O'Malley (PVM): Do you know what the code team does?
George O'Malley / George O'Malley (PVM): Saves lives.
Miranda Bailey / George O'Malley (PVM): Eyes shock a heart, and someone lives to see another day.
Unknown (possibly Cristina Yang or Alex Karev) / George O'Malley (PVM): That's upbeat.
Unknown (possibly George O'Malley) / Meredith Grey OR George O'Malley (PVM): It's, um, glass half full.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR George O'Malley (PVM): Bambi, don't say another word till after the hunter shoots your mother.
Unknown (possibly George O'Malley) / Meredith Grey OR George O'Malley (PVM): I don't like you.
Unknown (possibly Miranda Bailey) / Meredith Grey (PVM): I have a B.A.
Unknown (possibly Miranda Bailey) / Meredith Grey (PVM): from Smith, a Ph.D.
Unknown (possibly Miranda Bailey) / Meredith Grey (PVM): from Berkeley, and an M.D.
Unknown (possibly Miranda Bailey) / Meredith Grey (PVM): from Stanford, and I'm delivering lab results.
Unknown (possibly Miranda Bailey) / Meredith Grey (PVM): It's gonna take me all day to get through these.
Unknown (possibly Miranda Bailey's superior or attending) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Then get started.
Unknown (possibly Miranda Bailey) / Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, I wasn't complaining.
Unknown (possibly Miranda Bailey) / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): I don't complain.
Unknown (possibly Miranda Bailey) / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Intern was reassigned, so he's mine now.
Unknown (possibly Miranda Bailey's superior or attending) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Have him shadow you for the day.
Unknown (possibly Miranda Bailey's superior or attending) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You show him how I do things.
Alex Kreb: Alex Kreb.
Alex Kreb: Nice to meet you.
Unknown (possibly Miranda Bailey or Cristina Yang) / Meredith Grey (PVM): The figure who called Meredith a nurse.
Alex Kreb: Yeah.
Unknown (possibly Meredith Grey or Cristina Yang) / Alex Kreb OR Meredith Grey (PVM): I hate you on principle.
Cristina Yang / Alex Kreb (PVM): And you're the pushy, overbearing kiss-ass.
Izzie Stevens / Alex Kreb (PVM): I, uh, I hate you too.
Cristina Yang / Hospital PA System OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, it should be fun then.
George O'Malley: I'm Dr. O'Malley.
George O'Malley: I'll be running this code.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): What do we got?
Nurse / Patient (PVM): We have a 57-year-old male.
Cristina Yang / Patient (PVM): See you, sisterly.
Code Team Member / Dr. Cutlin OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): We're charging you 200, please.
Code Team Member / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): We're charged.
Code Team Member / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Cleared.
Dr. Izzie Stevens: All right, Mrs. Liu, I'm Dr. Stevens.
Dr. Izzie Stevens: I'm gonna sew up your wound.
Dr. Izzie Stevens: You're gonna need, yeah, about six stitches.
Dr. Izzie Stevens: Are you allergic to any medication?
Dr. Izzie Stevens: Oh, I'm sorry, I don't, I don't, um... Do you speak English?
Dr. Izzie Stevens: I'll find, um... Does anybody here speak Chinese?
Unknown / Meredith Grey (PVM): Hi.
Unknown / Meredith Grey (PVM): Is the chief in?
Unknown / Meredith Grey (PVM): He's on his way.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Is that it?
Meredith Grey / Alex Kreb (PVM): Yeah.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Can I see it?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey OR Alex Kreb (PVM): No.
Izzie Stevens / Doctor (PVM): Forget I asked.
Izzie Stevens / Doctor (PVM): Meredith, it's good to see you.
Cristina Yang / Doctor (PVM): Hey, I heard your mother was leaving the mail.
Cristina Yang / Doctor (PVM): She going back with the UN?
Meredith Grey / Doctor OR Meredith Grey (PVM): She's taking time off.
Cristina Yang / Doctor (PVM): Writing another book, I suppose.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Listen, so they said to bring this to you, so?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Doctor (PVM): Yes, for the police.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Right.
Cristina Yang / Doctor (PVM): When did the police say they were coming?
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): You know how slow they are, so she'd better take it with her.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): What?
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): You have to take it with you.
Cristina Yang / Doctor (PVM): Chain of custody rules.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR Doctor (PVM): All medical matter in a rape must stay with the person who collected it until it's placed into police custody.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): You collected the specimen, so you have custody.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Custody of a penis?
Meredith Grey / Doctor OR Dr. Richard Webber (PVM): Yes, until the cops come for it.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): OK.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): Well, what am I supposed to do with a penis?
Doctor (possibly Meredith Grey) / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): You have a disorder called multinucleic cell angio-histiocytoma.
Doctor (possibly Meredith Grey) / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Meredith Grey (PVM): It's not a cancer or sarcoma.
Doctor (possibly Meredith Grey) / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Meredith Grey (PVM): It's a very rare but minor.
Doctor (possibly Meredith Grey) / Meredith Grey (PVM): You'll be discharged today, OK?
Patient: I don't need a surgery?
Doctor (possibly Meredith Grey) / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey OR Alex Kreb (PVM): No.
Patient: I'm not going to die.
Patient: I'm fine.
Patient: Fit as a fiddle or whatever.
Cristina Yang / Hospital Intercom OR Meredith Grey (PVM): What's that?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Don't ask.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): You don't want to know.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): I do want to know.
Cristina Yang / Hospital Intercom (PVM): Really.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Richard Webber (PVM): You really want to know?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): It's a severed penis.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): OK.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Well, I didn't really want to know.
Cristina Yang / Alex Kreb OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Why do I have to be the one who gets hugged?
Meredith Grey / Alex Kreb (PVM): Because I don't do that.
Meredith Grey / Alex Kreb (PVM): Besides, you're the ovarian sister here.
Cristina Yang / Alex Kreb OR Hospital Intercom (PVM): Did you just call me an ovarian?
Meredith Grey / Hospital Intercom OR Meredith Grey (PVM): An ovarian?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Because when does that possession of ovaries become an insult?
Cristina Yang / George O'Malley (PVM): Married is carrying a penis around in a jar.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, from the rape surgery?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Yeah, and it's not a jar.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): It's a cooler.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Talk about taking a bite out of crime.
Meredith Grey / George O'Malley (PVM): You OK?
Cristina Yang / Alex Kreb (PVM): Yeah.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Allison's shoes are.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): What?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): The rape victim, Allison, her shoes.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): I have the same ones in my locker.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): And I normally never wear them because they're not comfortable.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): But today I did.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): And she was wearing the same shoes.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): And it's just stupid.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): And I'm tired.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): And forget it.
Cristina Yang / Patient (PVM): You know what you need?
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey OR Alex Kreb (PVM): No.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): It's sick and twisted.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): We said last time was the last time.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): You've been doing it without me?
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Nancy Reagan lied.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): You can't just say no.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Come on.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Do you know what would happen if anyone knew?
Cristina Yang / Patient (PVM): I'm doing it.
Cristina Yang / Patient (PVM): You can come with me, or you can stay here and be miserable.
Cristina Yang / George O'Malley (PVM): You are such a woman.
Izzie Stevens / George O'Malley (PVM): That's a code.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR George O'Malley (PVM): Yeah, I got it.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey OR George O'Malley (PVM): You are really cute.
Attending Doctor / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): What are you doing in here?
Younger Doctor / Meredith Grey (PVM): The, uh, there were no tests ordered, and the baby has a murmur.
Attending Doctor / Meredith Grey (PVM): I know.
Younger Doctor / Meredith Grey (PVM): He turned blue.
Attending Doctor / Meredith Grey (PVM): Your surgery, you're not authorized to be in here.
Attending Doctor / Meredith Grey (PVM): Do you know how much trouble you can get into for this?
Younger Doctor / Meredith Grey (PVM): Are you going to do any tests?
Attending Doctor / Meredith Grey (PVM): It's a benign systolic ejection murmur.
Attending Doctor / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Cutlin OR Meredith Grey (PVM): It goes away with age.
Younger Doctor / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): So you're not going to do tests?
Attending Doctor / Meredith Grey (PVM): He's not your patient.
Attending Doctor / Meredith Grey (PVM): He's not even on your service.
Younger Doctor / Meredith Grey (PVM): Are you sure it's benign?
Younger Doctor / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Cutlin (PVM): I'm a doctor, too, you know.
Attending Doctor / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Cutlin (PVM): You should get out of here.
Dr. Palmer: Dr. Palmer, agent of the pharmacy.
Unknown Doctor / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): You get a good kiss?
Unknown Doctor / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): No, her.
Unknown Doctor / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): She won't let me sew her up.
Unknown Doctor / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I wouldn't have called you, but I can't get hold of the translator.
Alex Karev / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Can you just ask her what's wrong?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey OR Alex Kreb (PVM): No.
Alex Karev / Meredith Grey (PVM): Why not?
Dr. Cristina Yang: Because I grew up in Beverly Hills.
Dr. Cristina Yang: The only Chinese I know is from a Mr. Chow's menu.
Dr. Cristina Yang: Besides, I'm Korean.
Preston Burke / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Chief, so you asked Shepherd to come to Grace?
Dr. Richard Webber: He's an old student of mine.
Preston Burke / Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh.
Preston Burke / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Well, he left a Manhattan private practice because you asked.
Dr. Richard Webber: Yes.
Preston Burke / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): No other reason?
Preston Burke / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Just a favor for an old professor?
Dr. Richard Webber: It'll be years before I retire.
Preston Burke / Dr. Richard Webber OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Chief, the surgery is mine.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Richard Webber OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Chief, the surgery is mine.
Dr. Richard Webber: It was yours.
Dr. Richard Webber: Now I'm not so sure.
Dr. Preston Burke: I am the best surgeon at Grace with the lowest mortality rate.
Dr. Preston Burke: You can't just bring some guy here for me.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke OR Doctor (PVM): Now ask me why I'm not so sure about you.
Alex Karev / Hospital Intercom OR Doctor (PVM): Ask me what?
Hospital Intercom: OB nurse to labor and delivery.
Hospital Intercom: Available over the doorstep.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Don't people get sick anymore?
Cristina Yang / Alex Kreb OR Meredith Grey (PVM): I mean, how are we supposed to get any of our time if everyone's gonna just live?
Alex Karev / Meredith Grey (PVM): Look, I'll take ten, you take ten.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Get in, get out.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): No smiling, no hugging, no letting them cry.
Alex Karev / Meredith Grey (PVM): Just be quick about it.
Cristina Yang / Alex Kreb OR Meredith Grey (PVM): You're the one that's slow.
Alex Karev / Meredith Grey (PVM): I am not slow.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): You are slow.
Alex Karev / Meredith Grey (PVM): You want to bet?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Yeah, you are.
Cristina Yang / Alex Kreb OR Meredith Grey (PVM): A comprehensive workup.
Cristina Yang / Alex Kreb OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Did not reveal any vascular abnormalities.
Alex Karev / Meredith Grey (PVM): Your Doppler was negative.
Alex Karev / Alex Kreb OR Meredith Grey (PVM): For deep venous thrombosis, so there's no need for chronic anticoagulation or an IBC filter.
Cristina Yang / Alex Kreb (PVM): Your biopsy was, however, positive.
Izzie Stevens / Alex Kreb OR Meredith Grey (PVM): For a mixed anaerobics.
Izzie Stevens / Alex Kreb (PVM): Non-group-based streptococci infection.
Izzie Stevens / Alex Kreb OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Your BUN and creatinine elevations had us worried.
Izzie Stevens / Alex Kreb OR Meredith Grey (PVM): About rapidly progressive glomerulonephritis.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Which could have signaled an autoimmune disease.
Patient (possibly Mrs. Liu) / Meredith Grey (PVM): What does that mean?
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): We're not going to amputate your leg.
Patient (possibly Mrs. Liu) / Alex Kreb OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Huh?
Izzie Stevens / Alex Kreb (PVM): You get to keep your kidneys.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Congratulations.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Cutlin OR Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): You can go home today.
Patient (possibly Mrs. Liu) / Alex Kreb (PVM): Yeah, yeah.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Congratulations.
Patient (possibly Mrs. Liu) / Alex Kreb (PVM): Whatever.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): There's nothing wrong with you.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): You're going to be fine.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Congratulations.
Patient (possibly Mrs. Liu) / Meredith Grey (PVM): What's your favorite age group?
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Queen.
Unknown / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey OR Alex Kreb (PVM): No.
Unknown / Meredith Grey (PVM): Twisted Sister.
Unknown / Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh.
Unknown / Meredith Grey (PVM): Not like there's a right or wrong answer to that question.
Unknown / Meredith Grey (PVM): Yeah, the Go-Go's, Duran Duran, Eurythmics.
Unknown / Meredith Grey (PVM): Have a nice day.
Unknown / Dr. Cutlin OR Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): You can go home today.
Unknown / Alex Kreb OR Meredith Grey OR Patient (PVM): Time of death, 1545.
Unknown / Hospital Intercom OR Dr. Cutlin OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Remember, call every hospital in the county.
Unknown / Hospital Intercom (PVM): Sooner or later, the guy that did this is gonna seek medical attention, and when he does, that penis you're carrying around's gonna nail it.
Unknown / Meredith Grey (PVM): Where is her family?
Unknown / Hospital Intercom (PVM): Doesn't have any.
Unknown / Meredith Grey (PVM): No siblings?
Unknown / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey OR Alex Kreb (PVM): No.
Unknown / Hospital Intercom (PVM): Both parents are dead.
Unknown / Hospital Intercom (PVM): She just moved to Seattle three weeks ago.
Unknown / Hospital Intercom (PVM): Welcome to the city.
Izzie Stevens / Hospital Intercom (PVM): Meredith, you OK?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Yeah, I'm fine.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): I just have to do something.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): I have to go.
Cristina Yang / Hospital Intercom OR Meredith Grey (PVM): All right, I'm going to sit with her.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Preston Burke OR Hospital Intercom OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Dr. Burke, there's a baby up in Peds.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): I saw him have his head fell, and I think I hear a murmur.
Dr. Preston Burke: Did Peds call us for a consult?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Actually, no.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Preston Burke OR Meredith Grey (PVM): They're not doing anything about it.
Dr. Preston Burke: So you want me to what?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): If you could just go up and look at him.
Dr. Preston Burke: Not without a Peds consultant.
Dr. Preston Burke: I'm a busy man, Gray, and there are rules.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Look, it's not like I'm the chief or something.
Hospital Intercom / Meredith Grey (PVM): Dr. Palmer, page the box.
Alex Karev / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): You're hot.
Addison Montgomery / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): You're drunk.
Alex Karev / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Hold still.
Alex Karev / Meredith Grey (PVM): Wait, you're that girl from the magazine, that red bikini?
Addison Montgomery / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Yeah, it was Pink.
Addison Montgomery / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I'm done.
Doctor / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): You can see the nurse outside now.
Patient / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Is she crazy or something?
Doctor / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): No, I don't think so.
Patient / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Okay.
Doctor / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Please, please sit down.
Doctor / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I really need to look at your arm.
Patient / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Okay.
Patient / Hospital PA System (PVM): When I left her, she was very young.
Patient / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Hospital PA System (PVM): It wasn't a good place, but we got the money.
Doctor / Meredith Grey (PVM): What are you doing down here?
Rapist Patient / Meredith Grey (PVM): Just sitting here with my penis.
Doctor / Meredith Grey (PVM): What about you?
Doctor / Meredith Grey (PVM): Hiding from Alex.
Doctor (possibly Izzie or another female doctor) / Meredith Grey (PVM): I kissed Eric.
Doctor (possibly friend/confidante) / Meredith Grey (PVM): You kissed Eric?
Doctor (confessor from 434) / Meredith Grey (PVM): In the elevator.
Doctor (friend/confidante) / Meredith Grey (PVM): Well, you kissed him in the elevator.
Doctor (confessor from 434) / Meredith Grey (PVM): I was having a bad day.
Doctor (friend/confidante) / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): I am having a bad day.
Doctor (confessor from 434) / Meredith Grey (PVM): So what do you do on your bad days?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Make out with Dr. McDreamy?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): You know, that and carrying around a penis just makes everything seem so shiny and happy.
Izzie Stevens / Patient OR Meredith Grey (PVM): George said Allison was wearing your shoes.
Meredith Grey / Alex Kreb (PVM): Yeah.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): It's weird, right?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): It's weird that you care.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): I think it's weird.
Hospital Staff (e.g., Nurse or Security) / Meredith Grey (PVM): Can I have security, please?
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Meredith Grey (PVM): What do we got?
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Take a look.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Let's get them to OR1.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Meredith, you call the chief and let him know we got the rapist.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Cutlin OR Meredith Grey (PVM): I saw Allison.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): You can't believe the beating that she took.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): And then to see this.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): It's like that old saying, you should see the other guy.
Dr. Preston Burke / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Why are we not attempting to reattach the severed penis?
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Teeth don't slice, they tear.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): You can only reattach with a clean cut.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): She wanted to slice him off with a knife.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Besides, the digestive juices didn't leave much of the flesh to work with.
Dr. George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): Right.
Dr. Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): So what do we do?
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Sew him up minus a large part of the family jewels.
Dr. George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): And his outlook?
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): He'll be urinating out of a bag for a very, very long time.
Dr. Alex Karev / Meredith Grey (PVM): Not to mention he'll never be able to have sex again.
Dr. Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, too bad.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Shane.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Let's all take a moment to grieve.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Richard Webber (PVM): Clamp.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Richard Webber (PVM): Richard.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Richard Webber (PVM): We got the rapist.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Richard Webber (PVM): He stumbled right into the hospital.
Dr. Richard Webber / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Yeah, I heard.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Richard Webber (PVM): Listen, Bert.
Dr. Preston Burke / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Why?
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Richard Webber (PVM): You really want to know?
Dr. Preston Burke / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): I want to know when you stop thinking of me as your number one.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Richard Webber OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Richard, I do more in this hospital than any other surgeon you have.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Richard Webber (PVM): You do only exactly as much as is necessary.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Richard Webber (PVM): You never take an extra step.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Richard Webber (PVM): You never give an extra minute.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Richard Webber (PVM): You're comfortable and arrogant, and it doesn't impress me.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Richard Webber (PVM): You want to be chief?
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Richard Webber (PVM): Earn it.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I'm sorry.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I have patients lined up.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I don't have time.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I don't understand you.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I'm sorry.
Hospital PA System: Dr. Bailey to ortho staff.
Meredith Grey / Alex Kreb OR Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): My head hurts.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Maybe it's a tumor.
Meredith Grey / Alex Kreb (PVM): You wish I had a tumor.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Look, I'd rip your face off if it meant I got to scrub in.
George O'Malley / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I've been suturing all day.
George O'Malley / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): My hands are numb.
Izzie Stevens / Alex Kreb OR Meredith Grey (PVM): At least you're helping people.
George O'Malley / Alex Kreb OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): At least you get to practice freaking medicine.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I had to send my Chinese lady away.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): She was, like, camped out down there.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, poor Izzy, turning away a patient.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Boo hoo.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): So the police say they can't send a crime scene guy down for hours.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): So I have to spend the night with a penis.
Izzie Stevens / Alex Kreb OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Alex, don't say it.
Dr. Alex Karev: Oh, it's too easy anyway.
George O'Malley / Alex Kreb OR Patient (PVM): Who here feels like they have no idea what they're doing?
Izzie Stevens / Patient (PVM): I mean, are we supposed to be learning something?
Izzie Stevens / Patient (PVM): Because I don't feel like I'm learning anything.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): Except how not to sleep.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): You know, it's like there's this wall, and the attendings and the residents are over there being surgeons, and we're over here being... Suturing, code running, lab delivering, penis minders.
Cristina Yang / Alex Kreb OR Meredith Grey (PVM): I hate being an intern.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Hi.
Baby's Mother / Meredith Grey (PVM): Hi.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Is he yours?
Baby's Mother / Alex Kreb (PVM): Yeah.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): He's adorable.
Mrs. Liu / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Thanks.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, please.
Dr. Karev / Meredith Grey (PVM): You are so out of line.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): She says the murmur might not be benign.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): I think we should do an echo to check.
Dr. Karev / Meredith Grey (PVM): This is your career.
Dr. Karev / Meredith Grey (PVM): There really is no reason to get along.
Dr. Karev / Alex Kreb (PVM): What's the problem?
Parent (Mr. Liu or Mrs. Liu) / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): If our baby is sick, we want him treated now.
Dr. Karev / Meredith Grey (PVM): Who said your baby was sick?
Parent (Mr. Liu or Mrs. Liu) / Meredith Grey (PVM): Her, the surgical intern who has no business on our service.
Dr. Karev / Meredith Grey (PVM): Who authorized you being here?
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): I was just actually... Hey, dude.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Could you excuse me for a second?
Dr. Karev / Meredith Grey (PVM): Are you messing with my intern, Dr. K?
Another doctor / Meredith Grey (PVM): No, sir.
Dr. Karev / Dr. Preston Burke OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Give me the check.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): There's nothing wrong with him.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): I checked.
Parent (Mr. Liu or Mrs. Liu) / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Are you sure?
Unknown / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Yes.
Mrs. Liu's companion / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): You can guarantee that he's fine.
Mrs. Liu's companion / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): You're 100% sure.
Mrs. Liu's companion / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): How sure are you?
Izzie / Meredith Grey (PVM): I don't know, 75%.
Mrs. Liu's companion / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Not good enough.
Izzie / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): He's my patient now.
Izzie / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): That okay with you, Dr. K?
Dr. Karev / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Absolutely.
Izzie / Unknown (PVM): We can take our patient.
Dr. Karev / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): He's an attending.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Which means I can do whatever I want.
Dr. Preston Burke: Mr. and Mrs. Johnson, I'm Dr. Burke, head of cardio.
Dr. Preston Burke: We're going to run some tests and get you an answer within the hour.
Mr. Johnson / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Great.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Excuse me.
Dr. Preston Burke: I want an EKG, chest x-ray, and an echo.
Dr. Preston Burke: I don't have all day.
Izzie / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): You're a busy man.
Dr. Preston Burke: I'm a busy man.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Anybody else?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey OR Alex Kreb (PVM): No.
Other intern / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): No more.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Then I need a bed.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Cutlin (PVM): Ms.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Liu?
Dr. Cutlin: Dr. Cutlin, thoracic surgery.
Dr. Cutlin: Dr. Frank Cutlin, thoracic surgery.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Cutlin (PVM): Ms.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Cutlin (PVM): Liu!
Dr. Burke / Dr. Cutlin (PVM): Liu, wait!
Dr. Burke / Dr. Cutlin (PVM): Ms.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Cutlin (PVM): Liu!
Ms. Liu / Dr. Cutlin (PVM): What is it?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): It's okay.
Cristina Yang / Unknown (PVM): I'll help.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): It's deep.
Dr. Burke / Meredith Grey (PVM): It's deep.
Patient (likely non-English speaking woman) / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Meredith Grey (PVM): I need to clean it out.
George O'Malley / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Clean it.
Patient (likely non-English speaking woman) / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Machine is broken in the factory.
Patient / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): It's gone.
George O'Malley / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Can you speak English?
George O'Malley / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Just, if you could come inside.
Patient / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): No, no, not inside.
Patient / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): No, no, no.
Patient / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Jail.
George O'Malley / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Jail?
Patient / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): She came inside.
Patient / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey OR Alex Kreb (PVM): No.
Patient / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): She been caught.
Patient / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Me, no.
George O'Malley / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): You're illegal.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): That's okay.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): We don't have to tell them that.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I just need to get you inside.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Meredith Grey (PVM): I have to sew that up.
Patient / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): No, no inside.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Please, I promise.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I promise you won't go to jail.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): It's raining.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Please, come inside.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Okay, okay, okay.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Not inside.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Wait here, okay?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Wait.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I'll come back.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I'll be back.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Well?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): It's a birth defect.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Tetralogy of a lower pulmonary atresia.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): You were right.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Book an OR for tomorrow.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Thank you for backing me up on this.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Preston Burke OR Meredith Grey (PVM): No, no, no, wait.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): You were right.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): But if you ever pull a stunt like that again, going to the parents behind a doctor's back, trying to steal a patient from another service, I will make your residency here hell on earth.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Cutlin OR Meredith Grey OR Dr. Preston Burke OR Meredith Grey (PVM): I came home in the morning and everything was gone.
Allison / Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, what have I done?
Allison / Meredith Grey (PVM): I dropped dead in the hallway, cursing the dawn.
Allison / Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, come on, son, why must I burn?
Allison / Meredith Grey OR Alex Kreb OR Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm just trying to learn.
Meredith / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Okay, you're all sewn up.
Patient (unknown) / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): That's pretty good.
Meredith / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I could have done a better job if I'd had more light.
Meredith / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): You might have a scar.
Patient (unknown) / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): It's good.
Meredith / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): You're gonna need to come back in five days, okay?
Meredith / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I'm gonna need to check the wound and remove the stitches, okay?
Meredith / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Here's my pager number on this card.
Meredith / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Right here.
Meredith / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Okay?
Meredith / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): We'll meet right back here.
Meredith / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): You have to come back.
Meredith / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): But you can't tell anybody that I helped you outside of the hospital or I might lose my job.
Meredith / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Understand?
Patient (unknown) / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Yes.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Alex Kreb (PVM): Come back and don't tell.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Yes.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Okay.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): That's it.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I'm done.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): You can go.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I'll see you in five days.
Meredith Grey / Alex Kreb (PVM): Yes, Eel.
Meredith Grey / Hospital PA System (PVM): She is my only family here.
Meredith Grey / Hospital PA System (PVM): You are a good person and a good doctor.
Allison / Meredith Grey (PVM): Thank you.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Thank you.
Derek Shepherd / Meredith Grey (PVM): Thank you.
Meredith Grey / Hospital Intercom OR Meredith Grey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Do you think I'm too confident?
Derek Shepherd / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey OR Alex Kreb (PVM): No.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Don't lie.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You are my boss.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): All right, then.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Anything you say in the next 30 seconds is free, starting now.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I think you're cocky.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Arrogant, bossy, and pushy.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You also have a God complex.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You never think about anybody but your damn self.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): But I... But what?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I still have 22 more seconds.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I'm not done.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): I need a drink, a man, or a massage.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): I've already drunk a massage by a man.
Cristina Yang / Patient (PVM): What's wrong with you?
George O'Malley / Patient (PVM): I lost five patients on the code team today.
George O'Malley / Patient (PVM): I feel like the angel of death.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): George, 95% of all code patients can't be revived.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Most of them are seriously dead before you can get there.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): What?
George O'Malley / Hospital Intercom OR Meredith Grey OR George O'Malley (PVM): Why didn't you tell me that when I was going on and on about how great it was gonna be?
Cristina Yang / Hospital Intercom OR Meredith Grey OR George O'Malley (PVM): Because.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): His heart surgery is scheduled for the morning.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): I really did think I was right, you know?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): I know.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): We almost never are.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): We're interns.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): We're not supposed to be right.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): And when we are, it's completely shocking.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): Are you... I mean, being an intern, do you feel...
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Terrified, 100% of the time.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey OR Alex Kreb (PVM): Good.
Meredith Grey / Alex Kreb (PVM): It's not just me.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey OR Alex Kreb (PVM): No.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): How is she?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): No change.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey OR Alex Kreb OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Have you been here all night?
Meredith Grey / Alex Kreb (PVM): Mm-hmm.
Cristina Yang / Alex Kreb (PVM): Yeah.
Izzie Stevens / Alex Kreb (PVM): You know I have four sisters?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Very girly, tons of kids.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): If I was in a coma, they'd all be here.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): I'd want them here.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Not having no one?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Can't imagine that.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): I can.
Meredith Grey / Hospital Intercom (PVM): What are you talking about?
Cristina Yang / Hospital Intercom (PVM): What about your mother?
Meredith Grey / Hospital Intercom (PVM): She'd be here ordering all the surgeons around.
Meredith Grey / Hospital Intercom OR Alex Kreb (PVM): She'd fly these cowboys in from Prague to do these amazing medical procedures.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): That's true.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Cutlin (PVM): I do have my mother.
Cristina Yang / Hospital Intercom OR Dr. Cutlin (PVM): So we're kissing, but we're not dating?
Meredith Grey / Hospital Intercom OR Meredith Grey (PVM): I knew that was gonna come up.
Cristina Yang / Hospital Intercom (PVM): Don't get me wrong, I like the kissing.
Cristina Yang / Hospital Intercom (PVM): I'm all for the kissing.
Cristina Yang / Hospital Intercom (PVM): Or kissing, I say.
Meredith Grey / Hospital Intercom OR Meredith Grey (PVM): I have no idea what that was about.
Cristina Yang / Hospital Intercom (PVM): It's gonna happen again, because if it is, I need to bring breath mints.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): But I can't in a moment.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Shut up now.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): There's this baby up in the nursery.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): He's brand new.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): No one's neglected him or damaged him yet.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): How did we get from there to here?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): She's wearing my shoes, and someone's beat the crap out of her.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): And she's got nobody.
Cristina Yang / Hospital Intercom (PVM): Your ICP's double.
Cristina Yang / Hospital Intercom (PVM): Get O.R.
Derek Shepherd / Hospital Intercom OR Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Perfect for craniotomy.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Let's hang a medical.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Uh, take a blood gas.
Hospital Intercom: Dr. Cutler to thoracic surgery.
Hospital Intercom: Dr. Frank Cutler to thoracic surgery.
Derek Shepherd / Hospital Intercom (PVM): I, uh...
Derek Shepherd / Hospital Intercom (PVM): Had to leave her skull flap off until the pressure in her brain goes down.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): She's not going to make it, is she?
Derek Shepherd / Hospital Intercom OR Meredith Grey (PVM): She's going to be fine.
Cristina Yang / Hospital Intercom OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): If she ever wakes up.
Nurse / Hospital Intercom (PVM): Dr. Burke, I'm off at 6.
Nurse / Hospital Intercom (PVM): Want to get that drink we talked about?
Dr. Preston Burke: I don't think so.
Nurse / Hospital Intercom (PVM): Well, what about tomorrow night?
Preston Burke / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Shepard, you should know that Richard promised Chief to both of us.
Unknown (possibly Doctor or Patient) / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): But you knew that already.
Unknown (possibly Doctor or Patient) / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Keep your friends close and your enemies closer.
Unknown (possibly Doctor or Patient) / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): You're not the enemy.
Unknown (possibly Doctor or Patient) / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): You're just a competition.
Doctor / Meredith Grey (PVM): So here is where you have the signature, and down here, the initials.
Doctor / Dr. Richard Webber OR Meredith Grey OR Doctor (PVM): It just says that the, um, the... Penis.
Doctor: I'm a doctor.
Doctor: I mean, it shouldn't be weird to say this.
Unknown (possibly Parent or Guardian) / Doctor OR Doctor (PVM): It's just that I used to change her diapers.
Doctor or Parent/Guardian / Meredith Grey OR Doctor (PVM): I get it.
Doctor / Meredith Grey OR Doctor (PVM): It just says that it was never on his side.
Doctor or Nurse / Meredith Grey (PVM): There you go.
Unknown (possibly Parent or Guardian) / Meredith Grey (PVM): It wasn't a penis.
Doctor / Doctor (PVM): Officer.
Surgeon / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): We'll be using a median approach for a transventricular repair with a right ventriculotomy.
Surgeon / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Let's open him up.
Surgeon / Dr. Preston Burke OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Moki, 15 blade, please.
Surgeon / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Gray.
Dr. Meredith Grey: Yes, sir.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Go scrub in.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): When we're finished cracking the baby's chest, I'll let you hold the clamp.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): Seriously?
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Don't make me change my mind.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm going.
Cristina Yang / Hospital Intercom (PVM): Good news and bad news.
Cristina Yang / Hospital Intercom (PVM): The good news is Dr. Bailey stops your bleeding.
Cristina Yang / Hospital Intercom (PVM): The bad news is we're giving your penis to the cops.
Cristina Yang / Hospital Intercom (PVM): Have a nice life.
Dr. Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): The results of your labs are clean.
Dr. Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): The tumor is benign.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Cutlin OR Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): You can go home today.
Meredith Grey: At some point, you have to make a decision.
Meredith Grey: Boundaries don't keep other people out.
Meredith Grey: They fence you in.
Meredith Grey: Life is messy.
Meredith Grey: That's how we're made.
Meredith Grey: Okay, fine, George and Izzy, you can move into the house.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): Yes!
Meredith Grey / Dr. Cutlin OR Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): I can't believe it!
Derek Shepherd / Meredith Grey (PVM): Yes!
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Thank you.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): I can't believe I caved.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): I blame the babies.
Derek Shepherd / Meredith Grey (PVM): They make you toxic.
Meredith Grey: So, you can waste your life drawing lines,
Meredith Grey: Or you can live your life crossing them.
Derek Shepherd / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Welcome back.
Meredith Grey: But there are some lines... So... It's intense.
Meredith Grey: This thing I have for fairy boats, I mean.
Meredith Grey: ...that are way too dangerous to cross.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm so taking the stairs this time.
Derek Shepherd / Hospital Intercom OR Meredith Grey (PVM): No self-control.
Derek Shepherd / Meredith Grey (PVM): It's sad.
Derek Shepherd / Hospital Intercom (PVM): Really.
Meredith Grey: Here's what I know.
Meredith Grey: If you're willing to take the chance, the view from the other side is spectacular.