Previously on "Grey's anatomy"...
Marry me, Cristina Yang.
Are you saying yes?
Y-yeah.
We're married!
Adele and I are getting a divorce.
Has it even occurred to you
that maybe I'm not interested?
I raised you to be
an extraordinary human being.
So imagine my disappointment when I wake
up after five years and discover
that you're no more than ordinary.
You want to know why I'm so ordinary?
You want to know what happened
to me? You. You happened to me.
Disappearances happen in science...
Disease can suddenly fade away,
tumors go missing.
We open someone up to discover
the cancer is gone.
It's unexplained, it's rare,
but it happens.
We call it misdiagnosis...
say we never saw it in the first place...
Any explanation but the truth.
That life is full of vanishing acts.
If something that we didn't know
we had disappears,
do we miss it?
Meredith.
Meredith!
What are you doing?
- That's not a bath. I know what
a bath looks like.
- Drop it.
- Look, your mother...
Your mother...
Look, your mother was lucid, and she
said things, and now she's...
Gone,
and everything's back to normal.
It's not a big deal.
Yeah, except she's having
heart surgery today.
Hey, do you want
me to talk to the chief?
I know you have the triage thing today,
but he'll give you the day off.
Stop.
I do not need rescuing.
Oh, you would have drowned in the
bath tub had I not been there.
I'm a surgeon. I do the rescuing.
You are not my knight in shining...
whatever.
So we're gonna fight because
I pulled you out of the tub?
You have a place. You could sleep at it.
And then you don't have to pull
me out of the bathtub.
You're everywhere,
all the time, saying things.
This is the happy ever after part.
And in the happily ever after part, the
guy is there, all the time, saying things,
and the girls love it.
Go to work. I'll see you there.
Just for the record,
I am your knight in shining whatever.
Good morning!
I did not try to drown myself
in the bathtub.
Hey, I ate everything out
of the fridge last night,
everything, including a tub of butter.
There's no judgment here.
You ever feel like
you were disappearing?
All the time.
Why can't I just be that
happily ever after person?
Why can't I believe in that?
I don't know what I believe in anymore.
- We're not telling people.
- I haven't told anyone.
I know, I know. Just don't.
I'm not going to,
- yet.
- No, I just... I need to tell
my friends he first.
But I have friends here.
Shepherd.
Oh, no. You can't tell Shepherd.
You cannot tell Shepherd until I've
told Meredith. It would be a thing.
You act like this is a disaster.
The world won't implode if people know.
I will tell them, today
Just...
Wait.
Good morning.
Morning. Morning.
What's different?
- Nothing.
- Leave him be.
What happened to your hair?
- Nothing.
- Mm-hmm.
What happened to your hair?
Leave him be.
He dyed it.
But why?
Leave him be.
- What am I doing?
- What?
Okay, but why?
Men  who have gray hair are noticed less
than men who don't.
By who?
- Well...
- By the ladies?
- Looks good, chief.
- Oh, very natural.
Ladies will love it.
He is alone... all alone.
Do any of you even know
what that's like?
Lives with Cristina,
dates the perfect 12 year old...
man-whore...
his wife left him after
25 years of marriage.
So if the man wants to dye
his hair for the ladies,
Let him dye his hair
for the ladies.
Leave him be.
It's weird. It's weird.
It's weird, right?
I need more triage tear tags.
Living with somebody
I'm married to is weird.
I mean, I'm his boss and his wife.
At work, I'm giving him orders.
In bed,
- he's giving me...
- Stop right there. I don't need to know this.
I'm tired. I'm busy.
While I will concede you and O'Malley
have some challenges to overcome,
I'm asking you to remember that this day
is a marathon
and my mind can only hold
what it needs to know.
Your sex life cannot be held in
my mind today.
Ever. It cannot be held
in my mind ever,
Never.
Whatever. Sydney Heron here
to lend a hand. Hey. Hi. Hello.
Oh, Miranda, hey.
Nice clinic. Very nice.
Hey, Sydney.
I mean real, real nice. Cheerful.
No better way to distinguish
yourself for chief resident
than to open a
multimillion-dollar clinic.
Smart thinking. Strategic.
Chief resident?
I myself have used the time to master
several complex surgical procedures.
But this is, um, another way to go.
What is she talking about?
- The chief resident.
Yeah, for next year. The one fifth-year
resident that rules all residents.
Oh, she... Okay, she's cute. She's acting
like she didn't know about it. Cute.
- I'm not cute.
- I'm on to you.
- Okay, I'm a competitor. Grr.
- I bite.
Okay. Well, I'll just
wait for you in the pit.
What?
Nothing.
What?!
Okay,  Cranky. Fo-forget it.
Am I the only one who thinks this triage
test is a waste of time?
There's a platysmaplasty on the board.
I had Sloan all prepped to let me scrub in.
George, hey.
- Hey.
- How's it going?
- Good.
You like living in a hotel?
Yeah, it's good.
'Cause your room's still there...
next to mine.
- Oh, Izzie.
- I'm just saying, if you don't like...
the hotel, you can always
just move right back in.
You think I'm this boy that you need
to save. I get that, but...
and it...It would be sweet if...
If it weren't so condescending.
Seriously, is it too much to ask
to be performing actual surgeries?
We are actual surgeons.
What?
Nothing.
A lot of arm swelling,
but good distal pulses,
so...
we can rule out compartment syndrome.
I suspect a radius fracture,
so I'd splint
and get an ortho follow-up.
Anything else?
No.
Okay.
- Then I guess this means...
- Time.
- And I'm dead.
- Dead?
You sent her home. The bone
punctured through her skin.
Yeah, but she had multiple
wounds and abrasions...
A puncture over a break is an open
fracture until proven otherwise.
Yeah, I got septic, and I
died at home thanks to you.
Oh, whatever.
Not "whatever" to dead
"minor puncture wound that's not" guy.
You have to be quick and thorough
while using your instincts.
You can't be fooled
by what your eyes see.
If your assess wrong, your patient
could die while waiting for treatment.
Karev, you're next.
Just think, I've already killed her.
You can't do more damage than that.
People, triage is one of the most
important tools a doctor has.
In a real emergent scenario,
you'll have only minutes.
And it's something you'll be
tested on in your surgical ex...
- Sorry.
- George.
I was just recording the drill.
- Yeah.
- All right, we're working George, okay?
- I'm your boss right now.
- Yes.
- All right?
- Yes. A very sexy one.
- No, no, no. You cannot undermine my
authority in front of the other interns,
- No... Yeah...
- in front of my peers.
- No.
O'Malley, take that back to
the clinic where it belongs.
Sorry.
People.
Look, I'm sorry. I have to interrupt
the session for a moment.
Chief, I like your new hair.
It really brings out your eyes.
Do you need something, sir?
We just received word of
a mass casualty incident nearby.
All available level one trauma centers
have been asked to respond.
I need to send a team
into the field immediately.
Is  this a part of the exercise? Are we
supposed to act appropriately, uh, tense?
This is not an exercise
or a drill, Yang.
This is an emergent situation,
and I need all hands on deck.
- Seriously?
- What happened?
I don't have details, just orders.
Meredith, I have a thing, news.
You aren't pregnant again, are you?
'Cause I can't handle the extra
months of bitchiness.
We're catching a ride with Seattle 34.
Space is tight, so
hold your kits on your lap.
Where are we going?
We'll know when we get there.
Fire, flood, volcano? I'm not
really dressed for a volcano.
- Stevens.
- Sorry. Inappropriate. Sorry.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I'm hauling supplies.
I only have room for five.
Yang.
Yes?
Stay with the chief. Take care of the
incoming wounded. The rest of you, come on.
Stevens was inappropriate.
Hey, what was your, uh, news?
Just forget it. Forget it.
Oh, everybody, move your I. D. S
to the outside of your jacket.
When we get there, remember, triage.
Karev.
Green tags: non emergent. Yellow: delayed care.
Red tags: needs immediate treatment.
Good. Assess carefully, tag and get all
the critical patients into the ambulances
as fast as possible. Don't get in the way
of Search and Rescue, and stay calm.
-  Any word yet on what happened?
- All we know is there are multiple traumas.
Holy mother of...
Dr. Bailey, where do you need us?
Where should we start first?
Dr. Bailey--
I don't have time to hold your hands.
You know the protocol. Go do it.
- Do what?
- Go help people.
- You need some help?
- There's nothing more I can do here.
How did this happen?
It was a fog bank. Container ship
clipped the ferry.
Take a deep breath for me.
Okay, you're gonna be okay.
Your injuries are minor. An E.M.T. is gonna
come and take you to the hospital, okay?
Is this your mommy?
Who are you with?
Okay, I want you to stay right here,
okay? Stay right here.
Did you... wet your pants?
That's okay. It happens sometimes
Coming through!
It just doesn't make sense.
Ferry boats don't get in accidents.
They're safe.
They're reliable.
The moment you take one for granted,
along comes a container ship and boom.
I have a thing for ferry boats.
Reschedule,  uh, Swanson's,
uh, valve replacement.
We're gonna need the O.R.
- For the incoming from the ferry accident.
- Okay
I mean, this whole day had just been...
There's something wrong with Meredith.
I asked her what's wrong.
She says nothing.
Then she tries to drowned
herself in the tub.
N... not actually drowned,
I don't think.
But something was going on,
and she will not talk about it.
We were fine, and now it's like...
I'm living with a ghost.
- You're confiding in me.
- Yes.
Cristina and I are engaged.
Congratulations.
I mean, she doesn't want to tell anyone.
At least not until she
tells Meredith first.
Yeah, they're different
than other women.
Yes, these women...
Yes, they are.
You know, maybe we'll never know them.
I mean, really know them.
And now that you and Cristina are
engaged, you've got a lot of work to do.
You right
You and Yang are gettin' hitched?
There's a mass casualty
incident rolling in,
There'll probably be some burn victims.
You should be prepared.
Sydney. I thought I could take
a few patients off your... hands.
I appreciate the gesture,
dr. Callie O'Malley.
but the chief asked me to roll the
non emergent E.R. Cases into the clinic
and take care of them, so I've triaged
these patients, and so far it looks like a
a sore throat, a sprain and a
tummy ache... Easy breezy.
So the clinic and I are fine.
Okay, I'm not, uh, trying
to take the clinic...
Uh, Bailey's Clinic, by the way away
from you. I'm offering to help, so...
your offer to help is duly noted and very
much appreciated, but I promise you...
Got it all under control.
So...Jason Kaye?
Fine.
I'll leave you to it
and, uh, find myself a recently traumatized
emergency surgery to scrub in on while
you stay down here with your sore throat
and your sprain and...
- What was the other one?
- Tummy ache.
Jason Kaye?
Are you a nurse, a doctor,
m...medical something?
I'm a doctor, but...
Come with me.
Um, no, you... you need
to get checked out.
There's a treatment area
right over there.
Follow me, please.
You've got some really bad
burns. They need to be treated.
My buddy's trapped.
He's trapped under a car.
If he's trapped under a car,
you need Search and Rescue.
They have... they have personnel...
their medical personnel...
I called them.
They're backed up, and he can't wait.
He's in a real bad way.
Please. He's my best buddy.
Please.
Shepherd, I need you in the next rig.
- Okay.
- I want you at that scene.
You don't need me here?
They're reporting lots of closed
head injuries. I want you go get
in there and bring'em back alive.
Okay, what's the news?
Shepherd and Grey are on the rocks.
Burke and Yang got engaged.
You need highlights. In your hair...
that's why it looks so odd.
I'm gonna go save lives.
Take him to the treatment area.
They'll fix you up there, okay?
Come on, let's go!
I got somebody down here.
Hey!
That's not secure.
- Doctor, I need you to get back up here.
- There's a pregnant woman down here!
Just shut the...
Oh, hell.
She dead?
Yeah.
Hold on. Hold on.
Immediate! Immediate!
I need help down here!
He's back. He's got help.
You hear that, Rick? We got help.
We got a doctor.
You'll be okay now, man.
He's gonna be okay?
Right?
What we know at this time, what we can
tell you is that there have been deaths.
We don't know how many... and we may not
know that for hours or even days
We also know that passengers
are still being evacuated...
A ferry of this size can carry
anywhere up to a thousand or...
All right, you're gonna need
these to handle the influx.
We're gonna need plenty of available
open chest trays, central line kits
- and a difficult intubation cart.
- Yes, sir.
- Oh, Yang.
- I know. Communicate with the scene
as needed.
No.
I heard you were engaged.
Congratulations.
Thank you, Sir.
All right go, and remember, we're hoping
for the best but preparing for the worst.
You got anyone for me?
Uh, yeah, those two need
to be transported.
Uh, these five didn't make it...
four adults and one child.
A child?
You found a dead child?
A boy or girl?
Ma'am, you're injured. You need to
lie down. Get a stretcher, now.
Is the child a boy or a girl?
I can't find my son.
We got separated I... I need to know
if my little boy is alive.
She was a girl.
The child was a little girl. No, no,
no, no. I need to examine you.
I'm gonna have to take you
to the hospital.
No, I can't leave!
- He's only 7. No!
And... and he's all alone.
- No
- No, I will not leave my son behind.
- No! No, I will find him.
Listen to me.
I will find him.
If you let me take you to triage,
I promise you I will find your son.
- He's so scared.
- Yeah, I know. I know.
I'll find him.
- Okay.
- Okay?
All right.
He's a mechanic. We... we work together.
We... we drive together to work,
and... and suddenly there was this
huge jolt. It was awful.
We were just trying to get outta there.
But Rick went back in...
figured we could help.
We should help.
He went back. There were people trapped.
He was trying to help.
We were behind him.
We... we were right behind him.
There are injuries to his chest and leg.
It looks like his arm is broken,
and I'd guess there's damage
to his spine and pelvis. I can't...
there's... there's not much that I can
do until we get him out of here.
You gotta do what you can.
I mean, we'll, uh...
Greg, go find some more guys.
Hey,  go find Search and Rescue, okay?
Give them this.
Tell them I said he can't wait.
He has to get to a hospital.
All right, I'm going.
Let'em know he needs a C.T. Make sure to
keep his neck stable. I felt a step off.
Ask for Waller. If Waller's not
available, ask for Krychek, okay?
Keep him stable.
What do you got?
My God! Oh!
Hey, nurse, let me have some
bandages. Thank you. Stop here.
Derek.
- Hey, Meredith, you got a free hand?
Hold this bandage for me, will you?
- Yeah
- You all right?
- Yeah, it's just a lot.
Do you want to get married?
and you haven't told me and I haven't
asked, so now we have a problem?
What?
No, I don't want to get married.
You want to get married
No
Good.
So if that's not it, what is it?
It isn't anything.
- Are you good? 'Cause I gotta
get this kid triaged.
- Yeah, I'm good.
- Okay.
- Let's go
She all right?
Yeah, she's good. She's just lost.
Hang in there. We're going to
the hospital soon okay?
All the non emergent surgeries
have been postponed.
- Good.
- I'm gonna go check on discharges.
I'm trying to free up as many beds
as I can in the surgical wing.
Oh.
- I was gonna do that, but...
- I can do it.
Oh, sure. Good.
- Unless you want to.
- No, no. Go ahead.
- You're still the chief.
- I know that.
- It just seems so quiet, you know?
- Yeah.
We're expecting the first wave
from the scene soon.
I dyed my hair blonde...
The day after Derek moved out.
Change is good. Your marriage is over.
You're...
You're starting over.
So am I.
Right.
I specifically told you I needed
to tell Meredith first.
I was talking to Shepherd, and...
it just came out.
- It was no big deal.
- It is a big deal,
Because now she's not even gonna care
about the fact that I'm getting married.
All she's gonna care about is the fact
that I didn't tell her myself.
Then why didn't you?
There was a major disaster.
That was 45 minutes
after we discussed it.
You were with your friends
for 45 minutes
running triage drills, and you weren't
compelled to mention it?
The chief says they're
rolling in soon, so...
Her pressure's low. Barely registering
and I don't see any good veins for an I.V.
She's all clamped down from hypothermia.
That's why I couldn't find a pulse.
I've never seen a crush injury
so bad and survive.
God, she's a mess
She needs to stay on her left side.
We gotta move her on her left side.
It's gonna take both of us.
We gotta get that B.P. up.
On my count.
One...
Two...
Your baby... Your baby's okay.
For now it looks okay.
Just try to breathe.
We need to move you to help
with your circulation, okay?
One, two, three.
Pulse is already better.
I'll attempt I.V. access again.
Just breathe through the pain.
What you can do for your baby right now
is take care of yourself.
Good girl.
Come on now.
Keep breathing for me, okay?
That's it.
Keep breathing.
Good.
Um, what do we...
So what do we do?
We wait.
We wait?
Okay, we need to find a grown-up...
Another grown-up... To help you
find your mom.
Hey, uh, I need you to take
this little girl to the triage tents.
I gotta get back to my unit.
No, I need you to take this little girl
to the triage tents for me, please.
You're gonna be okay.
You're gonna be fine.
I promise, okay?
Thanks.
Help! I need some help over here!
Stay right here.
How we doing?
It's bad. A lot of survivors,
so that's something.
Yeah, it is.
- Have you seen Stevens?
- No.
What about O'Malley, Grey?
Grey was...
I saw Grey about ten minutes ago.
She was on her way over here with a kid.
- You haven't seen her?
- No.
I gotta head out with this one, so keep
an eye out for my interns, all right?
Yeah, I'll do my best.
Jane Doe, about six months pregnant,
found under a pile of rubble.
She sustained crush injuries
to her right torso
and upper extremities as well
as severe trauma to the face.
B.P. Initially low,
but now up to 90 over 60
after a liter of fluid and
placing her on her left side.
What do we do? Karev?
Abc...
Her airway needs to be protected.
Her breathing will be compromised
because of the crush injury,
and we need to have blood available.
I would do a trauma panel,
type and cross
and C.T. of her head and neck.
Excellent. Let's get her started.
Uh, trauma room two.
- Let's go
- Right away
One, two and three.
Let's see what we have here.
The baby... the baby's gonna...
Make sure that you
shield her in radiology.
We've got to get her stabilized first
before you start worrying about the baby.
The amount of rads are negligible.
Right, but she's gonna need a lot
before all of this is over.
We need to protect them both.
Yang, you're on this.
Alex, go to the clinic.
The victims families are there.
They need answers.
This is my patient. I pulled
her out of the damn water.
Which is heroic and manly, and you still
need to talk to those families right now.
Why can't Yang do it?
This is all hands on deck.
Yang can handle this. Now go.
Okay
He likes fire trucks...
and police cars...
Anything with flashing lights.
Carlee Heit, 45-year-old female,
found at the scene.
Open abdominal wound
with horizontal evisceration.
Okay, we need to get her to an O.R.
As soon as possible.
He won't respond
if you call him Christopher.
He hates that. Just Chris.
- Okay.
- He likes Chris the best.
O'Malley, what is she talking about?
She lost track of her son
in the accident.
Dr. O'Malley and I made a deal.
He's gonna find my son
so I know that Chris is okay
before I go into surgery.
Mrs. Heit, your injury's
extremely serious.
We need to tend to it
as soon as possible.
As soon as he's located. I can't go into
surgery before I know about my son
I'm sure he's here.
All families are being dir...
O'Malley, just find the boy
in a hurry, and we'll start the workup.
I need more gauze.
There's no more here.
Maybe you could find some, uh,
paper towels the head?
I'll find something.
Vince...
Vince, it hurts like hell.
Can you do anything about that? I mean,
can...you got anything for the pain?
I've given him everything I've got.
- Where is Search and Rescue?
- It hurts.
What hurts, man?
E... everything.
Maybe if... maybe if I try to set
his arm, it'll help some with the pain.
What are you waiting for?
I, uh, um...
What?
- What?
- Nothing. Just, uh, just stay
there and hold his hand.
Hold his hand?
You think he's in pain now?
He's not. Hold his hand.
Place both hands on opposite
sides of the fracture...
Distract, exaggerate and reverse
the mechanism in one continuous motion.
You are a doctor, aren't you?
Shut up.
All right.
All right. Rick, you ready?
Yeah.
One...
Two...
Aah!
What happened?
Some metal... Something in my leg...
Thrown off.
- God, it hurts. It hurts.
- Okay.
I started swimming.
I needed to go... Got a meeting.
Aah!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Sir.
But try to stay still.
Oh. Oh.
Don't look. Turn around.
I need you to be brave for me.
Just stand right there and don't move
and don't look.
What do we got?
Oh, we just got started.
All right.
But I got this.
There's nobody covering my service.
I'm gonna need you to get up to
telemetry and check on my patients,
pre-op and post-op.
And then I should join you in surgery?
No. And then you should
report to the pit.
Uh, the Chief assigned me to Jane Doe.
Yes. Now I'm reassigning you.
To do what, sutures?
Yes.
Okay, so... So you're saying you don't...
you don't want me to scrub in.
Dr. Yang, I'm saying that I have
an unattended cardiothoracic wing
and a pit full of patients
that you have the ability to help.
I don't need you in the O.R.
I need you on the floor.
Do you have a problem with that?
No.
Thank you.
No, not... Chris Heit.
He's 7 years old. He's got brown hair.
I don't know if he's injured. I'm...
Could you at least check
to see if he's there?
Yes, I know all the families were
directed here. Could you just check?
Thank you. Yeah.
Callie, I need some help.
I can't. I'm busy.
Yeah, okay. It's just, uh,
I'm trying to find this...
George, I'm busy. I'm about to go into
surgery, okay? I can't be your wife
right now. I'm working.
I'm working, too. I have a patient who
needs surgery.
So do I.
Yes, any luck?
Thank you.
Okay. Damn it.
Can I get some help over here?
Sweetie, listen to me.
I need you to turn around
I know I told you to face away from me,
but we have to work together
to help this man.
I don't talk either when I get scared.
I don't...
talk when bad things happen.
You don't have to say anything.
But I need your help.
Okay, don't look down. Don't look
at the blood. Look at me.
Look at me.
Can you be my assistant?
Okay, good.
I can't move my hands off where
they are right now.
So I need you to go over to my kit
and pull out, uh, the things...
They look like, um, like tweezers.
You know what your mommy uses
to pull a splinter out with?
Hey, what was the site like?
Was it gory?
Was it a trauma Bonanza?
Obviously terrible.
I don't talk with thieves.
What?
You stole my Jane Doe right out
from under me.
I am not a thief.
You balked. You're a balker.
I was thinking.
Well, again, not my problem that thinking
is such a time-consuming process for you.
I rescued her. I climbed down. I pulled
a massive pylon off of her.
I got her here alive.
Pylons? There are pylons on people?
Whatever.
Now I get stuck babysitting the patients
families when you get to scrub in.
Well, I'm not scrubbing in.
I'm stitching up patients in the pit.
Ah who did you piss off to get that?
I happen to be pulling gaping pieces
of flesh back together.
You're stitching. You're just one-step
closer to knitting your grandma a sweater.
- Well, at least mine's medical.
- Well, you're knitting.
I pull pylons off people.
Orange juice?
Oh, sweetie.
Yeah, h... his color's not good.
Do you want some orange juice?
Maybe I have some wheat crackers,
something to put in your belly?
No.
Everybody, if you're... If you're
waiting to hear about your families,
we should be hearing something
very soon.
I'm sorry.
He must have saved at least a dozen
people who were stuck under cars.
We told him not to go back.
That's the kinda guy he is.
He's the guy that goes back.
He's got kids, too, five of'em.
Okay, I'm committed to the project.
I don't need to hear about the kids.
Leave the girl alone, Vince.
Sorry. You're doing a real
great job there, Doc.
Hey, how's he doing?
He's doing all right.
No, no, he's not.
I can't do anything more until
we get him out from under this car.
Can you please tell me why you've
come back by yourself?
Search and Rescue... They're buried.
They said they'd come when they can.
Did you show them the red tag?
He's a red tag?
They said they got 15 red tags.
Come on, guys. Don't worry about me.
I'll be fine.
No, no, no, no. Don't do this, man.
- S... stay with me. Stay with me.
- What happened?
He... he... he let go of my hand.
He's gone limp.
Rick! Wake up, Rick!
Hey.
I'm not gonna be able to make it
to your surgery.
But here's the thing...
You were crushed underneath
a cement pylon.
Now dozens of people
on that ferry boat died.
But you're still alive.
So when I come back to check on you after
the surgery, you better still be alive.
All right?
You hear me?
All right.
Her B.P.'s stable. So is the baby's.
You did good, Karev.
Is she gonna be okay?
You know, we're gonna...
We're gonna do everything we can.
What about the baby? I mean, is she
gonna be able to carry it to term?
Um...
You should get back down to the clinic.
Look, Mrs. Heit, it's time.
We really need to operate before you lose
any more blood or your bowels start to die.
Just... wait...
Till Dr. O'Malley finds my son. Please.
Dr. O'Malley... George... Did you find
him? Is...is he okay? Is he awake?
One of his pupils is blown.
We don't have a lot of time.
What are you gonna do?
God, you can't let him die.
I'm sorry.
I'm doing what I can.
Well, it's not enough.
Please just...
Just look, they're not gonna get
him out of here any time soon.
So you gotta figure out a way to
help him right here, right now.
Finally.
- Kelly Winter.
- Fatima? Fatima's a little girl...
Hold on. Hold on.
I'm... I'm, uh, I'm Dr. Karev.
This is a very rough situation,
and I can assure you,
we're doing everything that we can.
The following are the patients
we've identified at this time... Okay,
"John J. Anders, Kirk Demorast"...
This is the same list they gave us
a half-hour ago.
It's posted over there.
I... I understand, but...
Please, just, Kelly... She's got
brown hair. She's about 5'4".
Look, we had a lot of people
who came in without I.D.
Just take us over to the E.R.,
And we'll look for ourselves.
We can't let you do that.
- Why not?
- Those are our kids in there!
Okay. Let's see.
Now I have to deflate the blood pressure
cuff and see if he bleeds.
Good.
Okay. We saved him. You helped.
We just have to bandage him up,
We're gonna find someone
to take him to the hospital,
and then we're gonna find your mom, okay?
Aah! I can't stand it. The pain!
- I gotta get outta here!
- Sir, don't move! Don't move!
Transcript : Raceman
Synchro : ChipounetteF et Mickeyte
Traduction : Chryssie, Tbdb
Relecture : Cookie
Pour
www.forom.com et
http ://experts.heberg-forum.net/