Human beings
need a lot of things to feel alive.
Family.
Love.
Sex.
But we only need one thing...
To actually be alive.
We need a beating heart.
When our heart is threatened...
We respond in one of two ways.
- We either run...
- Or...
We attack.
There's a scientific term for this.
- Fight...
- Or flight.
It's instinct.
We can't control it.
Or can we?
Izzie.
His heart's barely beating.
We need to call a code.
I can't feel a pulse.
Izzie, we need to call a code!
- No! I have a plan.
- He's crashing! I need to call the...
No! If we call a code, they will rush
him to surgery and replace his LVAD
and he will stabilize.
He needs to get worse to get this heart.
- Izzie, this is crazy.
- He has to get this heart.
He will die waiting for another chance.
- We have to call a code!
- No!
You press that code button,
I will hurt you.
Not a lot, 'cause we're friends,
but enough so that things will break
and you lie on the floor out of my way.
- Izzie...
- You have a decision to make.
You can stay here and help me with this
or you can go.
What's it gonna be, George?
Chief!
How bad is it? It looks bad.
I'm here. I can help. If there's
anything surgical, I can help.
Why don't you go run Trauma 2,
Dr. Yang?
I get to run Trauma 2 all by myself?
Yes, but find me if you need help.
And get consults.
I'm on it!
- How bad is it?
- Uh, GSW to the right shoulder.
- He's lost a lot of blood.
- Get him to Trauma 1
and keep the blinds closed.
Yang's on the floor.
Self-inflicted GSW to the head.
Pulse is thready.
- This is the shooter?
- Emptied his clip, then shot himself.
And blew off half his head. OK, OK.
Um, push one of epi
and get him on the monitor.
- You're running this?
- Damn right, I am.
- Hey. Wait.
- I'm fine.
Lay down. You lost a lot of blood.
I'm fine. Let go. I'm fine! I have
a patient that I have to go check on.
No, no.
No, you are the patient. Lay down!
Dr. Bailey, when did you get here?
Page Shepherd.
Take over compressions.
- You're shot?
- Cristina?
- Back to your station.
- He's shot?
- Yang, we got it. It's OK.
- That guy shot you.
- Move.
- He's a lost cause.
- He's circling the drain.
- You don't get to kill yourself.
You do not get off that easily.
Push high-dose epi.
- Dr. Yang...
- What?
I want to be able to tell his family
I did everything I could
to save his pathetic, miserable life.
Give him three of epi. Now!
We should be hearing
from Dr. Burke any minute.
That's what you said half an hour ago.
Well, whether or not we hear from him,
we hit that hour mark,
I'm going in to get my heart.
- OK, no exit wound.
- Entry upper right shoulder.
Could be lodged in the spine.
OK, let's roll him over.
- Easy.
- Watch the arm.
- Dr. Burke?
- Hmm?
- The bullet is in dangerous property.
- We need to check your hand function.
- Try and squeeze my fingers, OK?
- They moved my guy upstairs. How is he?
- Wait outside.
I'm not going to wait outside. Burke?
Can we have a moment?
Only a moment.
I don't want to waste any time. OK?
- Cristina.
- Honey, you don't have to say anything.
I know you're sorry.
I know you didn't mean to kick me off
the transplant and I'm not mad.
I mean, I was, but I'm not anymore,
so don't worry about it.
Don't even think about it. OK?
I mean, all that matters is that you
get better and you get through this.
And I'm here for you.
Whatever you need. Anything.
I need...
you... to... to go...
to check on Denny Duquette.
OK.
OK, that was
my best "supportive girlfriend"
and you kind of ruined it
with medicine. OK?
Addison! Thank you for meeting us.
What's so important I'm keeping it
secret from my Chief of Surgery?
I was chaperoning a prom for my niece.
We had a little bit of a situation.
Camille Travis, 17, lost consciousness
during sexual intercourse?
- Oh, keep it down.
- It's OK, Aunt Adele. I'm fine.
When your Uncle Richard finds out
you were cashing in your V-card,
- none of us will be fine.
- Camille?
- Mrs. Webber!
- My God! Is she OK?
No one ever died from having sex, right?
You're not going to tell my parents,
right? I used a condom and everything.
George's page said it was an emergency.
- You paged Meredith?
- We need help!
- What the hell is going on?
- Exactly what I said.
- She cut his LVAD wires!
Are you trying to kill him?
I'm trying to save him. All I have to do
is confirm that his condition is worse,
then Burke can call UNOS and he'll move
up on the list and will get his heart.
- About Burke...
- She's gone insane, right?
- It will be fine!
- Izzie!
- When Burke gets here,
- he will know what to do.
- About Burke...
- What?
- He's been shot!
- Burke's not coming?
- Cristina, are you OK?
- I'm fine.
- Burke's not coming?
Why didn't I take the internship in San
Diego? None of this would be happening.
- Burke's not coming!
- No, Izzie. Burke is not coming.
I know you have problems
with your possible murder charges
and stupid idea about stealing a heart,
but Burke's kind of busy right now!
Denny's going to die.
Denny's going to die and I killed him.
You shouldn't have done it!
We have to tell someone.
Denny won't get the heart
and Izzie'll get kicked out.
- I'm leaving.
- Cristina!
Burke could die, too.
Complications arise all the time
because of gunshot wounds!
Oh, my God.
- If you were thinking with your head...
- I did what I thought was best!
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
No one is leaving. And no one is dying.
Thank you.
It was kind of getting on my nerves,
all this dying talk.
Denny.
It's OK.
I think, uh,
maybe we should all listen to Meredith.
- It looks like she might have a plan.
- You have a plan?
Just give me a minute.
- You girls should go back to the prom.
- Will you call Camille's parents?
Not until I have to. You know her mom.
She gets a little hysterical.
- Brian, disappear.
- What?
Go! Disappear! Richard.
- Richard.
- Adele.
- Hmm.
- What? Are you here to see Preston?
- No. What happened to Preston?
- Preston was shot.
- Preston was shot?
- Yeah.
Camille. What happened to Camille?
- Why didn't you call me?
- She's 17, sweetheart.
She'll be 18 in a few months.
Most girls lose it way before...
Uh-huh!
Do you think I want to hear that?
Do you think I want to picture
my baby niece... "losing it"?
Richard, Richard, take deep breaths.
Well, the bleeding has stopped,
but her pelvic exam does concern me.
I'd like to do an ultrasound.
Three years ago, Camille was diagnosed
with ovarian cancer.
They only removed one ovary
to try and preserve fertility,
but her checkups
have been clean since then.
OK. Well, let's not worry
until we have to.
You! You wait right there!
I want to talk to you!
- I said wait. Stop! I said stop!
- Richard, take deep breaths! Richard!
- Oh, that's a stupid plan!
- Well, if Burke isn't coming,
then we have to confirm Denny's
condition ourselves.
We get the blood work. We do the echo.
No one even has to know what Izzie did.
None of us have done an echo
on our own.
Cristina has. Burke taught her.
- I'm not involved.
- What if this were Burke?
- What if you were me?
- This is bad.
This is bad and serious
and against a lot of rules.
- It's not fun for me.
- What if you were me?
- I wouldn't fall for a patient.
- You fell for an attending.
- What's the point?
- We can't help who we fall for.
Yeah.
His hands are cold.
- My hands are always cold.
- Your hand is cold, Preston.
I have cold hands.
Bullet could be lodged in
the brachial plexus. That's dangerous.
Very dangerous.
My hands are always cold.
We'll have to do an angiogram.
I'm always cold.
Trachea's deviated to the right!
Absent breath sounds
on the right side! Let's go!
14-gage angio.
Let's hurry.
Dr. Burke? You gotta stay with me now.
There you go.
That's it! There you go! You're
all right. Right here. Right here.
Your lung collapsed. You're OK.
You're OK now.
He's been shot? Dude.
We'll have to run these tests ourselves.
UNOS gave us an hour.
In a couple of minutes, our time is up.
This chick is hardcore.
She's not gonna wait.
- OK, well, you just have to stall her.
- I'm not getting involved with this.
I don't care if that drawling
bedridden whiner ever gets a heart.
Alex. Do this. For Izzie.
I'm not guaranteeing anything.
So... was it totally romantic?
Yeah, before... the pain
and the paramedics and everything?
OK, so...
you know that feeling
when you look into someone's eyes
and you're totally comfortable
and you aren't self-conscious and
everything just... is, like, perfect?
Camille, have you had any symptoms,
um... any abdominal pain?
Nausea?
- Anything?
- No, she's been fine.
You haven't been fine, have you?
No, not for, like, a month or so.
You've been feeling sick for a month?
I wanted to go to prom. I, I... I didn't
want to be the girl with cancer, again.
You're not. She's not, right?
Hey.
Oh.
I was just trying to remember
the night I lost my virginity.
And I can't.
I remember who it was with
and I remember I was 18,
but... I can't remember
any of the details.
I can remember all of the details.
- Kind of wish I couldn't.
- That bad?
No, just not good.
Good came later.
And then really good came.
That little girl in there's
just getting started.
She hasn't even seen what good is yet.
Please. Addison.
Tell me she's going to have a chance
to see what the good stuff is.
Oh.
I'm so sorry, Adele.
How's his heart looking?
His left ventricle's shot
and he's barely pushing blood out.
I'm sorry. I know that you're worried
about Burke.
You know, whatever. It's fine.
Cristina, can't you just
try to understand?
I love him.
- You don't even know him.
- I do know him.
You've never even seen him outside
this hospital. You don't know him.
I know him. Maybe I don't live with him
or work with him like you do with Burke,
but I do know him.
And there's... there's possibility here.
And given the choice of running
or staying...
You should run. A sane person,
a person who values her career
and everything she's worked for,
a person who values her own heart,
for God's sake... that person would run.
A sane person...
would marry me.
What? What did you say?
What did he say?
He said marry me?
He said marry me, right?
- He did.
- Denny. Wake up. Denny.
- What's happening?
- I'm pumping harder. I don't know.
- He's flatline!
- He's not flatline.
There's movement in his heart.
OK, um, uh, let's shock him.
- Charge the defibrillator.
- Ventilate, George!
- I am.
- Charging to 200!
- You got it?
- Yeah.
Clear!
- Is Dr. Burke alive?
- Yes.
Shame.
He'd probably have made a good donor.
OK, people, let's get our organs
and get out of here.
That heart is not yours. Seattle Grace
is still waiting for test results.
Well, I'm not. Ten blade.
You can't do that.
I just did.
Girls.
Um, I called Jillian.
And I called Tessa.
And they called Simon and Bianca
and Deborah.
- Girls...
- It's her prom, Dr. Webber.
She can't miss her whole prom!
So... we, like, brought it to her.
Kids!
Kids! Listen up.
Look,
I know you wanted to see Camille.
Why don't you come back tomorrow?
During the day. In smaller groups.
Look, I'm sorry, girls.
I can't have a bunch of teenagers
running in the hallways.
People are sick. People are d...
Dying?
Yeah, we know.
How're you doing?
I'm developing numbness in my...
fourth and fifth fingers.
And there's a pseudoaneurysm
in the subclavian artery.
You know the drill.
Wait a few days,
maybe the aneurysm won't grow.
Yeah, if... if it stays this size,
there's too much damage.
We'll just go in there and we'll fix it.
Relieve the compression on the nerves.
But the operation
could cause damage to the nerves.
Yes.
And I could...
lose function of the entire arm.
Yes.
You can do this?
You're good enough to do this?
I think so.
- But you're not sure.
- But I'm not sure.
So...
what do I do?
It's not like you
to ask those kinds of questions.
not to have the answers.
How dare you send those kids away?
Adele. Please. You're emotional. OK?
I just told my sister
her baby's cancer is back.
You're damn right, I'm emotional!
If you don't want to bend
your precious rules for Camille, fine.
Don't do it for her. Do it for me.
Do it for your wife
who never asks you for anything.
Who says nothing about your long hours.
Who looks the other way while
you have an affair with another woman.
Who sobered you up
when that woman left you.
Who stayed with you when everyone
said I would be better off alone.
I'm not asking you, I'm telling you,
you're going to make this up to Camille.
You're going to prioritize
the needs of your family
above those of your other patients.
Or... you're going to find
a new place to sleep.
- Derek.
- Not now, Addison.
- Not now.
There's never a good place to hide
in this hospital.
I'm trying to get perspective.
Everything feels enormous.
Like it's all just...
I... I can't get perspective.
My niece's cancer has come back.
She's 17 years old
and she's going to die.
Plus...
25 years ago,
I had a secret affair with...
Ellis Grey.
And today, I find out that my wife
knew the entire time.
There was no... secret.
And she stayed with me.
Hmm.
I respect him, you know?
Dr. Burke. I...
I respect him.
He is decent. He's honorable.
An arrogant ass who just hogs the OR
and thinks he's God, but...
he's decent and he's honorable.
I respect him.
He's one of the foremost cardiothoracic
surgeons in the country and I have to...
It's his hand.
I cannot get perspective.
I can't do this.
I can't be responsible for him.
Preston's an honorable and decent man,
but, Derek, so are you.
You are honorable and decent. And
you're too honorable and decent to run.
You don't know how much
I wish this was bourbon.
Anything I can get for you, Dr. Burke?
No. I'm fine.
Um, there... there must be something.
It would be nice...
to have some ice chips.
And a touch of morphine if I'm allowed.
And, uh...
Cristina.
Coming right up.
Where is Cristina?
Where are...
where are all of the suck-ups?
Excuse me?
My interns. My ass-kissing,
surgery-hungry, competitive suck-ups.
Where are they? Why aren't they here
fetching you ice chips and morphine?
Why aren't they here sucking up?
You know something.
- I'm a patient.
- Preston Xavier Burke...
what have you done with my suck-ups?
What do we do? What do we do?
I'm starting dopamine and dobutamine
drips. We can use those together, right?
- Milrinone?
- I don't know.
None of us do.
Start the dobutamine and dopamine.
I feel like my chest
is running away.
- His heart rate's 217.
- He's in SVT!
No, no. Izzie, stop pumping. Stop.
- No change.
- We need that medicine!
- What medicine?
- I'll know when I see it.
The one that stops the heart.
No. The whole point
is to keep my heart beating.
It only stops it for six seconds.
- It's adenosine!
- Uh, his heart is speeding up! Guys!
We have to do something!
He cannot take this for much longer.
- What about shocking him?
- Found it!
Cristina, come over here.
Lift up his arm.
The nurses lift the arm when they push
adenosine. It gets to the heart faster.
- Denny. You're going to feel, um...
- Izzie!
No, it's OK. It just feels like...
- I'm gonna die.
- You're not, I promise. It's the meds.
- Are you sure we used the right drugs?
- The book said it was right.
- I used the one I know!
- He's not going to die, right?
Right? Right?
You fools better have
a good explanation for this.
Step away from the patient.
Step away from the patient!
I can't. I have to pump his heart.
Olivia, take over for Dr. Stevens.
Izzie, you're done here.
I need you to leave the room.
- Izzie...
- No! Do not touch me!
Olivia, stay with Dr. Stevens.
Help her if she'll let you.
You three. Outside. Now!
Where was rational thought?
Where was cognitive thinking?
First do no harm?
The morals, the ethics?
Where was sanity when you three
decided to help that girl?
- We didn't...
- No, no. No speaking.
I do not want to have to testify
against any of you in a court of law.
Not one word.
She cut his LVAD wire.
- I said no speaking.
- I didn't!
Then no moving!
Cristina, Burke is asking for you. Go!
I'm assuming you ran labs?
I'm asking a question.
- Answer me!
- You said no speak...
- I know what I said!
- Yes.
O'Malley, get me the lab results.
Do not pass go.
Do not talk to another living soul.
Get the labs! Get back here!
Grey...
come with me.
How are you?
You look good.
Are those your films?
Oh. Burke...
Shepherd, uh...
doesn't know if he can fix my hand.
Maybe I'll wait it out.
See if this numbness subsides.
Yeah.
Or I could let Shepherd operate.
Yeah. Yeah.
I could lose all hand function.
What if I can never operate again?
Yeah.
- Cristina?
- Yeah?
- Stop saying yeah.
- OK.
I need...
You said you were here.
- For me.
- Yeah.
Oh, sorry.
- Cristina.
- Hmm?
I need you to tell me...
what you think I should do.
I...
L- I told Dr. Bailey
that I would be back.
OK? L-I told her
that I wouldn't be long.
- Cristina...
- I'm-I'm-I'm going to think about it.
I mean...
I'm going to think about it. OK?
- How're you feeling, Denny?
- Really, really good.
Like an athlete or a superhero.
Or some other kind
of really healthy person.
- You're funny. You're a funny guy.
- Izzie. No speaking.
I cut my own LVAD wires, you know?
I went rogue. All by myself.
Shush. You're weak enough as it is.
Please don't waste energy on lying.
- Dr. Bailey?
- I did indeed say no speaking.
I don't care!
He's going to get the heart, right?
You're gonna sign the charts
and talk to the transplant coordinator?
Here are the labs.
See? See, his BUN and creatinine
are increasing.
He clearly has pulmonary edema.
He moves up to 1 A status
on the transplant list.
UNOS will give him the heart.
You need to call...
Isobel Stevens, I take my medical advice
from doctors. You are a visitor.
- What?
- You are a visitor in this hospital.
You will not be a doctor in this
hospital again until I decide you are.
Olivia, take over the heart pump.
He gets the heart, though, right?
Sir? Uh, I need to ask
you a hypothetical question.
Can we do this another time?
Uh, if someone on the staff
deliberately unhooked
a transplant candidate from his LVAD
in an attempt to worsen his condition
and get him moved up the donor list?
Hypothetically, sir.
I think you need to tell me
exactly what's going on here.
Believe me, sir,
you want this to stay a hypothetical.
Because I'm thinking if that did happen,
you'd be duty-bound to report it
and the hospital would be in danger
of losing its accreditation
as a transplant site.
So hypothetically?
Hypothetically,
if the patient got worse,
would it be unethical for him to receive
the heart even though, medically,
his worsened condition now puts him
at the top of the donor list?
Hypothetically?
How bad is he?
In the few hours it would take a new
LVAD to be delivered, he'll be dead.
Our responsibility is to the patient.
Lf, medically,
he's at the top of the list,
then he should get the heart.
- Hypothetically.
- Thank you, sir.
But practically? Whoever removed
the patient from the LVAD,
I expect to be given names
and there will be severe,
severe consequences.
Yes, sir.
Wait. Hold on. Dr. Hahn? Dr. Hahn!
Can't stop now, Karev. I only have a few
hours to get this heart into my guy.
Dr. Hahn.
UNOS gave the heart to Seattle Grace.
The transplant coordinator
stopped your guy from being prepped.
Oh, come on!
He has kids. They're four and five.
Do you know how long
he's been waiting for this?
He's a good person. He deserves a heart.
- I'm sorry.
- I'll bet you are.
No. I am. Believe me.
Listen,
we have a chopper waiting on the roof.
And?
You could take up fishing.
- I don't fish.
- Fishing's a lot more fun than surgery.
I have 80 percent hand function now.
Hmm. 80 percent's not enough.
Not for you.
- Fishing, huh?
- You don't fish.
Shepherd?
You don't have to thank me. I'm
sure you'll return the favor one day.
I was going to say,
please try not to kill me.
I'll do my best.
OK.
- Hmm.
- Look at that thing.
Left ventricle's excessively dilated.
He wouldn't have lasted another hour
with this heart.
No, he wouldn't have.
OK, retract that little bit right there.
OK, I am now removing the aneurysm
from the nerve cluster.
NAPs are dropping.
Arterial pressure's down 50 percent.
Did you cut the nerve root?
I don't see any discontinuity
of the nerves.
All right, let's do a reflex test
on his hand. Chief.
OK.
- Nothing.
- Damn it. Try it again.
Uh-uh.
This doesn't make sense.
I'd know if I severed a nerve.
Derek, is the arm paralyzed?
- I have to do a wake-up test.
- Derek.
There's only one person
who can help me figure out
whether or not I've damaged
the relay or not, and that's Burke.
He's been through a lot of trauma today.
I'm trying to prevent the trauma
he's going to feel
if I have to tell him he's paralyzed.
Bailey's treating us
like we're children. We're not children.
We shouldn't have to sit out here
like we're on a time-out.
It is a time-out. What we did
is way in need of a time-out.
You realize we could get kicked out
of the program for this?
Not we.
I did this.
You're probably right.
Maybe I should run.
But I'd rather be running towards
somebody than running away.
Yang? Shepherd's asking for you.
Uh, for Burke's surgery?
- Yes. Hurry up.
- Uh...
I- I can't. I'm... I'm in a time-out.
Time-out's over. Right now.
Yang, we need you.
He said marry me, right? He did?
- That really happened?
- It really happened.
It really did.
Screw this. I'm checking on Denny.
OK. How we doing?
He's at the edge of consciousness.
Very light. He should be up soon.
OK. Yang? You're up.
Oh... what? I'm sorry.
What do you need me to do?
When he comes to,
he's going to be disoriented
and he'll probably fight the intubation.
We can't numb the arm
because we need him to move his fingers.
He will be in a lot of pain.
- We need you to keep him focused, OK?
- OK. Yeah.
OK, let's, let's wake him up.
Burke?
Thank you. For calling me about Izzie.
L- I didn't do you any favors.
Well, it meant something that you
called. It meant something to me.
It didn't mean anything.
Right. OK. Sorry.
Stop saying that you're sorry!
You want to know something?
I knew.
I knew you didn't feel that way
about me.
Even during...
When we were in bed, I knew.
I knew and I still let it happen.
Because, um...
I...
I figured that...
one night with you
was better than never.
So you just stop saying
that you're sorry...
because you didn't know any better.
But I did.
And...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Meredith.
Burke, it's Cristina. I'm sorry.
Wake up. Wake up.
Wake up. Burke.
Baby, wake up. Do it for me.
Open your eyes.
Hi. Hi.
Get ready. Get ready.
Hold him down.
- Calm him down.
- Yang!
Cristina, get in there. Get in his face.
Talk to him, Cristina.
- Yang!
- Get in there!
Hold him down! Hold him down!
Calm him down! Cristina!
Scissors.
It's beautiful work, Dr. Hahn.
The hard part is still to come.
All right, let's start taking him
off bypass.
See if this heart will beat on its own.
- Nothing.
- Come on, Denny. Beat for me.
Cristina!
Hold him down, Chief. Hold his arm.
Preston? Preston, look at me!
Look at me!
Right here. Listen, listen.
Calm down. Calm down. Calm down.
Listen, there was a complication.
We can fix it.
We need you to move your fingers
on your right side.
Can you do that?
Come on, you can do this.
Look at me.
On your right hand. OK? I know. I know.
It's just you and me. We can do this.
OK. Come on. Focus. Focus.
Now you're going to move your fingers on
your right hand.
Come on, Preston. You can do it.
Move your fingers. Move your fingers.
Come on. Come on.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
- No response. Charge to 20.
- Clear.
Come on. Come on.
Come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on. Come on.
Come on. Good.
You're doing good, Dr. Burke.
OK, I need you to touch each finger
of your right hand to your thumb.
One.
Two. You're doing great.
Keep going.
- Three. Good.
- One more.
That's good.
- Dr. Hahn...
- Wait for it.
- Dr. Hahn? He...
- Just wait!
And that's how we raise the dead
in Erica Land.
Good job, Denny.
Hey.
- Camille's parents here?
- Yes.
There aren't any options.
I could do a hysterectomy,
an ovarectomy,
pick out the remaining ovaries.
We could try chemo, maybe radiation,
but the cancer's spread to her liver,
her lungs, her bowel.
- Even if we were aggressive...
- No.
I hate this.
I never get used to telling someone
their kid's going to drop dead
before she's 18.
Oh, dammit.
I'm sorry. I didn't...
I'm not usually this insensitive,
Richard, I just...
- It's just been one of those days.
- It's OK.
I'm gonna go...
I mean, do you want to go?
Oh, no, you go. They'd rather hear it
from the treating physician.
I got work to get back to. Deal
with this Denny Duquette situation.
I cut the LVAD wire.
Actually, I cut the LVAD wire.
No. I did it.
I'm the one who cut the wire.
Fine. I cut the LVAD wire.
- I'm totally innocent.
- Alex!
I wasn't here. He knows I wasn't here.
The guy's not mentally challenged.
That's not the point.
What about loyalty?
We made an agreement.
People! I know who did this. So, you
might as well come clean. I know.
With all due respect, sir, if you knew,
you wouldn't be asking us.
- I did what...
- You have your suspicions,
- but you don't actually know.
- Not for sure.
And you can't do anything to any of us
without proof, sir.
Well, one of you
compromised a patient's life.
One of you stole an organ.
One of you jeopardized the integrity
of this hospital and of UNOS.
Now, you tell me,
and you tell me right now!
All right, fine.
No surgeries.
- Sir?
- You heard. No surgeries.
No one scrubs in,
or watches from the gallery,
no one so much as goes near
the OR floor.
Until someone confesses, the five of you
will share a single patient:
Camille Travis. Whatever she wants,
the five of you will provide it!
Whatever she wants.
Now, get the hell out of my sight!
- He didn't say we were fired.
- He might as well have.
- No surgeries?
- That wasn't bad. We got off easy.
Yeah, for now. You think this is over?
I could use a good coma
right now. A nice, long coma.
There's only been three careers I've
ever wanted. Ruler of my own planet,
Wonder Woman, or a surgeon.
I don't see any invisible planes
or extra countries lying around.
I will go back and tell him.
I will tell him it was me.
And get kicked out of the program?
You will keep your mouth shut.
We all will keep our mouths shut.
- This is crap. I'm turning her in.
- Alex.
What? You said we had to stand by Izzie.
Now I get stuck catering some V.I.P.
Chick patient? I don't think so.
Alex, I am sorry and I really do
appreciate what you did for Denny.
Shut up. I only lied to Burke because
I wanted in on that transplant surgery.
I don't care about Denny and I hope
you get thrown out on your ass.
Hey! We stick together. We all did this.
Nobody's a victim.
We... we stick together.
- Damn it.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- We can handle this.
Camille Travis is a kid with cancer.
We give her what she wants for a while.
- How hard can that be?
- Harder than you think.
This is Claire and Natalie.
Camille Travis' friends.
Her very best friends
in the whole wide world.
Girls, who exactly is Camille Travis?
Like, the Chief of Surgery's niece.
And girls, what does the Chief
of Surgery's niece want, exactly?
- Like, a prom.
- No. Like, the best prom ever.
- We need a theme.
- Theme...
Ooh! Ooh! Can we have sparkly lights?
Because sparkly lights are amazing!
I didn't like teenage girls
when I was a teenage girl.
- I wore a lot of black.
- Oh!
Hmm.
I had the whole angry,
pink-hair thing going on.
I wouldn't have been
caught dead at a prom.
Oh, my mother made me go.
My date barfed on my dress
and then tried to feel me up.
Mm-hm.
There's a lot to be said
for being an adult.
Yeah.
You haven't mentioned Burke.
No.
- Well, have you checked on him?
- No.
OK, I could try harder to make you
open up and deal with the Burke thing,
or I could be neurotic and selfish
and talk about my problems.
Which would be
more supportive right now?
Selfish and neurotic, please.
Hm.
Finn says Doc's in pain.
Derek and I have to talk about whether
we should put him to sleep or not.
Finn thinks there's something going on
with me and Derek. Which there is not.
There so clearly is not.
- And Addison having that meltdown?
- Ugh.
I mean, dogs get sick and we're expected
to put them to sleep.
People get sick, we don't put them down.
We don't just give up on people.
There's nothing going on
between me and Derek.
There is a lot to be said
for being an adult.
Yeah.
- Bailey around?
- No, she was in here earlier.
Said she'd be back in a couple
of hours. The coast is clear.
You look... God, you look amazing.
They always tell you
that transplant patients rebound fast,
but, you know, to see it in person...
I have warm hands. I've never had warm
hands because of my circulation.
Feel.
Warm hands and check it out,
I have a regular heartbeat.
Yes, you do.
I should, um... I got to go.
I would stay,
but if Bailey catches me here, she'd...
And, uh, you know, the Chief has us
doing this prom thing. It's so...
But, yeah, I'm really happy for you.
You look... Whoo-hoo, Denny.
- OK. I'm going to go.
- What?
Huh?
You like your men sick and feeble?
You don't dig healthy guys?
I... I dig you.
Then why are you all swirly and twitchy?
- No, I'm not.
- Yeah, you're swirly and twitchy.
It's because I asked you to marry me.
- So you remember that?
- It's not the kind of thing I'd forget.
Yeah. Look, Denny, um...
I'm giving you an out.
Excuse me?
Well, I'm giving you an out.
I mean, you thought you were dying,
and I was saving your life,
and you know, everything was so...
So I won't hold it against you, or...
be hurt and offended if you wanna take
your proposal back.
I'm giving you an out.
I don't want an out.
You should take the out.
We can't get married.
I mean, that would be crazy. Insane.
We should date and have sex.
Plenty of sex.
When your heart gets better,
all the sex you can handle.
But marriage is, um...
- Marriage. I mean...
- OK. It's my turn now.
- But I need to...
- No, no, no. We're taking turns.
I've decided it's polite
and it keeps me from yelling.
When it's your turn again, you can talk.
For five years, I've had to live
by the choices of my doctors.
The guys that cut me open...
decided my life.
There wasn't one choice that was mine.
And now I have this heart
that beats and works.
I get to be like everybody else.
I get to make my own decisions,
have my own life,
do whatever the damn hell I choose.
Now, here's the good part.
So you listen close.
What I choose...
is you.
You're who I want to wake up with
and go to bed with
and do everything in between with.
I get a choice now.
I get to choose.
I choose you, Izzie Stevens.
OK. It's your turn again.
They're not talking.
Wagons have been circled.
I need answers.
Somebody's got to take responsibility.
I can tell you what I think happened,
what I assumed happened.
But they're the only ones that know it.
I want to meet with each of them
separately. I will break them.
- You have a dress for the prom?
- Excuse me?
I'm going to the prom. If I have to go,
everybody has to go.
What? I'm a grown woman.
Everybody goes to the prom! Everybody!
Central High? Two years ago,
they went with all black
and had purple lights and...
Everybody looked like ghouls.
Fine, we could go with all white!
I was reading Elle Girl and they...
- Are you having a seizure?
- Will that get me out of here?
Fine, let's go with seizure.
Seizure beats the hell
out of a 45-minute conversation
about what color balloons
we're gonna buy.
- You need to get a life!
- Chief's niece. Chief's niece.
It's OK. The hot ones are always mean.
It's like a rule or something.
- Doesn't he remind you of Nate Sims?
- Totally.
- He's totally Nate.
- No, I'm not Nate.
- Don't engage.
- Nate broke up with Camille
the first time she had cancer.
The other thing about the hot ones:
They're usually cowards.
Don't you dare try to judge us
for trying to make our friend,
who just happens to be dying of cancer,
happy.
The color does matter. Maybe not to you.
But it does matter.
Not to bother you, but...
What? One of you better spit out
the problem right now!
The problem is the colors and
the balloons and the "Under the Sea. "
"No, it's Titanic. " "Let's go with
Tears in Heaven. " "No, too morbid. "
"It should be pink. " "It should be red. "
"It should be a rainbow!"
He's saying we're very hopeful
that you speak teenage girl.
Silver and white.
It's mystical and magical.
Ever see fashion week in New York?
Silver and white runways and backdrops.
No matter what color the clothes are,
they pop.
- They pop?
- They pop.
- Sounds good.
- Yeah.
O'Malley and Karev, get 500 balloons
in silver and white and 100 in black.
Shiny black, not the matte.
Yang, stick with Camille,
keep her spirits up.
Make sure she has her shoes, dress
and makeup on standby.
Grey, get with Patricia.
Make sure we can rope off
the second-floor nurses' station
and waiting area. And get menus.
Got it?
Oh, no, no.
You don't get to look at me like that.
No, you compromised my medical license.
You nearly killed a patient,
lied to the Chief of Surgery,
and made me look bad.
We are doing this prom
and doing it right. Move!
There's an emergency appendectomy
happening in OR 1 as we speak.
Again, I'm sorry.
Stop saying you're sorry
when you're not.
You make me sick.
- Nice.
- Hey.
Hey.
- Can we talk?
- Yeah.
Hold it.
- Hey.
- You never called.
- What?
- Last night.
We had plans and you went off with Izzie
and never called.
- A lot of stuff went down last night.
- I know, everybody heard.
- So what exactly happened?
- I can't talk about it.
Come on. I'm not going to tell, George.
It's me.
Look, it's Vegas. What happened
in that room stays in that room.
- OK. Yeah, I get it.
- Hey.
Do you want to go to prom with me?
No, George. No, I don't want to go
to prom with you.
What was that about?
- She said she loved me.
- Oh.
Oh.
Oh! Hey.
- I've been calling your cell all night.
- Um... oh, well,
uh, it's a long story,
which essentially ends with me
inviting you to a prom.
An actual prom?
A... corsages and tuxedos?
Yeah, I know it's stupid, but...
No. I'm in. I loved prom.
I mean, I don't want to brag
or anything, but I was crowned king.
Really?
You were that kid in high school?
- What is wrong with being that kid?
- Nothing. It's very cute, actually.
- Hello.
- Hi.
What are you doing here?
Doc had some seizures last night.
Pretty serious. The cancer
spread to his brain. I'm sorry.
- Hey.
How's Preston?
He's recovering nicely.
- Addison...
- I don't want to talk about it.
I mean we've come so far. You forgave me
for Mark and we're trying.
- We are.
- We are trying.
We're trying.
And I was jealous
when there was no need to be.
Right?
Addison?
- What?
- Will you go to the prom with me?
I went to college
on a wrestling scholarship.
I played baseball, some basketball.
But we'll go with football.
What does football have to do
with who cut the LVAD wires?
Let's say you were drafted to a team
that wasn't your first pick.
You know, you don't like the players.
You hate the way they play the game.
You even think the quarterback
is full of crap.
Now the quarterback's a pain in the ass
that you don't owe a damn thing to,
but... it's your team. You don't quit.
You don't talk to the press.
You don't bitch to the coach.
You just... you just go out there
every Sunday
and you make the blocks and you take
the hits and you play to win.
You show up and you suit up and you
play. Because it's your freaking team.
I know your type.
You're a surgical junkie.
Yes, sir?
It's not going to be easy for you
to be away from the OR that long.
No, sir.
And if you want to get back to the OR,
you're going to tell me
what I need to know, aren't you?
You're right.
It's not easy for me
to be away from the OR.
to sit in front of you
or any other authority figure
for that matter,
and not be able to give you
the exact answer you want to hear.
I've always been the one
with the answers.
But right now, sir, I don't have any.
- Dr. Yang...
- How do you keep your edge, sir?
I watch you,
and you've been doing this a long time,
and you're clean. You're focused.
You are the job. Nothing gets to you.
And the thing is, sir, I was like that.
Until I got here.
Until I actually started doing this job
and now everything is...
- is fuzzy.
- That's besides the point.
No, see, sir, this is the point.
Because I can't tell you.
What happened in that room...
I can't tell you.
And before, I could have.
No guilt, no loyalties, no problem.
Before... before I wouldn't
have even been in that room.
I wouldn't have gotten involved.
I would have never frozen in surgery.
And I would have told him
what I thought he should do.
I had an edge, sir.
I had an edge and I've lost it.
And I need it. I need it back.
So if you could just tell me
how you keep yours
and how not to be affected,
I know I could be a great surgeon.
So, if you could just give me the
answers, I would really appreciate it.
You're excused, Dr. Yang.
- But...
- You're excused.
I'll tell you. I'll tell you who cut the
LVAD wires, sir, if you...
No, you won't. I don't want to know.
Not from you.
Yeah, I have the answers,
but I can't tell them to you.
I'm not going to be responsible
for you becoming less human.
I'm a pretty girl.
- What?
- I'm not being arrogant. It's just...
Just a fact. For a long time, I made
a career from my looks, so I get it.
I'm a pretty girl.
And not in a "from-a-certain-angle" way.
In an obvious way. It's the
blonde thing. And the big boobs thing.
Big boobs are key to "obvious" pretty.
- Dr. Stevens...
- It's how men see me.
I'm not a smart girl or an interesting
girl. I'm a pretty girl.
The blonde and the boobs confuse guys
into thinking that I'm someone else.
And I'm used to it. I'm used to them
walking away when they realize...
But then Denny goes
and asks me to marry him.
Is that why you cut the wires?
He doesn't make me feel
like I'm a pretty girl.
He makes me feel like...
like me.
I think he might know me.
And so, if I did cut the LVAD wire,
and I'm not saying that I did,
but if I did...
then no. I don't feel guilty.
And I know that I should.
And I would if it were anybody else.
But I can't feel anything but happy.
Are you gonna...
say anything or?
I'm not going to break.
I'm starting to get a little
freaked out, but I won't break.
It's not because I don't care.
I do care what you think about me.
I do... care.
I just can't tell you
what you want to hear.
Which seems to be a theme in my life
right now.
Just 'cause you can't say something
doesn't mean you don't want to.
You can be with a person and be happy
with them, and not love them.
And you can love someone
and not want to be with them.
You don't need to... love someone...
to want them.
But it's frustrating.
When your brain says what you want and
what you actually want don't match up,
it's exhausting.
And... well, it's complicated.
But that's life.
And life...
sucks.
I've known you for a long time.
I know your mother and father.
And I know, beyond a shadow of a doubt,
that you did not cut those LVAD wires.
Meredith,
I need you to tell me who did it.
I've been going over and over this in
my mind trying to piece this together.
It was you. You were the reason
my parents broke up.
And it wasn't just an affair.
She really loved you.
It wasn't just this cheap thing where
she didn't tell you she was married.
It wasn't all a lie.
She left her husband for you.
But you stayed with your wife
because it was the right thing to do.
Maybe safe, but she was the right person
for you to be with.
And let's face it, my mother?
Nothing wrong with being safe.
Being with the good guy
because he's good.
And we are talking about forever here.
You've never regretted your decision.
You've never looked back.
Right?
Finn says we need to make
a decision about Doc.
- Good for Finn.
- Can we just do this?
- Fine.
- We may have to put him to sleep.
Whatever.
Can we do this one thing together
without arguing?
What if he can get better?
He's not going to get better.
You know that.
Well, Finn thinks we should do it today,
then. So I guess I'll go over there.
- Be there.
- What time?
Are you coming?
He's my dog.
- Denny!
- What did I tell you?
Visiting hours aren't for another hour.
You are no longer his doctor.
Come back when the visitors come.
- I would, but I can't wait.
- Lxnay on the insubordinationay.
- But it's my turn.
- If the Chief finds out you were...
Hold on. It's her turn.
Yes. My answer is yes.
Oh, now see, you're going to make my
heart stop beating and it's brand new.
I will call security on you.
OK. I will come back
during visiting hours.
And it's prom,
so I'll show you my dress.
OK.
I'm going.
Izzie.
You did good.
I tricked her into marrying me.
How smart am I?
We're throwing a prom.
Chief's making us throw a prom.
O'Malley mentioned.
- George came to see you?
- He's my friend.
Oh.
I won't bear a grudge.
What did you?
I have to take care of me.
I don't expect you to take care of me.
But I have to take care of me.
If this...
If you can't stay here for this...
I won't bear a grudge.
Are you going to tell Shepherd about...
Not yet.
I'm, uh...
OK. There's a couple of forms
you need to sign.
I only need one signature.
- You?
- It's fine. Here, I'll sign.
So, how do we do this?
I'll give Doc an injection of terazole
to make him sleepy,
then I'll give him an IV injection
of phenobarbitol.
- And that will stop his heart?
- Yes.
And what do we do after? With his body?
We can... We have the means
to dispose of it for you.
That's fine. Go ahead.
We can't throw him away
like he's garbage.
- We would never...
- He's our dog, Derek.
There's that, uh, clearing
by the trailer.
Overlooking the water?
We can, uh, bury him there.
That sounds nice.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
I'm so sorry, Doc.
I'm sorry too.
- It's the hospital. I got to go.
- OK.
OK.
OK. I'll begin.
Shh, shh.
It's OK. It's OK. It's OK.
It's OK.
He's gone.
- Meredith?
- I have to go home and change.
- I'll see you later, OK?
- Meredith.
I'm sorry. For your loss.
Yeah.
You know, the thing is he wasn't
really my dog for that long.
He was more Derek's dog.
Meredith.
- He was a good dog.
- He was.
Oh, I'm too tired for this.
Where's your husband, Dr. Bailey?
Uh, at home with the baby.
Thought you would
at least get to get out of this.
- Why?
- Well, with Burke upstairs.
What happened to him, I'm sure
the Chief would have let you out.
Yeah.
Oh, God.
- Hey.
You seen Meredith?
I don't think she's here yet.
This whole thing brings back very
traumatic memories
of being a band geek with braces
and the lisp.
Spending the whole evening with
Skippy Gold talking about Star Wars.
- I hated Star Wars.
- Hmm. Thank God.
- This is terrible.
- It's bad.
So, you want to, um, dance?
Love to.
Can I cut in?
What did you say to my boyfriend
to make him that scared of you?
I'm a frightening man, Cammie.
No, you're not.
Where Brian's concerned, yes, I am.
Be kind to him.
He loves me. I've been loved.
And that's something everyone
should have once in their life.
I've been loved.
I have that.
Thank you for the prom, Uncle Richard.
You're welcome.
Hey, I was looking for yo...
Where are you going?
I'm wearing a dress, have on heels,
shaved my legs. I'm going to the prom.
- You said you didn't want to go.
- I said I didn't want to go with you.
Callie!
I said I love you. I said it.
I said it out loud to your face.
And ever since, you...
I've never said that to a guy before.
Never. And now I am just this idiot who
says I love you and then gets avoided!
No. I'm not avoiding you.
I promise.
You going to say it back?
- No.
- I'm humiliated.
No. George. Let me go.
George, let me go!
- Wait.
- Let me go. Let me go.
Stop fighting me!
If I say it back, you'll know I'm just
saying it because you said it to me.
When... when I say I love you...
I want to mean it,
because...
You just have to give me
some time to mean it.
I hate that I'm so into you.
You're a lot hotter
than my last prom date.
- Is that a compliment?
- Maybe.
- It feels like a compliment.
- Well, then it is.
Well, keep it up. You might get lucky.
Well, how lucky are we talking?
Are we talking kind of lucky?
Or are we talking
really, seriously lucky?
You have been a very patient man
and I appreciate it.
What?
Liz, uh... Liz was my wife.
And when she died...
You do this thing, you know,
where you stop making plans.
Because you had plans,
but then there was a car crash
and your plans disappeared.
So you just...
I just try and get
from sunup till sundown.
That's as far into the future
as I can handle.
And I've been fine with that. I have.
But right now, looking at you...
Damn, I have all kinds of plans.
Don't freak out.
I'm not.
- You're not?
- No. You have plans.
I have plans.
- You all right?
- Yeah, just, uh... hot.
And, uh, claustrophobic.
There's a patient I forgot to check on.
I'm just going to run and splash
some cold water on my face.
- Be right back, OK?
- OK.
- All right?
- Meredith.
- Leave me alone.
Meredith.
- I want to make sure you're all right.
No! I'm not all right! OK?
Are you satisfied? I'm not all right!
Because you have a wife
and you call me a whore and our dog died
and now you're looking at me.
Stop looking at me!
I'm not looking at you.
I am not looking at you!
You are looking at me! And you watch me.
And Finn has plans and I like Finn.
He's perfect for me!
And I'm really trying here to be happy!
And I can't breathe! I can't breathe
with you looking at me like that!
So just stop!
Do you think I want to look at you?
That I wouldn't rather
be looking at my wife?
I'm married. I have responsibilities.
She doesn't drive me crazy.
She doesn't make it impossible
for me to feel normal!
She doesn't make me
sick to my stomach
thinking about my veterinarian
touching her with his hands!
Oh, man, I would give anything
not to be looking at you!
- Oh! You look nice.
- Thank you. So do you. Hot date?
Nah. This thing is cheesy.
I wouldn't waste a decent chick on this.
You heading in?
- Yeah. Just going to see Denny first.
- Oh. OK.
$ I'm on my knees
$ Only memories
$ Are left for me
$ To hold
$ Don't know how
$ But I'll get by
$ Slowly pull myself
$ Together
$ I'll get through this
$ There's no escape
$ So keep me safe
$ This feels so unreal
$ Nothing comes easily
$ Fill this empty space
$ Nothing is like it seems
$ Turn my grief to grace
$ Nothing is like it was
$ Nothing comes easily
$ Where do I begin?
$ Nothing can bring me peace
$ I've lost everything
$ I just want to feel your embrace $
- What does this mean?
- Uh, I had panties on.
- Black. Do you see them?
- Meredith, what does this mean?
Help me look for them. Fix your tie.
Meredith. What does this mean?
Oh, the nurse told me to come find you.
You have to come now. It's Izzie.
Wait, wait, wait.
OK, go.
Chief.
Did my internship here.
My residency.
Came back here the minute
my fellowship was done.
The day they told me I would be Chief,
I was standing right there in that OR
when I got the news.
Spent my whole career in this hospital.
My whole life.
Sir...
Denny Duquette
died at 7:42 this evening.
Damn it.
What happened?
I didn't think you guys
would want me to go to the Chief...
- Where is she?
- She's in there with him.
Izzie...
I think it was a stroke.
He was prone to blood clots.
A clot could have formed on his sutures
and traveled to his brain.
It only takes a second.
Iz...
Dr. Hahn did a beautiful job
on the surgery.
But I don't know
why I didn't think of blood clots.
He died all alone.
He was alone.
There was nothing you could have done.
I changed my dress three times.
I wanted to look nice.
I would have been here sooner...
but I couldn't figure out
which dress to wear.
Izzie.
We shouldn't be in here.
There are things they need...
They need to move him.
Take him to the morgue.
You can't stay here. I know you want to.
Can you please... please just get out?
I want to be alone with Denny.
Izzie, that's not Denny.
Shut up.
Iz. That's not Denny.
The minute his heart stopped beating,
he stopped being Denny.
Now, I know you love him,
but he also loved you.
And a guy that loves you like that, he
doesn't want you to do this to yourself.
Because it's not Denny. Not anymore.
An hour ago he was proposing.
And now...
And now he's going to the morgue.
Isn't that ridiculous?
Isn't that the most ridiculous
piece of crap you've ever heard?
Come on.
- I'm sorry, these are ridic... Hey.
- Hi.
- Where've you been?
- Uh, I was with...
- Shepherd.
- Yes.
Uh, have you seen Bailey's interns?
Grey? Yang? I'm looking
for Izzie Stevens in particular.
- No. No.
- Chief.
It was me.
I cut his LVAD wire.
I did it. No one helped me.
And now...
I thought I was a surgeon, but...
I can't.
I thought I was a surgeon, but I am not.
So I quit.
Izzie.
I guess that...
puts an end to the evening.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I guess it does.
Come on. I'll drive you home.
Meredith?
www.tvsubtitles.net