Narrator (Meredith Grey) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Previously on Grey's Anatomy.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): How hot is the sex?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You know, some people would call this a relationship.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): It's just that I hardly know anything about you.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): We're having sex every night.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I think I deserve details.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You have more details than us.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): So it makes a hot shot doc leave a big apple for Seattle.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Thanks for the coffee.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Adoption?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Keeping the baby?
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I know this is a difficult decision.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I'm not interested.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I am not your sister!
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I am a man!
Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You need to get laid.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): See that nurse over there?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): She's single, she's got red hair.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mr. Franklin OR Olivia Harper (PVM): Go ask her out.
Nurse (possibly Olivia Harper) / Olivia Harper (PVM): Smooth moves, Doctor.
Meredith Grey / Olivia Harper (PVM): Who is that?
Richard Webber / Olivia Harper (PVM): That's Dad.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Olivia Harper (PVM): What's her diagnosis?
Richard Webber / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Alzheimer's.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): And she doesn't want anyone to know?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I'm the only person she'll allow to see her.
Dr. Meredith Gray: Secrets can't hide in science.
Dr. Meredith Gray: Medicine has a way of exposing the lies.
Dr. Meredith Gray: Within the walls of the hospital, the truth is stripped bare.
Dr. Meredith Gray: How we keep our secrets outside the hospital, well, that's a little different.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): George, you locked the door.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I need to take a shower.
Dr. George O'Malley: I'll be out in a minute.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): What are you doing in there?
Dr. George O'Malley: It's private.
Meredith Grey / Unknown (PVM): Oh.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Oh, God.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I'm sorry.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I get it.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I didn't mean to interrupt.
Dr. George O'Malley: No, it's not that.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It's OK, Dick.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Your time.
Dr. George O'Malley: I am not doing what you think I'm doing.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You know what?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): There's really no need to explain.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I'll wait.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You just finish.
Dr. George O'Malley: No, I'm coming.
Dr. George O'Malley: I'm coming out.
Dr. Meredith Gray: One thing is certain.
Dr. Meredith Gray: Whatever it is we're trying to hide, we're never ready for that moment when the truth gets naked.
Miss Henry: This is Miss Henry from the nursing home.
Miss Henry: I'm calling about your mother.
Meredith Grey / Miss Henry OR Olivia Harper (PVM): Is she all right?
Miss Henry: Oh, it's nothing like that.
Meredith Grey / Olivia Harper (PVM): Can I call you later, then?
Miss Henry: Uh, I just wanted to... I have to go.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Oh, my God.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Who is calling you at this hour?
Dr. Meredith Gray: It's the wrong number.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): There's no reason to be ashamed.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It's normal, healthy even.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Well, I'm not ashamed, because I wasn't doing anything.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I don't have to.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I have a girlfriend.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): An imaginary girlfriend?
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): An actual girlfriend.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You know what?
Izzie Stevens / Miss Henry OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It's no big deal.
Izzie Stevens / Miss Henry (PVM): You don't have to lie.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I get it.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You have needs.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): What is going on out here?
George O'Malley / Unknown (PVM): Nothing.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Nothing?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He's freaked out because I caught him playing with little Jimmy and the twins.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I have a girlfriend.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): OK.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Aren't you gonna get that?
Dr. Meredith Gray: I'm over at the hospital.
Dr. Meredith Gray: It's not.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Breakfast?
Dr. Meredith Gray: That's the problem with secrets.
Dr. Meredith Gray: Like misery, they love company.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Franklin (PVM): No, look, I told you people I'm not coming in for a counseling session.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Franklin (PVM): I know all my options.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Franklin (PVM): Yeah, uh, well, I made my decision and I made my appointment.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Franklin (PVM): I'll be there on the 16th.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mr. Franklin OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): They pile up and up until they take over everything.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I paged you last night.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Oh, I wasn't on the call.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): That's not why I paged you.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You could give me your home number.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Um, Burke.
Preston Burke / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I gotta go.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Until you don't have room for anything else.
Dr. Meredith Gray: Until you're so full of secrets, you feel like you're going to burst.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Olivia Harper (PVM): I had a really good time the other night.
Olivia Harper / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Olivia Harper (PVM): Yeah, me too.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Olivia Harper (PVM): Uh, you, uh, feeling okay and everything?
Olivia Harper / Olivia Harper (PVM): I'm good.
George O'Malley / Olivia Harper (PVM): You're great.
George O'Malley / Olivia Harper (PVM): Now that I got to see you, why?
Olivia Harper / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Oh, no reason.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I'm good, too.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You know, really good.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You know.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): But, um...
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): A little itchy.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Olivia Harper (PVM): George.
Dr. George O'Malley: Hey.
Olivia Harper: Olivia.
Olivia Harper: Hi, Dr. Stevens.
Olivia Harper / Dr. George O'Malley OR Olivia Harper (PVM): I'll see you later.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): OK.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Bye.
George O'Malley / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Yeah.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): She's into me.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Way to go, George.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): She's cute.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): So this morning you really weren't?
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Any time you want to apologize.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Then what were you doing in the bathroom for so long?
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I have to go.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I know I'm pretty to look at and all, George, but back up.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I need to ask you something.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I'm waiting.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): OK, I seem to be having this skin thing going on, like a rash, really.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): And I think I know what it is, but I can't get close enough to tell for sure.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Let's see it.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It's kind of located in a private.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You're Dr. George.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It's called a penis.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You have a rash on your penis?
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I think I can describe it.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Um, it's... red.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Look, let's just... Come on, just show me your junk so we can get this over with.
Cristina Yang / Bill OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): So?
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Dude, you've got syphilis.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Patient presented with abdominal pain and blood in his urine.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Once his workup came back unrevealing, the urologist suggested a cystoscopy.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Reason?
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Let's get a look inside the bladder.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Appreciate you doing this, Preston.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I know this is a little out of your field.
Dr. Preston Burke / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): That's not a problem.
Dr. Preston Burke / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): It gives my interns something to do.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I have a feeling you keep them plenty busy.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): We're in the same frat at Tulane.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): It's gone from torturing pledges to torturing interns.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Am I right?
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Be very careful how you two answer that.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I could tell some stories.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Bill, you have a camera snaking up your mojo.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): It's not the time to cross me.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): It isn't anything too serious.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): That's what this procedure will tell us.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You don't worry about anything but growing my godson in there.
Pregnant Patient / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He kicks like you wouldn't believe.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Badass, just like his father.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Move a little to the right.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Your other right.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): There.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): What do you see?
Dr. Preston Burke / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): What is it?
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Could be any number of things.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): O'Malley, take a biopsy of the mass.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Dr. Karev, schedule a CT.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Bill (PVM): Let's not worry until we have to.
Dr. Preston Burke / Bill (PVM): That's too much damage.
Dr. Preston Burke / Bill (PVM): We'll have to remove most of the colon instead of a local resection.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): More suture.
Mr. Franklin / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): And what's with these damn lights in here?
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley OR Olivia Harper (PVM): Mr. Franklin, how long has your abdomen been like this?
Mr. Franklin: It's been getting bigger for a while.
Mrs. Franklin / Mr. Franklin OR Mr. Franklin (PVM): I told him there was something wrong.
Mrs. Franklin / Mr. Franklin (PVM): No one gets fat like this so fast.
Mrs. Franklin / Mr. Franklin (PVM): I told him.
Mrs. Franklin / Mr. Franklin (PVM): Everybody told him.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He has dullness to percussion and spider angiomas.
Mrs. Franklin / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mr. Franklin (PVM): What's all that mean?
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): It means we have to admit your father and run some tests.
Mrs. Franklin / Mr. Franklin (PVM): Great.
Mrs. Franklin / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mr. Franklin OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): What's that going to cost us this time?
Mr. Franklin / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Alice, don't.
Lab Technician / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Results for George O'Malley.
Lab Technician / Bill (PVM): I don't see it here.
Lab Technician / Bill OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): What's the patient's name?
George O'Malley / Bill OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): O'Malley, George.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley OR Bill OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Look, it's just a simple blood test.
Lab Technician / Bill OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Here we go.
George O'Malley / Miss Henry (PVM): Franklin, Jordan, I need this back ASAP.
Lab Technician / Bill (PVM): What a shocker.
Alex Karev / Miss Henry (PVM): Hey, did you get something good?
George O'Malley / Miss Henry (PVM): Syphilis?
George O'Malley / Miss Henry (PVM): It's not surgical.
Alex Karev / Miss Henry (PVM): Who has syphilis?
George O'Malley / Olivia Harper (PVM): Excuse us.
Alex Karev / Olivia Harper (PVM): Sorry.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mr. Franklin (PVM): You have syphilis?
Dr. Alex Karev: I don't know how this happened.
Alex Karev / Miss Henry (PVM): Of course you do.
Alex Karev / Miss Henry OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): God, Olivia must really be getting around.
Dr. George O'Malley: Olivia, she's not like that.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It's a new millennium, George.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): The only people who aren't like that are the Amish, and apparently you.
Dr. George O'Malley: You don't know.
Dr. George O'Malley: Maybe I've been sleeping around.
Dr. George O'Malley: Maybe I got ladies.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Shut up.
Dr. George O'Malley: What am I gonna do?
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It's no biggie.
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Couple doses of penicillin will knock it right out.
Dr. George O'Malley: What am I gonna do about Olivia?
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Well, for starters, stop sleeping with her.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Unless you want that thing to fall off.
Dr. George O'Malley: Okay, that is twice.
Dr. George O'Malley: That you've trash-talked the girl that I could one day potentially, well, not love, but like a whole lot.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): If she gave it to you, you have to tell her.
Dr. George O'Malley: Fine.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): She didn't give it to you.
Dr. George O'Malley: She was a virgin when you met.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You still have to tell her so she can get tested.
Dr. George O'Malley: Oh, yeah?
Dr. George O'Malley: How am I gonna tell her?
Dr. George O'Malley: Uh, hey, Olivia, how you doing?
Dr. George O'Malley: By the way, I got the CIF.
Dr. George O'Malley: How about you?
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Well, maybe not quite like that.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): No, it's good advice.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Really good advice.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Thank you very much.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Bill (PVM): Retract here.
Surgical Nurse / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Here.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Bill (PVM): Oh, this just isn't holding.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Meredith Gray OR Bill (PVM): Give me a bigger retractor, please.
Surgical Nurse / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Sorry, Doctor.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): It wasn't you.
Richard Webber / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Dr. Bailey, you can finish this.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Thank you, Chief.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: I appreciate the opportunity.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I gotta say, George, I didn't think you had it in you.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It's always the quiet ones.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): So who's the woman?
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): None of your business.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Oh, come on.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Who gave you the cooties on the playground?
Dr. Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You must have had something like this before, right?
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I never talk about my penis with other men.
Richard Webber / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I don't know, either, normally.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): We better get Burke.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Mr. Franklin?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You have a condition known as ascites.
Alice Franklin / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Oh, my god.
Mr. Franklin / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I knew it was terrible.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Just means there's fluid in the peritoneal cavity, the abdomen.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): And the swelling is pressing against your lungs, which is why you're having trouble breathing.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): In your case, it looks like a symptom of liver disease.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): And it all comes together.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Alice, not now.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Is there something we should know?
Mr. Franklin / Bill OR Mr. Franklin (PVM): I drink a bit.
Unknown / Mr. Franklin (PVM): That's the understatement of the year.
Unknown / Mr. Franklin (PVM): That's enough out of you.
Alice / Dr. George O'Malley OR Mr. Franklin (PVM): Hey, I'm only here for mom, to make sure you don't pull any of your usual crap.
Doctor (likely Alex Karev) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): There's definitely a growth protruding into the bladder.
Unknown / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): But look at the edges.
Unknown / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I don't think it's a tumor.
Unknown / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Kind of shaped like an ovary.
Attending Physician (likely Dr. Bailey) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): That the flip answer you're going to give your patient, Dr. Karev?
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): This is one of my oldest friends.
Attending Physician (likely Dr. Bailey) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You might want to take this seriously.
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I'm sorry, sir.
Attending Physician (likely Dr. Bailey) / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You better be.
Lab Technician / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I got the rest of the labs back.
Lab Technician / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): They did a chromosome analysis of the tissue.
Lab Technician / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You won't believe this.
Alex Karev / Bill (PVM): Bill has an ovary?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Miss Henry OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): According to his daughter, Mr. Franklin is a heavy drinker.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Six to eight drinks a day.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): An alcoholic by any standard.
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Protocol?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Schedule a paracentesis.
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Reason?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Draining the fluid will relieve the pressure from the lungs.
Attending Physician (likely Dr. Bailey) / Mr. Franklin OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Good.
Attending Surgeon / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): But don't schedule it.
Attending Surgeon / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Do it.
George / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You want us to do the procedure?
Attending Surgeon / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You've seen one, right?
George / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Absolutely.
Attending Surgeon / Mr. Franklin OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Well, now do one.
Izzie / Mr. Franklin (PVM): I've never seen one.
Attending Surgeon / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Miss Henry (PVM): You're about to.
George / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Oh, my god.
Izzie / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): God, an ovary.
Alex / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Kind of gives new meaning to the term metrosexual.
Izzie / Olivia Harper (PVM): Hi, George.
George / Olivia Harper OR Olivia Harper (PVM): Olivia.
Alex / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): What am I, invisible?
George / Olivia Harper (PVM): Alex.
Izzie / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You go ahead.
Alex / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I'll catch up with you later.
Olivia / Olivia Harper (PVM): About time I got you alone today.
George / Olivia Harper OR Olivia Harper (PVM): Olivia.
Olivia / Olivia Harper OR Olivia Harper (PVM): What time is your shift done?
Olivia / Olivia Harper OR Bill OR Olivia Harper (PVM): Because mine's over at 8, and I thought maybe you could come over.
George / Olivia Harper OR Bill OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Olivia, I need to tell you something.
Olivia / Bill (PVM): What's wrong?
Olivia / Bill (PVM): You're breaking up with me?
George / Miss Henry (PVM): What?
George / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): No.
Olivia / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Oh, no, really.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): No, it's just.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Okay, you're the only person that I've been with in a long time.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I mean, not unusually long or anything.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Just a normal amount of a long time.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): But it wouldn't matter to me if you've been with someone else.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Maybe you have.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I'm not accusing you of anything or judging you or handing out scarlet letters or anything.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You're a woman.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): A very attractive woman.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Of course, you've been with other men.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Not that you've been with a lot of men.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It's not like you're a prostitute.
Olivia Harper / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Prostitute?
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): No, not a prostitute.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): No, opposite of a prostitute.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): A lady.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You're very ladylike.
Olivia Harper / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I mean, you're very bendy, but... George, breathe.
George O'Malley / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Okay.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It's just, okay, here's the... I really like you, Olivia.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I like you a lot.
Olivia Harper / Olivia Harper (PVM): Well, I like you too.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I have syphilis.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You dropped a retractor.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Fine.
Dr. Burke / Bill (PVM): A few weeks ago, I was operating, and a vision in my right eye became blurry.
Dr. Burke / Bill (PVM): After a few hours, it was fine.
Dr. Burke / Bill (PVM): It's come back again.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Franklin (PVM): Did you have it checked out?
Dr. Webber / Mr. Franklin (PVM): Examination was normal.
Dr. Webber / Mr. Franklin (PVM): My ophthalmologist tells me I'm just getting older.
Dr. Webber / Mr. Franklin (PVM): But do you know what a decline in my visual acuity can mean?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): I'll set up some tests.
Dr. Webber / Mr. Franklin (PVM): Sure.
Dr. Webber / Mr. Franklin (PVM): I know how the rumor mill runs around here.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Franklin (PVM): Let's just keep this to ourselves.
Dr. Webber / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Absolutely.
George O'Malley / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Yeah.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Do you think she's talking about me?
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): She's absolutely talking about you.
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Dude, that's a good thing.
George O'Malley / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): No.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): No, it's not.
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Georgia, get a clue.
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Syphilis is the best thing that ever happened to you.
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): In their eyes, you're a player.
Cristina Yang / Miss Henry (PVM): Hey, Sif boy.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You told her?
Izzie Stevens / Miss Henry OR Mr. Franklin (PVM): Just Christina.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Sif boy.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It's got a nice ring to it.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Franklin OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Kind of like Superboy, only diseased.
George O'Malley / Mr. Franklin (PVM): Izzy didn't have to say a word.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Franklin (PVM): Around here, the only thing that spreads faster than disease is gossip.
George O'Malley / Mr. Franklin OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It's not true.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mr. Franklin OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Just because Izzy can't keep her mouth shut doesn't mean everyone knows.
Unknown (likely a surgical team member or intern) / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mr. Franklin OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Hey, George.
Unknown (likely another intern or surgical team member) / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): How are you feeling?
Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Sorry about the syphilis.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Everybody in this hospital knows.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Knows you're a player.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You're disturbed.
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): True.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Everybody's got a secret.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Just be glad yours is out in the open.
Dr. George O'Malley: Oh, yeah?
Dr. George O'Malley: Alex, what's yours?
Dr. Alex Karev: Show me yours, and I'll show you mine.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I bet you've got some seriously kinky skeletons in your closet.
Dr. Alex Karev: What's in my closet is none of your business.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Well, I don't have any secrets.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): My life is boring.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Everybody's got something to hide.
Dr. Preston Burke / Bill (PVM): Well, the mass we found is not a tumor.
Bill: Well, that's good, right?
Bill: Everything's got to be better than cancer.
Dr. Preston Burke / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Well, that's where it gets a little tricky.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): The chromosomal tests have revealed that your body contains DNA from two different embryos that merged in the womb at the very beginning of development.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): In rare cases, such as yours, the condition can produce gonadal hermaphroditism.
Bill: I'm hearing scary words here, Preston.
Bill: You know, pay cable kind of words.
Dr. Preston Burke / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): In English, the mass on your bladder is an ovary.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Don't worry, we're going to remove it.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): We have an excellent gynecological surgeon on staff.
Dr. George O'Malley: You're telling me I'm a guy with an ovary?
Alex / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It's simply a quirk of nature, man.
Dr. George O'Malley: What am I going to tell Holly?
Izzie / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Bill (PVM): I bet you're going to be fine.
Dr. George O'Malley: I'm still a man, right?
Alex / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): A man's man, a Kappa man.
Alex / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I mean.
Dr. George O'Malley: You know, my sex life.
Alex / Dr. George O'Malley OR Bill (PVM): You been having any problems?
Patient (not main group) / Dr. George O'Malley OR Bill (PVM): Was it my very pregnant wife that gave it away?
Alex / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Come on, man.
Izzie / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Don't worry.
Alex / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You never knew it was there.
Izzie / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You won't miss it when it's gone.
Dr. George O'Malley: Are you sure you know what you're doing?
Izzie / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It's a shot of penicillin, George.
Izzie / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Be grateful I'm even doing this.
Izzie / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I've already seen more of you than I ever wanted to.
Alex / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I'll be fighting nightmares for a week.
Dr. George O'Malley: OK, you know what?
Dr. George O'Malley: Forget this.
Izzie / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Do you want to get rid of the CIF or not?
Alex / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Just shut up and drop them.
Dr. George O'Malley: I can't believe this.
Dr. George O'Malley: Meredith, go away!
Dr. Meredith Gray: Oh, George, I thought you could use some moral support.
Dr. George O'Malley: No, no moral support.
Dr. George O'Malley: I'm indisposed here.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): George, it's not a big deal.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): And you have a cute butt.
Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I have a cute butt, too.
Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You want to see?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Oh, get out.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You're doing it wrong.
Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Be my guest.
George O'Malley / Miss Henry (PVM): What?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Olivia Harper (PVM): Alex!
Alex Karev / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Hey!
Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): What are we doing here?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Breaking George's spirit.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Caring George's Sith.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I don't like needles.
Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Good thing you became a doctor.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Other side.
George O'Malley / Mr. Franklin (PVM): Izzy?
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Franklin (PVM): Yeah?
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Franklin OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Uh, Mr. Franklin's procedure's been scheduled for after lunch.
George O'Malley / Mr. Franklin OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): What are we doing?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): We are saving George from the future of festering sores and insanity.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Oh, cute butt.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Told ya.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): It is cute.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Like a baby's.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You know, I've spent hours, days, years imagining myself half naked in a room with three women.
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): The reality is so much better.
Cristina Yang / Miss Henry OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I think he's going to cry.
Miss Henry: Hi, it's Miss Henry again.
Miss Henry: Is this a better time?
Miss Henry: Sorry about this morning.
Miss Henry: I wasn't alone.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Miss Henry OR Olivia Harper (PVM): And what were you calling about?
Miss Henry: I just wanted to remind you that tonight's our monthly family dinner.
Miss Henry: You know you haven't been to any of our family functions.
George O'Malley / Miss Henry (PVM): You have to understand, I'm a surgical intern, so my time isn't my own.
Miss Henry: Our residents really respond to these events.
Miss Henry: They always enjoy themselves.
Miss Henry: which is so rare.
Miss Henry: I think it's important you attend.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I'll be there.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I'll try to be there.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I'll definitely try.
Patricia / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I've cleared some time for your MRI.
Dr. Webber / Mr. Franklin OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Good.
Dr. Webber / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Let's get going.
Patricia / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): OK.
Patricia / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Sorry to bother you with this, Chief.
Patricia / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): We've got kind of a situation.
Dr. Richard Webber: What now?
Patricia / Mr. Franklin OR Bill (PVM): Three interns, four residents, and six nurses on this surgical floor have been diagnosed with
Patricia / Mr. Franklin (PVM): Syphilis.
Patricia / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): There are over 70,000 new cases every year.
Patricia / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Undiagnosed, syphilis can lead to blindness, insanity, and death.
Dr. Richard Webber: If you are having unprotected sex with another member of the staff, get tested.
Burke / Bill (PVM): This is not a request.
Patricia / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Mr. Franklin (PVM): Patricia will now give you a safe sex demonstration.
Patricia / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): When the time is right, and gentlemen, you'll all know when that time is, carefully open the condom packet and roll it onto the banana.
Cristina / Mr. Franklin (PVM): I should try and get down to do the MRI now.
Burke / Mr. Franklin (PVM): This isn't really a good time.
Burke / Mr. Franklin (PVM): Do you want to do this without anybody else knowing?
Cristina / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mr. Franklin (PVM): You should do it now.
Patricia / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Open communication is essential to a healthy relationship.
Patricia / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): In a responsible relationship, poor George.
Izzie / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You know, I think he really likes Tyford Mary.
Cristina / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mr. Franklin OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Not many budding relationships survive a good dose of ED.
Patricia / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mr. Franklin OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Condom sense is common sense.
Meredith / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Yeah.
Cristina / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Yeah.
Patricia / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Gently peel off the condom and dispose of it properly.
Patricia / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): With every fresh banana, always use a fresh condom.
Song lyrics (background music): I'm just a walkin' my dog, singin' my song, strollin' along.
Song lyrics (background music): It's just me and my dog, catchin' some sun.
Song lyrics (background music): We can't go wrong.
Song lyrics (background music): My life was only in blue.
Song lyrics (background music): Yeah, I was sad as a sailor.
Izzie / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You're avoiding me.
George / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I'm busy.
George / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): At work.
George / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I'm working.
Izzie / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Why are you in this line?
George / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): It's a syphilis line.
Izzie / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You don't need to be in this line.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I don't?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): There's no one else.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): That surprises you?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Nothing surprises me.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Do I need to be in this line?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): No.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): OK, then.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): OK.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Hey.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Oh, hey.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Mr. Franklin is prepped and ready.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Excellent.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): God, look at this line.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Well, at least we don't have to stand in line.
Cristina Yang / Bill OR Mr. Franklin OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): That's the one good thing about the fact neither of us is getting any, right?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Bill OR Mr. Franklin (PVM): Mr. Franklin, we've given you a local anesthetic, but you might feel some pressure.
Mr. Franklin: Okay.
Mr. Franklin: I'm ready.
Cristina Yang / Bill (PVM): Grab a scale, okay?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Bill (PVM): Are you in the peritoneal cavity?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): The fluid is bloody.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Is it supposed to be bloody?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You've done this before, right?
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Of course.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Millions of times.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You're doing great, Mr. Franklin.
Mr. Franklin: Good.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Franklin OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Mr. Franklin (PVM): Now all we have to do is wait.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): You see that right there?
Another Doctor / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Mm-hmm.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): It's a tumor.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Mr. Franklin (PVM): And it's pressing against your optic nerve.
Patient / Mr. Franklin (PVM): Is it operable?
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Oh, definitely.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): You know, it does have its risks.
Patient / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): You mean I could lose my sight?
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Mm-hmm.
Patient / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): So that's what I need.
Patient / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): A syphilis outbreak and a tumor.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Well, it's probably unrelated.
Patient / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): All right, Derek.
Patient / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Let's see how good you really are.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): All right.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: I'll put a team together.
Patient / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): All my people only.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Mm-hmm.
Patient / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): And I still want this kept under wraps.
Patient / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): The vultures will be circling soon enough.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Aren't I one of the vultures?
Patient / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Why, do you think I want to keep an eye on you?
Patient / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Get going.
Patient / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): We're doing this tonight.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Right.
Another Doctor / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): You've aged.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Yeah, I need you to help me out on something for the chief.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Can you keep a secret?
Burke / Olivia Harper (PVM): Better than you think.
Dr. Knox / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Olivia Harper (PVM): How much fluid can one body hold?
Burke / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Shh.
Burke / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): There's a lot of fluid in there, Mr. Franklin, but we're almost finished.
Burke / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Mr. Franklin?
Dr. Knox / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You sleeping?
Dr. Knox / Miss Henry OR Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He has no pulse.
Burke / Miss Henry (PVM): What?
Dr. Knox / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He has no pulse!
Dr. Knox / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): How could he die just like that with no warning?
Burke / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): There was blood in the tube when it first went in.
Dr. Knox / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): What if it's our fault?
Burke / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): What if we did something wrong?
Burke / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): We didn't do anything wrong.
Dr. Knox / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): We did a textbook procedure.
Dr. Knox / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I checked your chart.
Burke / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You did everything by the book.
Dr. Knox / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He died on our watch.
Burke / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): We must have missed something.
Dr. Knox / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You couldn't have known.
Burke / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): There was no history of heart problems.
Dr. Knox / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): His death wasn't your fault.
Burke / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): When's the autopsy?
Dr. Knox / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): There's going to be an autopsy.
Burke / Miss Henry (PVM): What?
Dr. Knox / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Well, how are we supposed to know the cause of death?
Burke / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): It's going down as cardiopulmonary arrest complicated by liver disease.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): But an autopsy will... The family decided they didn't want an autopsy.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): But, Dr. Bailey... They don't want an autopsy.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Let it go.
Hospital PA System / Unknown (PVM): Dr. Burke to cardiology.
Dr. Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): How goes our special super secret silent sunset surgery?
Dr. Meredith Grey / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I've been practicing that.
Dr. Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You have too much time on your hands.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Uh, tell the chief I'll be there.
Dr. Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Just let me know when and where I'm in.
Dr. Meredith Grey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Okay.
Dr. Cristina Yang / Olivia Harper OR Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Are you nervous?
Dr. Burke / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): It's a complicated surgery.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I'm gonna make one mistake.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I end a fellow surgeon's career.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): My mentor's career.
Dr. Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Oh, no.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I'm not nervous.
Dr. Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): So just for the record... Mm-hmm?
Dr. Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You tell me if I need to get tested, right?
Dr. Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I have syphilis.
Dr. Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): No, I don't.
Dr. Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): It's just we never made any rules or anything.
Dr. Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Olivia Harper (PVM): I mean, we never said we have rules.
Dr. Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): And I wouldn't hold it against you.
Dr. Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): When would I have time to go out and get syphilis?
Dr. Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You're handful enough as it is.
Dr. Meredith Grey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): And besides, we're practically a condom ad.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): But no more glow in the dark ones.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): You see, there's nothing to worry about.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Olivia Harper (PVM): Maybe we should, you know, pick some walls, I mean.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Olivia Harper (PVM): We should.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): OK.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): OK.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): I like the glow-in-the-dark ones.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I bet you do.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): That's the last of the bilbarian material.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I just need to sew up the perforation on the bladder wall.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Is there a problem, Dr. Knox?
Dr. Knox / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Well, you said this man's wife is pregnant?
Dr. Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Due in five weeks.
Dr. Knox / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Why?
Dr. Knox / Mr. Franklin OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Our patient has a blind vest difference.
Dr. Knox / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Bill is sterile.
Dr. Knox / Mr. Franklin (PVM): And always has been.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Then who got his wife pregnant?
Izzie Stevens / Unknown (PVM): Oh.
Meredith Grey / Unknown (PVM): Oh.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Sucks to be Bill right now.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): How's Burke going to tell him the baby's not his?
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Burke's not going to tell him.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): He has to.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): They're friends.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Bill's better off not knowing.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Do you think Holly knows Bill's not the father?
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Maybe, maybe not.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I think Bill should know his wife's cheating on him.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I'd want to know.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I don't remember asking for your opinions, so keep them to yourselves.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Sorry, sir.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You're such a gossip.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): We know how confusing this must be, your husband dying so suddenly.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Franklin OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): But an autopsy will tell us why.
Family Member (Mrs. Franklin or Alice) / Mr. Franklin (PVM): So you think we should do the autopsy?
Family Member (Alice or Mrs. Franklin) / Mr. Franklin (PVM): No, we just want this to be over.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): But don't you want to know for certain what killed him?
Alice Franklin / Mr. Franklin OR Miss Henry (PVM): My father was a mean drunk who couldn't hold a job.
Alice Franklin / Miss Henry (PVM): That's what killed him.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I understand that you're angry, but knowing for sure might help give you some closure.
Mrs. Franklin / Miss Henry OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): And it was awfully sudden, Alice.
Alice Franklin / Miss Henry OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Sudden?
Alice Franklin / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Miss Henry (PVM): He's been killing himself for years.
Mrs. Franklin / Mr. Franklin (PVM): He was a good man.
Mrs. Franklin / Mr. Franklin (PVM): Maybe they're right.
Mrs. Franklin / Mr. Franklin (PVM): Maybe we should do the autopsy.
Alice Franklin / Mr. Franklin (PVM): Mom, stop it.
Alice Franklin / Mr. Franklin (PVM): He's dead.
Alice Franklin / Mr. Franklin (PVM): It's finally over.
Mrs. Franklin / Mr. Franklin (PVM): Alice, your father would have wanted to.
Alice Franklin / Mr. Franklin (PVM): Who cares what he wanted?
Alice Franklin / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mr. Franklin (PVM): Can't we please just try and get out of this with whatever shred of dignity this family has left?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): You guys want to perform an unauthorized autopsy.
Meredith Grey / Miss Henry (PVM): I know you, Christina.
Meredith Grey / Miss Henry (PVM): You do not want to be known as a new 007.
Cristina Yang / Miss Henry (PVM): An autopsy clears your name.
Meredith Grey / Miss Henry OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Christina, no.
Izzie Stevens / Miss Henry (PVM): What about Franklin's wife?
Cristina Yang / Miss Henry (PVM): You saw the way she was looking at me.
Cristina Yang / Miss Henry (PVM): She wants the autopsy.
Izzie Stevens / Miss Henry (PVM): She just didn't want to fight with her daughter.
Izzie Stevens / Miss Henry (PVM): She looks so sad.
Alex Karev / Miss Henry OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Okay, Christina Yang, license to kill.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Okay, I'm in.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I am so not involved in this.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Franklin (PVM): Meredith, this is Fight Club.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Franklin (PVM): Nobody talks about it.
Meredith Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Fine.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Franklin (PVM): We have to do it when Bailey's not around.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Bailey's always around.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): She's everywhere and knows everything.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Well, we have to take our chances.
Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Bailey's got something tonight from 7 to 11.
Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You two will be the last thing she's worried about.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): How do you know that?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): What kind of something?
Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Oh, I can't tell you that.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): It's Fight Club 2.
George O'Malley / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Mr. Franklin OR Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): If I'm missing out on a real patient because of this, they're going to call me 007 because I've killed you.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): How we doing?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Did you lock up the gallery?
Alex Karev / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Don't worry.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): We're flying under the radar.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): What did you put out there?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Mr. Franklin (PVM): The Midas Rex?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): We've got it, Chief.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Mr. Franklin (PVM): How much vancomycin is there?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): One gram is ordered, sir.
Miranda Bailey / Mr. Franklin (PVM): You're not going to be too liberal with those benzos, are you?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You know, doctors make the worst patients.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Why don't you just breathe in the happy gas?
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Stop running my OR.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Ready?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I got you covered.
Izzie Stevens / Miss Henry (PVM): We stole a body.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Miss Henry OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): We're body snatchers.
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Franklin OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): What if somebody from the morgue comes looking for Franklin?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mr. Franklin (PVM): Well, A, it's in the middle of the night, and B, the thing about being dead is people stop looking for you.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): OK.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): When's the last time you did an autopsy?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I took gross anatomy just like you.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I'm just trying to remember.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You know how to hold on.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mr. Franklin (PVM): Hold on.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Wait.
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Franklin (PVM): You brought a textbook?
Cristina Yang / Mr. Franklin (PVM): Uh, if we're going to do this, we're going to do it right.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): OK, got it.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Franklin (PVM): You sure?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mr. Franklin (PVM): It's not like we can kill him twice.
Intern (possibly George, Cristina, or Izzie) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Let me cut.
Bailey / Mr. Franklin OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You'll get your turn.
Intern (possibly Cristina Yang) / Mr. Franklin (PVM): You should really be using the 10 blade.
Bailey / Mr. Franklin (PVM): Will you stop backseat cutting?
Intern (possibly George) / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mr. Franklin (PVM): We'll get the saw.
Intern (possibly Izzie Stevens) / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): OK, I've sutured the drain in place.
Intern (possibly Cristina Yang) / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): The staples look fine.
Bailey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): All right, we're done here.
Bailey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Dr. Billy, you want to wrap him?
Bailey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Nice work, everybody.
Intern (possibly George or Cristina) / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Nicely done.
Intern (possibly Izzie Stevens) / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Meredith Gray OR Bill OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Thanks.
Intern (possibly George O'Malley) / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Hiya.
Intern (possibly Izzie Stevens) / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Do you think the optic nerve is damaged?
Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): If it is, when he wakes up, he'll be blind.
Intern (possibly George O'Malley) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): For how long?
Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Forever.
Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Paige, Stevens, and Yang, tell them I want them covering your patients.
Bailey / Mr. Franklin OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I need you to stay and monitor the chief.
Intern (possibly Meredith Grey) / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Christina and Izzy, I think they're already swamped.
Bailey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): With what?
Intern (possibly Meredith Grey) / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Labs.
Intern (possibly Meredith Grey) / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): They had to check on some labs.
Bailey / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Oh, you are lying.
Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I know you're lying.
Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You know how I know?
Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Because you're a bad liar.
Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I hate a bad liar.
Unknown / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Take over for me.
Unknown / Mr. Franklin OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I know exactly where they are.
Unknown / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Here, take over for me.
Preston Burke / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Your whole relationship is a lie.
Molly / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): We're happy.
Molly / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): We've wanted a child for a long time.
Molly / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Why do you want to take this away from him?
Preston Burke / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Does he know you've been cheating on him?
Molly / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Preston, this is between Bill and me.
Preston Burke / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): The man has a right to know that this isn't his child.
Molly / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mr. Franklin (PVM): Please, just let this go.
Preston Burke / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Why can't you let this go?
Preston Burke / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Because Bill is my best friend.
Preston Burke / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): That's why.
Molly / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You were really his friend.
Molly / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You wouldn't do this.
Preston Burke / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Molly, please, tell him the truth.
Molly / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Why?
Molly / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I'm not going to ruin my life because you think this is wrong.
Preston Burke / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Your life?
Preston Burke / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): What about his life?
Preston Burke / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): What about this child's life?
Molly / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): What Bill doesn't know won't hurt him.
Preston Burke / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Fine.
Preston Burke / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Maybe his friend wouldn't tell him the truth.
Preston Burke / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. Meredith Gray OR Bill (PVM): But I'm also his doctor, and his doctor is not going to lie to him.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Miss Henry (PVM): I know, but something came up, an important surgery, and I couldn't.
Derek Shepherd / Miss Henry (PVM): I'm just sorry you couldn't be there for your mother.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Miss Henry, if my mother were lucid, she would understand.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): She's a surgeon.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): She's done this countless times.
Dr. Meredith Gray: And besides, she doesn't even know who I am anyway, so.
Miss Henry / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Miss Henry (PVM): Today she did.
Dr. Meredith Gray: What?
Miss Henry / Miss Henry (PVM): Your mother's been asking when her daughter Meredith gets off from work.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Hey.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Hey.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): A lot of secret phone calls today.
Dr. Meredith Gray: Yeah, it's my mother.
Dr. Meredith Gray: She isn't traveling.
Dr. Meredith Gray: She isn't writing a book.
Dr. Meredith Gray: She isn't anything.
Dr. Meredith Gray: I've been lying to everyone.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Why?
Dr. Meredith Gray: She has Alzheimer's.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): How advanced?
Dr. Meredith Gray: Very.
Dr. Meredith Gray: She's in a home.
Dr. Meredith Gray: And I'm the only one who even knows she's sick.
Dr. Meredith Gray: I just don't know what to do anymore, you know?
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Don't even tell me you're doing what I think you're doing.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Miss Henry OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Not only did you disregard the family's wishes, you broke the law.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You could be arrested for assault.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Do you like jail?
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): The hospital could be sued.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I could lose my license, my job.
Unknown / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I like my job.
Unknown / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Did you think about any of this before you started cutting open a poor man's body?
Unknown / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I could seriously kick both your asses right now.
Unknown / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Do you have anything to say?
Unknown / Miss Henry (PVM): Look at his heart.
Unknown / Miss Henry (PVM): It's huge.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Miss Henry (PVM): It's over 600 grams.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Miss Henry (PVM): And there's some kind of grainy material in it.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): We want to run some tests.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mr. Franklin (PVM): Oh, now you want to run tests.
Unknown / Mr. Franklin (PVM): At this point, what could it hurt?
Unknown / Olivia Harper OR Mr. Franklin (PVM): I hate both of you right now.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Bill (PVM): Lab 2743, extension 2743.
Unknown / Bill (PVM): Meredith.
Unknown / Bill (PVM): He's an attendee.
Unknown / Bill (PVM): You're an intern.
Unknown / Olivia Harper (PVM): You saw us?
Unknown / Olivia Harper (PVM): You can see.
Unknown / Olivia Harper OR Bill (PVM): I'm going to tell you what your mother would say if she were here.
Unknown / Bill (PVM): You're making a mistake, a big one.
Unknown / Olivia Harper (PVM): And I would tell my mother it's not a mistake.
Unknown / Mr. Franklin OR Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): We specifically said no autopsy.
Unknown / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I understand why you're upset.
Unknown / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You understand.
Unknown / Mr. Franklin (PVM): We're going to get an attorney.
Unknown / Mr. Franklin (PVM): Come on, Mom.
Unknown / Mr. Franklin (PVM): We know what killed him.
Unknown / Mr. Franklin (PVM): He had a blood condition known as hematomacrosis.
Dr. Burke / Mr. Franklin (PVM): The disease causes an excess amount of iron to build up in the body, and that's what caused the heart failure, not the paracentesis.
Patient's Family Member / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): But I thought he was always so sick because of the drinking.
Patient's Family Member / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): And you never let him forget it.
Patient's Family Member / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Or me.
Patient's Child / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Mom, there's something else.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Miss Henry (PVM): The disease is genetic.
Patient's Mother / Miss Henry (PVM): You think Alice could have it too?
Dr. Burke / Miss Henry (PVM): A simple blood test will tell us.
Dr. Burke / Miss Henry OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): If you have it, we'll have caught it early enough to treat it before the condition becomes critical.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Dr. Stevens and Dr. Yang may have saved your life.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): If you could just sign this consent form for the autopsy.
Dr. Burke / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Just a formality.
Dr. Meredith Gray: forget is how good it can feel when you finally set secrets free.
Dr. Meredith Gray: Whether good or bad, at least they're out in the open, like it or not.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): But I'll find a way.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I'll find another way.
Olivia Harper / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): About before.
Olivia Harper / Dr. George O'Malley OR Olivia Harper (PVM): George, I want you to understand.
Olivia Harper / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Olivia Harper (PVM): When we started dating, I was already kind of seeing someone.
Olivia Harper / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I didn't know how much I'd like you.
Olivia Harper / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): And when I realized, I broke it off with the other guy.
Dr. George O'Malley: The other guy?
Dr. George O'Malley: Who's the other guy?
Olivia Harper: You and Alex.
Dr. George O'Malley: You and Alex?
Dr. George O'Malley: You gave me syphilis!
Olivia Harper: George!
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Olivia Harper (PVM): George!
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): George, back off!
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): George, back off!
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Olivia Harper (PVM): Alex!
Alex Karev / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Olivia Harper (PVM): George!
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Meredith Gray OR Olivia Harper (PVM): Back off, Alex.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): And once your secrets are out in the open, you don't have to hide behind them anymore.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Long day.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Yeah.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Somewhere out there is a stake with your name on it.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Olivia Harper (PVM): And maybe a bottle of wine.
Cristina Yang / Olivia Harper (PVM): This is why I keep you around.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): first, talk later.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You trying to, uh, get me drunk so you can take advantage of me?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I think I like this rules thing.
Meredith Grey / Bill (PVM): Me too.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Meredith, I'm so sorry.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): The problem with secrets is...
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Even when you think you're in control?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Addison.
Dr. Addison Shepherd: You're not.
Dr. Meredith Gray: What are you doing here?
Dr. Addison Shepherd: Well, you'd know if you bothered to return any one of my phone calls.
Dr. Meredith Gray: Hi.
Dr. Addison Shepherd: I'm Addison Shepherd.
Dr. Meredith Gray: Shepherd?
Dr. Addison Shepherd: And you must be the woman who's been screwing my husband.
Dr. Meredith Gray: Whatever gets you to today.