Previously on Grey's Anatomy:
- I told Thatch I'm leaving him.
- You left Thatcher, Ellis.
- If you could hold still...
- I'm working, Thatch.
Thatch?
I look like Meredith's dad?
Why didn't you stay and fight for us?
Why didn't you try harder?
I just saw my father
for the first time in 20 years.
I slept with George.
Can we please just go back to everything
the way it was?
I don't know how to go back.
At some point
you are going to have to talk to me.
Want to see something really cool?
All right!
A good basketball game can
have us all on the edge of our seats.
Games are all about the glory,
the pain and the play-by-play.
And then there are
the more solitary games.
Dude, is she knitting?
The games we each play all by ourselves.
You know, as a friend, I got to
tell you, you look a little weird.
I am making a sweater.
You're knitting. In a bar.
You're scaring the customers.
- Come on, have a drink.
- I can't have a drink. I'm celibate.
You mean sober? She means sober.
No. Celibate.
I'm practicing celibacy, and drinking
does not go well with celibacy
because it makes everything and everyone
seem kind of porny.
Then my head gets all cloudy
and the next thing, I'm naked.
And my point is, I'm celibate, and
knitting is good for surgical dexterity,
so I'm making a sweater.
You, celibate?
- I just don't buy it.
- No more men.
No more men? Really? You?
And I'm asking because we are friends.
Every guy I meet
turns out to be married.
- Ooh. Ouch.
- Sorry. Or Mark.
- OK, I'm going to go over there now.
- Sorry.
Or remember the horrible thing I did?
Remember George?
- You're making a sweater.
- I am making a sweater.
The social games, the mind games,
we use them to pass the time.
To make life more interesting.
To distract us
from what's really going on.
He's just not George anymore.
He's broken George.
First he chops off his hair. Then he
starts hanging out with this Callie.
That is not a name. Callie.
Who is she anyway? I'm his best friend.
- Not that he talks to me anymore.
- Triple word score. 69 points.
Woman, I'm beating the pants off you.
- Pay attention. What are you doing?
- I'm knitting a sweater.
Actually, Meredith, my friend that broke
George, she is knitting the sweater.
She's not really knitting the sweater
because she cannot knit,
but I want her to think she is
because we took a celibacy vow,
so she's replacing sex with knitting, so
I'm knitting some of Meredith's sweater
so I can switch them out with hers
so she can really believe she's knitting
because if anybody needs to be celibate,
it's Meredith,
because she broke George. You know?
- You took a vow of celibacy?
- Yes.
How am I supposed to get in your pants
if you're celibate?
That's inappropriate
to say to your doctor.
You know what's inappropriate?
Promising sexual favors to a patient
to get him to live and then backing out.
Denny Duquette!
I so never ever promised...
In my head, you did.
In my head, you delivered.
Well...
Don't worry.
You weren't very good.
OK. You know what? I was being nice.
I was letting you win. Because you're
"Mr. Sick Needs A New Organ Guy. "
But just for that comment,
I'm going to kick your ass.
Yeah, I'm going to...
You put down "mount," Denny?
There are those of us
who love to play games. Any game.
And there are those of us
who love to play... a little too much.
OK, uh, disastrous FEMA director.
- No.
- Oh, uh. Oh.
- Poo is?
- Brown. Poo is brown! Michael Brown!
- Yes!
- Time! Time!
Whoo!
Yeah, thank you.
- Impressive, O'Malley.
- Thanks.
"Poo is"?
- Apparently, we think alike.
- Can't believe you're proud of that.
Are you supposed
to open that ahead of time?
- Hey!
- It's called strategy.
- Cristina, it's a game.
- I know that.
You seem a little intense
and we're having fun.
I'm having fun. Let's do this.
- OK.
- Are you ready?
- Mm-hmm.
- Go!
Blond Ambition tour.
- Blond Ambition tour!
- Oh.
Vogue!
Oh, are you kidding?
OK, she's blonde! She's ambitious!
With the... She's ambitious!
And with the tour! And the vogueing!
Honey, OK, look at me!
OK... Shut up! Cones! Cones!
Blond ambition, boob cones,
and, uh, vogueing, honey, vogueing.
Sean Penn! Sean Penn!
Time!
Zero points for Madonna.
Oh! Madonna. Right.
Who doesn't know Madonna?
- Sore loser.
- I am not a sore loser.
And so what if I am? The point of games
is that there's a winner. A first place.
You want a second-best surgeon
operating on you?
No, you want the very best.
And second best is mediocre.
And to settle for mediocrity is...
is frankly, you know,
a sign of self-loathing
and substandard work ethics.
I've got to get George
out of my apartment.
You could sleep with him
and right in the middle start crying.
It's painful and humiliating
and unbelievably cruel,
but apparently it works.
Would you just keep knitting? Kick him
out so that he can come back home to us.
No, I can't kick him out.
You know, he's Burke's puppy.
It's got to be Burke's idea. I just got
to figure out a way to make him do it.
Got a lot of metastatic disease
here. How do we proceed?
Definitely excise the endobronchial mets
for symptomatic palliation.
You've been doing
your homework, Karev.
Lot of late nights.
Look at this. The mets have adhered
to her chest wall.
Dude, she's toast.
Don't you think
that's a little insensitive?
- She can't hear me.
- You don't know that.
Bedside manner
is part of the job, Karev.
Late nights won't get you anywhere.
You have to figure that out.
- Good morning.
- You going into surgery or coming out?
Going in. I had to push back.
Doc's sick.
- What are his symptoms?
- Polydipsia, lethargy, and vomiting.
- Any sign of fever or dehydration?
- It's unclear.
I was considering IV antibiotics
and a saline drip.
- Seriously?
- No, Addison. He's a dog.
I dropped him at the vet.
They'll observe him overnight.
- Meredith will check on him.
- I got a transfer in from Mercy West.
- Will you wait for me to get home?
- Yeah.
Today we'll be covering...
- Yes?
- Cristina Yang. Surgical intern.
Will we be covering both intra and
extracorporeal knots in today's seminar?
We'll be training in all aspects
of laparoscopic general surgery.
- Starting with basic instrumentation...
- Dr. Yang.
Chief.
...including tissue approximation.
The suggested time for...
You're taking the class?
It's a good refresher course.
Should be fun.
Fun. Yeah.
Now, who would like to volunteer
for our first...
Dr. Yang.
Molly Thompson, 22 years old,
32 weeks pregnant.
Transferred from Mercy West
when an ultrasound diagnosed the baby
with congenital diaphragmatic hernia.
Hello, Molly. I'm Dr. Addison Shepherd.
You're supposed to be the best.
And not to put any pressure on you,
but this is my baby
carrying my grandchild
so I really hope that you are.
The best, I mean.
Mom, you're kind of threatening
the doctor. Don't threaten the doctor.
Sorry.
My husband tells me I have
to try not to be such a mother lion
because Molly's a grown woman and
has her own life and everything, but...
roar.
It's OK. I can take it. I am the best.
You can fix this, though? Right?
We'll insert a scope into your uterus
and then inflate a balloon
in the baby's airway
which should help stimulate the lungs
to grow.
It's not going to be easy
on either of you.
But I do have a strong record
with this surgery.
Make sure you get her to the MRI and
get me the results as soon as you can.
I will.
Sir? Can I help you find something?
Uh...
Is there
a Dr. Meredith Grey working today?
Yes.
She's here in the hospital, right now?
I can have someone page her for you
if you want me to.
No. No. Thanks.
Wait! Excuse me, sir.
Are you... What's your name?
Thatcher.
- You're...
- Grey. Yeah.
- You're Meredith's father.
- Yeah.
Are you sure you don't want me
to page her for you?
No. I'm sorry. It's complicated.
Thatcher, honey? We're right here.
Oh. Oh. There you are, Susan.
Did you tell him? I roared a little.
Couldn't help it.
Oh. Oh, well, I knew you would.
Uh...
I'm sorry, I'm Dr. O'Malley.
I'm, uh...
Uh, well, Excuse us.
Uh... check on our daughter.
Uh, Dr. Bailey!
You have an extra intern?
- I'm available.
- No, no, no, no. I said intern.
- Shepherd, look at the board.
- OK. What am I looking at?
My name isn't there. It wasn't there
yesterday and it won't be tomorrow.
- Did you piss off the Chief?
- Yeah.
I went and had a baby. I gave birth.
I created a human life. I'm a surgeon.
We don't do that.
He's mommy tracking me.
- He's just going easy on you.
- No, I change diapers, I clean spit up,
I sing the ABCs. I'm covered in mommy.
But I will not be mommy tracked!
- You're freaking out.
- I just need a surgery. Now.
So for today, I'm your intern.
I have not begun to freak out.
All right. Come on.
Cristina told me that George
had a date with Ortho Chick.
Games night. She didn't even
take him home afterwards.
She hinted that she wanted to and then
said she couldn't. Weird, right?
George made it perfectly clear
that I'm not in his life anymore.
Think Ortho Chick is hiding something?
Stevens. Hold this.
George mentioned
you're not big on ortho.
Grey? Take the osteotome and the mallet.
Follow me.
Ms. Carver, unfortunately,
we found that the cancer
has metastasized to your chest wall.
We took out a small tumor
obstructing your airway
which will help with your breathing,
but... it's not a cure.
So this is the end of the line.
That's what you're saying? I die now?
- Beatrice...
- I want you to go back in
and I want you to cut out everything
that you can. As much as you can.
I want as much time as you can give me,
you understand?
Unfortunately, additional surgery...
Excuse me.
Mom, I'm not eating
any of that crap in the cafeteria.
We'll have to order in
Thai food or something
because I'm starving
and the food here blows.
I'll have the nurse bring a menu by
and we can have a picnic in bed.
- God, how many doctors do you have?
- They were just leaving.
After trailing by ten at the half,
the offense stepped up.
Leading a 13 and 0 run to begin
a seesaw battle right up to the end.
In five to ten years, cutting, as we
know it, will be virtually obsolete.
- Very nice, Dr. Yang.
- Thank you, sir.
A little less tension there, Chief.
Watch your grip. There you go.
- I wasn't copying you.
- Of course not, sir.
Done! I'm done!
I totally finished first. I'm done.
- So, Dr. Torres...
- Hold it steady, Grey.
Did you always want to specialize
in orthopedics?
Did you always want to model?
Oh. OK.
Grey, I mean it. Watch your grip.
And your husband? Is he a doctor too?
What are you trying to ask me,
Dr. Stevens?
My history? My marital status?
My deep dark little secrets?
- I'm George's best friend.
- Oh, I see.
Well, it's just funny
because from what I understand,
as his best friend, you haven't been
the best matchmaker in the past.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Your hair's growing.
I still think you should cut it.
I could cut it for you,
if we still lived together.
Or we could just hang out
and talk, about stuff.
Like your new friend. Callie.
She's, uh, she's very, um...
You know, if you like her,
I will like her. Eventually.
- I can't escape her.
- What?
All I want to do is forget her. All I
want to do is just escape her and...
you know, I can't.
You want to escape Callie?
Thank God,
because she is like a total freak
and I'm starting to get
really worried about you.
Not Callie.
Sorry. Oops.
Who? Or, uh... Oh! Meredith again.
Let me tell you something.
The minute I tell you this,
it officially becomes your problem.
- Not mine.
- OK.
Meredith has a sister.
- How we doing?
- Turning the skull flap.
- Patient's sedated.
- Very nice. Nicely done.
- He's a kid.
- Yes.
I just didn't think it would be a kid.
A tumor that size...
- What happens now?
- Now we wake him up.
- We're doing awake brain surgery?
- Yes. Thank you.
Andrew?
A little more. Andrew?
Can you hear me?
Hey. Want to count for me?
- One...
- Good. Keep going.
Two.
Three.
The tumor is located near
the language center of the brain.
It's always important
that we don't damage it.
Andrew? I need you to keep talking.
Can you do that? Can you talk to me?
I'II... I'll try.
- Great. Now what grade are you in?
- Um... seventh.
You into sports?
- Not really.
- How about baseball?
Um... baseball's a sport.
Right. OK. What about, uh, girls?
Do you have any girlfriends?
No.
Um... you probably don't have time
for girlfriends, right, Andrew?
- Probably too busy, right?
- Yes, ma'am.
What are you busy doing?
Getting ready for
the National Spelling Bee.
I won the greater regionals last month.
Oh, well, in that case, you need
to spell some words for us.
- Uh, can you do that?
- Sure.
Good. Uh...
You usually provide the word,
Dr. Bailey.
I don't hear you coming up with one.
Uh, let's see. Oh, right!
Um, "acetaminophen. "
Acetaminophen.
Origin of the word?
Heck if I know.
- Do you have Molly's MRI results?
- No. I haven't. Not yet.
- What the hell have you been doing?
- I was just going...
When I assign you to a case of mine
I expect you to give it
your full and undivided attention.
Give me one good reason why
I shouldn't take you off this case.
Molly Thompson's maiden name is Grey.
Her father is Thatcher Grey,
who is Meredith's father,
so Molly and Meredith are sisters, but I
don't think Meredith knows Molly exists.
That... I don't care.
I don't, except I'm on this case
and apparently God hates me.
- OK.
- OK. Thanks.
I want all this out now.
I'm getting out of the hospital.
- Oh, we can't, Beatrice.
- Tomorrow is my daughter's birthday.
Apparently, it's the last one I get to
celebrate. I'm not spending it here.
OK, I'm so sorry. But if we remove
this tube, your lung will collapse.
You don't want to spend her birthday
this way.
I'm a quick healer.
I'm breathing better.
The removal of some of the tumor
opened up your airway.
That doesn't mean that you are well.
You're at risk of infection
or hemorrhage.
Your kid doesn't even know
you have cancer.
You really want to risk dropping dead
on the street outside the hospital?
Dr. Karev.
So you thought... scaring her
back in the bed was the way to go?
It worked, didn't it?
She's lying to her kid.
She's frightened. She's in shock.
It is not your job or your place
to take a tone like that with a patient.
Not ever. Are we understood?
Yes, sir.
So what are the sister
and the father like?
Like? They're like people Meredith
is related to and never met.
- They're nice.
- Can you imagine?
A sister, a whole family
you know nothing about.
- You think she's going to freak out?
- It's not my responsibility to care.
Heads up. Heads up.
Hey, Chief.
Seems I'm a little rusty
on my bead transfer and rope pass.
Dr. Yang here,
has been kicking my ass all day.
- Oh, I can't imagine, Chief.
- No, really, she has.
Of course, speed and precision
aren't the most important
surgical skills, Dr. Yang.
The basics are the key. You need
a solid foundation before anything else.
OK, um...
Well, I'll see you back at the lab.
- Enjoy your lunch.
- You too.
Have a nice day, sir.
OK, I really am
kicking the Chief's ass.
- George.
- Not my responsibility.
- See you guys.
- So who's going to be the...
It's OK. I can accept rejection.
I've got my knitting.
- Mer...
- The weird thing is,
- I thought I just saw my father.
- Oh. That's good. That's so good.
Hmm. Did you meet your sister too?
"Appoggiatura" won last year.
The year before that? Akshay Buddiga.
He fainted, then got up
and spelled the word "alopecoid. "
Kid's a major legend.
All right. Now it's my turn.
"Fibromyalgia. "
- Fibromyalgia?
- What's wrong with fibromyalgia?
Andrew won the regionals.
He's going to D.C.
He's probably insulted by fibromyalgia.
- Fibromyalgia.
- Suction.
F- I-B-R-O-M-Y-A-L-G-I-A.
Fibromyalgia.
- She's right. That was kind of easy.
- OK.
You want me to bring on the heat?
I'll bring on the heat. "Omphalocele. "
- Omphalocele.
- Mm-hmm. More suction in there.
Omphalocele.
OK.
Andrew? What's happening?
Mark that. We've hit the language
center. We have to pull back.
Andrew?
Oh, Andrew. Andrew.
Uh, spell it again for me.
Give me the probe.
Dr. Shepherd's working on it.
I don't want you to be scared.
I want you to wait.
Wait, I want you to hold on.
Mark that as well, please.
- OK, try now.
- OK.
All right, Andrew, spell "omphalocele"
one more time for me.
Omphalocele.
Mark that, please.
O- M-P-H-A-L-O-C-E-L-E.
- Omphalocele.
- That's it. That's perfect.
Dr. Bailey, are you crying?
Ooh! I got something in my eye.
You're doing great, Andrew.
- We're almost done.
- Stop looking at me like that.
- It's my hormones.
- Mm-hmm.
I'm still a surgeon. I'm just a surgeon
with an excess of estrogen.
Deal with it.
Andrew, can you spell "estrogen"?
E- S-T-R-O-G-E-N.
Here's a word for you. "Delusional. "
Delusional.
Today's final assignment will show
how well you can take the skills
you have learned and apply them
to a single operation.
You may begin.
So I'm going do the surgery
with a small scope.
It will be minimally invasive.
You'll be able to do
the rest of your recovery from home.
Thank you.
Yeah. OK.
Uh...
Uh, Molly, this is Dr... uh...
This is Meredith.
She's going to be... continuing your
prep work and taking your vitals. OK?
OK.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- Uh, do you mind if I, um?
- No, it's fine.
I'm getting used to being
poked and prodded.
That's, uh, a pretty ring.
Oh, thanks. It was my grandma's
and then my mom's.
You think I'm too young to be married.
- No, I...
- That's OK.
Everybody thinks I'm too young.
If I saw me, I'd think I was too young.
Um, how... how old are you?
22. Eric's 23.
And he's in the army
and he was getting shipped out.
And... I just love him so much,
you know?
Anyway, I proposed.
Oh.
And your, uh, parents? They approve?
Oh. Oh, my parents are amazing.
You know how dads can be.
Mine's pretty overprotective.
But... you know, at my wedding,
when he gave me away,
my dad cried, which was...
I had never seen my dad cry before.
But I think it was also kind of weird
for him 'cause I'm his little girl.
I'm the youngest, and my sister's
nowhere near ready for marriage.
But... it was good crying.
Like... he was proud of me, you know?
I'm sorry. I'm nervous, so I'm talking.
- No, that's OK. So you have a sister?
- Yeah. Lexie.
She's in medical school. Harvard.
She's the smart one.
You should see how my dad
is about her. He's like crazy proud.
- Well, I'm going to go.
- Meredith?
- Hmm?
- Do you think my baby's going to be OK?
Oh. Well, I hope so.
Me too.
OK.
- I need some bones to break.
- What?
Some bones to break. Something
to smash. Can you help me with that?
Um... you can clean up this cast crap
if you want.
- She freaking out?
- No. Uh-uh. She's fine.
- Oh.
- She's great.
So, George...
he's really, really your type, huh?
You don't see him.
Either of you. You don't see him.
He's just...
He's just George to you. He's...
- He's just O'Malley. Your roommate.
- You don't have to get all up...
He makes my world stop.
George O'Malley is sweet and kind,
and smart and strong.
And he makes my world stop.
So you shut up about him.
Don't forget to clean it up.
When you're done smashing.
Holy crap. George is her McDreamy.
Oh.
I'm done! I'm done! I'm done!
Flawless, Chief Webber.
Absolutely flawless.
They call me Dr. Webber!
That's why I'm the Chief.
That's why I'm the Chief!
That's why I'm the Chief
Chief.
So when is my mom getting out of here?
I'm sorry, honey,
but it's going to be a few days.
Can you call Aunt Sue?
See if she can pick you up?
So I get to spend my birthday
hanging out with Aunt Sue?
- Perfect.
- I promise you, next year.
Next year we'll do something
really special for your birthday.
You name it. It's done. I promise.
Whatever.
So, this whole lying thing?
This is working out for you?
Excuse me?
You're going to die. And soon.
You get that, right?
There's no rosy picture to paint here.
You're not a mother.
You don't know what it's like
to hold your newborn baby in your arms,
and smell her head and know that your
only job in the world is to protect her.
- You think you're protecting her?
- I am protecting her.
I guess you can call it what you want.
But you should know,
you're leaving behind a kid
that will probably hate you
the rest of her life.
- Dr. Karev...
- No. I'm talking this time.
- Excuse me?
- I tell the truth. It's what I do.
It doesn't make me a bad doctor.
Everyone walks around this place lying.
We tell the patient that's dying that
there is hope when there is no hope.
Maybe I'm a pig. Maybe I'm an ass.
Maybe I'm a vermin like everybody says.
But I tell them the truth. It's the
one thing that I've got going for me.
And you don't get to take that away
from me and call it a lesson, sir.
I saw a picture once
from a long time ago.
You look just like her. Your mother.
You look a lot like my girls.
Especially Molly.
- You were talking to her?
- I didn't say anything about anything.
Oh, she knows about you.
Or she knows that her father was married
before and had another daughter.
- Has another daughter.
- No, had is right.
Your father thinks about you.
He thinks about you a lot.
He just...
Your mother...
She broke him.
Excuse me. I... I have to work.
I spent years studying this board.
Holding a crying baby,
trying to get an idea
when my wife would get out of surgery.
Appy takes about an hour.
Anything with the word "cardio"
and I knew not to plan on
seeing her at all that day.
Thatcher. Are you aware
of what's going on with Ellis?
You have no right.
No right to talk to me about Ellis.
I'm sorry. But I was trying
to talk to you about Meredith.
Thatcher,
Ellis has early onset Alzheimer's.
It's advanced.
And it's hard on Meredith,
as you can imagine.
And I thought you'd want to know.
Hey, Andrew.
It's Dr. Bailey.
Remember me?
I was in surgery with you.
I'm... I'm sorry.
No, don't worry. Don't worry.
A lot of times kids who are awake during
surgery don't remember afterwards.
Anyway, your operation went really well.
We got all that tumor out of there
and you're going to be just fine.
I... I... Thanks.
OK.
You know, I have a son, too.
And I'm going home right now
to tell him that today
I met the best speller in Seattle.
- Oh, hey. Dr. O'Malley.
- Hi.
I was looking for you. You're...
Before, when I was asking
about Meredith, you know her.
- You're her friend?
- I used to be her roommate.
Oh, wow.
- You know her really well.
- I know her pretty well.
Um, she... she came
to see me a couple of weeks ago.
- And...
- A couple of weeks ago?
Yeah.
I... I didn't know what to say to her.
She looks so much...
so much like her mother.
Ellis was cold.
I mean, I was a coward.
I was... I... I left.
But her mother would never
let me know her and...
now I don't know how to know her. Uh...
Well, Meredith is anything but cold.
She smiles.
Not that often, but when she does, uh...
you know, because she's been
going through a lot...
but... it's... it's like you feel warm.
She's kind.
I mean, she can be a little selfish.
She can be...
She's flawed, but she's kind.
She cares about people.
And, uh, she cares about...
about her patients.
I think she's going to be
a brilliant surgeon.
You know, around here,
she's known as the one to beat.
So, I... I mean, I guess she has that
in common with her mom,
but... I think the rest of her...
I think, uh, I think the rest of that
she gets from you.
Do... Do you know... where she is?
I think she left already.
But I could tell her you were here,
if you want me to?
Yeah. OK. Thank you.
OK.
- OK.
- OK. Bye.
Yeah.
Thank you, George.
The hernia is causing
the baby's abdominal...
- Hey.
- Hey, still knitting?
Oh, yeah. I'm getting so good at it.
Hmm. I did a craniotomy on a kid today
while he was awake.
I met a sister I never knew I had.
And I saw my father which was, uh...
- I don't know what it was.
- Hmm. You OK?
I have my knitting.
Study hard, keep your grades up.
But starting next year you're going to
want to take two AP classes a semester
if you want to get into
a decent college.
Mom, this is really morbid.
And your Aunt Sue is kind of lazy
when it comes to personal hygiene
so you may have to be
the one to remind her
when it's time to get your eyebrows
waxed or get your hair cut,
but eventually
she'll get the routine down.
Can we not have this conversation?
This might sound random,
but wear underwear with pantyhose.
I know it might feel a little bulky,
but honestly,
it's a little slutty not to
and also that's
how you get yeast infections.
Mom, this is totally gross.
And marry a kind man.
One who's nice to his mother.
Now, if he lives with his mother,
you run the opposite way.
Mom, I'm not
getting married any time soon.
You will someday.
And when that day comes,
just have one glass of champagne
and then you drink water
for the rest of the night
because there's nothing tackier
than a drunken bride.
Mom, I don't want to...
Why are you telling me all this?
Honey, I've been sick for a long time
and the doctors don't think
that I'm going to get better.
No.
Amelia. Listen to me.
Look at me. Amelia.
This is important.
This one is...
is really the important one.
Someday you're going to have a baby.
And you're going to feel overwhelmed by
this little life you're responsible for.
And you're going to think...
worry everything you do is wrong.
And that's normal.
You're going to obsess about
what to feed it
and where to send it to school
and whether it should
take violin or piano.
But I'm going to let you in
on a little secret.
It doesn't matter.
Whether your kid is a concert pianist
or a math genius, it just doesn't matter
because at the end of the day, all that
matters is if your kid is happy.
So you're going to feel sad...
for a little while.
And that's OK. That's... That's fine.
But don't feel sad forever. OK?
You can promise me that? You promise me
that you won't feel sad for too long?
- I promise.
- OK. Thank you.
You make me feel much better.
Life is not a spectator sport.
Win, lose or draw...
the game is in progress...
whether we want it to be or not.
Ta-dah!
You made me a sweater.
Today. In one day,
you made me a sweater?
Yeah, well, you know.
I just had some time, so...
That vow of celibacy
must really be something.
You know what?
Just accept your gift and say thank you.
Does this mean
I don't get any sexual favors?
Sweater instead of sex?
Smell it. Go on, smell it.
It smells like Izzie.
Yeah, I wore it for three hours.
So that is the closest you're going
to be getting to this body, mister.
You want to play some Scrabble
or you too tired?
Scrabble, please.
OK.
Just show me one boob.
- Sir.
- Nice work today, Yang.
Hopefully your fellow interns
will be as adept on the scope as you.
Thank you, sir,
but, um, you weren't even looking.
You actually had your eyes closed.
So, how... I was watching you
and... and you didn't even need the...
You didn't even need the screen
to help you guide the needle holder.
Old school, Yang.
Muscle memory.
You want to win,
always go back to the basics.
It's my move?
Cristina, what the hell are you doing?
Oh.
Um... being comfortable in my apartment.
I didn't see anything!
Dude, I did not see anything!
Get out.
Basics.
So go ahead:
Argue with the refs, change the rules...
cheat a little...
take a break...
and tend to your wounds.
But play.
Hello?
Play.
- Hi.
- Um, hey.
- Um...
- You live here?
Yeah.
I'm not... crazy or anything.
I just spend so much time here
in the hospital.
It's just... It's easier.
So...
I'm not... I'm not crazy or anything.
Do you know how to cut hair?
Play hard.
Play fast.
Play loose and free.
Play as if there's no tomorrow.
Come on.
Dandridge's Veterinary Clinic.
We certainly do.
Yes.
Thank you.
You getting the hang of it?
Not really.
You give up men?
No.
Yes.
I don't actually need to see the vet.
I really just wanted to sit with Doc.
I just want to spend time with my dog.
Hi. I'm Finn Dandridge. I'm Doc's vet.
And you are Dr. Grey. Doc's other owner.
We finally meet.
Hello.
OK, so it's not
whether you win or lose...
it's how you play the game.
Right?
www.tvsubtitles.net