Narrator / Meredith Grey (PVM): Previously on Grey's Anatomy.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): I've had this thing from my roommate since, like, day one.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): And I just, I can't tell her.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Wouldn't it be easier to just ask her out?
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Are you really as shallow and callous as you seem?
Alex Karev / Digby Owens (PVM): Oh, you want to go out for a drink later and hear about my secret pain?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): I can't.
Meredith Grey / Digby Owens OR Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm seeing someone.
Cristina Yang / Digby Owens (PVM): Save yourself the misery, man.
Cristina Yang / Digby Owens (PVM): She's off the market.
George O'Malley / Izzie Stevens (PVM): What?
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): But she's not.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): I mean, if she was seeing someone, I live with her.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): I would know it.
Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): And the longer this little fling goes on, the more favors you get over the others who are fighting to the nail just to make it through this program when those people start finding out what's going on.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Digby Owens (PVM): What is this that we're doing here?
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You need a definition?
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): The next time I see you favoring Meredith Gray in any way, I'll make sure she doesn't see the inside of an OR for a month.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Okay, anyone who says you can sleep when you die, tell them to come talk to me after a few months as an intern.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Of course, it's not just the job that keeps us up all night.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Taylor OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You have to get up now.
Derek Shepherd / Izzie Stevens (PVM): What?
Derek Shepherd / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Taylor (PVM): My God, what time is it?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): It's 5.20.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): And I have three rounds.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): And you have to leave before they see you.
Derek Shepherd / Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, come on now.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Why don't you just let him sleep?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): No.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Please.
Derek Shepherd / Jamie's Parent (PVM): No, no.
Derek Shepherd / Meredith Grey (PVM): You get any sleep?
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): She could boil the bed screens as a courtesy or at least buy a padded headboard.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey OR Jamie's Parent (PVM): So who's the guy?
Izzie Stevens / Izzie Stevens (PVM): You think it was just one guy doing all that work?
George O'Malley / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Yeah.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Do you mind if I don't think about that?
Izzie Stevens / Izzie Stevens (PVM): Oh, jelly.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey OR Izzie Stevens (PVM): You're not jealous.
Izzie Stevens / Izzie Stevens (PVM): Well, I am.
George O'Malley / Izzie Stevens (PVM): At least I know she'll be having a long day at work.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Well, at least we know brain surgery isn't his only skill.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): It can't be.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): He's her boss.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): We're late.
Izzie Stevens / Izzie Stevens (PVM): He's all of our boss.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey OR Izzie Stevens OR Izzie Stevens (PVM): You know, she has been scrubbing in a lot lately on his surgeries.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): No.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Meredith wouldn't sleep with him.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): Just no.
Izzie Stevens / Izzie Stevens (PVM): Well, if she's not ashamed of it, why is she keeping it a secret?
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): Maybe she didn't.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Maybe it just happened.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): You know, spontaneously last night.
Meredith Grey / Izzie Stevens (PVM): Hi.
Izzie Stevens / Izzie Stevens (PVM): Good morning.
George O'Malley / Izzie Stevens OR Izzie Stevens (PVM): Morning.
Izzie Stevens / Izzie Stevens OR Izzie Stevens (PVM): Hey, so it sounded like you were having some pretty radical sex last night.
Meredith Grey / Izzie Stevens (PVM): All night long.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Who's the guy?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): No one you know.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): We're late.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Let's go.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): I mean, if life's so hard already, why do we bring more trouble down on ourselves?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): What's up with the need to hit the self-destruct button?
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Yikes.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): Wouldn't want to meet you in a dark alley.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Right back at you.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, run?
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey OR Digby Owens (PVM): You run?
Cristina Yang / Digby Owens (PVM): Every day, babe.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR Digby Owens (PVM): Every day.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Not suffering enough?
Cristina Yang / Digby Owens (PVM): Doesn't kill you, makes you stronger.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey OR Digby Owens (PVM): Oh, come on.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Don't go acting all indefatigable crap.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): You're dragging like the rest of us.
Cristina Yang / George O'Malley OR Digby Owens (PVM): Oh, what is that?
Izzie Stevens / George O'Malley (PVM): Confession of weakness, Dr. Yang?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): It's called the flu.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Yeah.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey OR George O'Malley (PVM): I'm gonna need a major rush to make it through this day.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): I need a kick-ass surgery.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR Digby Owens (PVM): You a bad boy last night, George?
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): That would be Meredith.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR Digby Owens (PVM): You a bad boy, Meredith?
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Do tell.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Nothing to tell.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Well, it says it all, huh?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Sorry, I have a sex life.
Izzie Stevens / Digby Owens (PVM): Don't apologize.
Cristina Yang / Digby Owens OR Digby Owens (PVM): Embrace it.
Izzie Stevens / Digby Owens (PVM): Share it.
George O'Malley / Digby Owens (PVM): Count me in.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Yeah.
George O'Malley / Izzie Stevens (PVM): Next time, just let me know if I need to go to a hotel so I can get some sleep.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Izzie Stevens (PVM): Am I missing something?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Just a little loud.
Dr. Cristina Yang: Do they know it's McDreamy keeping them up all night?
Meredith Grey: I hope not.
Meredith Grey: I already have Bailey riding me.
Meredith Grey: I don't need my roommates thinking I'm getting special treatment.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: O'Malley, Yang, Karev, go on to clinic.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: O'Malley, patients are waiting.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: You two come with me.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Izzy, you're hanging with me today.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Taylor (PVM): Good morning, Dr. Shepherd.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Dr. Bailey.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Late night, Gray.
Meredith Grey: No, caffeine just hasn't kicked in yet.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: If you're at all religious, you would want to start praying it kicks in soon.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: There's a consult in the pit.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: A girl with a fever and abdominal pain.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: After that, Nicholas in 3311 needs his meds.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Mr. Mowers' IV fell out, and he's a hard stick.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Post stops in 1337, 3342, 3363, and 2381.
Unknown (likely nurse or resident) / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): 3381.
Unknown (likely nurse or resident) / Meredith Grey (PVM): 33-42, 33-63, and 23-81.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Why are you still standing in front of me?
Digby Owens / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You look more like me than you right now.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): What's the matter?
Digby Owens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Nothing.
Unknown (possibly Digby Owens or another patient) / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Help.
Unknown (possibly Digby Owens or another patient) / Meredith Grey (PVM): I need immediate help.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): What's the problem?
Unknown (likely a patient) / Meredith Grey OR Digby Owens OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): My damn boyfriend swallowed my keys.
Unknown (likely boyfriend) / Digby Owens OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I didn't want her to leave.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Locate the lady's keys.
Parent / Meredith Grey (PVM): I think she got some bug on her trip to Mexico with her friends.
Parent / Meredith Grey (PVM): I told her not to go to a third world country, but does she ever listen?
Parent / Mrs. Rice (PVM): She's been weak ever since, and she's lost weight.
Patient (the daughter) / Meredith Grey (PVM): Barely.
Parent / Mrs. Rice (PVM): And this morning, she passed out in the shower.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): When was the trip?
Parent / Meredith Grey (PVM): A couple weeks ago.
Patient (the daughter) / Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm really fine.
Patient (the daughter) / Meredith Grey (PVM): I just have a fever.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): OK, well, will you lie back for an exam for me?
Patient (the daughter) / Meredith Grey (PVM): No, please.
Patient (the daughter) / Meredith Grey (PVM): I don't need an exam.
Patient (the daughter) / Meredith Grey (PVM): Just give me some antibiotics and send me home.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Well, maybe it is just a fever.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): But they called down for a surgeon, so I have to give the OK to let you go.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): So just let me do the exam.
Patient (the daughter) / Mrs. Rice (PVM): Do the exam.
Claire / Meredith Grey (PVM): No.
Claire / Meredith Grey (PVM): This is crazy.
Claire / Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm fine.
Claire's Parent / Meredith Grey (PVM): For God's sake, Claire, I don't want to spend my entire day here.
Meredith / Meredith Grey (PVM): You know, actually, Mrs. Rice, this might be easier if we had some privacy.
Meredith / Meredith Grey (PVM): So would you two mind leaving the room?
Mrs. Rice / Digby Owens OR Mrs. Rice (PVM): That's fine.
Meredith / Digby Owens (PVM): Digby.
Digby Owens: Digby Owens.
Digby Owens: I have an appointment.
Meredith / Digby Owens (PVM): Excuse me, sir.
Meredith / Digby Owens OR Digby Owens OR Digby Owens (PVM): You're bleeding.
Meredith / Digby Owens OR Digby Owens (PVM): Do you mind if I?
Digby Owens: Sure, sure.
Meredith / Digby Owens (PVM): Have a look.
Meredith / Digby Owens (PVM): That's a gunshot.
Digby Owens: Yeah.
Meredith / Digby Owens (PVM): We got a gunshot wound.
Meredith / Digby Owens (PVM): We got to get him down to pit.
Digby Owens: I'm sorry.
Digby Owens: Mr. Dickby, all right, but just remember, see, look, I scheduled this.
Meredith / Digby Owens (PVM): What, gunshot?
Digby Owens: Yeah, my buddy shot me.
Meredith / Digby Owens (PVM): Your buddy?
Digby Owens: Yeah, just as a favor.
Meredith / Digby Owens (PVM): On purpose?
Digby Owens: Hell, yeah.
Digby Owens: I mean, he wasn't trying to hurt me or nothing, but you know.
Jamie / Digby Owens (PVM): But why?
Jamie / Digby Owens (PVM): I like the scars.
Tattooed Patient / Meredith Grey OR Digby Owens (PVM): Look, everyone in town has tats, but my art is about commitment.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): So this is your art, huh?
Tattooed Patient / Meredith Grey (PVM): Damn straight.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Damn stupid.
Tattooed Patient / Meredith Grey (PVM): The bullet went all the way through.
Tattooed Patient / Digby Owens (PVM): Bounced off my ribs.
Tattooed Patient / Digby Owens (PVM): I have another one still in my shoulder.
Meredith Grey / Digby Owens OR Digby Owens (PVM): Nice, huh?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): You could hang it in the Louvre.
Tattooed Patient / Digby Owens OR Digby Owens (PVM): I have an ethos.
Tattooed Patient / Digby Owens OR Digby Owens (PVM): Why do anything unless you're willing to go one step further than anybody else?
Meredith Grey / Digby Owens (PVM): What doesn't kill you makes you stronger, right?
Tattooed Patient / Digby Owens (PVM): Exactly.
Tattooed Patient / Digby Owens (PVM): And pain is the great divide.
Tattooed Patient / Digby Owens (PVM): My coach used to say it's all about how we process pain.
Meredith Grey / Digby Owens (PVM): Football?
Tattooed Patient / Digby Owens (PVM): Wrestling, Iowa State.
Meredith Grey / Digby Owens (PVM): Iowa?
Tattooed Patient / Digby Owens (PVM): 141.
Tattooed Patient / Digby Owens (PVM): 157.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Digby Owens (PVM): Well, you gotta be more than 180 now.
Meredith Grey / Digby Owens (PVM): I'd like to see you get back under 145.
Jamie's Parent / Meredith Grey (PVM): Excuse me, but thinking of you men in tights makes me want to puke.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): There's a flu going around the hospital.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Somewhat ironic.
Tattooed Patient / Steph (PVM): Ow.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Steph (PVM): Don't push so hard.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Can you lift your shirt so I can examine your stomach?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Where did you get these?
Jamie Hayes: There.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): You've had surgery recently.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): These scars are still pink.
Jamie Hayes: Don't tell my parents.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): You did this in Mexico so your parents wouldn't know?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): What did you have done?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): And you noticed her foot twitching?
Parent (Mrs. Hayes or Mr. Hayes) / Meredith Grey (PVM): Come on, Jamie.
Jamie Hayes: Oh, yeah.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): About three months ago?
Jamie Hayes: Just a little.
Jamie's Parent: We took her to county hospital, and she got the CT scan, which showed her brain abnormality.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Here, you can put it.
Jamie's Parent: And the twitching has gotten worse.
Jamie's Parent: A lot worse.
Jamie's Parent: They just don't have the proper equipment back home to figure out what's wrong.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Jamie Hayes (PVM): You did a good thing.
Jamie Hayes: Yes, your mommy.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Jamie's Parent (PVM): Okay, you did a good thing by coming all this way, Mr. and Mrs. Hayes.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): You sit tight, Jamie, okay?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm gonna bring in Dr. Shepherd to see you, okay?
Jamie (patient) / Meredith Grey (PVM): Dr. Shepherd, okay?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): He's the brain specialist.
Jamie Hayes: To Mommy.
Jamie Hayes: To Mommy and Daddy.
Jamie's Parent: Doctor, is he good, this Dr. Shepherd?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Jamie's Parent (PVM): At just about everything,
Alex Karev / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I assume the lady needs her keys to leave this guy's sorry ass behind.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Yeah.
Alex Karev / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Well, how about?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): He needs a bronchoscopy.
Alex Karev / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): So you want to do one, teach one.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You've seen one.
Alex Karev / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): It's time to do one.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey OR Izzie Stevens (PVM): Alone?
Izzie Stevens / Jamie's Parent (PVM): Seriously?
George O'Malley / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Thanks.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey OR Izzie Stevens (PVM): I mean, the vote of confidence in my skills and all.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey OR Izzie Stevens (PVM): I didn't think you, well, anyone was noticing how hard I have been working with you.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Easy.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Go.
Dr. Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): You paged?
Dr. Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Where are we?
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): I did the consult, did the IV, the meds, the post-ops, everything.
Dr. Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): How's your pit patient?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): She's febrile and has peritoneal signs.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You all right, Dr. Yang?
Dr. Cristina Yang: Fine.
Dr. Cristina Yang: On my way back to clinic.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): I think she had some sort of illegal surgery done in Mexico.
Alex Karev / Meredith Grey (PVM): Botched abortion?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): No.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): She has four laparoscopic scars on her abdomen and won't say what they're from.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): And the parents are clueless.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): She's a minor.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): 17, freshman in college.
Attending Doctor / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You order her up for a CT?
Junior Doctor / Resident / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Yes.
Attending Doctor / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): So while she's there, the nurses couldn't get a Foley on Mr. Garay.
Attending Doctor / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Cristina Yang OR Izzie Stevens (PVM): He may need a cadet cath if you can't get a normal one in there.
Attending Doctor / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Write up post-op notes on all surgical floor patients that are esky surgery within the last 24 hours.
Attending Doctor / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Be sure to document their EKGs and x-rays.
Attending Doctor / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Hunt them down if you can't find them.
Junior Doctor / Resident / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Right away.
Another Doctor / Resident / Digby Owens (PVM): Hey.
Doctor or Resident / Steph OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Whoa.
Doctor or Resident / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Digby Owens (PVM): You got the flu?
Doctor or Resident / Meredith Grey OR Digby Owens (PVM): Yeah, and thanks for it.
Doctor or Resident / Digby Owens (PVM): It's making my life so much easier.
Doctor or Resident / Digby Owens (PVM): I didn't give it to you.
Doctor or Resident / Digby Owens (PVM): It's all over the hospital.
Doctor or Resident / Digby Owens (PVM): You should be in bed.
Doctor or Resident / Meredith Grey (PVM): Disease diagnosis and prescription from one man.
Doctor or Resident / Digby Owens (PVM): Seriously, I'll give you a ride home.
Doctor or Resident / Meredith Grey OR Digby Owens (PVM): This is not going to make me go home.
Doctor or Resident / Digby Owens (PVM): You go home.
Doctor or Resident / Digby Owens (PVM): But I feel fine.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Hey, hey, hey, have you seen Shepard?
Alex Karev / Meredith Grey OR Izzie Stevens (PVM): Not as up close as Meredith has.
Meredith Grey / Izzie Stevens (PVM): What?
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey OR Izzie Stevens (PVM): Are you trying to get her in trouble?
Cristina Yang / Izzie Stevens (PVM): She's our friend.
Cristina Yang / Izzie Stevens (PVM): George, this program will make or break our careers, OK?
Cristina Yang / Izzie Stevens (PVM): Some of us will make it through, and some of us won't.
Cristina Yang / Izzie Stevens (PVM): And that decision depends entirely on recommendations from doctors like Shepard.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): There is a reason we don't sleep with the attendants.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): It's not her fault it's Shepard's.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): He's the attending.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): He should know better.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey OR Izzie Stevens (PVM): He's taking advantage of her.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR Izzie Stevens (PVM): Didn't exactly sound like anything was happening against her will last night.
Orderly / Meredith Grey OR Jamie's Parent (PVM): Here you go, Doc.
Orderly / Meredith Grey OR Jamie's Parent (PVM): The kid's CTs just arrived from county.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Thanks.
Unknown Doctor / Jamie's Parent (PVM): Excuse me.
Unknown Staff / Jamie's Parent (PVM): Sorry, Dr. Taylor.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Taylor (PVM): That would be bourbon.
George O'Malley / Izzie Stevens (PVM): What?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Taylor (PVM): I smelled it too.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Taylor (PVM): And he's the best anesthesiologist on the staff.
George O'Malley / Dr. Taylor (PVM): I'll worry when he's too juiced to do his crossword puzzle.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Can you close up for me?
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Thank you, everyone.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Taylor (PVM): Dr. Shepherd.
Dr. Shepherd / Meredith Grey (PVM): I gotta get some coffee.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Jamie Hayes has been admitted.
Dr. Shepherd / Meredith Grey (PVM): The little girl with the brain abnormality?
Dr. Shepherd / Meredith Grey (PVM): How's she presenting?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): She has what looks like continuous seizure activity in her left foot.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Her balance is off.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Her parents have come a long way to try to find out what's wrong.
Dr. Shepherd / Meredith Grey (PVM): How old are these?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Taylor (PVM): They're three months old.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Taylor (PVM): I need new ones.
Doctor (possibly Meredith Grey or Miranda Bailey) / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Her brain could look dramatically different today.
Another Doctor (possibly a resident or intern) / Meredith Grey (PVM): OK.
Doctor (possibly a resident or intern) / Dr. Taylor (PVM): I'll order them.
Doctor (possibly attending or senior resident) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Thank you.
Team Member (possibly Alex Karev or Cristina Yang) / Digby Owens (PVM): Doc.
Team Member (possibly Alex Karev or Cristina Yang) / Digby Owens (PVM): And that?
Doctor (possibly attending or radiologist) / Digby Owens (PVM): That's a bullet from a previous gunshot.
Team Member (possibly Alex Karev or Cristina Yang) / Digby Owens (PVM): Previous gunshot, OK.
Doctor (possibly attending or senior resident) / Digby Owens (PVM): No reason to take it out.
Team Member (possibly Alex Karev) / Digby Owens (PVM): No, guy likes pain.
Team Member (possibly Cristina Yang) / Digby Owens (PVM): It's his ethos.
Team Member (possibly Meredith Grey) / Digby Owens (PVM): Pain is an ethos.
Team Member (possibly Alex Karev) / Digby Owens (PVM): Wait, I think I know this guy.
Team Member (possibly Cristina Yang) / Digby Owens (PVM): You remember this guy?
Team Member (possibly Alex Karev) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Hey, the tattooed masochist.
Team Member (possibly Cristina Yang) / Digby Owens (PVM): Had himself shot again.
Team Member (possibly Alex Karev) / Meredith Grey OR Digby Owens OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Glad to see he's still stupid.
Team Member (possibly Cristina Yang) / Digby Owens (PVM): It's his ethos.
Team Member (possibly Meredith Grey) / Digby Owens (PVM): Let's go tell him what he gets to do today.
Doctor (possibly a nurse or intern addressing Dr. Bailey) / Meredith Grey (PVM): Dr. Bailey, Claire Rice's abdominal CTs.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Is this girl fat?
Team Member (possibly intern or resident) / Meredith Grey (PVM): Not at all.
Team Member (possibly intern or resident) / Meredith Grey (PVM): She's a normal college kid.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): So what do you see?
Team Member (possibly intern or resident) / Meredith Grey (PVM): Her stomach's stapled.
Team Member (possibly intern or resident) / Meredith Grey (PVM): She's had a gastric bypass.
Team Member (possibly Dr. Bailey or another doctor) / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): And a bad one at that.
Team Member (possibly intern or resident explaining to others) / Meredith Grey (PVM): Gastric bypass is a procedure normally done on obese patients to help them lose weight.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Claire?
Meredith / Meredith Grey OR Mrs. Rice (PVM): She doesn't need to lose weight.
Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Are you kidding?
Mrs. Rice: This means the world to her.
Mrs. Rice: But it is so typical of this girl to take the easy way out.
Mrs. Rice: She's done it with everything since she was a little kid.
Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Ms.
Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Rice, nothing about this is going to be easy.
Bailey / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): She's going to face a lifelong struggle with malnutrition unless she has surgery to reverse the procedure.
Mrs. Rice: Do the surgery.
Mrs. Rice: I told her to watch the freshman 15.
Mrs. Rice: Don't eat junk, exercise.
Mrs. Rice: But when she came home Christmas, who had to take her out and buy her a brand new pair of size 6 jeans because she couldn't get in the ones I got her last summer?
Unknown (possibly Meredith or another doctor) / Mrs. Rice (PVM): Tina, you know, she tries so hard.
Claire's Mother / Meredith Grey (PVM): She gets good grades.
Claire's Mother / Meredith Grey (PVM): She gets A's.
Claire's Mother / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): She has illegal surgery in Mexico.
Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Unfortunately, there were complications with the bypass.
Mrs. Rice: What do you mean?
Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): She has what looks like an abscess under her diaphragm and edema, which is a swelling of the bowel wall.
Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I can't say for certain she'll recover completely.
Mrs. Rice: Just do whatever you have to do to make her well, okay?
Unknown (possibly Claire's Mother or a nurse) / Mrs. Rice OR Dr. Taylor (PVM): You look like a princess.
Unknown (possibly Claire's Mother or a nurse) / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Do you know you're a princess?
Unknown (possibly Claire) / Dr. Taylor (PVM): It's not lipstick.
Unknown (possibly Claire's Mother or a nurse) / Dr. Taylor (PVM): It's not lipstick?
Unknown (possibly Claire) / Dr. Taylor (PVM): No, it's not lipstick.
Unknown (possibly Claire) / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Want to do my shoulder?
Unknown (possibly Claire's Mother or a nurse) / Dr. Taylor OR Dr. Cristina Yang (PVM): Oh, good.
Jamie / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Thank you.
Doctor / Dr. Taylor OR Dr. Cristina Yang (PVM): And your nose.
Doctor / Dr. Taylor (PVM): We're going to find out what's causing the seizures.
Doctor / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Does MRI know we're coming down?
Nurse / Dr. Taylor (PVM): You said CT.
Doctor / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Now I'm saying MRI.
Nurse / Meredith Grey (PVM): It's available.
Jamie's Parent / Meredith Grey (PVM): Doctor, is she gonna need surgery?
Doctor / Meredith Grey (PVM): I don't know yet.
Jamie's Parent / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Cristina Yang OR Dr. Taylor (PVM): It's just that my wife and I, we both work, and I don't know... We know it can be very expensive.
Doctor / Dr. Taylor (PVM): I don't want you to worry about that.
Doctor / Dr. Taylor (PVM): It's a focal left-side seizure.
Doctor / Dr. Taylor OR Steph (PVM): Okay, let's get that diazepam running right now, please.
Nurse / Dr. Taylor OR Steph (PVM): Diazepam IV.
Doctor / Dr. Taylor OR Steph (PVM): Okay, tourniquet, please.
Nurse / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Tourniquet.
Doctor / Dr. Taylor OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Hey, Jamie, here's what we're gonna do.
Doctor / Dr. Taylor OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): We're gonna put this on your arm, okay?
Doctor / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Isn't that fun?
Doctor / Dr. Taylor (PVM): We're gonna put that right there like that.
Doctor / Dr. Taylor (PVM): This is gonna feel cold.
Doctor / Dr. Taylor (PVM): This is a butterfly.
Doctor / Dr. Taylor OR Dr. Taylor (PVM): Butterfly lands right there.
Doctor / Dr. Taylor (PVM): There we go.
Doctor / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Blanket for the butterfly.
Nurse / Jamie's Parent OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Good.
Doctor / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Nicely done.
Doctor / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Taylor OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): It's amazing stuff, isn't it?
Medical Staff / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Hey, you like spaceships?
Medical Staff / Izzie Stevens OR Dr. Taylor OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): You do?
Medical Staff / Meredith Grey (PVM): OK.
Medical Staff / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Should we take Captain O'Malley, my first lieutenant, to the spaceship MRI?
Medical Staff / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Let's go.
Medical Staff / Meredith Grey OR Izzie Stevens (PVM): It'll be safer to wait until your lunch digests before we do the procedure.
JP / Meredith Grey (PVM): Perfect.
JP / Meredith Grey OR Jamie's Parent (PVM): This is just perfect.
JP / Jamie's Parent (PVM): I was hoping to be in Portland right now.
Medical Staff / Izzie Stevens (PVM): You're gonna be under conscious sedation, JP, which means you'll be awake but groggy.
JP / Izzie Stevens (PVM): Is this gonna hurt?
Medical Staff / Izzie Stevens (PVM): You'll have some discomfort, but we'll give you something for pain.
JP / Digby Owens OR Izzie Stevens OR Jamie's Parent (PVM): Do you know how stupid you make me look?
Athena / Digby Owens (PVM): I thought you would think this is funny.
Athena / Digby Owens (PVM): Romantic.
JP / Jamie's Parent (PVM): Like the therapist thing was funny and romantic?
Athena / Digby Owens OR Jamie's Parent (PVM): That was funny.
JP / Jamie's Parent (PVM): No, that was sad.
Athena / Izzie Stevens OR Jamie's Parent (PVM): He called my therapist pretending to be his therapist to find out what I'd said about him.
Medical Staff / Jamie's Parent (PVM): He's a little passive-aggressive, isn't he?
Athena / Jamie's Parent (PVM): A little.
Athena / Jamie's Parent (PVM): He is the king of passive-aggressive.
Athena / Jamie's Parent (PVM): And he's manipulative.
Athena / Jamie's Parent (PVM): And needy.
Medical Staff / Izzie Stevens OR Jamie's Parent (PVM): That's the trifecta.
Athena / Digby Owens OR Izzie Stevens (PVM): What do I win?
JP / Izzie Stevens (PVM): What?
Athena / Digby Owens (PVM): Duh.
Doctor / Digby Owens (PVM): I prefer we stop meeting like this, Mr. Owens.
Digby Owens: Digby.
Doctor / Digby Owens (PVM): So how's the trumpet playing?
Digby Owens: Very safe compared to your hobby.
Doctor / Digby Owens (PVM): Getting shot is a little more risky.
Digby Owens: That's kind of the point.
Doctor / Digby Owens (PVM): He's running a fever.
Doctor / Digby Owens OR Digby Owens (PVM): Due to the extra stress on his body from the gunshot.
Doctor: Digby, the impact of the bullet in your chest fractured a rib and caused a hemopneumothorax.
Digby Owens: That sucks, I guess.
Doctor: Well, there's blood in your collapsed lung.
Doctor: The price of body art went up since your last gunshot.
Digby Owens: Eh, no pain, no gain, right?
Doctor: That's one way to look at it.
Digby Owens: And we have that in common, you docs and me.
Doctor / Digby Owens OR Digby Owens (PVM): Do it.
Digby Owens: Yeah, the way you guys push and push and push.
Digby Owens: When I was wrestling, if you wanted to pin me, you was gonna have to kill me.
Doctor / Digby Owens (PVM): Iowa style.
Digby Owens: Iowa State style.
Doctor / Digby Owens OR Digby Owens (PVM): Back home, we were sworn enemies.
Digby Owens: But here in Seattle, man, we're brothers.
Digby Owens: Now, so what are we going to do about this, uh, hemo-numo-jurassic?
Doctor: We're going to insert a chest tube to drain the blood and then reinflate your lung.
Digby Owens: Oh, please.
Digby Owens: Tell me I get to watch.
Digby Owens: Oh, man.
Doctor / Meredith Grey OR Digby Owens (PVM): I will stop.
Claire Rice: Before you guys start, I know you're mad.
Claire's Mother / Meredith Grey (PVM): Disbelief, Claire.
Claire's Mother / Meredith Grey (PVM): Just...
Claire's Mother / Meredith Grey (PVM): Disbelief.
Claire's Father / Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm just concerned.
Claire's Father / Meredith Grey (PVM): Where did you get the idea to do this?
Claire Rice: The internet.
Claire's Mother / Meredith Grey (PVM): But honey, there is a healthy way to lose weight.
Claire Rice: Yeah, I've tried that, but it doesn't work for me like it does for you.
Claire's Mother / Meredith Grey (PVM): Hey, you don't need to lose weight.
Claire's Father / Meredith Grey (PVM): What are you waiting?
Claire's Father / Meredith Grey (PVM): And how much have you been working out?
Claire's Father / Meredith Grey (PVM): I mean, you know, most of the time when people hit their target weight, they have to work to stay there.
Claire Rice: Everyone gains weight in college, Mom.
Claire Rice: It's stressful.
Claire Rice: There's not enough time for exercise.
Claire Rice: I just thought if I wasn't worried about my diet, then I could focus more on my studies.
Claire's Mother / Meredith Grey (PVM): So you took yet another shortcut.
Claire's Father / Meredith Grey (PVM): Life doesn't work that way, Claire.
Claire's Mother / Meredith Grey (PVM): Tina.
Claire's Father / Izzie Stevens (PVM): What?
Claire's Mother / Meredith Grey (PVM): You want to argue this?
Claire's Mother / Meredith Grey (PVM): She has so much potential.
Claire's Mother / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): If she would just apply herself.
Claire Rice: OK.
Doctor: I think we should focus on taking care of your daughter.
Doctor: And Claire, your parents agree the best thing to do is to reverse the bypass.
Claire Rice: No.
Jamie / Meredith Grey (PVM): No, it's my body.
Jamie / Meredith Grey (PVM): I do not want surgery again, please.
Dr. Shepherd / Meredith Grey (PVM): There are serious complications, and this is about your health.
Jamie / Meredith Grey (PVM): But I'd rather be thin.
Dr. Shepherd / Meredith Grey (PVM): Well, I'm afraid the choice isn't up to you.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Taylor (PVM): It's called Rasmussen's encephalitis.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Taylor (PVM): What it amounts to is that this side of her brain, this part's all healthy.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Taylor (PVM): It's working perfectly.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Taylor (PVM): This black part of the brain, his, all of that is dead or dying.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Taylor (PVM): The condition has gotten radically worse since her CT scans three months ago.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Left untreated, the disease is going to kill her.
Jamies Mother / Meredith Grey (PVM): How soon?
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Too soon.
Jamies Mother / Dr. Taylor (PVM): So is there a cure?
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Yeah, the treatment requires the diseased portion of her brain be removed and sealed off.
Dr. Shepherd / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Taylor (PVM): See, eventually, the spinal fluid will fill the cavity.
Jamies Mother / Meredith Grey (PVM): Remove what?
Dr. Shepherd / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Taylor (PVM): I mean, that's... Half her brain, yes.
Jamies Mother / Meredith Grey (PVM): Half her brain?
Jamies Father / Meredith Grey (PVM): That seems impossible.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Her age makes it possible.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Her brain's not fully developed, so the remaining neurons will...
Dr. O'Malley / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Compensate for the loss.
Jamies Mother / Dr. Taylor OR Dr. Taylor (PVM): But will she be normal?
Jamies Father / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Is there a risk to any surgery?
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Taylor (PVM): And this is, you know, a major one.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Taylor (PVM): But if, you know, we're successful, Jamie could walk out of this hospital in a couple of weeks, go on to live a relatively normal life.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Look, I know this is a lot to digest, but the important thing to remember is that we can save a life.
George O'Malley / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Thank you.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Taylor OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Dr. O'Malley.
George O'Malley: Yes, what?
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Taylor (PVM): I'm sorry to bother you, but if the parents consent, I thought you'd like to scrub in on a hemispherectomy.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Are you in or not?
George O'Malley: Uh, in.
George O'Malley: Gang, I'm scrubbing in on a hemispherectomy with Shepard.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Get out.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): I would kill for that.
Alex Karev / Meredith Grey (PVM): We're going to cut out half the girl's brain, and it's going to work.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): It's outrageous.
Alex Karev / Meredith Grey (PVM): Almost makes it hard to hate him.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Why do you hate him?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, no reason.
Alex Karev / Meredith Grey (PVM): You know about him and Merida?
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Taylor (PVM): You know?
Dr. Cristina Yang: I'm going to figure out that I know everything.
Alex Karev / Meredith Grey (PVM): She knows.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): All about Dr. Sest.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): It's been going on for like ever.
George O'Malley / Izzie Stevens (PVM): What?
Alex Karev / Meredith Grey OR Izzie Stevens OR Dr. Cristina Yang OR Izzie Stevens (PVM): And you didn't tell us?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, you're a gossip, huh?
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): I am not.
Dr. Cristina Yang: I am.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): He's about to go into major brain surgery on no sleep.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Not very responsible.
Alex Karev / Meredith Grey (PVM): Shall I smash?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Sex all night isn't about being responsible.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): No, it's about sex all night.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): I can't believe you're not more pissed off about this, you of all people.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): She works hard all day.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): She's good at her job.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): Why should you care how she unwinds?
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): I mean, you like to bake all night.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Some people like to drink.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Others like an occasional screaming orgasm.
Izzie Stevens / George O'Malley (PVM): Yeah, we do.
Izzie Stevens / Digby Owens (PVM): Forget I said that.
Izzie Stevens / Digby Owens (PVM): Pretend like I'm not here.
Izzie Stevens / Digby Owens (PVM): You look like you need to be spoon fed.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): You look like Alex.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): OK, about drinking, Dr. Taylor, the anesthesiologist, do you think he drinks?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): I said, whatever gets you through the day.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Cristina Yang (PVM): No, but I mean here at work.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): Earlier, I thought I smelled.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): You know, do you think?
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey (PVM): I mean, his patients trust the.
George O'Malley / Meredith Grey OR Digby Owens (PVM): So I should say something, right?
Meredith Grey / Digby Owens (PVM): It's a can of worms, George.
George O'Malley / Digby Owens (PVM): And why are we talking about sex, anyway?
Digby Owens / Digby Owens (PVM): This is going to leave a pretty sexy scar, huh?
Doctor (likely Bailey or Meredith) / Digby Owens (PVM): Don't get any more crazy ideas.
Digby Owens / Digby Owens (PVM): You really think my ideas are crazy?
Doctor (likely Bailey or Meredith) / Digby Owens (PVM): I'm leaning that way.
Digby Owens / Digby Owens (PVM): We wrestle, he plays trumpet.
Patient / Digby Owens (PVM): I feel pretty dizzy.
Meredith Grey / Digby Owens (PVM): You've lost some blood.
Meredith Grey / Digby Owens (PVM): This too shall pass.
Unknown / Digby Owens (PVM): Hey.
Alex Karev / Digby Owens (PVM): How come I don't see you down at the mat and bell time?
George O'Malley / Digby Owens (PVM): Oh, man, no time.
Alex Karev / Digby Owens (PVM): Bro, make time.
Alex Karev / Digby Owens (PVM): I'll be expecting you.
George O'Malley / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Digby Owens OR Digby Owens (PVM): Oh, man.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Handle with care.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): This thing's full of gunk, I know.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): We need to free the bowel from the adhesions caused from the abscess.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): This poor girl.
Dr. Bailey / George O'Malley (PVM): Cell phone.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): What was she thinking?
Dr. Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): She wants her mother's approval.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): She wanted to please her.
Dr. Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): And this damages the result?
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Here, resect that.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Needle tip bovie, please.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): When you're done here, you have post-ops waiting.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I know, Dr. Bailey.
Dr. Bailey / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Christina's got the flu, so you need to pick up the slack in the clinic.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Look, I'm off the floors, OK?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Sorry, that was inappropriate.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): It's not the only thing that's inappropriate.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Are we on the subject?
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): You care to tell me what you think you're doing?
Dr. Taylor / Meredith Grey (PVM): Look, I'll jump through hoops if you want me to.
Dr. Taylor / Meredith Grey (PVM): But what I do when I leave this hospital is my business.
George / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Half this hospital knows your business.
George / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Flu isn't the only virus spreading around here.
Dr. Taylor / Meredith Grey (PVM): I made a choice.
Dr. Taylor / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): And I know you don't respect me for that choice.
Dr. Taylor / Meredith Grey (PVM): But I'll live with the consequences.
George / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Then I'll have lots of hoops for you to jump through.
Dr. Taylor / Meredith Grey (PVM): I've done everything you've asked me to do.
Dr. Taylor / Meredith Grey (PVM): I may not do it your way, but it gets done.
Dr. Taylor / Meredith Grey (PVM): So whatever else you got, bring it on.
Dr. Taylor / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Okay, Dr. Gray, now that you've drained the organ, we can attempt to repair it.
Meredith / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Now my day is perfect.
Unknown (possibly Nurse or Assistant) / Unknown (PVM): Okay, bye.
Meredith / Meredith Grey (PVM): I appreciate this.
Meredith / Meredith Grey (PVM): The chance to scrub in on this kind of procedure is, well, yeah, I appreciate it.
Unknown (possibly Nurse or Assistant) / Dr. Taylor OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Here you go.
Unknown (possibly Nurse or Assistant) / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Triple espresso, not too hot.
Dr. Taylor / Dr. Taylor OR Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Oh, I love you.
Dr. Taylor / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Seriously.
Dr. Taylor / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Ah, coffee.
Dr. Taylor / Dr. Taylor OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Where would medicine be without it, huh?
Meredith / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Yeah.
Dr. Taylor / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Oh, I hope you have a new crossword, too.
Dr. Taylor / Dr. Taylor OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): I'm going to be here a while.
Unknown (possibly Nurse or Assistant) / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Never go without.
Dr. Taylor / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Big day for you, kid.
Dr. Taylor / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Congrats.
JP / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Thanks.
Staff Member / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Hey, princess.
Staff Member / Dr. Taylor (PVM): You ready to take a nap?
Child Patient / Dr. Cristina Yang OR Dr. Taylor OR Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Izzie Stevens (PVM): Hey, look what I can blow bubbles.
Staff Member / Dr. Taylor OR Dr. Taylor OR Izzie Stevens (PVM): That's it.
Staff Member / Dr. Taylor OR Dr. Taylor (PVM): You just breathe in.
Staff Member / Dr. Taylor OR Dr. Taylor (PVM): Oh, that's it.
Child Patient / Izzie Stevens (PVM): What?
Staff Member / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Do you smell?
Child Patient / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Smell what?
Staff Member / Dr. Taylor (PVM): You can't have a mask.
Staff Member / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Taylor OR Steph (PVM): I'm sorry, Dr. Taylor, but did you just... Have you been drinking?
Dr. Taylor: I beg your pardon?
Staff Member / Izzie Stevens (PVM): What?
Staff Member / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Do you smell... I smell alcohol.
Dr. Taylor: Where the hell do you get off accusing me of something like that?
Staff Member / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Taylor (PVM): George, you're out of wine.
Staff Member / Meredith Grey (PVM): There are rules.
Staff Member / Meredith Grey (PVM): You know, there are rules for a reason.
Staff Member / Meredith Grey (PVM): You just...
Staff Member / Meredith Grey (PVM): There is a two-year-old girl on this table.
Athena / Dr. Taylor OR Meredith Grey (PVM): You shouldn't take advantage of someone else's vulnerability.
Dr. Taylor: Look, I don't need some punk intern telling me what's at stake here.
Dr. Taylor / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Get him out of here, Shep.
Staff Member / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Shep.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: You're out, George.
Staff Member / Dr. Taylor (PVM): You damn well better be ready, Taylor.
Dr. Taylor: I wouldn't be here if I wasn't.
Athena / Jamie's Parent (PVM): Do you really seriously want to know why I'm leaving?
JP / Jamie's Parent (PVM): Seriously?
Athena / Jamie's Parent OR Jamie's Parent (PVM): How about when you started insisting that I quit my job right when I started to make more money than you?
Athena / Jamie's Parent OR Jamie's Parent (PVM): That should have been the last straw.
JP / Jamie's Parent (PVM): No, no.
Athena / Jamie's Parent OR Jamie's Parent (PVM): No, the last straw should have been when I found out that those mysterious phone calls that you'd been getting that you kept denying were from other women were really coming from your mother.
JP / Jamie's Parent (PVM): This isn't healthy.
Medical staff (possibly Meredith or nurse) / Meredith Grey OR Jamie's Parent OR Jamie's Parent (PVM): Just hold still, please.
Athena / Meredith Grey OR Jamie's Parent (PVM): Don't you dare try to catch this.
Medical staff (possibly Meredith or Bailey) / Meredith Grey OR Jamie's Parent (PVM): Okay, could the both of you just please stop?
Athena / Meredith Grey OR Steph OR Jamie's Parent OR Jamie's Parent (PVM): You don't love me, JP.
Athena / Jamie's Parent OR Jamie's Parent (PVM): You love to smother me.
Athena / Steph OR Jamie's Parent OR Meredith Grey OR Izzie Stevens OR Jamie's Parent (PVM): And if I could just get you to admit that, then I could leave you with an ounce of respect.
Medical staff (likely Bailey) / Izzie Stevens OR Jamie's Parent (PVM): Hey, Athena, I let you stay in here to keep him calm, so if you're just gonna keep on... Check that.
Athena / Jamie's Parent (PVM): I can't respect a man desperate enough to swallow my exit strategy.
Athena / Jamie's Parent (PVM): That is the last straw.
Medical staff (likely Bailey) / Jamie's Parent (PVM): Michelle, can you get her out of here?
Michelle (nurse or orderly) / Izzie Stevens OR Dr. Taylor OR Jamie's Parent (PVM): Ma'am?
Athena / Jamie's Parent (PVM): Fine.
Michelle (nurse or orderly) / Dr. Taylor OR Dr. Taylor (PVM): Come on.
Athena / Izzie Stevens (PVM): What?
JP / Meredith Grey (PVM): What's happening?
Medical staff (possibly Meredith or Cristina) / Izzie Stevens (PVM): The keys move farther down.
Athena / Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, my God, what does that mean?
Medical staff (possibly Meredith or Cristina) / Meredith Grey (PVM): What did you do?
Athena / Meredith Grey (PVM): Don't you dare die, JP.
Medical staff (possibly Meredith or Cristina) / Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, please.
Medical staff (possibly Meredith or Bailey) / Meredith Grey (PVM): Please, just shut up.
Team Member (likely doctor or nurse) / Meredith Grey (PVM): Just breathe, JP.
Another Team Member (doctor or nurse) / Meredith Grey (PVM): Just breathe.
JP / Jamie's Parent (PVM): Got it.
Team Member (doctor or nurse) / Meredith Grey OR Izzie Stevens OR Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Izzie Stevens (PVM): Very impressive, JP.
Team Member (doctor or nurse) / Meredith Grey OR Izzie Stevens (PVM): You OK?
Another Team Member / Meredith Grey OR Izzie Stevens (PVM): Are you OK?
JP / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Yeah.
Team Member (doctor or nurse) / Meredith Grey (PVM): You'll be fine.
JP / Jamie's Parent (PVM): You did that on purpose, didn't you?
Team Member (doctor or nurse) / Izzie Stevens (PVM): Can I offer you some advice?
Team Member (doctor or nurse) / Meredith Grey OR Izzie Stevens (PVM): Get in your car and go, for all of our sakes.
JP / Meredith Grey (PVM): You're never gonna find where I parked it.
Team Member (doctor or nurse) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I need a shower.
Another Team Member / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I need a shower.
Team Member (doctor or nurse) / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You need to go tell that girl's parents what kind of kid they're getting back.
Team Member (doctor or nurse) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You're not going to let me shower first?
Team Member (doctor or nurse) / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): That would be a hoop, would it not?
Another Team Member / Meredith Grey (PVM): It would qualify.
Team Member (doctor or nurse) / Meredith Grey (PVM): Shower first, then.
Another Team Member / Meredith Grey OR Izzie Stevens (PVM): Ew, it smells.
Team Member (doctor or nurse) who was in surgery / Meredith Grey (PVM): That would be me, or more specifically, my patient's insides all over me.
Another Team Member / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): That makes me strangely happy.
Team Member (doctor or nurse) who was in surgery / Meredith Grey (PVM): I smell like karma.
Another Team Member / Izzie Stevens (PVM): What?
Team Member (doctor or nurse) who was in surgery / Meredith Grey (PVM): Nothing.
Another Team Member / Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, there's something vile stuck in your hair.
Team Member (doctor or nurse) who was in surgery / Meredith Grey (PVM): You know, just go stand over there, please.
Another Team Member / Meredith Grey (PVM): Ugh.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): How much do I love being a surgeon right now?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Izzie Stevens (PVM): Karma?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): What does karma have to do with anything?
Meredith Grey / Izzie Stevens (PVM): I'm just saying, you've been given all the best surgeries, and now you smell like putrid goo.
Meredith Grey / Izzie Stevens (PVM): And you're giving off a stench.
Cristina Yang / Izzie Stevens (PVM): Karma's a bitch.
Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Dr. Shepherd needs an intern in surgery.
Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Which one of you is clear to go?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I'm good, Dr. Bailey.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Where do you want me?
Miranda Bailey / Meredith Grey (PVM): You need to lie down somewhere.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm fine.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm completely healthy.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Gray.
Meredith Grey: Of course.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): What is your problem?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Um, you.
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey OR Izzie Stevens (PVM): Because apparently you can help Dr. McDreamy in ways the rest of us can't.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You did not just say... Yes, I did.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Hey!
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Hemispherectomy and OR1 with Dr. Shepherd.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Go.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Steph (PVM): Apparently, I'm not the only one with hoops.
Cristina Yang / Digby Owens OR Steph (PVM): If you're gonna get up, you might as well get up.
Miranda Bailey / Digby Owens (PVM): Doctor.
Izzie Stevens / Digby Owens OR Digby Owens (PVM): Digby's post-op CBC shows a severe spike in the white blood cell count.
Miranda Bailey / Digby Owens (PVM): What is it?
Izzie Stevens / Digby Owens OR Digby Owens (PVM): It's 27 with 16% bands.
Dr. House / Digby Owens (PVM): Something else is wrong.
Dr. Foreman / Digby Owens (PVM): That's a little high for simple stress.
Dr. House / Digby Owens (PVM): Check for any other possible sources of infection or recent illness.
Dr. Chase / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Taylor (PVM): All right, we're going to start the procedure with the left temporal rectum.
Dr. Chase / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Thanks for joining us, Dr. Yang.
Dr. Chase / Dr. Taylor OR Dr. Taylor OR Jamie's Parent (PVM): After the temporal, we'll do the frontal and then the occipital rectum.
Dr. Cameron / Meredith Grey (PVM): We were able to reverse the gastric bypass, but we did lose a significant portion of her bowel.
Dr. Cameron / Meredith Grey (PVM): And because of the short gut syndrome, Claire will never eat normally again.
Claire's Parent / Meredith Grey (PVM): OK.
Claire's Parent / Izzie Stevens (PVM): What?
Claire / Meredith Grey (PVM): Can we?
Claire's Parent / Meredith Grey (PVM): How do we help her here?
Dr. Cameron / Meredith Grey (PVM): Well, getting proper nutrition will be a lifelong problem for Claire.
Claire's Parent / Meredith Grey (PVM): Great.
Claire's Parent / Meredith Grey (PVM): As if we already don't have our hands full with her.
Claire / Meredith Grey (PVM): She gets good grades.
Claire / Meredith Grey (PVM): She stays out of trouble.
Claire / Meredith Grey (PVM): She's smart.
Claire's Parent / Meredith Grey (PVM): I just think she feels like nothing she does is good enough for you.
Claire's Parent / Meredith Grey (PVM): If you somehow think that I'm responsible for this.
Claire's Parent / Meredith Grey (PVM): I think Claire is killing herself to please you.
Claire / Meredith Grey (PVM): Please.
Claire's Parent / Meredith Grey (PVM): You have no idea what's going on in that girl's mind.
Claire / Meredith Grey (PVM): You're her mother.
Claire / Meredith Grey (PVM): She worships the ground you walk on.
Claire / Meredith Grey (PVM): She didn't do this for herself.
Claire's Parent / Meredith Grey OR Izzie Stevens (PVM): I think that this situation is completely ridiculous.
Claire / Izzie Stevens (PVM): Shut up.
Doctor (possibly Dr. Yang or Dr. Shepherd) / Digby Owens (PVM): What is it?
Dick B. / Digby Owens (PVM): I'm freezing, doc.
Dick B. / Digby Owens (PVM): I can't stop shaking.
Nurse or Intern / Meredith Grey (PVM): His temp's way up and BP's dropping, doctor.
Doctor (possibly Dr. Yang or Dr. Shepherd) / Digby Owens (PVM): All right, Dick B. Have you had any recent illnesses, new piercings, tattoos, wounds?
Dick B.: New tat on my calf.
Doctor or Nurse / Digby Owens OR Digby Owens (PVM): Oh, my God.
Doctor or Nurse / Digby Owens (PVM): It was nowhere near that nasty this morning.
Doctor / Digby Owens (PVM): But it was infected.
Doctor / Digby Owens OR Digby Owens (PVM): Why didn't you say anything?
Dick B.: Ah, it was nothing.
Dick B.: I'm not here to complain about a little pain.
Doctor / Digby Owens OR Digby Owens (PVM): Well, the infection's been exacerbated by the stress in your body from the gunshot.
Doctor / Digby Owens (PVM): Get him to ICU.
Doctor / Digby Owens (PVM): We'll get you started on some antibiotics.
Dr. Yang / Dr. Taylor OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): We'll encounter the anterior cerebral artery.
Dr. Shepherd / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Taylor OR Dr. Taylor (PVM): Yes, and we're going to need to... The branches of the artery need to be coagulated and divided.
Dr. Yang / Dr. Taylor (PVM): You know, Taylor, her anesthesia is awful light.
Dr. Yang / Dr. Taylor OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Come on, Taylor.
Dr. Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): She's waking up.
Dr. Yang or Dr. Shepherd / Meredith Grey (PVM): Dr. Taylor.
Dr. Yang or Dr. Shepherd / Meredith Grey (PVM): He's asleep.
Dr. Yang or Dr. Shepherd / Meredith Grey (PVM): Taylor!
Dr. Yang or Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Taylor OR Digby Owens OR Izzie Stevens (PVM): Dr. Taylor!
Dr. Taylor / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Oh, god.
Dr. Taylor / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Sorry.
Dr. Taylor / Dr. Taylor (PVM): I'm on it.
George / Dr. Taylor OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): My bad, Chuck.
Dr. Taylor / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): He was right, wasn't he?
Dr. Taylor / Dr. Taylor (PVM): I nodded off.
George / Dr. Taylor OR Dr. Taylor (PVM): Come on.
Dr. Taylor / Dr. Taylor OR Dr. Taylor (PVM): Yeah, whatever you got to do to get through the day, all right?
Dr. Taylor: Steph, get me some coffee.
Steph: Yes, doctor.
Dr. Taylor / Dr. Taylor (PVM): I'll be fine.
Dr. Taylor / Dr. Taylor (PVM): It won't happen again.
Dr. Taylor / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Yeah, not in here it won't.
Dr. Taylor: Steph, call Dr. Pennington.
Dr. Taylor: Hopkins, take over until she gets here.
Dr. Taylor / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Get out of here and get it together.
George / Digby Owens (PVM): What happened?
Hopkins / Dr. Taylor OR Digby Owens (PVM): He went into multisystem organ failure, secondary to overwhelming sepsis.
Hopkins / Digby Owens (PVM): Now he's all.
Steph / Digby Owens (PVM): If it fixes his BP, that should help his mental status.
Hopkins / Digby Owens OR Dr. Taylor (PVM): He's maxed out on presto.
Steph / Digby Owens OR Dr. Taylor (PVM): We got V-tach.
Hopkins / Digby Owens (PVM): He's looking bad.
Hopkins / Digby Owens OR Digby Owens (PVM): Put the D-fib pads on him and give him 150 on amiodarone.
Steph / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Yeah.
Steph / Digby Owens (PVM): I lost his pulse.
Hopkins / Digby Owens (PVM): D-fib, get the pads.
Hopkins / Meredith Grey OR Digby Owens OR Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Digby Owens (PVM): Get the paddles in charge of 200.
Hopkins / Meredith Grey OR Digby Owens OR Digby Owens (PVM): Clear.
Dr. Taylor / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Taylor OR Digby Owens (PVM): This packing we hope will, uh...
Dr. Taylor / Dr. Taylor (PVM): prevent hemorrhaging.
Dr. Shepherd / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Taylor (PVM): Dr. Yang, do you want to add something to that?
Dr. Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): We'll allow the cerebral spinal fluid to eventually fill the cavity.
Dr. Shepherd / Meredith Grey (PVM): Very nice.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Taylor (PVM): You two, you want to close up?
Dr. Karev / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Taylor (PVM): Yes, Doc.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Taylor (PVM): I'm going to go to bed.
Dr. Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): That was unreal.
Dr. Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): I mean, that's all there is.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): I was feeling sick until I came here.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Taylor (PVM): I was tired.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Now I'm tired again.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Taylor (PVM): It's back to reality.
Dr. Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): So forget about your troubles
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Let me explain.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Taylor (PVM): It's fine.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Taylor (PVM): No, there is a code among doctors.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Taylor (PVM): We're not supposed to ask each other questions.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Not within the walls of this hospital.
Dr. Bailey / Jamie's Parent (PVM): Okay, I was out of line.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Taylor (PVM): No, you weren't.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Taylor (PVM): I was.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Taylor (PVM): I was out of line.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Somebody should have taken responsibility, and it should have been the guy doing the cutting.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Taylor (PVM): It should have been me.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Taylor (PVM): You didn't deserve what happened to you today.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Taylor (PVM): You did the right thing.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Code or no code.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Taylor (PVM): You saw me leave the house this morning, didn't you?
Claire / Jamie's Parent (PVM): Oh, is that you?
Doctor / Dr. Taylor OR Jamie's Parent (PVM): I'm not using her.
Doctor / Dr. Taylor (PVM): And I don't favor her.
Claire / George O'Malley (PVM): She's pretty great, you know.
Doctor / Unknown (PVM): Mm-hmm.
Claire / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Yeah.
Doctor / Dr. Taylor (PVM): So come on, let's go tell Jamie's parents she's going to be fine, barring any complications.
Claire / Meredith Grey (PVM): Did you fix me?
Doctor / Meredith Grey (PVM): No, not completely.
Claire / Meredith Grey (PVM): So I won't get fat?
Doctor / Meredith Grey (PVM): No.
Claire / Meredith Grey OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, that's awesome.
Doctor / Meredith Grey (PVM): Claire, I've asked social services to contact your parents.
Claire / Meredith Grey (PVM): Why?
Doctor / Meredith Grey (PVM): They can help you.
Claire / Meredith Grey (PVM): With what?
Doctor / Meredith Grey (PVM): You don't know this yet, but life isn't supposed to be like this.
Doctor / Meredith Grey (PVM): It's not supposed to be this hard.
Narrator / Digby Owens OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Well, don't worry with your suitcase, dear.
Doctor / Digby Owens (PVM): Time of death, 2049.
Narrator / Digby Owens OR Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Digby Owens (PVM): Don't worry with your suitcase, dear.
Narrator / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Digby Owens (PVM): First guy I ever met out here from back home.
Narrator / Meredith Grey (PVM): Because the people out to get you don't know that you're here.
Narrator / Meredith Grey (PVM): So don't worry with your suitcase, dear.
Doctor / Meredith Grey (PVM): I thought you'd be asleep by now.
Claire / Meredith Grey (PVM): Yeah, well, I'm not.
Doctor / Meredith Grey OR Izzie Stevens (PVM): You wait a few minutes, you can have a piece of cake baked a chock full of love.
Claire / Meredith Grey OR Izzie Stevens (PVM): Actually, chock full of unrelenting, all-consuming rage and hostility, but still tasty.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): So you know.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): I know.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Well, do you want the long-sworded version, or do you want the short version where I started sleeping with a guy who turned out to be my boss?
Izzie Stevens / Izzie Stevens OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Neither.
Meredith Grey: Izzy, cut me some slack here.
Izzie Stevens: No.
Izzie Stevens: You went to Dartmouth.
Izzie Stevens: Your mother is Ellis Gray.
Izzie Stevens: You grew up... Look at this house.
Izzie Stevens: You know, you walk into the O.R., and there isn't anyone who doubts that you should be there.
Izzie Stevens: I grew up in a trailer park.
Izzie Stevens: I went to state school.
Izzie Stevens: I put myself through med school by posing in my underwear.
Izzie Stevens: You know, I walk into the O.R., and everyone hopes I'm the nurse.
Izzie Stevens: You have their respect without even trying, and you're throwing it away for what?
Izzie Stevens: A few good surgeries?
Meredith Grey: No.
Meredith Grey: It's not about the surgeries.
Meredith Grey: It's not about getting ahead.
Izzie Stevens: Then what?
Izzie Stevens: A little hot sex?
Izzie Stevens: You're willing to ruin your credibility over that?
Izzie Stevens: I mean, Meredith, what the hell are you doing?
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, my god.
Izzie Stevens: You're falling for him.
Meredith Grey: I am not.
Izzie Stevens: Oh, you so are.
Meredith Grey: No, I'm not.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): You so are.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Damn it.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): You poor girl.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): You know, it's just that he's just so, and I'm just, I'm having a hard time.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): You're all mushy and warm and full of secret feelings.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): I hate you.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): And your cake.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey (PVM): My cake is good.
Izzie Stevens / Meredith Grey OR Izzie Stevens (PVM): So, um, how hot is this sex?
Meredith Grey / Izzie Stevens (PVM): Izzy.
Izzie Stevens / Izzie Stevens (PVM): What?
Izzie Stevens / Izzie Stevens (PVM): Come on, I'm not getting any.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Taylor OR Izzie Stevens (PVM): Help a girl out with a few details.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Taylor OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Maybe we like the pain.
Meredith Grey / Jamie's Parent (PVM): How's she doing?
Cristina Yang / Jamie's Parent OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Good.
Meredith Grey / Jamie's Parent OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Good.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Maybe we're wired that way.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Digby Owens OR Dr. Taylor (PVM): Christina?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Taylor OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Because without it, I don't know.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Taylor OR Meredith Grey (PVM): Maybe we just wouldn't feel real.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Taylor OR Dr. Taylor (PVM): You know, we could just... Sleep?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Taylor OR Dr. Taylor (PVM): We could, yeah, if you want to.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Taylor (PVM): Yeah?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): What's that saying?
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey (PVM): Why do I keep hitting myself with a hammer?
Cristina Yang / Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, thank God.
Meredith Grey / Meredith Grey OR Dr. Taylor OR Meredith Grey (PVM): because it feels so good when I stop.