previously on "grey's anatomy"...
I'm getting married to burke.
Ouch.
I went to the board this morning and told them I was retiring.
One of us could be chief.
We were here long before you and george started fooling around.
- He is my husband.
- Stop saying that like it means something.
jane doe,about six months pregnant.
Found under a pile of rubble.
She can't remember anything from before the accident.
Go 60 days with no sex,no other women.
- My mother's dead,isn't she?
- Yes.
Why didn't you stay and fight for us?
I-I tried.
Alex,I'm sorry.
I can'T.
people have scars in all sorts of unexpected places,
like secret road maps  of their personal histories,
diagrams of all  their old wounds.
Alex!
God.
Yeah,yeah,yeah.
Seen it all before.
What the hell are you doing here?
- Moving in.
- What?
Most of our old wounds heal,leaving nothing behind  but a scar.
But some of them don'T.
Alex is moving in?
To this house?
- He's taking george's room.
- Why?
I was asleep just a minute ago.
Yeah.And I was naked in the bathroom when alex walked in.
I'm lucky I didn't come out of the shower
to find him peeing all over the seat.
And we're up.
What's wrong with where he was living before?
- I don't know where he was living before.
- Probably a whorehouse.
I can't have him living in the room right next door.
It's weird.
People are what matters.
Alex is one of our people.
We can't leave him out in the cold.
"People are what matters"?
You don't like people.
- Is this about your mother?
- No.
I had a near death whatever,and...
I was dead.
And now I'm not.
So I'd like to use this chance
I've been given to be more positive.
People are what matters.
Paint with all the colors of the wind.
Oh.
Okay.
You're crazy now.
- I'm alive.
- Yeah,okay.
No,no.
Um,I'm not done in there yet.
Oh,don't worry.
Not looking,not interested.
Some wounds we carry  with us everywhere,
and though the cut's  long gone...
no,she's selfish,is izzie's problem.
The pain still lingers.
She's not selfish.
She's generous.But...
she--
she's self-absorbed.
I mean,her problem is that she doesn't see other people's perspectives.
Hey,give me a bite.
You know,it's weird because she's so ridiculously compassionate with her patients.
You'd think she'd roll some of that out for her friends,
- how about we not talk about her anymore?
- but not the way--
That's a fine idea.
He is in george's room,
and when george's stupid marriage crashes and burns,
he's gonna want to move back in,and he won't be able to.
His life will be in a shambles,
he'll finally notice that his dad is dead
and he made a fool out of himself
by marrying somebody he doesn't really love,
and he'll have no place to go.
Is that what you want?
That's exactly what I want.
- Hey,look who found some clothes.
- Shut it.
How you doing?
Okay,everybody,let's do this once.
I'm fine,she's cremated,I picked out a beautiful urn,
and she's hanging out in the back of my closet.
Any more questions about my dead mother,or can we get back to work?
does anyone know who the new chief candidate is?
The chief's bringing in a ringer in case
he doesn't want to give the job to either of your boyfriends.
O'malley,you're with shepherd today.
Yang,Dr. Montgomery.
Stevens,to the clinic.
Karev,jane doe.
Grey,scut.
Once again,I am fine.
You can tell everybody you fine till you're blue in your face.
Your mom died,and you almost joined her.
You're taking it easy.
Anybody come looking for me yet?
Well,no match on your prints,no.
No hits from missing persons,plus--
my face is hard to identify.
Well,the second they find something out about your identity,
I'm gonna come tell you.
Dr. Sloan says I need surgery on my eye.
Well,he just wants to make sure you don't lose vision there completely.
But Dr. Montgomery says I should wait a day or two 'cause of the baby.
I don't know what I'm supposed to make of that.
Yeah,well,I mean,surgery can be hard on a baby,
but you're gonna be on a fetal monitor the whole time,
so if anything goes wrong,we'll catch it.
Thank you.
I really--
I really appreciate you taking the time to...
I mean,you're--
you're all I've got in this place.
does that hurt?
Of course it hurts.
Don't poke it like that.
Has the lump been there a long time?
I got shot 50 years ago.
It's been there a long time.
But it hasn't bothered you till...
recently?
It bothers me there's a bullet in there.
It'd bother you,too,
but it didn't start hurting till a couple of months ago.
You think it's a bullet?
I don't "think," lady.
I know.
I wanted it out,but the army doctors didn't want to go get it.
So they let me keep it in for half a lifetime.
Well...
let's get some pictures,see if you're right.
I know I'm right.
Save your film.
Just get me something for the pain.
Mr. Scofield,I'm sure you are right,
but we're still gonna do this my way.
- Derek.
- There she is.
How was your flight?
They didn't feed me,which I don't understand.
Dr. O'malley,Dr. Crawford.
She's a big pain in the ass.
- Pleasure.
- He says that because we worked together in new york,
and I was the only one who never had a crush on him.
No,I-I don't buy that.
What do we know,o'malley?
Dr. Crawford has a parafalcine meningioma along
the superior sagittal sinus.
You've operated three times.
It keeps on coming back.
Yeah,it's in dangerous territory,so we leave a little bit of
the tumor behind each time,
and we go back every couple of years and,uh,tune it up.
But this is the last time.
- Sorry?
- This is it,derek.
I'm done after this.
Helen...
the recovery takes forever,and it's not like when jake was around.
I go through this by myself now.
Don't throw in the towel.
I'm looking at the situation as it is.
I am going to do this now,
then I am going to spend
the next two years of my life lying on a beach,
enjoying the sun.
- Helen...
- stop looking at me like I killed your cat.
The decision is made.
You guys seen bailey?
- What are we doing?
- checking out the new chief candidate.
chief's in with the ringer.
We're lurking in a way that was subtle when it was two of us,
- but isn't now that it's 12.
- I heard it was someone from stanford.
All the professors there loved me.
- They loved you?
- I was a great student.
- how you doing,grey?
- Oh,I'm fine,sir.Thank you.
- move,move,move.
- She doesn't like it when people ask.
The ringer's in there with the chief.
Yeah,and whoever it is loves cristina
because everyone at stanford  just loved cristina.
- Shut up.
- She's a motivated student.
- That's nothing to be ashamed of.
- Thank you.
A bit of a kiss ass,but that's hard to control.
oh,they're coming out.
Look away.
that's colin marlowe.
like the marlowe transplant?
Like the brightest thing in cardiothoracic surgery in a generation.
Uh,Dr. Marlowe...
I'm,uh,preston burke.
I'm a great admirer of your work,sir.
- Uh,particularly the--
- yes,thank you.I--
would you excuse me for just a second?
Well...
you gonna give me a hug or what?
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:YTET-gagegao colleen
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Greys Anatomy
Season 03 Episode 18
So what was that,exactly?
He was my professor.
We were close.
Well,"close" appears to be something of an understatement.
It was a long time ago.
I talk about him all the time.
You never thought to mention it?
Well,um,I didn't think you wanted to hear about every guy I ever slept with.
I have a hysterectomy to prep.
Are we done with the curiosity?
Great.
What are you doing tonight?
'Cause I don't want to go home and find alex there,
and it's just the two of us,you know?
And it's weird and awkward,
and he doesn't know whether he should talk to me or not talk to me.
it's just such an awkward situation.
I'd rather it be group awkwardness,you know?
I don't want to just be standing there staring at him.
Meredith?
- Hey,have you seen montgomery?
- No.
Hey!What are you doing tonight?
You want to come over?
'Cause you and I never really get a chance to hang out and...
it might be kind of fun.
Alex just moved in,which was meredith's brilliant idea.
And he still has a thing for me,so it'S...
what the hell?
This is my hiding spot.
My father is out there.Go somewhere else.
- I need this closet,meredith.
- Colin marlowe?
Yes,he was my professor.
We were close.
He had his hand on your ass.
I sure hope you were close.
Did you see somebody go in there?
I did.
Someone's hiding from me.
Yes,I think someone's hiding from me,too.
You were that girl,huh?
The girl who slept with the professor.
We had one in my class.
She only got to the radiologist,though.
No one got near  the cardio god.
Yeah,yeah,yeah.I scored big.
You know,hide in the bathroom.
My awkwardness with my father is well-established.
You and the cardio god,on the other hand,have loads to catch up on.
But I don't want to talk to the cardio god.
you know we can hear you in there,right?
Loud and clear.
oh.
Hi.
- Excuse me.May I?
- Yeah.
- Oh,I was just leaving,actually.
- We heard about your mother.
- I'm so sorry.
- Thank you.
There wasn't a funeral or anything?
Oh,she didn't want that.
I hope everything's okay with the baby.
Oh,we're not here with the baby.
We're here because we wanted to make sure that you were all right.
Oh,well,that's sweet,but we don't have to do this.
I'm not in shock.
I'm not racked with grief.
I'm just moving on.
But you're hiding in a broom closet.
Well,if you could just move my father...
I sent him to go get some coffee,but we'd really like to...
you know,make dinner or something...
for you.
He's been really worried about you.
And he's the family you have left,meredith.
I-I don't see it that way.
Oh,when is this gonna stop?
Yes,he made some mistakes,but he's not a monster.
He's just...
an inarticulate person who spills food on his shirt,a lot.
Have dinner with us,tonight.
I'll make some chili.
The whole thing will be over in an hour.
You think you can do that?
I can't believe you hid in a closet when you saw me coming.
If it wasn't just tragic,it might be the most adorable thing I've ever seen.
You could've warned me.
I thought,cristina yang wouldn't hide in a closet
'cause she doesn't want to talk to me,
which clearly she doesn't
because she fled like a roach in sunlight when she saw me coming.
You know,I did not flee.
I was--I have work to do.
I'm not a professional note taker anymore.
You grew your hair.
It's lovely.
Don't flirt with me.
I have a person.
Really?
Who?
Preston burke.
you never change.
Must be adorable.
No.Shut up.
It is a real relationship.
- I bet it is.
- I'm marrying him.
Oh...
good.
Congratulations.
No,I'm being genuine.
It's wonderful.
can I give you a congratulatory hug?
Don't touch my ass.
My stomach is growling.
Sorry.
We can't let you eat before the surgery.
That's okay.
I stayed at the archfield last night.
I had them make me breakfast at midnight.
You should try the french toast.
It'll blow your mind.
Breakfast at the archfield on an intern's salary?
Yeah,I kinda live there at the moment.
My wife has a deal there.
That's one hell of a deal.
So our room service bill at the archfield,is that part of the deal?
Yeah,sure.
I mean,breakfast alone is,what,probably 50 bucks a day?
And they still only charge us $400 a week?
Sometimes I pay them more for room service.
Okay.Well,then just tell me how much it is,
and we'll split it like we do the rest.
- Don't worry about it,george.
- No,come on.
I'm not gonna have you pay for all the food.
Just tell me how much the room service bill is.
We pay about,mm,800 a week.
Dollars?
I told you not to worry about it.
- You can't afford that.
- yes,I can.
How?
I'm your husband now.
You're supposed to tell me this stuff.
Okay.
Just come here.
All right,my parents have a lot of money...
- what?
- And so I...
have more money than I'm making.
And we don't have a special deal through family friends at the archfield.
- I just--I pay for it.
- How much?
$2,500 a week.
- You're an heiress.
- Okay.
- See,this is why I don't tell people.
- You're an heiress.
- No,stop talking.
- You're an heiress?
Don't-- just don't,okay?
Stop talking.Stop talking.I mean it.
I-I didn't tell you because my parents' money
has affected every single relationship in my life,
and so I've stopped talking about it and living it--
no,wait,wait.So wait.
So I've been--
I've been paying you $200 a week for what,fun?
no.
I use it to tip housekeeping.
Great!
Oh!
Oh,I'm--
you know,I'm glad I could pitch in.
You know,is there anything else that I should know about that's,
I don't know,huge like this?
Uh,I-I-I used to have a pet ferret for nine years.
George...
great.
Stop distracting the staff.
You're pushy.
Anybody ever tell you that?
um,so what do you think of a sagittal sinus bypass?
Have you ever scrubbed in on a sagittal sinus bypass,Dr. O'malley?
No.
It is what they call "big balls" surgery.
- Apparently I have a surgeon with--
- it's been very successful.
When the patient doesn't stroke out.
If it works,the tumor's all gone.
We never have to go back in there again.
- If it doesn't work,I'm dead.
- If you refuse to come back in two years,you're dead anyway.
- That's a decision I can live with.
- That isn't a decision  i can live with.
O'malley,go find her labs.
So what do you think,huh?
A few years on a beach,and then what?
After you piss away your savings,your memory goes,
motor skills deteriorate,and you're dying a very slow,
- miserable,painful death...
- derek--
you're gonna call me up and you're gonna ask me
why we didn't do something when we had the chance.
Now that is not something I can live with,
not when we can do something right now to prevent it.
Well,it looks like the bullet has damaged your scapula.
No wonder it hurts.
How did you get shot,sir?
Korea.Garden spot.
Makes a nice vacation.
Can I get a damn painkiller?
I think we'll do you one better.
We're gonna take it out.
My bullet?
there was no reason to remove it
when you first got hit,but now it's infected.
It's working its way into your scapula,and we can't have that.
- I need to see that bullet.
- You gonna frame it?
No,smarty-pants.
I was fragged a couple of weeks before it all ended.
- "Fragged"?
- yeah,shot by one of his own men.
I made a decision,and they didn't like it.
And then what do you know?
We're facing enemy fire,and I take a hit from the wrong side of the line.
I could never prove it,but we can prove it now
when you pull the damn thing out of me.
- Get me my bullet.
- Let's calm down,Mr. Scofield.
Do you know what it's like when your own men turn on you?
It's not a good feeling.
I just agreed to have dinner at my father's house,tonight.
And cristina slept with colin marlowe.
"Marlowe transplant" marlowe?
They had a thing when she was a student.
How could I have a meal at my father's house?
- He slept with cristina?
- Derek.
Oh,right.
Sorry.Okay.
Um,have dinner at your house.
It's your place.
I'll come.
I'll be your wingman.
It'll be fun.
Okay,it won't be fun.
But it'll be...it'll be fine.
- They're your family.
- Why does everyone assume that?
You deserve to have a family,whether you like them or not.
I thought we had a deal.
We agreed I wouldn't sleep with anybody for two months.
We never said I wouldn't look.
- You didn't think I'd hold out.
- No,I didn'T.
- You're worth it.
- You bet your ass I am.
She's rich,totally rich,boatloads of money.
- George,that's fantastic.
- No,it'S...
it's not fantastic.
cristina did colin marlowe.
Callie's rich.
- Don't talk to her about it.
- "Her"?
- I'm sorry,I don't have a name anymore.
- "Don't tell anyone.¡± Those were my words.
- So--so she's rich.
- Just shut up about it.
Do you think that's possible?
If you give me the "people is what matters" thing again,
I will kill you.
Colin marlowe.
Was it good?
Was he good?
Did he make you a better lover?
Remember all the other times I've talked to you about my sex life?
No.
Exactly.
Did I miss anything about her doing the old guy?
- She's not talking.
- Oh,she'll talk.
So I was supposed to be back in the game today,
but instead I'm planning dinner for my father in my dead mother's house.
I don't cook.
How am I supposed to cook for them?
I will make your stupid dinner.
So were there any little blue pills involved,or is he untouched by time?
Dude,that's just wrong.
Don't answer that.
Because I am your friend,I will show up at
your house 45 minutes into the dinner with a fake crisis.
So if it's,uh,unbearable,you can abort.
Oh,thank you.
Come on.
He's not a young man.
He wasn't getting a little help?
Poppin' the pill?
Dad's best friend?
Come on.
You're gonna give me nothing after everything we've been through?
Nothing?
It's a miracle drug.
And someday,it'll save your life.
Ah,Dr. Marlowe?
Rek shepherd.
I'M doing a sagittal sinuspass today if you'd like to observe.
Really?
That's quite a procedure.
Well,it's a good trick,but if you're really interested to see
what this hospital can do,
I'm performing an arterial switch operation for a T.G.A.
This afternoon.
If you gentlemen are trying to intimidate the competition,
it's working.
Good.
I'll see both of you in surgery.
Colin marlowe.
The one and only.
- He...
- yes.
- With...
- Wow.
- Indeed.
Yeah.
Suction.
No,not like you're driving a tractor.
Slowly.
Better.
What's the chance she wakes up and remembers everything?
I wouldn't count on it.
Dr. Sloan,the baby's having decels.
Are you sure?
Sometimes the monitor's not on right.
You get a false read.
She's got vaginal bleeding.
The baby's in distress.
- Oh,damn it.
- Page Dr. Montgomery.
Now!
you're making an honest woman of cristina yang.
That's--
that's impressive.
I always thought she was collecting us,like baseball cards.
Baseball cards?
Well,she likes an authority figure,someone with something to teach her.
But I never thought she would actually commit.
She use to say to me that she thought that marriage was for the weak and undirected.
I made a number of marriage proposals.
It seemed the polite thing to do after such a long time together,
but,uh,she wouldn't have it.
All what time?
You were just having a fling with a student.
A fling?
Cristina and i were together for three years.
Is the problem that I slept with my professor,
or that I was committed enough to keep at it for three years?
Oh,no.
You told him that you thought marriage was an idiotic institution.
- It is.
- Then why did you say yes?
- Because I want to make you happy.
- "Happy"?
You know,I'll do a lot of things to make you happy.
Do I give a crap about a ceremony with a dress and a flautist?
No.
But I'm happy to do it if it'll make you happy.
Heartwarming.
Thanks.
you couldn't have waited one day?
She was 40% vision compromised in her right eye.
It would've been gone tomorrow.
No,it wouldn't,actually,
but there's a snazzy new chief candidate marching around the hall today,
and you needed to be a hero.
That's what needed to happen today.
The patient was fine,addison.
The baby's still in her uterus,and she's not losing an eye.
Every surgery is risky.
The patient chose this one.
Karev...
don't just stand there.
The patient's baby was in distress.
Go.
Stay with her.
Something happen with jane doe?
Yeah,she can see,and addison's got a problem with it.
He rushed her into surgery,and she almost lost the baby.
I had to sew  her cervix shut.
The complications had nothing to do with the surgery.
And why?
Why do you think mark moved so quickly,derek?
Do you think it's because a piece of
the orbital bone was floating towards the brain?
Well,I think it's because mark wants a promotion.
You're not her husband.
This isn't your patient.
Stay out of it!
What the hell do you people think you're doing?
You're supposed to be the leadership of this hospital.
Screaming about a patient in the hallway?
Are you out of your minds?
- tough procedure.
- Mm-hmm.
It's a bold choice.
We've been fighting this one for a while.
I'm hoping this will be the end of it.
what h happened?
end-tidal c0-2 just dropped from 30 to 16.
Bagging manually.
Doppler's showing air in the left ventricle.
0-2 stat's down to 89.
aspirate the central line.
- She's bradycardic.
- Push 1 of atropine.
There's no air in the central line.
All right,level her out.
I'm gonna flood the field.
asystole.
Push 1 milligram of epi.
Start compressions.
Go.
Get in there.
Get in there! Do it!
That things been in there since the korean war?
He's lucky it didn't travel down to his aorta.
Okay,a little suction there.
Almost...
I got it.
make sure we get that back.
The patient wants it.
He's got a warped sense of nostalgia.
Hmm,I get it.
If they pulled a bullet out of me,
I'd want it cast in gold and mounted on my wall.
Yeah,well,you can afford it.
just a little more suction.
Let's get ready to close.
she's not responding.
- I'm gonna open her up.
- Open cardiac massage?
You're a neurosurgeon.
You have no privileges in this hospital.
Get the glasses off.
- Should we page Dr. Burke?
- No,I've got it.
Cross clamp the hilum.
You don't want air in the cerebral arteries.
Yeah,I got it.
Give me a 10-blade.
10-blade quickly,please.
O'malley,get over here.
Let's roll her.Ready?
One,two,three.Go.
Okay,rib spreader.
okay,scissors.
Massage her heart,o'malley.
I need to aspirate.
any air return?
10 cc'S.
end-tidal c0-2 is going back up.
the heart's starting to beat on its own.
Pressure's 60 over 40.
It's low,but it's there.
She's gonna make it.
should I start closing her up?
Dr. Shepherd?
O'malley,I just sliced my friend's chest open.
Give me a moment.
that was very well-handled,Dr. Shepherd.
Very impressive,indeed.
Not something I want to do every day,but thank you.
What happened?
Dr. Shepherd's patient had a venous air embolism.
He had to split her chest open,massage her heart
and manually aspirate right in the middle of his procedure.
Why didn't you call me?
- Uh,you were operating.
- I was next door.You could've pulled me out.
There was no time.
I handled it.
You think I crack people's heads open if you're in the building
- just because I think I can handle a brain bleed?
- The patient is fine.
- The patient is lucky,and you were showboating.
- Showboating?
What,are you out of your mind?
I was--
we seem to be going out of our way to impress Dr. Marlowe.
- I'll bet we are.
- Gentlemen...
good day,doctors.
How you feeling,Mr. Scofield?
Where's my bullet?
that it?
Where's the rest of it?
That was it.
Is that a letter?
Can you read that?
I-I don't think it's much of anything.
I-I think it's just a scratch.
It's so small.
It could just be anything.
It's been a long time.
They don't hold up that well.
Could you have your lab,you know,analyze it?
Tell me if it's one of ours or--
we're not set up for that kind of investigation,Mr. Scofield.
You could try to send it to a forensic lab,
but I don't know if they'll tell you much either.
I've been stewing for 50 years.
Maybe it's time to move on.
To what?
I lost my whole unit over this.
I came home.
My wife,she didn't get it.
I've been blazing mad my whole life.
I got nothing left.
It's not too late to let it go and start over.
You're a sweet kid,
but you don't know what
it's like to have something change you in your soul.
I do.
I wish I didn't,but I do.
Don't let it turn you.
you look like you had a long day.
You know what fragging is?
We've got an epidemic of it today.
My esteemed attendings are gonna be the death of me.
Is there a front-runner?
I don't know.
What I do know is I don't want my attendings tearing each other's throats out
because of some internal power struggle.
It's too dangerous for the hospital.
Does that mean...
is colin marlowe gonna be the new chief?
Good night,Dr. Bailey.
This is ready.
Don't slosh it around.
It's all about the presentation.
Come in and eat with us.
You need to bond with your people,meredith.
People are what matters.
- I hate people.
- Yeah,well,do your own talking.
We talked.
We talked hospital,we talked his research,we talked dead mother.
- I'm out.
- Ask about the baby.
Ask if it poos.
People can go on about that for hours.
- oh,the chicken looks delicious.
- Yeah.
It's from the store.
Well,the green beans look great as well.
I...
didn't do those either.
It's beautifully presented.
Izzie did that.
Alex!
Come,sit.
oh.
no,go ahead.
Eat.
We're eating.
This is susan,and this is my father.
Hi.
- Here,you can have this plate.
- Cool.
Okay.
So how are you?
How was your day?
Okay.
Hungry.
Good.
How's the baby?
- Great.
- She's smiling now...sometimes.
she looks exactly like
molly wh-when she smiles.
I mean, it's amazing.I've got this
old picture of molly and me
when molly was...
I don't know, 5,
and she's sitting on this red sled
in the snow, this great, big fir tree...
- you know, I'm not sure that that--
- yeah.
No, honey, it's a massive douglas fir.
And in the picture, couldn't
look more like the baby.
- I mean, incredible.
- That's me.
The red sled and the big fir tree in the
park at the middle school in the ugly,
yellow, plaid wool coat.
That isn't molly.
It's you and me.
- Oh, great.
- crap.
Sorry.
I think I blew a fuse.
- I'll get it.
- No, you know, I could get it.
- It's--
- oh, in the laundry room.
- I keep forgetting.
- What?
It's his house.
I'm going home.
Are you going home?
How did it end?
It ended.
School was ending, I was leaving.
You were done.
I came here.
I fell in love with you.
A new mentor with a host of
new things to teach you.
If you think that I'm
in this for the education--
do you or do you not find
my knowledge and my skill compelling?
Oh, god.You know what?
You are blowing this way out of--
a man three times your age
believed that he was having
a substantial relationship with you...
well, yeah, he was.
And one day, you're done, just like that?
yes.
You don't open yourself up...
to anyone.
Sometimes...
I think it's charming--
she's different, she's not like other women.
But the simple fact is--
is that you have never let me in.
What, you think that it's
gonna make a good marriage?
Well, I don'T.
I don't want you to marry me
because you're placating me.
That doesn't interest me.
It doesn't interest me at all.
- Do you think he's okay?
- He'll find it.
He probably can't see.
Um, there's a flashlight in the closet.
- I'll go get it.
- Thanks.
Excuse me.
- I'm sorry.
- It's going fine.
I just...
I don't know what to say to him.
Well, it's not easy.
That's 'cause he's afraid of you.
I shouldn't have bit his head off.
I wish I could've just...
meredith, it's okay to get angry.
It's you in the picture.
Izzie stevens?
I share something with you that
I clearly feel uncomfortable about,
and you tell izzie stevens?
No, I didn't tell izzie.
I told meredith.Meredith told--
oh!
Oh, so that's better?
No, it was an accident.
I--
it was an accident.
I was pissed off--
why can't you give me
the benefit of the doubt that--
that maybe sometimes I'm on your side?
Because you choose your friends
over me
- every chance you get.
- No, I don'T.
I married you, and I haven't talked
to my best friend in weeks.
Meanwhile you lied to me
about where we live and why.
You lied to me about your background.
You lied to me about your family!
And still I'm the dog who gets whacked
on the nose with a newspaper all the time.
When is this gonna stop?
- Oh, so this is my problem?
- Yeah, maybe it is.
Oh, oh, so the fact that your
best friend violently disses our marriage
every chance she gets,
publicly, repeatedly...
why do you think she does that george?
Have you ever thought about that?
She's having a problem with this.
I understand that.
She has feelings for you.
- What?
- She wants you.
She wants you.
That's what this is about.
That's why she hates me.
george, george, do not laugh at me.
Do not laugh at me.
No.
no, I'm not.I'm not.
Oh, god.
I'm not.
I--
it's just, come on, she's izzie.
She's--
she's bl--
she's blonde, she's stacked, she's--
she's a supermodel.
I'm george.
- So what does that make me?
- No.
No, come on.
You are gorgeous...
and you're curvy, and I never
thought you'd go for me.
- Just shut up.
- Callie--
this is my hotel room that
I pay for with my huge piles of money.
Get the hell out of it!
I'm sorry about the lights.
eh, whatever.
The food was good.
- You want some pie?
- Nah, I gotta go.
Oh, big plans.
Got a hot date?
Oh.
Well, good for you.
I guess "not interested"
really meant not interested.
Iz...
- you didn't want me.
- Yeah.
But that doesn't mean I want
you to want anyone else.
Am I gonna be alone,
pining over a dead guy forever?
I hope not.
It's kind of a waste.
am I supposed to move on now?
Do people look at me and go,
"she's gotta get over it already.
It's ruining her life"?
You'll move on when you're ready to.
Why are you sitting in the dark?
- Izzie blew a fuse.
- Okay, I'm having a crisis.
Oh, I don't need rescuing.
Susan is very nice,
and we're getting through it.
Limping through, but we'll make it.
Okay, no, this isn't a fake crisis.
This is a real, "my ex is about to
ruin my impending marriage" crisis.
Oh.
Hey.Hey.
Where's izzie?
Kitchen.
Sorry.
It's not always like this.
Yeah, it--
it kinda is.
They're in the other room.
I need you to get over yourself.
I need you to start liking my wife.
I need you to like her
because sometimes I don't,
and I need you to talk me back into it.
You say you're my friend?
That's the job.
Okay.
I need to vent,
and I need it to be okay.
Okay.
And I need to vent with alcohol.
I got married,
and I'm scared it was a bad idea.
nobody ever got married and
didn't think that at least once.
did you find the fuse box?
Yeah.
Yeah, I just needed to...
- take a break?
- I don't know how to--
or what to talk to her about.
Work's a good place to start.
You know, she's proud of what she does.
She's good at it, too.
I'd start with that.
You get each other.
That's nice.
Some days it's nice.
Some days I'd like to come home to someone
who doesn't know a thing about it.
Rough day?
I almost lost a friend in my own O.R.
Was it your fault?
I don't know.
you were both nervous tonight.
- It'll get easier.
- She was nervous?
Yeah.
She's tough.
She tries to hide it.
She's difficult.
But if you make an effort, she's worth it.
You okay?
Not entirely.
She's worth the effort.
All right.
Ah, nice.
damn it.
- Gotta go back in, huh?
- Yeah.
why is there an 11-inch
incision in my chest?
you coded on the table--
air embolus.
I had to open you up and aspirate.
See, I'm sure you did a great job,
but that's why you're gonna have some
real trouble convincing me to do it again.
Helen...
we got it all.
The tumor--we never have to
go back in there again.
- You're sure?
- I'm sure.
You're gonna live a long, long life.
And here I thought
you were just being an ass.
Ah, I was an ass.
I had no right to push you like that.
No, you did not.
I was going through some stuff, and I just--
I...
I was an ass.
Okay.
But in this moment, you're the ass
who gave me my life back.
I'm so glad we did this.
I am, too.Thank you for suggesting it.
Because I--
you never would have in a million years.
- good night, sweetie.
- Thank you.Good night.
I'm--
I'm sorry a-about your mother.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
Swing's still here.
yes, it, uh, doesn't swing.
Nobody uses it.
I put this in there.
You used to catch your fingers in it.
suck it up, go back with your tail
between your legs and just apologize.
- No!
- No, really.Look, you just--
- I'm always apologizing.
- "I'm sorry.I'm an ass." blah.
And it's over.
And then it's all over.
No.Not real--
I can't be wrong all the time.
is that really possible?
Don't--
don't finish it.
- Hey, don't be grabby.
- You--I don't have any.
Bogie.
Maybe you're wrong all the time,
maybe she's just really insecure.
It doesn't matter.
You still have to grovel.
Don't you--
fill...
yeah, um, she'S...
- she's insecure.
- Yeah.
That is a fact.
She's insecure.
What?
just tell me.
- Come on.
- No.
Come on!
shut up.
no, it's, um, ju--nothing.
Just that she thinks you have feelings
for me, like that's the problem.
I love that.
That's fabulous.
- No, and--and--and...
- oh, I need a tissue.
That, uh, I-I-I desperately want you.
I'm crying.
Is she crazy?
You know, I think--
I think she's maybe a little crazy.
- oh, can't breathe.
- Shut up.
I can't breathe.
We gotta be quiet.
Ow.
- scary day, huh?
- Yeah.
Well, your amniotic sac's intact,
the placenta's in good position.
Dr. Montgomery sewed your cervix up
so tight, nothing's coming outta there.
So the baby's gonna be okay?
We're gonna have to see how it goes.
I'm sorry.
You asked me what I thought,
and I told you to go for it, and I'M...
- I'm really sorry.
- It's not your fault.
No, see, when I pulled you out of
that water at the ferry, I...
you're...
I talked to you like you were
my sister, and I shouldn't have.
I'm an intern.
You gotta get your medical
advice from an attending.
I asked you 'cause I trust you.
Why don't you sit and tell me
a bedtime story or something?
What's worse,  new wounds,
which are  so horribly painful...
move over.
You're in the middle of the bed.
Or old wounds that should've
healed years ago  and never did?
am I gonna screw up this engagement?
I don't know.
Do you want to?
My mom is dead.
Yeah, she is.
Maybe our old wounds  teach us something.
They remind us  of where we've been
and what we've overcome.
They teach us lessons about
what to avoid in the future.
That's what we like to think.
But that's not the way it is, is it?
Some things  we just have to learn
over and over and over again.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:YTET-colleen gagegao
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Grey's Anatomy
Season 3 Episode 18