Previously on Grey's Anatomy:
I slept with George.
It was a horrible mistake.
I'm done. We're done.
- Pancakes?
- He's not my roommate.
I shouldn't have given up my place.
He'd still be our roommate
if Meredith apologized.
You know, at some point
you are going to have to talk to me.
Your ex did a real number on you, huh?
- You didn't call me.
- I did, I did. A few times.
I just hung up every time.
- How is she today?
- She's great.
She really lights up
when Dr. Webber visits.
Denny, you're congestive heart failure
is getting worse despite the meds.
We need more time.
My college campus has a magic statue.
It's a long-standing tradition for
students to rub its nose for good luck.
My freshman roommate
really believed in the statue's power
and insisted on visiting it
to rub its nose before every exam.
Are you sure my scrub caps
weren't in laundry delivery?
I triple-checked.
- You're sure?
- Yeah, I'm sure.
Studying might have been a better idea.
She flunked out her sophomore year.
But the fact is we all have
little superstitious things that we do.
All right. It's a beautiful morning
to save lives. Let's have some fun.
If it's not believing in magic statues,
it's avoiding sidewalk cracks, or always
putting our left shoe on first.
OK.
Knock on wood.
Ten blade.
Step on a crack,
break your mother's back.
Paddles.
Ten joules.
- I have to take him off.
- I'm in the middle of his brain.
We're losing him.
Time of death...
Call it, Grey.
The last thing we want to do
is offend the gods.
Time of death 8:17.
Four surgeries, four fatalities
and the day has barely started.
- Can I have a bite of that?
- No.
- You're in my apartment, not my food.
- Dr. Burke gave me a protein bar.
Burke packs his lunch for him.
Did I mention?
- I talked to the morgue guy.
- The one with the unibrow?
The one with the teeth thing.
He said surgical fatalities
come in threes and sevens.
There'll be three more today.
OK then.
Since "dead tooth" morgue guy said so.
He's the morgue guy.
He knows things about death.
You dropped this.
- He's ignoring me.
- Ignore him back.
Derek says I should apologize
until he listens.
- Derek says?
- It's good advice.
He's my friend.
That's good friend advice.
- Hey.
- Meredith...
What?
- Did you sneak out last night?
- Yeah. I, um... I couldn't sleep.
- Come on.
- Where?
- ER.
- All of us?
We've all had deaths.
Let's all go save a life.
Uh, Dr. Bailey.
- Here you go.
- What's this?
Hot cocoa.
It's a little ritual we had in New York.
Four surgeries, four deaths,
we could all use a little good juju.
- And cocoa equals juju how?
- Hey, hey, hey.
Don't question the cocoa.
Carry on.
Meredith.
Thank you for your help this morning.
Oh. Thank you, Addison.
Yeah. Thank you.
- Here you go.
- Juju.
Yep.
- You jujued Meredith.
- I did.
In the spirit of friendship.
- Hmm.
- Are we not friends with Meredith now?
No, no, we are.
Meredith and I are friends.
And you and I are married. So then,
by proxy, Meredith and I are friends.
- That's very big of you.
- Yeah.
You don't have to do that.
It's not like I'm going to be friends
with let's say, uh... Mark.
Yeah, well, neither am I.
Now finish your juju
before somebody else dies.
Hmm.
There are ten.
Music notes. Colorful patterns.
They were sent out last night.
- Sorry about your valve replacement.
- The laundry misplaced my scrub caps.
There's some foolish talk about
fatality clusters in threes and sevens.
Are you sure they weren't sent
to another hospital?
How many electives
have they canceled today?
This is our third.
And what have
the surgeons' reasons been?
Because I prefer my own caps.
You're not pushing surgeries
because you don't have your caps.
- You understand me?
- I didn't push any surgeries.
No, no. The question is:
When will you find them?
No one changes that board
unless they talk to me.
No one.
Great. No blood, no guts,
no lives to save. It's dead quiet.
- Did you really say that?
- Cristina...
- What?
- You said the Q-word.
- It's like saying Macbeth in a theater.
- Please.
You think because someone
says it's quiet...
Can somebody help us?
She's coughing up blood.
O'Malley!
- Denny Duquette.
- I got it.
- He's my patient.
- He's both your patient. Answer it.
Two incoming.
There should be more under there.
OK, uh, Yang, first one's yours.
Grey, take number two.
Go.
Jesse Fannon, 32, unrestrained driver
in a rear-end collision.
Spider-webbing on the windshield
where his head hit.
- BP's 120 palp. Pulse 75.
- Well, what do you want to do, Yang?
Primary and secondary survey.
Uh, head CT and X-ray.
OK. Page Shepherd when you get there.
Wait! I'm counting the siren whoops.
We can't go until it reaches 33.
He also seems to have a touch of OCD.
Nikki Ratlin, 30, erratic BP
in the field. Chest and leg pain.
- What happened?
- I got struck by lightning.
Can anyone spell coincidence?
My horoscope said,
"Stay close to home today. "
Aries couldn't have been any clearer.
OK, I guess it could have said,
"Don't leave the house today
unless you want to get
struck by lightning. " Ouch.
Ms. Ratlin, you have no sign
of wounds from lightning.
It was a sign.
Clearly getting struck by lightning
is a sign.
That I shouldn't have left my house.
Normally people struck by lightning
have a wound
where the bolt
entered and exited the body.
Well... well, I wasn't struck struck.
The tree was struck and it fell on me.
A tree fell on you?
A big, like, branch or limb. Whatever.
Same difference.
No, actually, medically,
it isn't the same difference.
And it would be helpful if from now on
you told us the whole truth.
You want to know the truth?
My boyfriend loves that tree.
He's totally going to freak out.
Ow.
Chief? There's a Ms. Warner
down in Admitting. She's asking for you.
- Who?
- Um, Olive Warner?
Fifties. Uh, blonde hair.
She said she's known you
for about 20 years.
Are you talking about Ollie?
Right. OK. Uh, Ollie Warner.
She presented with upper GI bleeding.
And she had a TIPSS procedure
last month for esophageal varices.
I'll take this from here, O'Malley.
Happy to help, sir.
No, thank you. I got this myself.
Ollie.
Hi, Richard. Good to see you.
Sinus tachycardia,
low-grade fever, pulse ox 75.
- I'm hearing rales in your lungs.
- Yeah.
A freight train rolls through at noon.
How bad is the pain?
I don't know.
A five or six when I breathe.
Which means a seven or eight when you're
not trying to impress your doctor.
Heard, uh, four people died
in surgery this morning.
Said they were expecting three more.
You get that from a nurse?
Never reveal my sources.
Just like to avoid the OR.
And I'm not liking that look.
This could be
a pulmonary embolism, Denny.
A complication from the LVAD surgery.
We have to talk to Dr. Burke.
I got hot chocolated.
The She-Shepherd hot chocolated me.
- It's her juju.
- I don't like people who say juju.
- I say juju.
- Juju, juju, juju. Juju, juju, juju.
Juju, juju, juju.
I didn't drink it.
You're not obligated
to honor someone else's juju.
- Thought you were being friends.
- I am. With him.
Do I have to be friends with her too?
Definitely not.
Maybe.
Juju, juju, juju.
- I'II, uh, call Psych for you.
- That'd be good. Thanks.
Ow! Ow!
All right. That's the worst of it.
I never should have gotten out of bed.
But I really wanted to surprise
my boyfriend before he left for school.
He had a huge exam today and I just,
you know, wanted to wish him luck.
Dr. Torres. Hey. Hi.
Uh, can I give you a hand?
You missed the boat, George.
You mean on this case or?
Or... a hot chick gives you her number,
you're supposed to call.
Yeah.
- I... I was... I mean, I am.
- Too late.
Ouch. Don't give up.
I mean, if you really like her.
Uh... OK.
OK, the plot thickens.
Nikki, Dr. Grey here is going
to take you upstairs for a CT.
But before she does, I have to ask:
You're bruised all up and down your left
side. Sure a tree branch did all this?
You think my boyfriend did this?
He would never hit a woman. Ever.
Mm-hmm.
The bruises doesn't look like
a tree branch hit you.
Fine.
OK, you guys are going to think
I'm really weird,
but I was sort of up in the tree
when the lightning hit.
- And... I fell.
- You climbed a tree in a thunderstorm?
I really wanted it to be a surprise,
you know, for my boyfriend.
And... um, I just... I had to see
if his psycho dog was in the yard
because of, like,
the barking and stuff and...
I know. It sounds really weird.
Does it sound really weird?
- Not at all.
- No.
And the thing is,
I mean, he wasn't even there.
The dog?
No. My boyfriend.
He wasn't even home.
I really shouldn't have
gotten out of bed.
Oh, Dr. Shepherd.
I've got a 34-year-old male with a blunt
head trauma and severe case of OCD.
- Did you call for a psych consult?
- Yes.
- Let me know when you get a CT.
- OK.
Hey.
Hey. Hey, uh, sorry about
that, uh, valve replacement.
Oh, thank you. Laundry lost my caps.
The guy didn't die because
you weren't wearing one of your caps.
I know that.
I just prefer to operate wearing my own.
It's a comfort thing.
Huh, well... I prefer having George
out of our apartment.
So I guess we both have comfort things.
- Yeah, what are you saying?
- Uh, you know, um...
I have one of your caps in my locker.
- Why do you have one of my caps...
- That's not the point.
The point is, um, is that I think
I'm going to keep it hostage.
So you kick Bambi out
and you get your cap back.
Oh, well.
I don't do well with ultimatums.
Maybe you should think of it
more as a... trade.
Dr. Burke.
I've got free time. Do you have
any cases you need help...
Actually, I do.
Cristina has something of mine
and I need you to get it back.
OK, so just call Catherine.
Yeah.
Gretchen, would you mind
leaving us alone for a minute?
- OK.
- Thank you.
She's my new baby. Six months sober,
she's already on the ninth step.
- You must be proud of her.
- Always.
- You're on a transplant list, Ollie?
- A couple of years now.
The cirrhosis prevents blood
from flowing into your liver.
So it's backing up into your esophagus.
Causing the ruptures. It's serious, Ollie.
Well, of course it is. I mean, you don't
puke blood if it's not serious.
The question is: Can you treat it?
Maybe. Surgically.
We'll have to run more tests and...
whatever we do, it's a stop-gap.
You need a new liver.
Yet another reason
I should've laid off the sauce.
You look scared.
I am scared, Ollie.
Haven't seen you at a meeting
in a while.
I know, I know.
How've you been?
- We're talking about you.
- Now I'm asking about you.
Ellis Grey's daughter's
working at the hospital.
Ellis is in a nursing home
with Alzheimer's.
I try to go see her every chance I get.
You're having an affair with the woman
who drove you to your alcoholic bottom.
Ollie, we're not having an affair.
She's sick.
- You're lying to your wife?
- I'm not lying.
You're lying by omission.
You are having an emotional affair.
And now you're lying
to your sponsor about it.
- You haven't been my sponsor in years.
- I still have a right to bust your ass
- if I see you slipping.
- I'm not slipping.
Not yet.
But you're making a pretty big mess.
- How many years you have now?
- Just passed 17.
I'm proud of you.
And I'm scared too.
You got me sober, Ollie.
You walked me through it.
And I'm going to walk you through this.
OK. That's...
She still has...
Oh.
You're a pervy little boy, George.
- You won't find the cap.
- I'll do your dishes for a month.
- I don't do dishes.
- Laundry.
- Or laundry.
- Maybe that's why Burke has me around.
Interesting, interesting.
Are you having sex with him?
- No.
- Then he likes having me around more.
Why does it always have to be
a competition?
- What do you want for the cap?
- You out.
- I'm not leaving until Burke says so.
- Then no cap.
- Now clean up my crap.
- No.
Wow. Is that her spleen?
Looks like a grade three laceration.
Maybe a four.
What was she doing standing under a tree
in a thunderstorm?
She wasn't standing under it.
She was climbing it.
- Why?
- Uh...
I get the feeling
she's a little bit of a stalker.
- Do we need to call the police?
- I don't think so.
I think she's more of a gentle stalker
than a "kill you" stalker.
Right. Well, let's hope she lives
to gently stalk another day.
Hey, you don't believe
in that seven fatality thing, do you?
I believe this girl needs her spleen
removed immediately.
Go pick up her labs and get her
on the board. Then we'll break the news.
It's almost over.
You like horses, Izzie?
Everybody likes horses.
That's not true.
You know,
horses are a great judge of character.
You don't like horses,
means they don't like you.
- Huh.
- My uncle's a rodeo cowboy.
Huh. No kidding.
This is a big clot, Denny.
I can't get it with the catheter.
I'm sorry.
We have to open your chest again.
I was counting the clicks.
The... turn signal clicks.
I couldn't move until it hit 333.
The light was green,
but I couldn't move.
I can't blame them for hitting me.
How long have you had
these compulsions?
A little bit all my life, but it's been
out of control the last three years.
- Onset at 30 is typical.
- Ruined a marriage.
- I can't hold a job...
- OK, Mr. Fannon, do you...
Is it clean?
- I need to know if it's clean.
- It's very clean.
- Any relatives with OCD?
- My mother.
Killed herself at 38.
Ruined her life.
Now it's ruining mine.
- Clean, clean, clean?
- Uh, we clean it between each patient.
I think he needs you to say
"clean, clean, clean. "
It's clean, clean, clean.
Thank you.
I know it's annoying. I can't help it.
Uh, find a penny, pick it up,
all day long you'll have good luck.
Find a penny, pick it up,
- OK, Mr. Fannon, do you...
- Find a penny...
Repetitive rhymes, prayers.
It's classic.
He needs to say it a specific number
of times. Probably a multiple of three.
Let's get him in
before he decides to start again.
Is everything all right
with, uh... that?
Find a penny, pick it up,
all day long you'll have good luck.
Just, uh, don't look at him.
Hey.
Hi.
- Hey...
- Oh, hey.
- Hi.
- I, uh... have to...
- Yeah.
- I do too.
Yeah, I got... something too, so...
I wish I had good news.
The TIPSS procedure
you had last month failed.
What does that mean?
It means you're lucky
you got sober young.
Ollie, it means I'm going to have to
put in a portacaval shunt.
It's complicated.
It has only a 50% survival rate.
What's my other choice?
OK, then.
Um... you'll be the one to do it?
I've performed this surgery nine times.
Had four patients survive.
It's perfect then.
I'll be your five out of ten.
- I'm not having surgery today.
- You have a ruptured spleen.
And I'm sure that the spleen
is very important.
But I'm not having surgery today.
You can operate after midnight
but not one minute before.
If I thought it was safe I'd be more
than happy to wait until after midnight.
However, I have a husband and a baby
at home who won't be happy.
You know who else won't be happy? You.
Your spleen is bleeding.
Spleen trumps horoscope.
But it was more than just my horoscope.
I went out to my car this morning.
Flat tire. That's a sign,
but I just changed the tire.
Then there's a wreck on the freeway.
Do I turn around and go home
like it's telling me to?
No, I detour an hour out of my way
so that I can get to Kevin's house.
And when I get to Kevin's house,
I get struck by lightning!
But you weren't struck by lightning.
I'll die, OK?
If you operate on me today,
I will die because I know I will.
Please, just...
just call my boyfriend and tell him that
I'm having an operation at midnight.
Because he will want to be here.
- OK.
- Please.
- Should I call Psych?
- You can give it a shot.
In the meanwhile, get her down to ICU.
Poor girl's going to kill herself
trying not to die.
Izzie paints a pretty picture
because she likes you.
- OK.
- I'm just saying she likes you.
Which is going to be hard on her.
You mean... when I die?
Come on. I'm asking you... man-to-man.
With a clot in your pulmonary artery,
it'll cut off the oxygen to your lungs
and you'll die of hypoxia.
If the hypoxia doesn't kill you,
the strain on your heart will.
- And the surgery?
- It's not a routine procedure.
You're at serious risk for bleeding
because of the anticoagulants
already in your system.
What I'm saying is Izzie likes you.
And she's not going to be the one
to pull away.
How's your guy?
Brain's bleeding. Needs surgery.
Want to know why?
He couldn't move his car
until he stopped counting.
My girl? Ruptured spleen? Won't have
surgery because of her horoscope.
Well, we should introduce them.
They make a nice crazy couple.
Uh, you know what? I'm sitting
with Meredith. Have some self-respect.
Dr. Burke's orders
trump any personal issues I might have.
Is the craziness rubbing off on him?
He's trying to...
stalk Burke's lucky cap from me.
- Burke has hat juju?
- Apparently.
- And you're using it against him?
- Well, they're forcing me to.
Because of the clarinet playing and the
running and all the breakfast food.
You guys, this whole death cluster thing
is just ridiculous, right?
I mean, just 'cause four died today
it doesn't mean
there'll be three more before midnight.
It doesn't, Tinkerbell? For reals?
- Are you worried about Denny?
- Yeah. Of course I am.
He's my patient.
But if you're asking me
if I'm "worried" about Denny, no.
I'm sleeping with Alex, so...
It's just...
Hey, did Burke say anything to you...
about Denny's surgery? Did he?
- No. It's your case.
- Yeah. I know.
I'm just asking that, you know,
as your boyfriend, if...
I don't know why you'd care.
You're sleeping with Alex, right?
- Yeah.
Right. No, whatever. I'm just saying.
There's no such thing as a
death cluster. It's just stupid. Right?
I have to go convince my patient
to let us operate.
Mm-hmm.
You're removing part of my skullcap?
Do you really have to do that?
It's the only way to get to
the affected part of the brain.
And the operating room,
it's clean, clean, clean?
Yes. It's clean, clean, clean.
I'm going to go get ready.
- Can you stop that, please?
- No. Sorry. I wish I could.
- She's judging me.
- No, she's not.
Yes, she is. I've been living with this
for three years.
And it's always the people who are
most like me who judge me the most.
You're type A, right?
Straight A student? Top of your class?
Yes, I was.
You managed to turn your compulsions
into something productive.
But we're cut from the same cloth.
That's why you can't stand me.
Oh. Time to go.
- But I'm not done.
- Uh, yes you are, sir.
- How many do you have to do?
- 96.
Let him finish.
Fine. I'll see you in the OR.
There's Richard.
Hey. Ollie says you should come in.
She says you need a meeting.
Not now. Not here.
Yeah. She said to say not to protect
your anonymity over your sobriety.
God, grant me the serenity
to accept the things I cannot change,
the courage to change the things I can,
and the wisdom to know the difference.
Amen.
Hey. How you feeling?
Do me a favor?
My will is inside my nightstand.
Just make sure
it gets in the right hands, OK?
Why are you talking about your will?
We have to be realistic, Dr. Stevens.
Dr. Stevens?
We got to be realistic.
And if you can't, well, I can.
No, wait, um...
can you just wait one minute?
Denny, listen to me.
You're not going to die.
You can't go into surgery
thinking you're going to die.
- You want me to pee in front of you?
- You have it on you.
- Really? You want to go there?
- Yes.
What are you going to do, Bambi?
Take it from me?
Burke said to do whatever I have to do
and I'm going to do whatever.
It's not there. You're not getting it.
Oh! No.
No, you're not going to... No.
No. Oh! You've got my breast.
That's my breast.
That's my breast. My breast.
Hey, Dr. Torres.
Dr. O'Malley. You're aware
this is the women's restroom?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Good.
Dude. You called her ma'am.
She's never going to sleep with you now.
Oh, hey. Have you seen Burke?
He's on the phone with the laundry.
They can't find his scrub caps.
That's what I got to tell him.
Cristina won't give hers back.
Unless I'm ready to hit a woman.
Even though it's Cristina,
I won't cross that line.
Wait! Wait, a moment.
Cristina has one of Burke's scrub caps?
She's holding it hostage. Why do
you think I am stalking her? You...
- Uh, ow. You're touching me.
- George says you have Burke's cap.
- So?
- Give it to him.
- No.
- Give it to him, Cristina.
- What is with you?
- He needs it to operate.
- No, he doesn't.
- That isn't your decision to make.
Not when he's going in on Denny. Now, do
I have to physically take it from you?
Are you threatening me?
I swear to God, Cristina, I like you,
I really do.
But I grew up in a trailer park
and I am not above kicking
your pampered little Beverly Hills ass.
And I do mean
physically kicking your ass.
You don't have to follow me.
Well, thank you.
How long have you had this?
It's one of my favorites.
You know, you don't need it.
I keep that cap in my locker
because every morning I look at it
and I'm reminded of what I'm here for
and what I want to be.
A great surgeon.
A surgeon who is decisive,
and who executes,
and who doesn't need a piece of clothing
to give him an edge in surgery.
You don't need it.
I know. You're right.
I know I'm right.
Nicely done, O'Malley.
Let's go scrub in.
How am I doing?
Nikki, is it possible
you're misreading the signs?
I mean, isn't two surgeons
telling you that you need surgery
a sign that you need surgery?
Did you call my boyfriend?
I did.
What'd he say?
He said he hasn't been your boyfriend
in a while.
Did you tell him
I got struck by lightning?
- What did you say to him?
- Who?
You know who. What the hell?
Why does Denny think he's dying?
Well, maybe because
there's a good chance he is.
Just so we're clear.
We're over, Alex. This is over.
What? You're breaking up with me
over a corpse?
No! No.
I am breaking up with you
because on your very best day...
that corpse is twice the man
you will ever be.
You're not good enough for me, Alex.
You're not good enough for anyone.
You two, you're not scrubbing in.
Whatever's going on with you,
I don't need it in my OR.
- Fine. I'll watch from the gallery.
- No, no, you won't.
You will take your energy as far away
from my OR as you can get.
Both of you.
Find a penny, pick it up,
all day long you'll have good luck.
Find a penny, pick it up...
We're going to give you
your anesthetic now.
I'm sorry but we have to start.
Find a penny, pick it up...
It's a beautiful afternoon
to save lives, people.
Let's have some fun.
The incision begins
along the left subcostal margin,
across the right rectus,
and extending well into the flank.
Dr. Bailey? It's Nikki Ratlin.
I'll be all right, Bailey. Go.
She, uh... yeah, she's bleeding out.
We need to get her to the OR now.
I don't want an operation.
Nikki, your boyfriend called.
He said he doesn't want you to die.
Kevin called?
Yes. Will you let us operate?
Nikki?
Oh, code blue. Come on.
Code Blue ICU, Code Blue ICU.
- OK. Charge to 200.
- Charge.
Clear.
You have the back row of sutures
in place.
Give me some... clear field.
- Pressure's dropping.
- Hang another unit.
I need the field clear.
Clear!
Charge 300!
- Charge.
- Clear.
That clip should've done it.
I don't know.
There's something I'm missing.
He's losing pressure, Dr. Burke.
I'm working as fast as I can.
We're losing him.
- I heard they're dying left and right.
- See? Told you there'd be seven.
Who? Who died?
Don't know.
I bet it was that spleen chick.
- She wouldn't let them operate.
- My money's on the chief's shunt.
I have twenty
says Burke's guy went down.
Dude's a walking time bomb.
Bet.
That makes five.
You lost her?
Yeah.
I heard there's a number six.
Do you know who else?
No.
I'm going to inform the family.
She made it through.
Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
You're welcome. You're welcome.
Superstition lies in the
space between what we can control...
and what we can't.
So, I wasn't one of the seven?
It's past midnight. There were only six.
- Then why are you crying?
- I'm not crying.
You are too.
Oh, damn it.
I cannot fall for a patient.
Oh.
OK.
Good luck with that.
Find a penny, pick it up,
and all day long you'll have good luck.
O'Malley, you are a sad excuse
for a man.
- Excuse me?
- I know you heard me.
You're like a whiny little girl.
Alex.
You know why he's not speaking to you?
Because he's not over you.
Man, you got laid, it went badly.
A man would move on. But you?
You mope around this place
like a dog that likes to get kicked.
You make me sick, and if it wouldn't get
me thrown out of the program,
I'd smash your pathetic little face
right into that locker.
No one wants to pass up a chance
for good luck.
But does saying it 33 times really help?
Is anyone really listening?
Hey.
I'll ask O'Malley to leave tonight.
No, no, don't.
- I thought you wanted him out.
- I do. But... not tonight.
- Scrub cap.
- Oh.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
And, if no one's listening,
why do we bother
doing those strange things at all?
Hi. I didn't call.
I should have called. I just...
Hi. This is George O'Malley calling.
You gave me your phone number.
I know I should have called sooner,
but I'm calling now.
And I just want to know... maybe
you want to go out with me sometime?
Because... I...
love to watch you set bones.
And I... oh, I...
rarely spend...
that much time in a women's restroom.
And I really like you.
So...
is that a yes?
We rely on superstitions
because we're smart enough to know
we don't have all the answers.
- Hey.
- I'm sorry to hear about your patient.
- Thank you, Addison.
And that life works in mysterious ways.
Here you go, babe.
Thank you.
Hmm. Ready?
Yeah. Here you go. Thank you.
Don't dis the juju...
from wherever it comes.
www.tvsubtitles.net