We all get at least
one good wish a year...
over the candles
on our birthday.
Some of us throw in more.
On eyelashes...
fountains...
lucky stars.
And every now and then...
one of those wishes comes true.
I don't wanna go to work.
It's warm in here.
It's a cocoon.
- No Cristina
with the mean face.
- No lives to save.
A quickie?
A quickie will
make me feel better.
You definitely need a quickie.
So what then?
Is it as good as we hoped?
Do we bask in the warm
glow of our happiness?
Or...
do we just notice we've
got a long list of other wishes
waiting to be wished?
- Happy birthday.
- What? Oh. Yeah. Thank you.
OK, we gotta move
fast, people, so focus.
O'Malley, the pit. Karev,
you're with me. We got a surgery.
Stevens, clinic budget is due.
Yang, Grey, wait for the
Chief at the trauma bay.
- What? Why?
- Both of us?
Yes, both of you. I don't know
what, I don't know why. Just go.
They're all silent rage-y.
- What do you got?
- Take a look.
So, what do we have?
- Caldwell, as in the prison?
- Yeah.
- You read up on our VIP?
- Yes.
Multiple stab wounds, badly beaten.
He'll have guards with him at all times.
Cuffs stay on,
leg irons stay on.
Watch your syringes, sharps and
pens. I don't want any accidents.
And he's here. You four
are my team. No interns.
Keep this as quiet as possible.
Get him in and out quickly.
Patch him up, get him on his way.
What's PDR?
Get him out of trauma
as fast as you can.
Those guards attract attention.
Sir, it's stamped
PDR. What is PDR?
Prisoner...
Death Row.
How's everybody
doing this morning?
- Mr. Dunn,
can you hear me?
- You have a lovely voice.
We need a trauma series.
I hate to be a bother, but
my legs really, really hurt.
- Was I stabbed in the leg?
- - We didn't find anything.
- Add T-spine, L-spine films.
- We're getting a CT,
- extra films are a waste.
- More shots can't hurt.
If I wasn't stabbed, why
does it feel like I was?
The less you talk
the more we can work.
- Derek.
- That's OK.
He'll warm up as we
get to know each other.
- I don't think so.
- You'll see. We're not that different.
People are alive when they meet
us, and then it all changes somehow.
Hi there.
What are you doing?
I'm saying hello.
Listen.
My best friend made
one simple request,
that I not get anywhere
near you, and I slipped.
It was fantastic.
You're fantastic.
But it's not gonna
happen again, ever.
OK.
Damn it!
Yep. I think you broke your hip.
Are you kidding me?!
Come on!
- Who are you talking to?
- Last month,
I tripped and I cracked a rib. In April, I
fell in the shower and I broke my arm.
January, broke two
fingers doing yoga. Yoga!
This is my sixth break in a
year. So I stare at the heavens
and without belief in a higher
power but a need to blame someone,
I yell "Come freaking on!"
Tell you what: how about we
call ortho, have them run tests.
More satisfying than
shouting at the heavens.
Thank you.
Ow.
Jackson Prescott,
you shot up again!
- No, I didn't.
- Then why do you look so big?
- You're short.
- I've always been short,
you grew.
While I check Jackson, why don't you
take Melinda through today's procedure.
Yeah, no problem. Come on.
Did you see he
looks more yellow?
OK, Dr. Kenley's going to
check his liver function test.
Before we start, let me explain.
Jackson's had 12
bowel resections.
Dr. Kenley calls me
any time Jackson's here.
Now, Melinda is a single mom.
She works like a maniac to make
sure that beautiful boy has coverage.
- Miranda...
- Don't even start.
This is a special family. We
do whatever we can to help.
- It's really not necessary...
- It is necessary.
We'll take good
care of your kid.
Thank you.
Now let's talk
about the surgery.
Are you gonna let me
have a lollipop this time?
- My stomach's
not bad right now.
- It's not?
So how come I'm about
to cut a piece out of it?
Give me one of the
lollipops, and if I keep it down
we don't have to
do the operation.
I'm not sure that's gonna...
I'm not...
- I'm...
- Dr. Kenley?
Jackson, hit the blue button.
Behind you. The blue button!
- Code blue, second floor.
- What...?
Code blue, second floor.
Oh, my God!
- What happened?
- He just fell over.
Sir...
I have some bad news.
It looks like Jordan Kenley
just had a massive coronary.
He was gone before
he hit the deck.
His wife's on the way.
She'll probably want to speak to you,
the wife. Hear something reassuring.
He'll be missed.
Honored colleague.
Decades of service.
Sir, you in there?
Sir?
I have to tell Alex. About us.
"Us" us? No. That's a bad idea.
- That is monumentally bad.
- It's not fair. You know about him.
Yeah. I don't like it. And
if I could off him I would,
but he's the moody, broody
one, whereas I am mature and...
Dead.
You're dead.
I'm alive, and he's alive,
I'm happy when I'm with him.
Don't you want me to be happy?
Yes, there isn't anything in
this universe that I want more.
Why can't I have you both?
That's what makes me happy.
He's gonna think
you're a whackjob.
He told me that he loves me.
That's a huge deal for him.
The least I can do is be honest.
Sorry about your doc.
Whatever.
Dr. Kenley was gonna sign this,
before he died and everything.
- Can you?
- What is it?
I want to get a wish
from the wish people.
- You have to have
a doctor sign it.
- No. I'm not signing that.
Don't look at her, she's
not gonna sign it either.
Come on. Look, if you sign,
you can help me pick my wish.
These are the ones kids have
already done, like go on a circus trapeze,
or be in the rodeo. Put stars by
the ones you think would be cool,
X's by the ones
you think are lame.
No way Kenley
was gonna sign that.
It's for kids with life-threatening
diseases. You're not dying, just sick.
Dude...
The rodeo smells like horse
crap. You're not missing anything.
I think we've got a parathyroid
tumor for you to remove.
- Really.
- Did I just hear tumor removal?
My resident abandoned
me. Do you need any help?
- Sure.
- No!
Or... Fine, but you'll watch.
You're not touching
anything. Get it? No touching.
Uh, she's up in ultrasound.
Call and see if they took her yet.
- You slept with her?
- Absolutely not!
Only once.
She came to my hotel room, took
off all her clothes and said teach me.
I had no control. She violated
me with her nakedness.
Derek's gonna kill me.
- Shouldn't have
been alone with her.
- Never gonna happen again,
- mind-blowingly
fantastic as it was.
- Hey, you are a professional.
Hi! Oh, hold on.
Hold tight.
Just a bit of lint.
Ultrasound's backed up,
but they'll have
results in half an hour.
All right. Well, tell Grey.
And let George... Dr. George...
Dr. O'Malley know when... Let
him know when you know, OK?
You were saying something
about professionalism.
Did you see that? That
was not in my head, right?
These interns
are out of control.
- Stalkers.
- Sexed-up stalkers.
Dr. Bailey? Arizona Robbins.
- I'm taking over
Dr. Kenley's patients.
- You're the peds surgeon?
You're assisting
with Jackson Prescott.
All due respect to Dr. Kenley,
he was a wonderful physician.
I'm surprised he
followed this treatment
when it wasn't,
you know, working.
I'm not criticizing you.
You didn't make the call.
But I supported the call. We
hadn't turned the corner yet,
but Kenley was sure that if we
kept doing what we were doing...
- Jack's case is quite severe...
- Jackson.
- Excuse me?
- Jackson is his name.
And if you're suggesting we were
torturing him with useless procedures...
A lot of senior peds surgeons
believe that strictureplasty works,
and sometimes they're
right. So we'll go with it today,
but we should start
exploring other options.
I gotta run. Dr. Kenley had a
big case load. See you in the OR.
He's still in a lot of
pain, I'm not sure why.
It'll help if we get
him off this backboard.
Shouldn't we wait for X-rays?
Decreased sensation in his lower extremity.
According to him. He
could tell you anything.
We pushed morphine. He
shouldn't be in this much pain.
Maybe we could
push a teeny bit more?
Not here to feed
your drug habit.
I've been behind
bars for 11 years.
The drug trade in solitary
isn't what one would hope.
- Let's just wait for the films.
- This is a waste of time.
I hate to agree with Yang,
but I agree with Yang.
Dr. Grey?
Dr. Shepherd?
What's that?
Whatever they stabbed
him with is in there.
- In his back?
- Spine.
Does that mean I'm paralyzed?
My execution date is in a week.
I've exhausted all my
appeals. But if I'm paralyzed,
my lawyer might be able to make
a case for staying my execution.
Do you think you
could let me be a gimp?
No.
Is the Chief in there?
I need to see him.
So do I. We're going
to be disappointed.
What exactly is
he doing in there?
Ever since he heard
about Jordan Kenley,
he's been in there and
he wants to be alone.
I need to see...!
It's impinging on the spinal cord.
Can't tell if it's going through or not.
We'll get a better picture
once we get the CTs back.
I ordered an MRI. The CT may
not give us a clear view of the cord.
We'll look at all the images.
Everything by the book. I don't
want some lawyer keeping him alive
on the basis we did not
give him the standard of care.
- You're pro-death penalty?
- Pro-punishment.
Good people do bad
things. People screw up.
He's still a person. We don't
know what crime he committed.
Maybe he killed a cop. Feel
all warm for the cop killer.
We don't know what
he did. We can't judge.
No, but a jury can. Death row.
We're wasting time
debating this. Do a repeat crit,
let me know if he needs blood.
- I thought they were friends.
- They were.
- And now?
- You and I are in
for a very long day.
The annoying twins
got a mass murderer.
Think one will pay
the guy to off the other?
No. If they're gonna get
violent, they'll do it themselves.
- It's weird, right? Them fighting?
- Um...
There's something that I need to talk
to you about, it's gonna sound weird.
And I want you to know
I know it sounds weird,
- so just don't freak out.
- Are you breaking up with me?
- No, not at all.
- Though that's not a bad idea.
I see Denny. A lot, lately.
Around here, and at the house.
Are you OK? 'Cause that
sounds kind of whacked.
What did I tell you?
You never saw your
grandmother after she died?
Yeah, she showed up in a dream
and told me not to play with the parts.
Well, it's kind of like that.
- Excuse me?
- All right. Whatever.
That's it?
I don't know.
Tell him I said hi.
Kind of like his grandmother
telling him not to...
OK, so I panicked!
Mr. Dunn, are you
feeling any better?
Everybody's been so attentive.
I'm still in a lot of pain.
We're gonna get that thing out
of your back as soon as we can.
You're on the cord.
She's kind of a bitch.
Not to use coarse
language, but she is.
- Well, she's my friend.
- Really?
We had a fight.
Mr. Dunn, it will really
help us when we take it out
if we know what that
thing in your back is.
I'm pretty sure it
was a toothbrush.
Somebody snapped the
head off and melted it down
till it was less toothbrush
and more knife.
How did it end up in your spine?
Got in a fight with a friend.
Hey, lady!
- Can you help me?
- Sure.
- You feeling OK?
- Yeah.
You see, I'm gonna get a
wish from the wish people,
but I'm having trouble
deciding which wish to pick.
I'm getting people's opinions.
Put stars by the ones you like
and X's by the ones you think are
lame. Then you have to sign something.
OK. How about a trip to
China? That sounds cool.
- I get airsick.
- Hmm.
- How about the rodeo?
- Some guy said
it smells like poo.
What the hell are you doing?
Stars and X's.
We're picking wishes.
He's not even eligible.
You're a little scammer.
- You're fake dying?
- I want to go to the rodeo!
You just told me
it smells like poo!
Nice try.
Come on, let's get you
prepped for surgery.
You told him. He
knows. Stop worrying.
You've got a tumor on a
little gland in your neck.
Come on!
She does that. Margaret,
the tumor is benign
and it's not hard to
remove. Dr. Harris?
A parathyroid tumor tells your body
to leech calcium out of your bones.
That's why you've had fractures.
Once the tumor's out,
you'll be back to normal.
Come on!
- This is good news.
- I've been living
like an old lady.
I don't take the stairs, I
gave up running, skiing.
I sit and knit and hope the
knitting doesn't break a finger.
- All because of a tumor?
- Tumor that's benign,
easy to remove.
Come on!
There was a guy.
I fell in love with the
most amazing guy.
He was sweet, kind,
best sex of my life
and he had to move to Denver.
And he wanted me
to move with him.
And I didn't because Denver is icy.
Too many ways for me to slip and fall.
So I lose my guy and I break all these
bones from a bone-sucking tumor?!
Are you kidding me?!
Sorry. From the lab, Dr. Sloan.
Did you need something else?
- This is torture.
- Focus.
OK. Karev, can you
pull the retractor more?
- Like that?
- Yeah. Great.
Damn. Look at this. It's a mess.
He'll have maybe 10 centimeters
of bowel when we're done.
Can't we try a Bianchi procedure,
see if we can save more of it?
Bowel's dead and the liver's
cirrhotic. No saving anything.
But...
He should have been on a transplant list a
year ago. It's a miracle he's still alive.
What are...
What are you doing?
I'm not seeing
anyone today, Bailey.
I know that, but
this is important.
Every conversation
I have is important.
Kenley has been replaced with an
infant on roller skates named Arizona,
who didn't have sense
enough to change her name,
which shows poor judgment,
as does her diagnosis of a patient
that I've been working
with for three years.
She's changing Kenley's
treatment protocol
based on half an hour of
experience with the child.
We just took out
most of his bowel,
and instead of trying to
salvage what he has left,
she wants to throw up her
hands and pray for a transplant.
The child hasn't eaten
solid food in months.
He hasn't grown in
years. His liver is shot.
It is a serious case!
Now we need someone
who can handle it.
Dr. Bailey...
you thought Shepherd
was just a haircut.
You didn't like Hahn,
and you think
Dr. Sloan is a hussy.
Can you name any attending
that you thought was good?
I've always been
a fan of your work.
Arizona Robbins was
top of her class, like you.
And she was chief
resident, like you.
And she's the best anyone's
seen in a long time, just like you.
She is who we have, we don't
have anyone else. Deal with it.
What's that for?
You're short of a friend
today. So I thought I'd fill in.
Colleagues aren't
friends, they're competitors.
Oh. So does that mean you're
not gonna drink this coffee?
No. I'll drink the coffee.
MRI. He's got brain contusions
on top of everything else.
Mr. Dunn is still in a
huge amount of pain.
Can I give him more morphine
or will that cause problems?
Mr. Dunn has had
enough morphine.
He's got a foreign
body in his spine.
- It's inhumane.
- Killing people is inhumane.
Denying them painkillers
is a judgment call.
Derek, what's wrong with you?
I watch people die all the time.
I go to families and tell them their
world's been ripped apart all the time.
I fight to make sure I don't
have to deliver that message
and I lose that
fight all the time.
Then some guy like Dunn comes
along and simply throws it away. Life.
Then he's got the nerve to tell me he
and I are two sides of the same coin?
You're not.
He doesn't need morphine.
But she's exquisite.
And it's not just the sex. We
talked for hours, and laughed.
It's just the sex.
You're gonna tell me you're
not thinking about Sadie?
Nope. No.
I cannot have another stupid
romantic disaster in this hospital.
- It's embarrassing.
- You do have quite
a track record.
You know what? We need to
find something else to think about.
Worth a try.
Nope, not working.
Nope.
OK. Ooh, OK!
We're like addicts, right?
We need a 12-step program.
I'm not going to a meeting
to discuss my obsession
with my friend's
girlfriend's half sister.
It'll just be us. We'll be
each other's sponsors.
- Make sure we stay
on the program.
- What are the steps?
Don't get naked with an intern.
It's more of a one-step program.
- Maybe I should
write this down.
- Yeah.
Hey, Cristina, can you mention
that it's Izzie's birthday today?
Someone should do
something about it.
I myself am planning a
party with balloons, streamers,
- and a bouncy house.
- You know what?
- Alex should do something.
- I know. I got it under control.
Bouncy house?
Is he here?
Who?
Your friend.
No. He's not here.
If he shows up, tell him I'll share
my girl, but not my sandwich.
This thing cost four bucks.
Oh, I'm done here.
Dude from MRI was all
freaked out about death row guy.
Couldn't put his cuffs in the
machine, They had to Velcro him.
Tech thought he was gonna
tear it off and storm the booth
- like the Hulk or something.
- What did he do?
He laid there and had that MRI.
No. What did he do
to get on death row,
mow down people
with a machine gun?
Probably found his wife with
a hooker and a handyman.
They don't give the death
penalty for crimes of passion.
- People understand that.
- All crimes are crimes
of passion.
People don't do stuff like that
because they forget it's illegal.
When you kill her, is it
gonna be a crime of passion?
- That still hasn't blown over?
- It's not a big deal.
We had a fight.
She took it too far.
- You want to know what I think?
- Not really.
Hey.
I need to scream or kill someone.
I'm leaning towards killing.
Working.
I'm feeling much better, thanks.
Thank you for whatever
it was you gave me.
Is there family or someone who
should know you're having surgery?
We can't call your family. I
think what she's trying to ask is,
- what did you do
to get death row?
- You don't have to answer that.
- That was not
what I was asking.
- I don't mind.
It's an obvious question.
One Monday, I slit
this woman's throat.
I'd been thinking about it
for a while, dreaming about it.
And one Monday, I just...
I had to do it.
I just... really wanted to
draw a knife across her neck.
And I thought it
would be terrifying
or sad or something,
but it wasn't, it was just...
kind of fun.
So I did two more on Tuesday
and another two on Wednesday.
I was gonna go for three on
Thursday, I liked the alliteration,
but I got caught so I didn't.
Can I get some Jell-O?
Or is that bad, before surgery?
- Read the sign!
- I was told to ignore the sign.
- Well, don't!
- Bailey told me.
I'm gonna kill that woman.
Look, I didn't know
Kenley all that well,
but it's gotta be tough.
Losing a co-worker you've
worked with for a long time.
Jordan Kenley
was a son of a bitch.
Great with kids, good with a
scalpel. Horrible to his colleagues.
Competitive, insecure, aggressive.
I won't miss him for a minute.
So... is this about
your mortality?
I'm not worried about me
dying or Jordan Kenley dying.
I'm worried about
my hospital dying.
I made some calls
to replace Kenley.
No one wants to come here.
I can't keep a cardiac surgeon on staff.
Burke quit, Hahn quit, Dixon's autistic.
My OR roof collapsed,
the whole place flooded.
The interns are literally
chopping each other into pieces.
No wonder we're
number 12. Twelve!
I've failed at the one thing
I spent my whole life doing.
Failed!
So I'm going to stay
right here on this table
until I find a way to walk
the halls without cringing.
Aren't you supposed to give me
that "get back on the horse" lecture?
I have got to stitch a serial
killer back together today.
I don't have a
rousing lecture in me.
We're gonna need a strategy. Their
hot little eyes tracking our every move.
OK. No casual glances
over the shoulder.
No "this is interesting,
can everybody see?"
Soon as Margaret's tumor's out,
we'll have them take it to
pathology to get it analyzed.
- Go team.
- Break.
- They still not speaking?
- Doesn't look like it.
- Wow. Two hours in an ice cave.
- Working on Seattle's man of
the year.
At least we got each other.
We can pretend not to notice,
talk about the Seahawks.
Or we could take off, go grab a
beer, let them pull out the shiv.
Onward and upward.
I don't think I was clear
earlier. It is not like a dream.
I see Denny when I'm
awake. We hang out.
This is because I said I
loved you. You're freaked out.
- I'm not.
- You're a little freaked out.
Um, we still do stuff together.
Sex stuff. I see him,
and we have sex.
There's nothing wrong
with a good fantasy.
I'd rather you fantasize
about me, or chicks.
- But whatever.
- You really don't care?
You're trying to
work something out.
People die, and then the
other people, you know...
get messed up about it.
- Yeah, but...
- Iz.
I've been competing with
that tool for a long time,
but I'd say he's kinda
got the handicap now.
I mean, is he here?
Can he see me do this?
Yeah, dude, I can see you!
And this?
Is he still here?
- I think you should go.
- Yeah, I got things to do.
Do you see him now?
No. No, he's gone. Don't stop.
- Don't stop!
- What about now?
No, don't stop!
Wow. Sharp.
No wonder he was
complaining so much.
He wasn't complaining after
he got 10 extra of morphine.
He got an extra 10 of morphine?
It made him much
more comfortable.
Doesn't bother you this guy probably
hacked a family with a machete?
A knife. And women, not a family.
Five women. It's what he likes.
You shouldn't be on
this case, either of you.
What's he gonna do, jump off the
table and get us? You're holding the knife.
We'll be doing a nephrectomy. Either
of you ever mobilized the renal hilum?
Never done one,
but I'd love to try.
I've practiced on
cadavers hundreds of times.
It wouldn't be my first try.
To some of us surgery comes
naturally. Others have to practice.
You see the Seahawks
game last week?
- You know,
I am the jealous type.
- I know. I'm sorry.
I can't choose. Please
don't make me choose.
Are you gonna make me?
I can't do anything that
would make you unhappy.
You know that.
I love you.
That's what you
tell all the guys.
You know today is my birthday?
I do know that.
You gonna get me a present?
I think I just did.
- Why is she shaking her head?
- Jackson's post-op LFTs.
This kid needs to be put
on the transplant list today.
- Just the intestine...?
- Liver too.
We should get another opinion.
Norman McCale at Hopkins.
Head of Pediatric Surgery.
Tell him Arizona sent you. When he
tells you Jackson needs a transplant,
which he'll do two minutes
into the call, put him on the list.
- There's no need to snap at me.
- There is, actually.
You've been
second-guessing me. I get it.
You liked Dr. Kenley. And
I'm a stranger with a ponytail.
But I'm not the
problem, the patient is.
So stop thinking about me
and start focusing on him.
Jackson needs a transplant. If we keep
wasting time, he's not going to make it.
You OK? Want to get
a drink or something?
Oh, now we're on again,
'cause the mood suits you?
I'm the sad little
girl with no friend?
I tripped your savior
complex into action?
Usually, I can deal with the
hot and cold thing, but not today.
Just leave me the hell alone.
Is that him?
- You ever find out what he did?
- It doesn't matter what he did.
He did something really
bad, and he's gonna pay for it.
- You want to get a drink?
- I'm not in the mood.
You know, you and I
had a fight like this once.
- What?
- Amsterdam.
We used to be as close as you and
Cristina, then Amsterdam happened.
You shut me down.
We never got past it.
We still hung out,
but not like before.
We'd go dancing. Go someplace
loud, where we don't have to talk.
That's OK. I'm a
rolling stone, I bounce.
But you're about to do the same thing
to Cristina, and that girl mates for life.
If you don't make it right,
she'll never talk to you again.
I apologized. To Cristina.
Like you meant it?
Like you could imagine
she had a point?
I miss you.
As my friend, I miss you.
Now transplants aren't
easy, that's the bad news.
But the good news is,
you've got a
crackerjack new doctor.
I spoke to one of the most
respected kid surgeons in the country,
and he thinks she's
the best there is.
So she's gonna take good
care of you. We all are.
Why don't we go out and sign
some of the transplant consent forms?
♪ And you ♪
♪ Who love to love ♪
♪ And believed ♪
♪ We can never give enough ♪
♪ And you ♪
♪ Who hoped that underneath ♪
♪ We all felt the same ♪
♪ That was until ♪
Stars and X's.
♪ The day before the day ♪
Looking good. The surgery
couldn't have been smoother.
- When could I get out of here?
- Soon.
- You're young,
you'll heal fast.
- Eager to get home?
I'm going to Denver.
- We did good work today.
- If we stay strong...
- And don't get drunk...
- Keep staring at Joe,
we'll be fine.
Hi! Get you anything?
- OK, you're weirding me out.
- You only live once.
You can't waste it.
No! No, Mark. No!
Look at Joe. Look at me.
Look at me. No!
- Sorry, kid. I'm going to Denver.
- No! Mark, come back here!
No, Mark, no!
Damn it. Damn
it, damn it, damn it!
- You need another drink?
- Yes!
She's all right.
Arizona Robbins.
Mm-hmm.
I don't know if the patient's
going to make it, though.
We don't wish
for the easy stuff.
We wish for big things.
Things that are ambitious...
out of reach.
Let's take a look.
He's got 10...
Two guys shot my
dad for his watch.
My mom saved up for it.
Two guys came into his store and
shot him 'cause he wouldn't give it up.
That's how my dad died.
We are supposed to
treat everybody the same.
But they're not all the same.
I'm sorry. It's a bad
day all around, I guess.
I wish I could make things
better with you and Cristina.
I wish you could, too.
I try to think what she would
do, in a situation like this.
I don't know.
Well, she would turn
the music up pretty loud
and she would dance it out with me,
but I don't think you want to go there.
Well...
let's see what we got here.
Whoo! Yeah! Look out!
Hey! Come on, get up!
Get your ass over here.
I'm not doing this by myself.
♪ No place of their own ♪
♪ There's no place ♪
♪ Like home Like
home, like home ♪
♪ Got lucky ♪
♪ Found my way
back here somehow ♪
There you go.
♪ We have 'em right here ♪
♪ A slight variation
From here to here... ♪
We wish because we need help...
and we're scared...
and we know we may
be asking too much.
Oh, my God! You made it.
Well, the cake tastes kind of
funny, but the frosting's pretty good.
It's beautiful.
It's a nice gesture,
him baking for you.
Make a wish.
What if I don't have
anything to wish for?
What if I have everything
I could ever want?
We still wish, though.
Then wish that nothing changes.
Because... sometimes...
they come true.
♪ It felt just like home ♪