Surgeons aren't known
for being warm and cuddly.
They're arrogant, impatient,
- mean, as often as not.
-  Go with straight-up chemo
and immunotherapy. Survival rates
are low, but there's been a lot of success
with mestastasectomies. We
could probably cut this thing out.
You'd think they wouldn't have
friends. Who could stand them?
- What are you hiding?
- Nothing. It's just
work stuff.
- What is that? A cool surgery?
- No, it's nothing. It's nothing.
Whatever it is, they'll pick me. I flew
solo. You're still on training wheels.
- Sure you still
don't wanna tell him?
- Yes, I'm sure.
OK. Look, I researched a ton
of information. Read all of this
- before you see
the oncologist.
- When?
I called Dr. Golding. He
gave me a referral to Swender.
- I'm gonna try
and get you in today.
- Shh!
What are you doing
here? I told you I was fine.
- You are so not fine.
- I'd be fine if
I knew Derek was fine.
You still haven't heard
from him? No word?
Izzie, don't you think you
should call in sick today?
- What? Why?
- Because this is
a lot of reading,
- and you're sick.
- You coming? Big surgery today.
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Izzie, just...
But surgeons are
like a bad cold:
Nasty, but persistent.
Uh, Chief, I need
to ask you about...
Sloan, have you
heard from Derek?
No.
I'm sorry. You were
saying? Oh, Meredith.
No, I don't know how he is. I've
heard nothing. Nothing today, nothing
yesterday, nothing the day before.
And no, I will not go back out there.
Hey, who moved my
surgery? Chief? Chief?
Don't. Just don't. He's a wreck.
He's disintegrating
before our eyes.
- That's why men
die earlier than women.
- Mm. The board's a mess.
He can't lose Shepherd. I'd
go talk some sense into him,
- but I've got
too much on my plate.
- Tried calling?
About 100 times.
Mm.
No. Oh, you...
You want me to go to the
woods? No. I don't do woods.
The woods are dirty and
there are many, many bugs.
What am I gonna
say? I barely know him.
You don't have to know him. You're
surgeons, been through the same war.
Just remind him we've all
been there, we all came back.
You're kind of a
bully, you know that?
I wouldn't do it if it
didn't work so well.
This is one of the biggest surgeries
you may get near so pay attention.
The patient is a 38-year-old male
hit by a drunk driver 12 years ago.
- He suffered
severe facial trauma.
- No nose, no lips.
That's why we dubbed him Blowhole.
He's had nine reconstructive surgeries,
none of which have brought
back full form or function.
This surgery has only
been done four times.
All candidates have to undergo
extensive psychological testing
to determine whether they
can handle the process.
Psychological components aside, this
has a chance of rejection or infection.
He'll be on life-long anti-rejection
drugs which put him at risk
for lymphoma, diabetes,
hypertension, renal failure.
- I hear they call
the dude Blowhole.
- What did you just say?
Nothing. I just heard
he had a nickname.
Don't talk anymore. Ever.
- Holy crap! Blowhole is right.
- What'd I tell you?
Surgeons:
nasty, aggressive, unstoppable.
Just the kind of people you want on
your side when you're really screwed.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is Mr. David Young.
Today he'll be receiving
a face transplant.
Dr. Hunt and his team'll be
recovering the donor graft.
We're replacing 70
percent of Mr. Young's face.
- You can see
the deficit here.
- Or here.
The donor recovery will include
his nose, left eye, lips, left zygoma.
Why will allotransplantation work
better than traditional techniques?
Aesthetic outcome allows re-enervation
of nerves, giving a better result.
Very good, Dr. Grey.
We'll position the flap
over Mr. Young's face.
- How do we know we're clear?
- The graft turns pink.
Excellent.
- Dave, any questions for us?
- Has anyone seen the donor?
Yes, he's a match with your
age, skin tone and blood type.
- What does he look like?
- I think you'll be satisfied.
Who am I kidding?
It's a face, right?
If I end up anything above
a point and stare freak,
I'm gonna call it a success.
Karev, you're with me and the donor.
Usually we take them at the same time,
but donor's life
support is fading. Move.
- Thank you, sir.
- Stevens, Grey.
- Yes.
- No, the other Grey.
- Really? Great.
- Great.
You did an awesome job in there.
- Call me after
the pre-op labs come in.
- Dr. Sloan, only one resident?
Wait for Bailey. There's
enough of a crowd.
- What the hell?
- Izzie, I don't think
you have time
- to scrub in.
- Don't worry. I can handle it.
- Awesome job.
- She probably
quizzed him in bed.
- She gets to work
on Blowhole...
- Shut your mouths!
Finish the chart. I'll be back.
O'Malley, Grey? I need
you on pre-ops and post-ops.
There's the biggest surgery
in the world happening.
Yes. Half our attendings are involved,
which is why we need strong residents
on pre-ops and post-ops.
Yang, you're with me.
- Moving to the big leagues.
- What?
- She gets a solo?
- Today?
Nice old lady with a
hernia, you're gonna fix it.
Congratulations. I know I
should seem more enthusiastic,
- but I'm not
that big a person.
- Don't worry about it.
Is it wrong to have
hatred in your heart?
Good morning, Miss
Sulley. I'm Dr. Cristina Yang.
- I'll perform
your hernia repair.
- Lovely to meet you.
- Have any questions
before we start?
- Yes. Hand me my purse.
My friends gave me
a bunch of questions,
and I can't remember
any of them.
They're such worrywarts. They're
all off on a European tour without me.
They threatened not to go when
this became a problem. I told 'em no.
No. We have been saving
up for this for two years.
I was able to get my deposit
back with a doctor's note.
Cristina Yang. Yes?
No. No, it has to be today.
It's stage four. She has to
see Dr. Swender, not a partner.
Um, I'm sorry, ma'am.
I will get to your questions
when I come to examine you. OK?
Referral is Golding? Golding.
A little early in the day
for that, don't you think?
- You sound like my mother.
- I met your mother. I liked her.
- Who sent you, Richard?
- Uh, Bailey.
Of course.
I'm sorry about your patient.
I know how hard it can be.
I had a patient a
couple of years ago...
Young guy, 50 maybe.
Simple knee replacement.
He was post-op, he was fine.
I told his wife she could get him lunch.
A simple knee replacement. Nothing.
He'd been getting short of
breath. I put him on blood thinners
for a post-surgical PE.
And... it wasn't until he was vomiting
up dark blood, looking me in the eye,
telling me that he was
dying that I figured it out.
That I was wrong. It wasn't a
PE. He was bleeding internally.
It wouldn't have been
fatal, but the blood thinners...
God, I will never forget
the look on his wife's face
when she came back with
that sandwich in her hand,
asking me why her husband
wasn't in his room anymore.
How do you live with it?
Killing him.
Taking him from his wife.
How do you live with it?
- We call it malpractice...
- I know. I'm asking
when you get up,
how do you look at
yourself in the mirror?
Look, I'm not... I'm...
I'm asking.
Can I get one of those?
Yeah.
It's the not knowing that
does it. Not knowing if he's OK,
not knowing if he's coming back.
Maybe I've just been dumped.
It's not knowing if I'm single that
makes me wanna throw up all day.
- You are not listening
to me, are you?
- Uh, sorry.
No, no, that's OK. I get it. You've
got solo surgery and GI Joe.
It's a charmed life. You
don't have time for me.
I have not had GI Joe.
We've kissed a couple times.
It's like friends with
benefits... without the benefits.
- Still no sex.
- Mm-mmm. Not a charmed life.
Lab results from
the splenectomy.
- Do we ask?
- No.
'Cause he might tell us.
Can you imagine? This
guy's got a family, right?
Wife, kids? One day they'll see
his face on somebody else's body.
- It's kind of creepy, right?
- Mr. Young won't look exactly
like the donor. The underlying
facial structure of two people can be
- very different.
- A person's identity
is more than
skin and bone. His
expression, style, eyes.
The donor's family wouldn't
recognize this face on anyone else.
- Transplant surgeons are antsy.
- They're always antsy.
They can't relax until they
got live tissue in their coolers.
I am making the
final dissection.
Karev, hold right of the temple
and gently lift.
Don't tear the flesh.
Awesome.
Tenderness around the incision
is normal. No signs of infection.
Could you redress that wound?
Megan, will you
please go to 20...
Um, go to room 2214
and just take out the drain.
When you're ready.
It seems personal,
we wouldn't ask if we
didn't need to know,
but have you passed gas yet?
Sorry.
We can't release you
until that happens. The gas.
I'm sorry. I'm trying to listen, but
are they supposed to look like that?
- Like what?
- The bleeding
and the shiner.
And that one looks
like she's suicidal.
They're supposed to be doctors?
We're gonna reserve
judgment on that.
- Freak show.
- What the heck
do we do with them?
- Can we shove them in a locker?
- We should talk to them.
No. We're professionals.
That's clearly personal.
Besides, we'll waste time,
never see the solo surgery
- or the face transplant.
- Oh, that's a good point.
- I guess we should
ignore it then.
- Yeah, just ignore it.
- It's the professional
thing to do.
- Professionally...
It's important that you
take all the medications...
Risk of rejection and infection. I
know. You drilled it into my head
- a thousand times.
- Is your family here yet?
I ask because someone needs
to take care of you afterwards.
I don't have family, but my
friends are coming after the surgery.
I'm excited to meet them
and show them my new face.
We met in an online chat
room for orchid lovers.
We've never actually
"met" met, so...
Dave, after the surgery, this
device helps prevent lung problems
by exercising the muscles
you use to breathe.
- I'd like you
to practice on it now.
- Sit up straight.
Take three easy breaths
and then blow into that.
- Hole.
- That's it!
Both of you, in the hall, now!
You really think that was OK?
- That was doctorly?!
- Find something else to do.
- What the hell's
going on with you?
- They made inappropriate jokes
at the expense of the
patient. Right in front of him.
I have been trying to teach them,
and they were cruel and inappropriate.
OK, they were inappropriate. You
know what else is inappropriate?
This. You.
This case is my baby. I've
spent three years planning for it,
and you are not
about to piss all over it.
- You're off the case.
- No. He needs me
in there with him.
You can't leave
him alone with them.
You wanna be
there for his feelings,
you can be there before
and after the surgery,
but you're not coming in my
OR. Whatever's going on with you,
get it under control.
- I found them.
- What? Your questions
about the surgery?
One of my friends,
Phil Ferguson,
he's a retired surgeon. He
told me to ask you these.
I can't seem to find my glasses.
My friends should be here.
I put my glasses down
somewhere, they find them...
Will you finally be able to pick up your
grandkids? A question from a doctor?
No. No, my other friends
helped me with questions.
I added a few on my own.
Like, "Will it hurt?"
Will it... hurt?
- You'll be anesthetized.
- Yes, I know that.
- I mean after. Will it hurt?
- You should expect
normal post-op pain.
Yes? Yes.
No, that is
fantastic. I'll take it.
Thank you so much. I'll get
in touch with her right away.
2:30. Anytime is fine.
So I've covered
22, 13, 19 and 33.
Yeah, OK. I've
got 2011 and 2007.
Mer, there is something
wrong with Izzie.
- What do you mean?
- I don't know.
I know that there
is something wrong.
We're drowning in intern drama.
We don't need
resident drama too.
If it's a problem, she'll tell
us. Until then, just ignore it.
I repeat, ignore it.
- What in God's name
is going on?
- A personal issue.
We are just trying to
give them their privacy.
Gee, you think for a second I wanted
to get involved with your intern drama?
- We were not this bad.
- Getting married in Vegas.
Shacking up with attendings. Cutting
LVAD wires. You don't have to like it,
- but you have to manage it.
- We've got it under control.
Wait! I love you, Megan!
Sir, are you OK?
Oh, God, I'm so sorry.
Whatever it is the two of you
have going on, it stops now.
- I didn't mean to...
- Don't talk while
she's talking.
You are scaring the patients. You're
making this hospital look ridiculous.
- You're making us
look incompetent.
- Not a good idea.
Just stay away from each other. So
much as a tear or a glance at each other,
- and it's over. No!
- I don't understand.
- Don't talk while I'm talking.
- That's what I was
trying to tell...
Now just get out! Go!
Not together.
That felt good.
- You paged me, Dr. Bailey?
- Oh! Yes.
Um, finished your part
of the face transplant?
I cleared my schedule to watch
Sloan and Yang do surgery.
Whatever it is you need, I
hope it's not too time-consuming.
That all depends on how
fast you can drive and talk.
- I'm sorry?
- I need you to drive out
to the woods
and talk Derek Shepherd
into coming back here.
And I believe you also might run
into Callie Torres. With a flat tire.
Or a broken heel. Or an
axe-wielding serial killer.
- You're serious?
- I sent Torres
after Shepherd,
and she's fallen off the grid.
Her phone goes to voicemail.
I'm normally not a panicky person,
but I'm a fan of daytime television.
My crazy scenarios...
Never mind.
I need you to go get Torres and
Shepherd and bring them back here
before the chief
notices you're gone.
Shepherd's been gone all week...
Hunt! You survived a
war, you can do this.
I know I can do this.
I'm saying I don't want to.
People don't really say
"no" to you, do they?
Not when I say please.
I'm saying please!
OR is set,
transport's on its way.
- You ready?
- I've been ready
for 12 years.
You said you had friends
coming to take care of you?
- Yeah, after my surgery.
- They're coming now.
Surprise!
Hi. It's me, Sheena.
You can probably tell from
my Vanda roeblingiana.
I hope you're not mad
that we came early.
We thought we should be here
through it all. Make sure you knew...
Get out. Get them out. They're
strangers. I don't want them in here.
We're hardly strangers, Dave.
We chat every night,
all night, for years.
- We flew in...
- Get out! We've never met.
You don't know me,
anything about me. Get out!
Get them out! Get out. Get out!
Get out!
Hey. Did you get my
page? I got the appointment.
It's in, like, 15 minutes.
How amazing am I?
Usually takes weeks to get
in. You look at the research?
- Seriously,
can I just eat?
- No.
- I'm sorry. You don't have time.
- Time for what?
There's a... an enema.
- Uh, Izzie's enema.
- Yes.
I was supposed to get an enema
today, but I decided it can wait.
- Talk about something else?
- We need to talk about it.
You've been complaining
about being really backed up.
- I got you an appointment.
- If you need an enema,
- you shouldn't have fries.
- You booked her for an enema?
You can't just say that you're
all backed up and just sit there.
If you make the
decision to get an enema,
- you should get an enema.
- Maybe you're the one
that's backed up.
Solo surgery
panic? Tell you what.
I'll scrub in. If you can't
handle it, I'll take over.
I don't... OK. You know...
I'm just saying... enemas
can be a serious business.
OK. Izzie, enema
is code for what?
- My enema, my business.
- Uh, fifteen minutes!
This is a really strange day.
I was a second-year
resident. MVC rolls in.
Parents in the front seat. Three kids in
the back. Kids were OK. Mom and dad
a little banged up. Nothing terrible,
talking and laughing in the ER.
Turns out both parents
had massive internal injuries.
I operated on them
both that night. Hours.
Lost them both.
If I'd moved faster,
rushed them to CT,
known how bad off
they were sooner,
but... I didn't. The
oldest kid was nine.
When I came out to
tell them about their dad,
he was consoling the three- and
five-year-old about their mother.
I'll never get that image out of
my head. This nine-year-old boy
trying to hold these two little
ones, his arms just not big enough.
I don't know how I
came back the next day.
I think part of me never did.
I'm surprised you
didn't talk about Iraq.
I don't talk about Iraq.
What my point was, I kept...
You know, I... I went back.
I showed up. I...
I showed up for work, you know?
You go dead inside...
You go dead inside
because if you felt it,
if you let yourself feel that,
no way you're going back.
No way.
- You blew it off?
- Cristina, please.
I called every favor I had in
this hospital and then some.
Swender's the best surgical
oncologist. Why didn't you go?
- Why do you care so much?
- Why don't you?
I'm working really hard on
this. The least you could do...
They were calling the guy
Blowhole. Not just the interns, Alex.
What are they gonna call
me when I'm the patient?
- Swiss Cheese for Brains?
- No, that's awkward and long.
- Blowhole's pithy.
- I'm not gonna be
a piece of meat
while you all fight over
who gets to slice me up
- and then laugh
while you do it.
- OK, this right here,
this, um, is an emotional
thing you're having,
which is why you should
tell Meredith, or George...
I'm not telling
anybody, so just drop it!
No! You're not
dumping this on me.
You're not dying in my arms.
So either you
tell them or I will.
I don't even know
if I want treatment.
I know too much. I know
how violent surgery can be.
They're gonna cut into my
brain, slice open my abdomen
and pull my organs
out. And for what?
Surgery fails all the time. Derek
Shepherd is in the freaking woods
because we fail all the time!
Even if they do everything, I have
a five percent chance of survival.
Five percent.
Why would I put myself through
hell, run poison through my veins,
irradiate my brain if it's
not gonna work anyway?
Why did you tell me then?
If you don't want my help and
you're not gonna do anything about it,
why did you tell me?
Keep your mouth shut.
Forget I told you anything.
Izzie!
You need to call
them back, Dave.
You're my surgeon,
right? You're not my shrink.
- So why don't you
just do your job?
- I can't do my job anymore.
It took us three years to find the
right candidate, and part of you being
the right candidate is having
a support system post-op.
You cannot do this alone. The
ethics board will not allow me
to let you do it alone.
You need your friends.
You see that orchid?
It's ugly. To anyone who doesn't
know orchids, it's dark and droopy
and it's ugly,
unless you know it.
Unless you understand how it
adapted, what it's lived through,
and how strong it
had to be to survive.
A photo of that orchid, that's the
only picture my friends had seen of me.
That's how I wanted them to
picture me until I had my new face.
People look away from me.
Kids cry and adults cringe.
They look away.
I didn't want my friends...
I didn't want them to ever
have any reason to look away.
They didn't look away.
Your friends, they didn't
cringe. Not one of them.
They didn't look away. You
looked away, didn't trust them.
You looked away from them.
Let us call them. They
flew all the way here.
Just let us call them
back. It's not too late.
If you want this surgery, Dave,
you gotta give them a chance.
Uh, Chief?
- Dr. Bailey?
- How's your mood?
Eager. Anxious. I'm excited
about Sloan's face transplant.
I'm a little concerned
about Derek, but all in all...
- Do I look
like a therapist?
- You asked.
I've lost Hunt and Torres. I
sent them to get Shepherd,
and I never heard
from them again.
I was trying to solve the
Shepherd situation for you, sir.
But it appears I've somehow
made it three times worse.
So I'm telling you, and
my next move, I believe,
is that I'm gonna
call the police.
Because I'm half
convinced they're all dead.
On a spit with a one-armed man
turning them into shish kebabs, sir.
It's my mind, it
just goes there.
- Don't beat yourself up.
- It's a hard decision.
Yeah, you've been with
Pierce for the whole year.
Just listen to your heart...
- Why are they starting late?
- A problem with the recipient.
They've only got a few hours
left for that face to be viable.
Sloan must be
freaking out, right?
- Home wrecker.
- What did you say? What did you say?
- Guys!
- You two, get out. You, come with me.
- Come on.
- Hey, buddy.
You need to start talking.
You need to start talking now.
- I really can't. Talk to Steve.
- You gotta start talking, dude,
because any second, they're gonna
start that face transplant surgery.
- Her friend...
- Best friend.
Is gonna have her very
first solo surgery, and so...
- we have little
patience right now.
- It's not my place...
OK!
You are gonna tell me
everything that's going on.
Or else every time I have a
rectal exam or an infected abscess,
it's gonna have your
name on it. Every time!
Megan was with
Pierce. But they broke up.
While they were broken
up, she slept with Steve.
Then she got back together with
Pierce. But Steve sent her an e-mail
about how they slept together.
Instead of e-mailing her,
he hit "reply all," went
to a bunch of people.
One of them was Pierce.
Now Steve says he loves her.
Pierce wants to kill him.
Megan's really freaking out
because... OK,
wait. So a while back,
someone sent this text message.
I didn't get it,
didn't get to see it.
It just came to certain
people's phones.
Why would they come back?
I was cruel. I was hateful.
You were scared.
They surprised you.
You were in shock. It wasn't what
you were expecting. You were...
- You were just...
- I was awful.
You were scared.
And you were trying
to protect them.
If they're your friends,
they'll understand.
I didn't want you
to see it. This.
This ugliness,
it... it isn't me.
I... I didn't want
you to see it.
This, right here,
looks just like the
Coryanthes speciosa.
- You guys see that?
- She's right.
The coloring's just the same.
If the surgery doesn't take,
if I reject the donor
face, I'll be uglier.
I'll... I'll be even uglier
than I am right now.
Please don't call
my dear friend ugly.
You're a survivor.
And it's written
all over your face.
What the hell is
this? This is not OK.
I have a hospital to run.
And Derek! What's
the matter with you?
- We've all been there.
- We said that.
- We've all had tough losses.
- He knows that.
We show up the next day and
we try and save the next life.
- Yeah, we covered that too.
- OK, what about this?
Nothing we do can stop death.
We can hold it at bay now
and then. But everyone dies.
And that's not on us.
I took a pregnant woman in for a
simple surgery, and I botched it.
That is on me. I should
feel badly about that.
And you? You should feel
badly that while I was out here,
you sent Meredith out here expecting
a ring. Why would you do that?
Why in God's name
would you do that?
I was trying to help.
She didn't wanna come.
She wanted to leave
you out here alone...
- I was trying to help.
- Trying to help
yourself, not me.
Yourself.
I hit the ring in the woods.
In the woods.
You destroyed me.
This is the final dissection.
We'll place the facial graft.
I'll connect vessels and nerves.
Get the microscope ready.
Yes, right away.
OK, people. It's time.
- Ever put a new face
on someone?
- Really?
I'll take the right
side. You take the left.
Very gently.
That's it. Take your time.
He's not going anywhere.
Thank you.
Watch the left corner of his
mouth. You're off center just a bit.
There we go. Careful
around the eyes.
Good. Very good, Dr. Grey.
- Get out.
- No.
- Get out!
- No!
- Richard, get out!
I've destroyed lives
before. Several, in fact.
Yours is not one of them. I sent the
woman you love out here to help you.
I sent the woman who loves you
out here to bring you back to your life.
If you ruin it with her, that's
on you. I don't accept it.
You're scared, drunk,
don't know which way is up.
You threw a punch at your best friend,
a ring at Meredith, wanna throw me out.
I'm not accepting it!
Because I'm older than you,
and I've been where you are.
You been drunk for a few
days. I was drunk for years.
And I know you're gonna
need at least one friend
when you come out of
that hole you're digging.
I hope you come out of it soon.
I'll be here when you do.
I don't think I
can get her back.
Did you call her?
What am I gonna say?
I had an affair for years.
When Adele found
out, somehow she...
She took me back.
You can make your way back...
from anything.
This is year one
of your residency.
You turn on each other
now, you're not gonna make it.
OK. Here's what's gonna happen.
All of you are going to go find
the sense the good Lord gave you
and never behave like this
within the four walls of this hospital
ever again. You are doctors.
Pierce, get an ice pack and put it on
that oozing, disgusting mess of an eye.
And, Steve, go to the pit
and get that unsanitary,
bloody hand
X-rayed and stitched.
And, Megan, you should go to
OB because yes, you are pregnant.
That was very Bailey.
- You ready, Dr. Yang?
- Wait! I'm sorry.
I need one thing from
you before I go under.
I haven't asked for much. You
haven't answered my questions.
I understand you're
busy, but I'm scared.
I don't wanna die. I want to go
on a tour of Russia with my friends.
I may just be a batty old lady to
you, and this may be a silly procedure,
but I need you to tell
me that it's gonna be OK.
You're my surgeon, after all.
This isn't a silly procedure
to me, Miss Sulley.
- And I will get you
through this.
- OK.
Thank you.
I'm ready now.
Izzie has stage four
metastatic melanoma
that has spread to
her brain, liver and skin.
She may only have months to
live and she's resisting treatment.
She needs help.
Scalpel.
♪ Look, it's a mirror
without a face ♪
♪ Without a face ♪
Don't try to talk.
It'll only hurt.
- You did great.
- Can he see his new face?
- I think he'd really
like to see it.
- It's still early.
It's very swollen and bruised.
The tissue needs time to settle.
But yeah. I'll give
you a sneak peak.
Sometimes we fail, but
that's not always the case.
I know.
Blowhole has a new face.
And what people call him
to get through the day has...
I know.
I told Alex. And Bailey.
And they're telling
Meredith and George.
- Cristina...
- I couldn't do my job.
I think you came to me for
help, and that's what I did.
Because sometimes we win, Izzie.
And I want you to fight.
OK? For whatever that's
worth, I want you to fight.
Thank you.
Dr. Grey.
They think you're
taking advantage of me,
that I'm using you.
But they don't know us.
They think that we're ugly,
but I know that we're beautiful.
And we can adapt to
a hostile environment.
♪ And you're staring
at the ceiling ♪
♪ And where we're from ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm looking
out my window... ♪
- Thanks for coming.
- Thanks for calling.
I love you.
I know.
Would you still love
me if I wasn't a surgeon?
No.
No, because Izzie...
has skin cancer that's
spread to her brain.
You're one of about 20 people
in the world who can save her.
I don't know if I respect somebody
who could walk away from a gift like that.
So please don't.
Here are her scans.
It's pretty bad.
♪ And if we go
sailing down the old ♪
♪ Old front ♪
Practicing medicine
doesn't lend itself well
to the making of friends.
Maybe because
life and mortality...
are in our faces all the time.
Maybe because in staring
down death every day...
we're forced to
know that life...
every minute...
is borrowed time.
♪ And did you have a thought ♪
And each person we
let ourselves care about...
♪ And did you remember what ♪
is just one more loss,
somewhere down the line.
For this reason,
I know some doctors who just
don't bother making friends at all.
♪ And did you remember what ♪
But the rest of us...
we make it our job
to move that line.
To push each loss...
as far away as we can.