Previously on Grey's Anatomy:
- I didn't get the heart.
- You didn't.
I cannot fall for a patient.
What's going on between Stevens
and Denny? Is it a crush?
An innocent flirtation?
Or is Stevens crossing the line?
I'm considering the possibility
of maybe having a date with a vet.
Is he sick again?
He was listless
and hadn't eaten all day.
Those girls were staring at me
like I was a rodent.
- I'm a surgeon first, just like you.
- No. Not like me. I am a person first.
If Burke forgave me
for sleeping during sex...
- Burke hasn't forgiven you.
- You left me.
You don't get to call me a whore.
This thing with us is finished.
It's over.
In life, we are taught
that there are seven deadly sins.
Let's see what you got here.
We all know the big ones:
Gluttony, pride, lust.
He's picturing my face. He's totally
picturing that dart puncturing my skull.
But the sin you don't hear much about
is anger.
Whoa! Look at that.
Maybe it's because we think
anger's not that dangerous.
Derek... Derek is picturing you.
That we can control it.
He called me a whore.
He lost the right to picture me.
- Hmm.
- So I fall asleep during sex. So what?
Ass.
Oh, ass! Hey!
Isabel Stevens has left the hospital.
Did heart patient dude finally kick it?
I'm sorry. This section of the bar
is for surgeons.
We don't socialize with gynecologists.
George!
My point is, maybe we don't
give anger enough credit.
- Hey.
- Hi, Callie.
Hi, Dr. Torres.
Maybe it can be a lot more dangerous
than we think.
After all,
when it comes to destructive behavior...
Uh, gin and tonic and a beer.
...it did make the top seven.
That's it? That's your diagnosis?
He said bone cancer,
so that would be his diagnosis.
I heard him. I was double checking.
I still need to do a bone scan
to see how far it's spread.
Osteosarcomas are aggressive,
but we can try and treat it with chemo
or remove the tumor entirely.
If it's spread too far,
we may have to amputate the limb.
- At that point, should we even bother?
- Oh, right. Let's just let him die.
- I don't want him to suffer, Meredith.
- Right.
So what's...
I mean, is there something going on?
No.
- Did you guys have a fight?
- No.
So... we're all still... friends?
Yes.
I heard you might be getting a heart.
For a transplant.
Mercy West has a heart
and I'm going to get it, yes.
Can I go?
Because, um, I've done it before.
With Dr. Bailey,
when she went to get a heart.
You can ask her. I was very helpful.
Yeah, I'm sure you were. But I'm not
going to need your help on this one.
White male. GSW to the left shoulder.
Multiple walking wounded.
Five injured coming in behind us.
- Why are they all in the hallway?
- Overflow from the ER.
An employee went postal.
Shot up a restaurant.
- I heard he got away.
- Really?
Neal Hannigan and Deborah Fleiss.
They were paying when he came in.
She's got a through and through
to the right arm. Good distal pulses.
He's sustained a possible graze wound
to the right back.
Let's irrigate the wound and get them
to X-ray and order a tet-tox for both.
- Take care of my Deborah first.
- Oh, now you're concerned.
I said I was sorry.
The shooting starts, you duck behind me
and you're sorry?
- You ducked behind her?
- It was instinct.
I couldn't help it.
Deb, honey, you know I love you.
Love means never having to use
your girlfriend as a human shield!
We shared a bullet, Deborah.
It went through you and into me!
That's a sign we should
be together forever. A sign.
No, Neal, this is a sign!
She's squirting water through my arm.
Look. I can see you through my arm.
That's another sign!
Good luck.
Lower left leg deformity from GSW.
Pedal pulse is strong and intact.
Paramedics said he got five of morphine
in the field.
- Trust me, it was not enough.
- Probably got the tibia.
Rule out other injuries
then get him up to Radiology.
Let's get her up to CT.
Get a hold of her parents.
Get them down here.
What's her name, by the way?
- Kendra. Kendra Thomas.
- Kendra.
Almost... Got it.
Do you know what you're doing?
Because that really hurts.
You know what really hurts?
Gunshot wounds. You're lucky.
There's no luck.
Quick thinking, doll.
Excuse me?
I'm a quick thinker. Smart.
Always right on it.
As soon as I saw him,
Petey... he's the shooter...
I knew when I fired him he was no good.
Soon as I saw him,
I thought, "Oh, here we go. "
I just knew it was coming.
Hey, Chaz. Larry. No offense, but you
guys got to think quicker on your feet.
They have gunshot wounds.
Very serious gunshot wounds.
Life threatening gunshot wounds.
Really helps that I'm an athlete because
the second I saw Petey with that gun,
I was like cat-quick.
Just dove right through the window.
Those guys? Not so smart.
I'm going to take a guess
and say Petey was looking for you.
You seen any enema kits?
We have 13 GSWs.
You're looking for enema kits?
I'm trapped with the gyno-beast
on the uterus parade.
- Addison can't do this to you forever.
- You want to bet?
Swear to God,
she's ruining vaginas for me.
Two dead, 14 injured. The policemen
say the gunman got away
so there could be more incoming.
I could stay. We could send Bailey.
No. You're our only
cardiothoracic transplant specialist.
You go get that heart.
Oh, forget it, Karev. I already asked.
It's not going to... happen.
Dr. Burke!
I heard you were getting a heart.
Can I go with you?
I asked first.
You didn't get assigned
to any gunshot cases?
Well, yeah, but if you had put me on
this when I asked I would've been free.
- I didn't.
- He's on the gynie squad!
Not if you put me on this transplant.
Please.
- Let's go, Karev.
- You can't be serious!
Whoo! See you later, Yang. Whoo!
So who's the lucky patient?
Denny Duquette.
The answer is no, Stevens.
You don't know what I'm going to ask.
You want to help prep Denny Duquette
for transplant.
So it's true? He's getting a heart then?
See, your face right now?
That's the problem.
You're overly attached to your patient.
So the answer is no, you cannot
prep him. Go back to sutures.
I know Denny's cardiac parameters.
I know how his LVAD works
better than any other intern.
I know his meds better.
I know the frequency, the dosage, the
quantity, and his physical limitations.
I promise I will...
I will be 100% professional.
No flirting, no knitting him sweaters,
no marathon games of Scrabble?
I will treat him with the same protocol
I would any other patient.
All right. Fine.
You can inform him the heart's coming.
- Thank you, Dr. Bailey.
- If you so much as sit on that bed...
I got it!
Can you imagine?
You're at work, you're doing your job
and somebody comes in and shoots you.
Just... puts a bullet in your head.
- 19 years old.
- Her parents are on their way. Also...
We need to get her
into the OR immediately.
- The bullet's gone through the midline.
- Also, uh...
Look at the size of the hematoma. Also?
- What?
- You said "also" twice.
Yeah. Also, she's pregnant.
Hey, I'm management,
so I'm 100% covered.
So I could spend a year in this
hospital, wouldn't cost me a cent.
When I told you about management,
you should've listened.
Because now you're screwed.
Even if you just spend one day
in this ER, that's three months' rent.
You want to be 16-year-old...
Is there any chance
you can, please, up my morphine?
He keeps talking,
pretty soon I'm going to need some.
Can you find out about Kendra for me?
Are you two friends?
Not friends, exactly.
But, uh, everybody likes her.
You know,
she's... she's just... she's nice.
She'll cover your shift when you
need it. She's good with customers.
She's real generous
when it comes to tipping busboys.
- Let me guess. You're a busboy?
- I am.
Plus, she's the only one
that calls Brad on his crap.
Well, why don't you say something?
Yeah, I wish.
I'm saving up to go back to school.
I need the job.
What are you, socializing?
I've got five more patients for you to
see and Will needs to get to surgery.
Move your ass.
I need the job.
- I have some news for you.
- Am I getting a better television?
Because this one is ridiculously small
and it doesn't get the porny channels.
You're getting a heart, Denny.
I don't mean to be dramatic and all...
but I'm going to need you
to repeat that.
And you say it slow, because this is
one of those moments in life
that I'm going to want to remember
in detail.
You... are getting a heart...
from Mercy West.
Dr. Burke already left to get it.
I guess this means I'm going to have to
start taking you on some real dates.
I guess so.
Here we are, Mr. Duquette.
- What are these?
- DNR papers.
Do not resuscitate?
I'll leave these here and come back.
Why are you signing these?
You're getting a heart.
- If this heart doesn't come through...
- It will.
- The last one didn't.
- You're on an LVAD.
That could give you
another two years right there.
Izzie... if I don't get this heart...
I'm done.
I'm... I'm sorry... I'm tired.
No. No. I'm not going to let you
make this decision. Not now.
Well, that's funny because I thought DNR
was a patient's choice.
Listen to me.
I believe in heaven, Izzie.
And if I had to choose
between this life here...
and one in heaven...
I choose heaven. OK?
OK.
OK, the X-rays will tell us
the location of the bullet.
Mine was a through and through,
so there's no bullet.
We'll make sure it didn't hit bone.
Whatever happens, I want you
to operate on my fiancée first.
- I don't care if I'm dying.
- You're not dying.
I'm also not your fiancée anymore.
We sent out the invitations.
We're getting married in six weeks.
Deborah, please.
I love you.
- Oh, don't fall for it.
- Excuse me, but...
That's how they do it, huh? With the "I
love you's" and the "move in with me's"
and they suck you in
and they melt your resolve.
The minute you need something,
something you deserve,
forget it, it's not going to happen.
They pass you over for surgery or duck
behind you when someone's shooting.
You're very, very bitter.
That's exactly what I was thinking!
See? We're meant to be together.
Shut up, Neal.
Mm-hmm.
There are two donors?
Two brothers tried to pass a semi
on a double yellow
and came out on the losing end of a
head-on. Both are a match for your guy.
- So we get our pick.
- It doesn't work like that.
UNOS has already assigned
who gets which donor.
- So who's retrieving the other heart?
- Took you long enough, Preston.
Why is Junior here? Your ego get too big
for one man to carry?
Dr. Hahn here graduated second in
our class at Johns Hopkins, Dr. Karev.
Ask her who graduated first.
God.
Kendra's fetus is 12 weeks along.
It seems healthy.
- Did you hear me, Derek?
- I heard you.
You're not going to tell me
what's going on between you two?
- I told you. There's nothing to tell.
- Kendra's parents are here.
Let them know the situation,
get the consent forms, then scrub in.
- Yes, Dr. Shepherd.
- Thank you.
- What happened to my donor?
- He went into v-fib.
I see. Give me the paddles. Karev,
take over compressions! You gave epi?
- Three rounds and shocked him twice.
- I'm going to hit him again at 360.
Clear!
He's asystolic.
I don't get it.
I mean, if the guy's already dead...
And now his heart
has joined the rest of him.
Hmm. So, we can't use it?
No, Karev, we cannot use it. The muscle
is dead. The heart is useless.
Dr. Burke?
Move, move, move, move, move!
Stop right there! Don't move that
scalpel! Not even a single slice!
Just because your donor's heart died
doesn't mean you get mine.
Is your patient higher on the transplant
list? Is he higher on the list?
- I have no idea.
- Well, neither do I.
Karev, get UNOS on the phone now.
Oh, give me a break!
- Hey! Hey!
- What? Are you going to beat him up?
- If I have to.
- OK, just hold on.
It's pathetic, Preston. Really pathetic.
I've finished all five of your patients.
Do you mind if I scrub in?
I've never seen an ORIF before.
Can't.
The board's all backed up like crazy.
Will's going to have to wait,
because every specialty thinks their
surgeries are more important than Ortho.
Freaking superior macho jerks.
Can I ask you a question?
About bone cancer.
Yeah.
- In a dog.
- A dog?
My dog. Well, Derek's dog.
Do you know Dr. Shepherd?
It's our dog. We share the dog,
which is... well, never mind.
I wanted to ask
if you knew the success rate
of curing osteosarcoma
in a canine leg?
We have an actual human patient
with a bullet lodged in his tibia
who might walk with a limp for the
rest of his life, or even lose his leg,
and you're asking me
about your precious dog
that you share with your precious
McDreamy? Yeah, I... I know about him.
And you think I care?
Unbelievable!
Your guy's on an LVAD.
He'll be up and walking around.
My guy still needs his dobutamine drip.
That's the best you can do?
He could climb Mount Shasta
on a dobutamine drip.
This morning, Dr. Hahn's patient
was 22 hundreds of a point ahead.
That's basically a tie.
Dr. Hahn's patient was admitted into the
transplant program before Mr. Duquette.
How long before?
17 seconds.
Might as well be 17 weeks.
- Hello?
- Alex? Where's Dr. Burke?
- What do you want?
- How the heart recovery is going.
He's working on it.
He's working on it?
So, he's operating then?
There were two donors, Izzie.
Our heart flatlined.
He's trying to get the other guy's.
- But there's a list.
- And the higher guy gets the heart.
Denny's getting sicker.
What?
Denny's getting worse by the second.
His, uh, sats are in the eighties.
- Izzie.
- It's seventies.
His sats are now in the seventies
and dropping.
- Izzie, I'm not going to lie for you.
- Then put Burke on the phone!
Hey.
- Hey.
- Have you seen Dr. Karev?
Uh... hours ago.
OK.
Sorry. I, uh... I'm not sorry.
I just... I'm having a little trouble
because I need to ask you something.
And I don't usually have trouble.
But what I need to ask...
I'm not even sure I want the answer to,
but I have to ask.
So I'm just going to ask you
and then you answer and then...
I'll go from there, OK?
OK.
Are you sleeping with my husband?
Not since before I knew he was married.
OK.
Except, you know, it just... it felt
like in the vet's office this morning,
and then again in the elevator...
it felt a little like you two
were having a lover's quarrel?
No. We're not.
I've moved on. I'm dating Finn.
You're dating the vet?
- OK.
- Addison...
No, no. Thanks. I'm... I'm good.
Thanks. I'm great.
Flash pulmonary edema?
Is it the LVAD?
Is the LVAD working?
- Absolutely.
- Did you put him on a nitro drip?
Um, yes. Yes, of course.
Preston, she could be putting paddles
directly on his heart.
- He's not getting it.
- Blood pressure?
It's, uh, still dropping. 82 over 40.
Then take him off the drip
and put him on dopamine. Now!
Don't hang up.
According to my intern,
Denny Duquette now qualifies
as a 1 A candidate for that heart.
- So he's ahead of Dr. Hahn's patient.
- I'm out of here. This is just crap.
- Dr. Hahn?
- What?
If Dr. Burke wants to run labs,
do an echo and a BNP
to fully ascertain the status
of his patient, we'll allow it.
That'll take an hour.
Is the donor stable?
- Dr. Hahn? Is the donor stable?
- Yes, the donor is currently stable.
In that case, Dr. Burke,
you've got an hour to get those tests.
- Dr. Stevens?
- I heard.
Good. Get going then.
BP's 220 over 130.
The brain's fungating
out of the wound.
- What's fungating?
- Herniating.
She's bradycardic.
Um, give me 50 mannitol and
20 of furosemide. What's her pulse?
- Down to 32.
- Come on, Kendra. CO2?
40.
Oh, God. Clot's already
evacuated. All right, everybody.
- But...
- She's brain dead.
There's nothing we can do now.
There is no spontaneous brain activity
and she isn't going to wake up.
Oh, God.
What about the baby? Is the baby OK?
As far as we can tell, the baby's fine,
but... that's not the point.
Essentially your daughter is dead.
We need your consent
to remove her from life support.
What if we kept Kendra alive?
Could the baby live?
With all due respect, sir,
you don't want to do that.
Are you part of this family?
Do you have a daughter?
If you don't,
you really ought to just shut up!
Our daughter could have this baby?
You know, even with all these cuts,
I don't feel any pain.
I swear, I have the highest
pain threshold of anybody I know.
God! If I could say something
to that guy and not get fired...
He can't fire me.
Uh, Mr. Eckles? Brad?
Uh, I'm happy for you
that you're not feeling much pain
from your very minor injuries.
But there are a great many people in
this hospital in a great amount of pain.
See, they have bullets in their bones,
in their chests, and in their brains.
Bullets from a gun
that was aiming for you.
And although they can't say it
because you are the boss of them,
most of these people at this moment
are praying... not that they'll live,
not that the pain will subside,
they're praying to God
for you at this moment
to shut the heck up!
No problem.
Karev. He stood there
and chose that moron over me.
I mean, I'm trying to help the dog
and he's standing there
talking about putting the dog down.
Like Doc means nothing.
He's not rewarding Karev,
he's punishing me.
And he hates Finn.
Who, by the way, is great with dogs.
He withholds surgery
when I'm a bad girlfriend.
It's his M.O.
I mean, how controlling and macho
and petulant is that?
At least he's not shooting people
or putting down dogs.
I'm dumping him.
This relationship is so over.
- Um, I... I told a lie... to Dr. Burke.
- Good for you. Fight the power.
No, no. I need... um...
God, I can't think. I... I can't...
I don't know what to do. What do I do?
There's this guy ahead of Denny
on the transplant list.
- He'll get the next heart, Iz.
- No! He needs to get this heart!
He'll probably get a heart
at some point,
but as long as Denny's doing well
on the LVAD
and there's someone ahead of him
on the list,
he's not going to get this heart. OK?
Yes. You're right.
OK. Thank you. Thank you.
If I was going to pick someone who'd
go psycho and shoot up the place...
it's Izzie.
Totally.
- What's all that?
- Heart stuff.
You're putting this heart in me
in my room?
I didn't know transplants
were so informal.
There may not be a heart, Denny.
Somebody at Mercy West
might get it instead.
So this isn't going to happen... again?
Not necessarily.
I have been over this and over this and
it can't be a lie and it can't be fake.
We need charts, we need test results.
We need UNOS to believe us.
So it has to be real.
What are you talking about, Izzie?
In order for you to get the heart, you
would have to get worse. Much worse.
And you would have to do it
very quickly.
Well, I don't see that happening.
You see that happening?
I am going to make it happen.
It's been 30 minutes.
Is Stevens answering her page?
She's probably busy
getting test results.
- Did you call Bailey?
- Well, she's not answering either.
Check the chart all you want.
You're not getting this heart.
Well, you may not want it.
His angiogram shows 30% LAD.
It's still not enough to give it to you.
Izzie. Izzie, stop and listen to me.
We're not doing this.
Don't worry. You're not going to die.
I'll be here the whole time to make sure
of that and that's what this is for.
This isn't about me dying. All right?
This is wrong.
You've waited 18 months to get this.
Who knows when the next one will come?
- I'll take my chances.
- No! It may be too late by then.
Then it's too late!
Get this stuff out of here!
Denny, please.
- You have to do this.
- No, Izzie!
I'm not about to steal a heart
from another man's chest.
Not to mention, this will be the end
of your medical career.
- I don't care about my medical career.
- All right, you know what?
This has gone on long enough.
I'm calling a nurse.
Everyone's entry into the transplant
program is clocked in to the second.
You were clocked in to the second and so
was the other guy. I checked with UNOS.
The difference between
when you entered it
and when he entered it is 17 seconds.
That's it, Denny.
Seventeen seconds.
I mean, it's not even
the length of a decent kiss.
So this other guy?
I'm not saying that
he doesn't deserve this heart.
I'm sure he does. But so do you!
So do you!
And if you tell me any more crap
about heading towards the light
or looking down on me from heaven,
I swear I will kill you myself.
Izzie.
I'm going to be all right.
All right? You don't have to worry.
What about me?
What about me when you go to the light?
- Izzie...
- No! I get it, OK? I get it.
You'll be OK.
You'll be fine, but what about me?
So don't do it for yourself.
Do it for me! Please!
Please, Denny! Please do this for me!
Because if you die...
Oh, God, you have to do this.
You have to do this for me
or I'll never be able to forgive you!
- For dying?
- No! For making me love you!
Please! Please do this for me.
OK? Please! OK?
I can't do this if you don't.
Please do this for me! Because
if you don't do this... Please!
OK. OK, I'll do it.
I'm analyzing an X-ray and your friend
Meredith starts asking me about her dog.
Her dog. She wants a medical opinion
about her dog.
She likes her dog.
- Why are you defending Meredith?
- What?
I get Izzie. I mean, I don't. But if
you want to defend Izzie, that's fine.
I don't get how you can defend Meredith.
Hey! We're interns.
We all started out together,
Meredith, Izzie, Cristina and me.
George, that woman hurt you
as badly as anyone can be hurt.
You were devastated when I met you.
Hey.
They're family.
Izzie and Meredith and Cristina,
they're... they're my family.
I can hate Meredith and I can be
angry at her but I'll always defend her.
So you don't have to forgive Meredith,
but I do?
If you want a chance
to be part of the family, yeah.
Dr. Burke. Hello.
Stevens. Where the hell have you been?
Have you got the lab results?
Um... I'm working on that.
Stevens, I need answers.
- Stevens?
- You should get back here.
With the heart. As soon as you can.
What the hell...
What are you talking about?
Preston.
Izzie, what did you do?
When I get confirmatory tests and labs
to raise Denny's UNOS status,
I will fax them to you. Then you
should waste no time getting back here.
Because I don't know enough to know
how long Denny will have once I start.
Start?
What did you do, Izzie?
- What did you do?
- I'm going to hang up now. Just hurry.
According to my intern,
Denny Duquette is in pulmonary edema.
He has been intubated
and placed on multiple IV drips.
So, Preston gets the heart.
Great, let's open this guy.
However, given this unusual situation
and out of respect to Dr. Hahn,
- I'd like to confirm those results.
- You just did.
In person.
I want to confirm them in person.
Are you kidding? By the time you
get there, it'll be another hour.
What are you up to, Burke?
Why don't you just talk to your chief?
Confirm the results with him.
Well, because of the shootings
today... at the restaurant.
- All our attendings are in surgery.
- Exactly.
If you'd prefer, I could call UNOS
and have them give me the heart.
Or I could go and make sure
that it really belongs to me.
Go.
Thank you.
I'm going back to Seattle Grace.
You stay here and protect my heart.
If that woman so much as looks at a
scalpel, tackle her. Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
- Hey, you got a minute?
- You ready to talk?
Uh, my patient, Kendra Thomas.
She's brain dead.
Her parents want to keep her alive
to have the baby.
You want me to talk to the parents?
I tried, but you're neonatal, you might
have a better shot at it than I do.
- OK.
- You can give them a more detailed...
I said I'd do it.
Mr. And Mrs. Thomas.
Dr. Shepherd asked me
to talk to you about your daughter.
We've made up our mind.
She's having the baby.
I know Kendra meant the world to you
and I know the terrible grief
you must be going through,
but from a medical standpoint,
this is a very bad idea.
Well, if we wanted your opinion, miss,
we'd ask for it.
It's just... we love our daughter.
Please try to understand.
I do understand. I do.
You think if you love her enough
or love her baby enough
that will keep her close to you.
But she's already gone and if you
go with this, you're risking...
I mean, if Kendra
were to contract an infection,
she could pass it on
and it could cause brain damage...
We're taking our chances.
Now they keep organ donors alive
after they're... gone.
Why not Kendra?
Organ donors aren't kept alive for
six months. Your daughter is brain dead.
She can't regulate body temperature,
hormone output.
These things are very important
for a fetus.
- You can regulate that stuff, right?
- We could try. I...
Then try, damn it!
What the hell's the problem here?
The problem is you want to use
your daughter's corpse as an incubator.
- That's the problem!
- OK, I'm sorry. Would you excuse us?
- What?
- They just lost their daughter.
I know. They need to face that.
She's not coming back.
A little sensitivity
would be nice here, OK?
They love their daughter.
They don't want to let go.
What they're doing is not about love.
It's... It's... Well, it's like you.
- Excuse me?
- Like how you pretend to love me,
but you're just using me
to fill your need to be a good guy.
Now is not the time to talk about this.
- You walk away? That's all I get?
- Just calm down.
You're not going to yell at me?
Call me names?
Or I don't know...
ignore me in an elevator?
- What do you want from me, Addison?
- I want you to care!
I sleep with your best friend
and you walk away.
He comes out here from New York
and rubs it in your face,
and still you get a good night's sleep.
What do I have to do? Oh! I know.
Maybe what I should do
is go out on a date with the vet.
Because that seems
to send you into a blind rage.
Oh, but wait. That won't work either
because I'm not Meredith Grey!
I know it's a bad time, but do you
still want to go ahead with the baby?
We haven't decided on anything.
Sir? You asked me before
if I had a daughter.
I don't. But I have a family.
I... actually have a couple families.
The thing about families, you don't
necessarily like what they do.
Their choices and their decisions.
But you stick by them.
Right now one of my friends,
her boyfriend is dying.
Heart failure. He's 36. Kendra's
driver's license says she's a donor.
She's not a match,
but she could save a dozen other lives.
And from what I know about Kendra,
what I've heard,
I got to believe that if she had the
choice between where she is right now
and saving a dozen other people,
she'd save those people.
That would be her decision.
So the question is...
whether you stick by her one last time.
Excuse me.
You paged?
Yeah. These are X-rays of a human
with an osteosarcoma on his tibia.
It's the closest I could get to
mirroring what's happening to your dog.
In this patient,
the cancer was aggressive.
And it spread quickly and he died when
it finally metastasized on his lungs.
- The human died?
- Yes. The human died.
Thank you, Callie.
You're welcome, Meredith.
- You OK, baby?
- Yeah.
Well. You made up with him?
- I said I'd give him one more chance.
- And I said she won't have to.
What I went through today, what we went
through today, it's changed me.
This bullet will always remind me
to do the right thing by my Deborah.
Here you go.
And whatever's going on
with you and your boyfriend?
Maybe you should just
try and forgive him.
It really feels so much better
than all that anger.
Thanks.
We haven't forgotten you, Will.
We'll get you to the OR
as soon as possible.
My friend, Kendra...
Dr. Grey said that if anybody
had any information
that they would let me know
as soon as possible.
OK. I'm sorry.
I'm going to get you some time off, man.
I'm going to talk to the owner,
make sure they keep your job for you.
It's not your fault you got shot.
Not my fault either.
You know, I... I didn't...
I didn't pull the trigger.
Petey had the gun. I'm just saying.
People blame management,
but we do the best we can.
I mean, I... I do the best I can.
I know what you're going to say,
but if you knew the day that I had...
Everybody in this hospital
has those days, Addison.
And no one makes a scene in front
of their peers. Get it together.
Addison.
I can't compete.
He's not having an affair.
He's not trying to hurt me. He's just...
The only people who don't know Derek
loves Meredith are Derek and Meredith.
How do I compete with that?
So what makes anger different
from the six other deadly sins?
It's pretty simple really.
You give in to a sin like envy or pride
then you only hurt yourself.
I love you.
I'm sorry. I'm...
I... I didn't mean to... I just...
I... I have verbal diarrhea
and I'm a moron.
What are you thinking?
Are you freaking out or?
George, I need your help. I wouldn't ask
if it weren't important. It's...
OK.
I'll call you? Later?
Sure.
Were we supposed to have dinner tonight?
- Tell me the truth about Doc.
- What about him?
You've been downplaying how sick he is,
haven't you?
The best-case scenario,
I would say Doc has maybe a year left.
- OK.
- And Doc is not the best-case scenario.
- Meredith?
Oh, damn it.
I am sorry. I'm so sorry.
I know how much you love him.
I do.
I love him so much.
- You need my help for an EKG?
- No. Come.
OK, after I do this,
I might have to shock you a few times.
- Do what?
- You feeling good?
I think so. Explain this to me again.
The LVAD has been inserted into your
abdomen and is connected to your heart.
This leads to the power source,
this one is connected to the pump
that pumps your heart for you.
I have the crash cart, the
defibrillator, the Ambu bag, saline...
Do what, Izzie?
Um, I feel like we should say stuff.
Denny, do you want to say stuff?
Kiss me. Right here.
Izzie, that kiss was worth
1,000 words.
A picture.
A picture is worth 1,000 words.
- You're correcting me now?
- I don't mean to be intrusive...
Just give me a second, George!
OK, are you ready?
As I'll ever be.
Wait. What are you doing?
Try lust or coveting
and you'll only hurt yourself,
and probably one or two others.
But anger... Anger is the worst.
- OK. We're done!
- What was that? Were those gunshots?
The mother of all sins.
Petey.
Denny. If there really is
some kind of big glowy light...
- I'll try like hell to stay out of it.
- Exactly.
- I don't like the sound of this.
- Just make sure nobody comes in.
What are you doing?
I'm stopping his heart, George.
Not only can anger
drive you over the edge,
when it does, you can take
an awful lot of other people with you.
Izzie.
Oh! Dr. Burke. I need some help!
It's OK.
Burke will be here any minute.
www.tvsubtitles.net