- Previously on Grey's
Anatomy: - Izzie has
stage four melanoma that has
spread to her brain, liver and skin.
He threw the first punch.
I should talk to him?
- Mr. Torres.
- She's my only little girl.
- The minute you hurt her...
- I'm engaged.
I broke up with Owen.
Defeat isn't an option.
Not for surgeons.
We don't back away from the
table till the last breath's long gone.
"Terminal's" a challenge.
"Life threatening" is what gets
us out of bed in the morning.
♪ That I ♪
♪ Knew well ♪
♪ I hope ♪
♪ It goes as follows ♪
♪ And I hope it's
all so special ♪
We're not easily intimidated.
We don't flinch,
we don't back down...
and we certainly
don't surrender.
♪ King of Sound get some rest ♪
♪ And now there's room
for happiness here ♪
♪ And he laughs beneath
his crooked crown ♪
Not at work, anyway.
♪ And he won't ask
for nothing now ♪
Does it bother you that
I don't wanna wear it?
- Because I... I could.
- I don't want you to wear it.
You're not a ring bride.
What?
I'm not really a
church wedding bride,
or a poufy white
dress bride either.
We'll get naked and get
married in a field of flowers.
- I'm not a naked bride!
- We'll get married in scrubs.
- Ooh! There's a wedding
I can get into.
- We gotta go.
So I told Izzie she could
help with the wedding,
keeps her mind off of everything. I'll
tell her about the scrubs and no church.
We have a theme: simplicity.
Maybe they can make you a
bouquet of scalpels and clamps.
That would be fun. I'd
have to run it by Izzie first.
I don't feel anything.
Nothing?
No anger, happiness,
unhappiness?
Guilt?
Survivor's guilt?
- It's very common
with veterans.
- It's not about my platoon.
You have shoved your
feelings aside for so long.
I'm asking you to claim them.
And Owen, this is
about your platoon.
It's about the fact that I tried
to choke my girlfriend to death.
The way I feel about my platoon and
what happened with Cristina are the same?
They're not.
How will you know if you
can't name those feelings.
That's not what it's...
It's...
I don't know.
What do you mean you don't
deliver dresses? Just to try on?
No, no, I can't come
in. I... have cancer.
I'm bed-bound and dying.
Fabulous! I'll fax
you my choices. Hi!
Uh, what do you need?
Blood, pee, what can I get you?
Just checking in on you,
see how the chemo's sitting.
Fine. I haven't puked yet.
- I'm making progress
on Mer's wedding.
- You should take it easy.
Chemo's gonna
take a lot out of you.
I'll let you know
if I hit the wall.
Hello? Hi, yes. I wanted to
discuss, um, flower arrangements.
She needs to save her energy. This
isn't just chemo. It's high dose IL-2.
It makes the body attack itself. She's
walking around, but it's not gonna last.
Blood pressure will tank,
shaking with chills, nauseous.
She might even
have a heart attack.
Believe me, a few
hours from now,
Izzie Stevens is gonna
wish she were dead.
- Is he here yet?
- Talking about Calliope's dad?
The answer is I don't know
because I'm not meeting him
- because it's way too soon.
- And Torres is OK with that?
Her idea. The man's here for one
day, then he's gone. No muss, no fuss.
- Run. Run for your life.
- What do you mean
"run for my life"?
- Oh, God! Dad!
- Give me one good reason
- I shouldn't kill you.
- Stop it!
- You committed adultery.
- Who hasn't?! I slept with him
before we were divorced, so
George isn't the only one who cheated.
Good God!
Give me one reason
I shouldn't kill you.
- Mark Sloan. Pleasure to meet you.
- Dad, Mark's just a friend.
I'm happy, OK? I'm dating
someone now and I'm happy, OK?
You're dating again.
That's good, healthy.
I'd like to meet this
new gentleman suitor.
Yeah. Yeah, no, um...
They're pretty busy 'cause they're a
doctor here, but, um, you'll love them.
You'll love them because
they're smart and funny, and...
both handsome and, and
beautiful and, and very supportive.
Daddy? Please be OK with this.
Dad, this is Arizona Robbins.
This is who I'm dating now.
I really hope you draw the line
at throwing women against walls.
- You page me?
- Driver's face went through window.
- Your cup of tea.
- Right you are.
- What do you got?
- Anthony Meloy, 32-year-old male
pedestrian with a left arm injury
and road rash to his face and torso.
Stable vitals. Landed on the
street after he was hit by the driver.
I didn't hit him. He
jumped in front of me!
Dan Gates. Swerved
after he didn't hit Mr. Meloy
and sideswiped a pole.
Complains of abdominal pain.
- Blood from his left ear...
- He came out of nowhere!
Give him a blood alcohol
test. Driving like a madman!
- Now he's just lying.
- I'm lying? I'm lying?!
- Try to stay still.
- No sign of head trauma.
Check out the other guy.
I got it from here. Let's go.
- I need to look
at his injuries.
- When we're inside.
- Drunk!
- Liar!
- Pathetic.
- Ass.
I was just driving to the bank.
Next thing, this guy jumped
in front of my car. Whack job.
- Can you move your eyebrow?
- I can't examine his ear.
- Would you get out of the way?
- Just wait.
Free fluid in the upper quadrant.
Grey, schedule a stat CT.
How you doing, Mr. Meloy?
- My arm's killing me,
otherwise fine.
- Tenderness and bruising
over his humerus,
but good pulses.
We should still
do a full work-up.
Check in with Karev once you
assess, let him know what you find.
- I'm reporting to Karev?
- He's overseeing the pit today.
- You good with that, Karev?
- Yes, sir.
I'll be in the OR
if you need me.
Off you go.
Meeting Callie's dad was so
not on the agenda for today.
Seems like a man
who needs preparation
for meeting his daughter's
girlfriend. Should have seen his face.
- Can you stop doing that thing?
- What thing?
Telling me your business
thing. It's my day off.
- I'm here to watch
the fundoplication.
- I checked.
You worked a 90 hour
week. You should be sleeping.
- You can stop doing that, too.
- It's just that Peds can be
tough.
- It can be hard on a family.
- Not mine.
My husband... is
very supportive.
He is... can't wait for
me to start my fellowship.
- He doesn't know, does he?
- No.
Why?
Dr. Robbins, Jessica had
a seizure and can't breathe.
She's got Tay-Sachs. Get a mask
on her and crank it up to 15 liters.
All right, sit up.
You're OK, honey.
You just need to
breathe. Slow, slow.
Good, good.
You're getting better.
Slow, slow. I think you're OK.
There's no blood in the brain.
ZMC fracture of the temporal
bone, ruptured eardrum.
- Book us an OR.
- Not so fast, Dr. Grey.
Mr. Gates, the patient has a name,
injured a facial nerve. Which means?
That Mr. Gates will
also need a nerve repair.
Does that take place before or after
Dr. Sloan's ossicular reconstruction?
- Before.
- Incorrect.
You have to explore for bone
fragments, reversing his hearing loss.
Which is why I need
you to book that OR.
If he has facial paralysis, it won't
matter if he can hear out of one ear.
- Am I right, Dr. Grey?
- Uh...
- Dr. Grey.
- Lexie?
- Lexie.
I think you both are
amazing doctors.
The car hit you while
you were in the crosswalk?
Yeah. Are you almost
done? 'Cause I need to go.
Uh, no, um...
Because we need to wait for
the police. They need a statement.
Is that necessary? Can't I just
leave my name and number?
I just need you to wait
here for one minute. OK?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
Alex. I need to order a
psych consult for Mr. Meloy.
He said he was walking,
but the pattern of his injuries
aren't consistent. Plus,
he's acting agitated.
Maybe because he was hit by a
car. Or 'cause he has you as a doctor.
You need to discharge him.
We've a lot of other patients
- with worse injuries.
- If he leaves
and he hurts
himself, it's on you.
Fine. Get your consult. But if
someone in that waiting room dies
because we don't have
a bed, that's on you.
I hear congratulations
are in order.
- What?
- The engagement.
Our very own Seattle Grace wedding. I
couldn't be happier for the both of you.
Thank you, sir. Did you
have an assignment?
- Dresses.
- I'm sorry?
Stevens has transformed her
room into a bridal boutique. So go.
Try on dresses. That's an order.
- I didn't think
you wanted a dress.
- I don't.
- How does he even know
we're engaged?
- Richard's my friend.
He didn't order the dress. If
you don't want to wear a dress,
- talk to Izzie.
- Yeah. As the chemo drips
into her cancer-y arm and she
looks at me with those cancer-y eyes,
- those cancer-y,
wedding-loving eyes?
- Be strong.
We'll have bridesmaids in pink taffeta.
You'll wear top hat and morning coat
and somebody will sing
Wind-Beneath-My-Freaking-Wings.
- You want me to talk to her?
- OK, I'm glad we talked.
Apparently, a morning
coat is non-negotiable.
Also, we have to make time
for ballroom dancing lessons.
Just so you know, I wasn't
looking for a relationship.
Not with anyone,
a he or a she. But...
it just happened.
And, uh...
It feels good with her.
It feels easy and, uh...
comfortable.
I'm saying I'm happy.
When have you ever heard
me willingly admit that?
When you lived at home
with your mother and me.
- You were happy then.
- I was 12. It didn't take much.
Fly home with me.
I'll talk to the chief,
- explain the circumstances.
- What?!
Dad, no. I'm not
moving back home!
Don't worry.
Everything's gonna be OK.
Everything is... O... OK.
Tay-Sachs is always fatal in children,
usually by the age of four or five.
She's six.
I spoke to my friend who's
fundraising for Jessica.
This place in Mexico. They do
experimental stem cell therapy.
A couple of weeks, we'll
have enough money...
Matt, Jessica doesn't
have a couple of weeks.
It's quite possible she
only has a couple of hours.
We talked about this.
We've talked about this a lot.
And now it's here.
And I know it's hard.
I know it's impossible. But
we've done everything we can.
- You have done
everything you...
- No. No!
Listen. All we need
is a little more time.
If you read about
these treatments...
I don't mean to insult you. I
know you've done everything.
I just need a few more days, more time.
She's a fighter. You know she'll fight.
- I just need to get her there.
- Matt.
She's not gonna
make it to Mexico.
And I am so sorry,
but the best thing you can
do for her now is to be here.
No!
Don't tell me what's best.
You don't tell me.
I will find a way.
I will get her to
Mexico tonight.
Shame on you for giving up on
her. Shame on you, Dr. Robbins.
Get a crash cart to Izzie
Steven's room! Izzie!
What?
I'm sorry! You should see your
face! It's your totally-freaking-out face!
- You're joking? This is a joke?
- I'm sorry.
I really did need you, though.
I have all these dresses. I keep
paging Meredith to come try them on,
and she won't answer. So
will you tell her to come in here?
She'll listen to you.
You have damage to your facial nerve
from a broken bone behind your ear.
- Which I'll repair.
- Also, bleeding
around your spleen.
- We'll keep an eye on it.
- Your eardrum ruptured.
You might lose the
hearing in your left ear.
Unbelievable. Unbelievable!
- That son of a bitch!
- Mr. Gates, try and stay calm.
No. Don't tell me to stay calm.
That son of bitch dove in
front of my car. He dove!
Like he was Superman. Had his
arms stretched out and everything!
I was going to the bank.
I was just...
going to the bank.
If I show you the dress, you can
never tell anyone because it's bad.
- Really, really bad.
- OK, fine. It'll be
our little secret.
Oh, wow.
- Photos are not secret!
- Isn't there a tiara
that goes with it?
- Put it on so I get
the full effect.
- No tiara. I told you simple.
- Buffalo wings
at the reception.
- You can't.
Caterers don't do buffalo wings.
Iz, this is a small
wedding. Small.
This is a big dress
for a big wedding.
Don't you have a dress that
doesn't make noise when it moves
- or stand up by itself?
- You're getting married.
It's a miracle. Meredith Grey,
child of darkness, found someone.
Don't want to celebrate
that? It's your day, Meredith.
You can't just piss it
away on a slip dress
and a cheese tray from the grocery
store. That will make me so sad.
I don't want to be sad. I'm suffering
through cancer. That's sad enough.
Fine, give me the tiara.
Oh! You're like a princess.
Smile.
I mean, home! He's
dragging me home!
Who I want to spend it with!
Got it. Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
I can see you're very upset.
You page me, Robbins?
You're her best friend
and I am at a giant loss,
- not to mention
the sick children...
- Go. I got this.
Hey!
Stop speaking Spanish because
I have to go to surgery in a minute
- and I don't speak Spanish.
- My dad is taking me home.
Talking to the chief and making
me quit my job and relationship,
he has yet to
acknowledge exists.
Are you 12? Tell him he's crazy.
You don't understand. There isn't
anything he hasn't done for me. Nothing.
He paid for my college, med
school. I have a huge trust fund.
He doesn't want me to worry
about anything but being a doctor.
The man's done nothing
but support me his whole life.
Supporting someone and respecting
someone aren't the same thing.
You need to tell him that.
Well, look who's up.
- Where's my dad?
- He should be here soon.
How you feeling?
You want some water?
- I want my dad.
- It's OK.
It's OK.
Um...
When my little boy is scared,
know what makes him feel better?
When he rocks in the chair
with me. Let me show you.
Here we go. All righty.
There we go, sweetie.
Yeah. He likes this.
He likes this a lot.
There you go.
I got you the cheeseburger
you wanted. You sure about this?
- You're OK? Not feeling nauseous?
- No, I'm good, I'm fine. See?
Hi.
- French fries. I love French fries.
- Meredith, let's go.
I feel like this dress is giving me a
mammogram. It's squishing my boobs.
- Let me see it.
- I'm taking it off.
- Izzie, you OK?
- I think she's choking.
Let's hit her with oxygen. Izzie.
Speak to me. Say something. Izzie?
I'm not choking!
I'm joking.
OK, you gotta stop
doing that. It's not funny.
Got Meredith out so I could see
her in her the dress. And it's gorgeous.
- Tell her she has to stop.
- Izzie!
- Very romantic. It's pretty, right?
- Pretty.
And I see you've invited more
people to witness my humiliation?
No. Derek and Mark aren't speaking.
We're heading into a six-hour surgery.
Unless I slip this burger into a
sterile area, I'm not gonna make it.
- Can you please come
talk to them?
- Fine. OK. You can go.
Cristina, will you help
her take the dress off?
I'll be in the scrub room.
Lexie just ate all my fries. Can
you please get me some more?
Nice. The IL-2 isn't
affecting you at all.
OK.
Doctor said if we can find a way
to get her there, he'll treat Jessica.
Matt, she's been asking for you.
Hey, baby. Guess what?
We're gonna go to Mexico
and you're gonna love it there.
The sky is so blue
and the sand is white.
- And the water...
- Can we go tomorrow, Daddy?
I'm so tired.
Why don't you trade places
with me. It's you she wants.
All I need is plane fare.
Then we'll be on our way.
I can get someone to
relieve you for a while.
If you still want to watch
me do that fundoplication.
I'm OK.
OK. Before you guys go in there
and start cutting on this patient,
you need to apologize to each
other. If not for the patient, for me.
Or for Lexie. Look at her.
Her face is breaking out.
Her ass is humongous.
It's true. I had to get the
scrubs with the elastic waistband.
If you don't apologize,
she's not scrubbing in.
I won't. You can't make me.
This should be a joyful time.
- You should be the best man.
- The chief will be my best man.
What?
- Is my ass really...?
- Lexie, will you excuse us? Please.
- The chief?
- The best man is my choice.
When are you gonna let
go of the grudge you have?
Derek, the man had
an affair with my mother,
broke up my parents' marriage
and basically destroyed my childhood.
Meanwhile, you've been best
friends with Mark for 20 years,
and you're willing to throw
all that away over nothing.
So don't talk to me about grudges. I'll
get over mine when you get over yours.
- What are you doing up here?
- I stopped by
to see Dr. Stevens.
- I'm on my way back.
- What happened
with the pedestrian?
- Did the cops talk to him?
- I don't know. I don't think so.
You don't know? That guy
may have tried to kill himself.
- I called for a psych consult.
- A potentially suicidal patient
and you're wandering around up here?
The guy who hit him is headed to an OR.
He's in terrible
shape. He may not live!
- I...
- Quiet!
If that guy threw
himself in front of that car,
he should pay. He should pay.
He better not walk out of that ER!
Move faster, Karev!
- You asked for a psych consult?
- Yes, I did.
Where is he?
- Oh, crap.
- Wonderful. You've lost him.
I have not... Have you
checked the waiting room?
O'Malley! Where's Mr. Meloy?
Pysch was supposed to be examining
him and he's not my only patient.
Nice. Nice! You lost him.
Hunt is gonna love
hearing about this.
You didn't want
the pysch consult!
I don't get it. I don't... I tried to
give you the benefit of the doubt...
I don't get what Hunt sees in you
and I don't understand what Izzie sees.
Shut up! I'm the one who's
tried. Izzie likes you. So I've tried.
I've tried to find one little
ounce of respect for you,
but you lost him. You thought he
was suicidal and turned your back.
That's not on me. I'm done with
you. I'm done trying to respect you.
I'm done!
- What happened?
- We did ATLS protocol,
- but he's...
- We inserted
bilateral chest tubes,
but he kept bleeding.
Then he started bradying
so we pushed atropine. I opened
his chest when we lost vitals.
Found edge of rib protruding
into his ascending aorta.
I attached a clamp and
I'm getting heart activity.
- You got an OR lined up?
- OR Two.
- Good work, O'Malley. Scrub in.
- His aorta was looking...
We got it, Karev.
Do a middle fossa
craniotomy approach.
- Let's get diamond burrs in.
- Don't bother. I ordered them.
I may be irresponsible and
untrustworthy out there. I'm not in here.
- I never said untrustworthy.
- You put the Berlin Wall
around Lexie.
Meredith asked me. People do
when someone they care about
asks them to do
something. They do it.
You should have, when I asked you
to stay away from Lexie. Or Addison.
Oh, here we go. Addison.
The only note he can ever play.
You know, I was gonna apologize
for decking you, 'cause I felt bad,
but now, I'm gonna play it over and
over in my head and really enjoy it.
Oh, hell!
- It's coming from the pterygoid plexus.
- - Get me 4-0 vicryl!
- A clamp.
- You know what? I'm done.
I give up. If I hadn't fallen for Little
Grey, you would have found a reason
not to respect me. Always have. To
you, I'm always gonna be the charity case
the Shepherds had to take in.
- I got the bleeder.
- You threw the stitch already?
Yeah.
Hmm.
Do you know where Dr. Grey is?
- No, do you want me
to page her?
- No, it's OK.
OK.
Thank you.
Can you hold the
retractor, please?
He'll need 3-0 Prolene and a
Gore-Tex graft. I'll get it ready.
You're good at this.
You're thinking ten steps ahead of
what you're doing. Not many can do that.
And the hairier things
get, the calmer you get.
It's something you're wired
with. Chosen your specialty yet?
- No, sir.
- It's trauma.
I'm sorry. You want to
take Dr. Torres home?
Now, I recognize that my
daughter is a senior resident
and you've invested in her education.
I'm happy to write out a check
for whatever amount as a
donation to your hospital.
In exchange, I would ask you to
transfer her to St. Mary's in Miami.
Um, I appreciate the offer,
sir. But, with all due respect,
your daughter is a grown woman.
Does she know you're here?
You don't have children, do you?
- No, no, no. I don't.
- No. You don't.
Because if you did...
"Your daughter's a grown
woman..." That means nothing.
I mean, she's my child.
It's like the blood running through
your veins. You don't outgrow it.
Never goes away. The love.
The need to protect them from
everything. From everything.
Even from themselves.
They grow up. They move out.
They change. Become people
you don't even recognize.
Make decisions...
And they think you don't love
them because you don't understand.
But it's the opposite.
See, it's the opposite.
You fight for them. Always.
You never surrender.
When your child is on the
line, you never surrender.
I called eight organizations. And they
have a wait list for emergency funds.
- I don't know what to do.
- Mr. Smithson,
it's time to stop now.
Maybe if we just go to the airport,
they'll let us on a flight. I mean...
- People do things like that...
- Mr. Smithson.
No! Please don't make me stop.
Please don't make me stop.
Please don't make me stop!
I wouldn't want to stop either.
But Jessica is terminal, Matt.
In a few minutes, her
heart is going to stop.
Now, I can pump her chest,
I can push all
sorts of medicines,
and put her on a ventilator 'cause
she'll no longer be able to breathe.
But even with all of
that, she's going to die.
And the last person who
will have her hands on her,
who will have been
able to touch her,
it's gonna be me or a nurse.
Or it could be you.
You don't want to miss this.
This next part, she needs
her daddy for this part.
Daddy?
Are we going to Mexico?
♪ You're my sweetheart ♪
♪ If I never see you again ♪
Yes.
We're going to Mexico.
Where the sky is blue, blue.
And the sand is white.
The water is so clear, you can
see all the way to the bottom.
We're going.
Just you and me.
No more doctors.
No more medicine.
No more hospitals.
Just you and me.
We're gonna go. Just
relax. We'll be there soon.
♪ Just want you to
know what I think ♪
We'll play on the beach all day.
We'll make sand castles.
♪ So don't smoke yourself to death I
will be the one who'll always be there ♪
♪ If you've got to run ♪
We're going.
We'll be there soon. You'll see.
We're gonna have so much fun.
Just you and me.
98 over 72. That's
good. That's good.
Don't.
Don't try to make me out
better than I am, because I'm not.
I'm sick.
You had an incredibly
high dose of IL-2 today.
- This is how
you're supposed to feel.
- All I wanted to do today
was flip through
magazines, call caterers
and make Mer try on
dresses I knew she'd hate.
I thought it would be fun or...
funny.
I thought I could be the same person
I was when I woke up this morning.
But I'm not.
I'm just another patient
trapped inside a sick, dying,
cancer-ridden body.
What happened?
He, uh... gave me an ultimatum.
He said if I don't come home,
he'll take away my trust fund.
He'd cut me off.
So I cut him off.
If he can't accept
me for who I am...
I cut him off.
Are you OK?
No.
I mean... yeah. I don't know.
I jumped in front of her car,
and she was just
driving to the bank.
- We're talking about Cristina?
- I jumped in front of her. I knew.
I knew I wasn't together, I knew I
was no good for her, for anyone.
And I wrecked her.
And that is unforgivable.
I don't forgive myself for that.
I can't forgive myself for that.
And I'm feeling
shameful about that.
That's what I feel today. Shame.
Good. That's a start.
- How is that a start?
- You named it.
The feeling.
You have to know what it is
before you can start to
navigate to somewhere better.
He has a long recovery ahead of him.
He severely damaged his facial nerves,
- shattered his inner ear,
lost blood.
- Oh, my God.
But he'll be fine. He'll be in some
pain for a while, but he'll be fine.
Oh, my God. Thank you.
Thank you both so much.
Thank Dr. Sloan. That bleeding,
not a lot of surgeons can handle.
He saved your husband's life.
- Would you like to see him now?
- Yes. Thank you.
You know, that's the first
compliment you've ever given me.
- It was a statement of fact.
- See, why do you do that?
Why can't you just give
a person a compliment?
If you have to ask, it's not a
compliment. Are you asking?
- Yes.
- Then it's not a compliment.
Is there anything else
you need before I go?
No.
- You want to sit a while?
- No, I do not want to sit.
I been sitting and
lying down all day.
- Dr. Bailey...
- Holding a child.
If I wanted to spend
the day holding a child,
I would have stayed
home to hold my own child.
I didn't do a single
medical thing today.
I didn't even put a Band-Aid
on a patient. I'm just tired.
I... I'm done.
Are you gonna tell your husband?
What would I tell him?
That it's more
than just cutting.
Peds is more than just cutting.
And what you did
today was heroic.
And you know it.
OK.
Maybe I'll tell him that.
To do our jobs...
we have to believe
defeat is not an option.
That no matter how
sick our patients get...
♪ Running like hell ♪
♪ Making my getaway ♪
You're gonna make
a beautiful bride.
There's hope for them.
♪ The walls are caving
in with no warning ♪
♪ This ship is sinking
I gotta swim for it ♪
♪ I'm running out of air ♪
♪ Break me out tonight ♪
♪ I wanna see the sun
rising anywhere but here ♪
♪ Come with me ♪
♪ Oh this could be ♪
♪ The only chance we
get We gotta take it ♪
Thanks.
♪ We don't do it now
we'll never make it ♪
♪ Lose this crowd ♪
♪ Oh, break me out ♪
You kicked ass today,
O'Malley. You kicked my ass.
- I just did what I had to do.
- No. You kicked ass.
I'm not like that.
I'm good, but I'm not like you.
I'm not good under pressure.
She's really sick.
Really sick. And I'm
not good under pressure.
But even when our
hopes give way to reality...
and we finally have to
surrender to the truth...
it just means we've
lost today's battle...
Could I have another, please?
Not tomorrow's war.
So I guess a big
wedding won't be that bad.
I'm just sad 'cause I didn't get a
chance to see you in the actual dress.
- You will.
- How?
- If Derek
and Mark don't make up...
- You're my sister, Lexie.
You're in the wedding.
Oh, my God! I'm
gonna be a bridesmaid?
Oh, my God! I don't
know what to say.
Wait and see what Izzie's picked out
for you to wear. You'll have plenty to say.
Here's the thing
about surrender.
-  You want one?
- So much.
- Once you do it...
-  We can still catch
half of the game.
- Yeah, that's what
I was thinking.
- Actually give in...
you forget why you were
even fighting in the first place.
- You can stop eating now.
- Oh, thank God.