Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Intimacy is a four-syllable word for here are my heart and soul.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Please grind them into hamburger and enjoy.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): It's both desired and feared.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Difficult to live with.
Roommate (possibly Izzie or George) / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Excuse me.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): And impossible to live without.
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Is that my toothbrush?
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Intimacy also comes attached to life's three Rs.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Relatives, romance, and roommates.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Copy.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): There are some things you can't escape.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): And other things you just don't want to know.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Hello, kitty.
George O'Malley / Zona (PVM): You don't understand.
Dr. George O'Malley: Me gonads, you ovaries.
Izzie Stevens / Zona (PVM): Oh, that reminds me.
Izzie Stevens / Zona (PVM): We are out of tampons.
Dr. George O'Malley: You're parading through the bathroom in your underwear when I'm naked in the shower.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): Can you add it to your list, please?
Dr. George O'Malley: What?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): Tampons.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): It's to the list.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): It's your turn.
Dr. George O'Malley: I am a man.
Dr. George O'Malley: I don't buy girl products.
Dr. George O'Malley: I don't want you walking in while I'm in the shower, and I don't want to see you in your underwear.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): It doesn't bother me, okay?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): Look at me in my underwear, George.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): Take your time.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): It's no big deal.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You are the first person they see in the morning.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You say please.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You say thank you.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You apologize for waking them up.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: You make them feel good about you.
Intern (likely George O'Malley or Izzie Stevens) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Why is that important?
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Because then they'll talk to you and tell you what's wrong.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Because then you can tell your attending what they need to know during rounds.
Intern (likely George O'Malley or Izzie Stevens) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): And why is that important?
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Because if you make your resident look bad, she'll torture you until you beg for your mama.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Now, get out there.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: I want pre-rounds done by 5.30 a.m.
Dr. Alex Karev: Morning, Dr. Model.
Dr. Isobel Stevens: Dr. Evil Swan.
Dr. Alex Karev: Ooh.
Dr. Alex Karev: Nice tat.
Dr. Alex Karev: They ever brush that off for the catalogs?
Dr. Isobel Stevens: I don't know.
Dr. Isobel Stevens: What do they do for the 666 on your skull?
Dr. Cristina Yang: I'd better get good patients today.
Dr. Isobel Stevens: Yesterday, I had two guys with colostomies who needed dressing changes every 15 minutes.
Dr. George O'Malley: I don't want to be in surgery.
Dr. Cristina Yang: Today's my day.
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): On what?
Dr. Cristina Yang: Like I tell you.
Alex Karev / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): What do you know?
Dr. Cristina Yang: Know that I was here at 4, and you didn't get here till 4.30.
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Tell me.
Dr. Cristina Yang: No.
Dr. Alex Karev: I'm not the intern who's screwing and attending.
Dr. Meredith Grey: I am not screwing...
Dr. Derek Shepherd: You're here early.
Dr. Meredith Grey: Have a quart out of me at 5.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: I'll be out at 6.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: I thought I might.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: Buy your breakfast before you round.
Dr. Meredith Grey: I've already eaten.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: What would you have?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Mr. Humphrey (PVM): None of your business.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Mr. Humphrey (PVM): The cereal person?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Straight out of the box, you're all fruit and fribery.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Pancakes?
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Do you like pancakes?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): Fine.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Leftover grilled cheese.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Curiosity satisfied?
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): That's sad.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): That's pathetic.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): A good day starts with a good breakfast.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Look, I'm not being seen with you in this hospital.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Learn it, live it.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): It's unprofessional.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Mr. Humphrey (PVM): I think there's an attending getting to know one of his interns.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Zona (PVM): He slept with the intern.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Zona (PVM): He's barely newer.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Zona (PVM): And it should stay that way.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Mr. Humphrey OR Zona (PVM): You want me to be professional?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Mr. Humphrey (PVM): I'll be professional.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): That's what I want.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): And that's what you get.
Cristina Yang / Zona (PVM): You're going to be late for your chordotomy.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Nice talking to you, Dr. Gray.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Anyone seen the floor chart on the new admission?
Elizabeth Fallon: You always come in like that, bang the light on?
Dr. Cristina Yang: You're Elizabeth Fallon?
Elizabeth Fallon: What does my chart say?
Dr. Cristina Yang: It says you used to be a nurse here.
Elizabeth Fallon: A scrub nurse.
Dr. Cristina Yang: And that you have abdominal mass consistent with pancreatic cancer?
Elizabeth Fallon: Oh, and you are hoping they're going to give me a whipple.
Dr. Cristina Yang: Pancreatic duodectomy.
Elizabeth Fallon: This hospital sees those one, maybe, once every six months.
Elizabeth Fallon: That's why you got here at 4.30, huh?
Unknown / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): 4.
Cristina Yang / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Grab my chart for anybody else could see it.
Cristina Yang / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Press Dr. Burke with your pre-round exam so you'd be the logical intern for him to ask to scrub in.
Nurse Fallon / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): I know all the tricks, Doctor.
Nurse Fallon / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Yang.
Dr. Cristina Yang: Christina Yang.
Elizabeth Fallon: I'll call you Christina.
Elizabeth Fallon: You call me Nurse Fallon.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): Mr. Humphrey?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): Sorry to wake you.
Mr. Humphrey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Come on.
Mr. Humphrey: What time is it?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): Ten after five.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): I'm sorry, I just need to do a brief exam.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): If you could sit up for one moment.
Mr. Humphrey: Thanks.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): This might be a little bit cold, so just take a deep breath.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): If you could just take a deep breath.
Mr. Humphrey: You're not a doctor.
Dr. Isobel Stevens: I'm Dr. Stevens, but you can call me Izzy.
Dr. Isobel Stevens: I'll be helping Dr. Bailey with your biopsy this morning.
Mr. Humphrey: No, I don't think so, no.
Dr. Isobel Stevens: Mr. Humphrey, this will just take a moment.
Mr. Humphrey: Give me Dr. Bailey or Dr. Victor.
Dr. Isobel Stevens: I just need to do a briefing.
Mr. Humphrey: You don't need to do anything.
Mr. Humphrey: Is this you?
Dr. Isobel Stevens: Huh?
Mr. Humphrey: It is, isn't it?
Mr. Humphrey: You know, get out of my room.
Dr. Isobel Stevens: Mr. Humphrey.
Mr. Humphrey: Get out of my room.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): There need to be some rules.
George O'Malley / Zona (PVM): So what?
George O'Malley / Zona (PVM): We can walk around in our underwear on alternate Tuesdays?
Alex Karev / Mr. Humphrey OR Zona (PVM): Or you could see bras but not panties?
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Humphrey OR Zona (PVM): Or are you talking Amish rules?
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey OR Zona OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Because if you think you're going to get Izzy to cover herself from neck to ankle... The amount of flesh exposed is not the point.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): You have to do something.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): It's your house.
Dr. Meredith Grey: It's my mother's house.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Meredith.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Do you like Izzy?
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Is that what this is about?
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Do you have a crush on Izzy?
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Izzy?
George O'Malley / Mr. Humphrey OR Zona (PVM): No, I don't like Izzy.
George O'Malley / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): No.
George O'Malley / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): She's not the one I'm attracted to.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Not the one, so there's a one.
George O'Malley / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): This is not.
George O'Malley / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Look, there just have to be some rules.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: O'Malley, Gray, get Karim, head down to trauma.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Shepard needs you.
George O'Malley / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Shepard's in surgery.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: He got pulled before he could start.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): Those look like... Nails.
Jorge Cruz: I can't see my head.
Meredith Grey / Jorge Cruz (PVM): Oh, my god.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Jorge Cruz OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): He's conscious, but blind.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Read deeply, George.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: You won't pass out.
Bailey / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Which four milligrams of morphine titrate up to 10?
Bailey / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): If you have to, you know what?
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): I don't want him to move.
Jorge Cruz: I can't see.
Meredith Grey / Zona (PVM): It's okay.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Mr. Humphrey OR Zona OR Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): We need you to be very still, Mr. Cruz.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey OR Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Jorge Cruz.
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Humphrey OR Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): He tripped and fell down a flight of stairs holding a nail gun.
Alex Karev / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Sick.
George O'Malley / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): So now he managed an incendiary blood vessel.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Not so much a miracle.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Optic nerve's been affected.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Do you feel this on his right side?
Alex Karev / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Zona (PVM): What's our immediate concern?
Izzie Stevens / Zona (PVM): Infection.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Right.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): I want to be pulling these nails out in the next half hour.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): I need a CT.
George O'Malley / Zona OR Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): CTs are down.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Isobel Stevens OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): What?
Izzie Stevens / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): They exchanged them out last night.
George O'Malley / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Computers crashed, have them back up by one.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): So typical.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Mr. Humphrey (PVM): So what are the options?
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): An MRI.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): No.
Alex Karev / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Brilliant.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): The man's got nails in his head.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Let's put them in a giant magnet.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Mr. Humphrey (PVM): You want films from three access points and a C-Arm insertion.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Excellent.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): You guys dig up research and find out if this has ever happened before.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Go.
Jorge Cruz: My wife?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Zona (PVM): She's on her way.
Alex Karev / Mr. Humphrey OR Zona (PVM): Your life is on the way, Mr. Cruz.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Mr. Humphrey OR Zona (PVM): Stay with him, keep him calm, and look for changes.
Jorge Cruz: I can't see.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): 55-year-old woman with adenocarcinoma of the pancreas has had radiation therapy to reduce the tumor load.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Rates for abdominal pain, 3 out of 10.
Intern (possibly George O'Malley or Cristina Yang) / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Positive, nausea, but no vomiting.
Intern (possibly George O'Malley or Cristina Yang) / Dr. Preston Burke OR Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Diarrhea, hematochesia, melina, ephedra with T-max 37.2 and stable vital signs.
Intern (possibly George O'Malley or Cristina Yang) / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Lab significant for a total billy of 7 and elevated liver enzymes.
Attending Physician (possibly Dr. Burke or Dr. Bailey) / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): Thank you.
Attending Physician (possibly Dr. Burke or Dr. Bailey) / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Dr. Yang.
Liz (Scrub Nurse) / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Aggressive little witch, isn't she?
Liz (Scrub Nurse) / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): She stole my chart during pre-round so she could scrub it on my surgery.
Liz (Scrub Nurse) / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): She's hoping for a whipple.
Attending Surgeon (possibly Dr. Burke or Dr. Bailey) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Actually, Liz, I was going to give you to Meredith Gray.
Liz (Scrub Nurse) / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Ellis' daughter?
Attending Surgeon (possibly Dr. Burke or Dr. Bailey) / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Yeah, she's an intern this year.
Attending Surgeon (possibly Dr. Burke or Dr. Bailey) / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Thought you'd have something to talk about.
Liz (Scrub Nurse) / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Oh, I doubt that.
Liz (Scrub Nurse) / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): I was Ellis' scrub nurse for 18 years, practically lived with that woman.
Liz (Scrub Nurse) / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): I didn't meet that daughter once.
Attending Surgeon (possibly Dr. Burke or Dr. Bailey) / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Well, anyway, Shepard has her on a guy with the nails in his head.
Liz (Scrub Nurse) / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): There's a guy with nails in his head?
Attending Surgeon (possibly Dr. Burke or Dr. Bailey) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Seven of them.
Attending Surgeon (possibly Dr. Burke or Dr. Bailey) / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Shot himself in the head with a nail gun.
Liz (Scrub Nurse) / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Nail?
Liz (Scrub Nurse) / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Nails?
Attending Surgeon (possibly Dr. Burke or Dr. Bailey) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): 16 pennies.
Attending Surgeon (possibly Dr. Burke or Dr. Bailey) / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): 3 and 1 half inches long.
Liz (Scrub Nurse) / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Wait, and he's still alive?
Attending Surgeon (possibly Dr. Burke or Dr. Bailey) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Fully conscious.
Attending Surgeon (possibly Dr. Burke or Dr. Bailey) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Should be a pretty interesting surgery.
Attending Surgeon (possibly Dr. Burke or Dr. Bailey) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): But I guess you've got the whipple.
Attending Surgeon (possibly Dr. Burke or Dr. Bailey) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I'm going to need a full blood workup and abdominal CT.
Intern (possibly Cristina Yang or George O'Malley) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): CT's a dime this morning.
Attending Surgeon (possibly Dr. Burke or Dr. Bailey) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Then an MRI.
Attending Surgeon (possibly Dr. Burke or Dr. Bailey) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): She needs an enema and ERCP for a stent and brush biopsy this afternoon.
Attending Surgeon (possibly Dr. Burke or Dr. Bailey) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Take care of her.
Liz (Scrub Nurse) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Liz, there's an institution around here.
Attending Surgeon (possibly Dr. Burke or Dr. Bailey) / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Good call, Doctor.
Attending Surgeon (possibly Dr. Burke or Dr. Bailey) / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Ray's got the human two by four, and you have the institution in need of an enema.
Izzie Stevens / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): You'd say your health's been good recently?
Mr. Humphrey / Jorge Cruz (PVM): Maybe some headaches.
Mr. Humphrey / Jorge Cruz (PVM): Nothing compared to now.
Mr. Humphrey / Jorge Cruz (PVM): Sona, that's my wife, Sona, she'll say, why you think they call it a gun, moron?
Mr. Humphrey / Jorge Cruz (PVM): She hates the damn things.
Izzie Stevens / Zona (PVM): With good reason.
Sona / Zona (PVM): Baby?
Mr. Humphrey / Zona OR Zona OR Jorge Cruz (PVM): Sona.
Unknown (possibly a nurse or intern) / Jorge Cruz (PVM): Hey, man.
Sona / Zona (PVM): You are in so much trouble.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Alex Karev OR Zona OR Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Get a history from him before you scrub in.
Izzie Stevens / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Okay.
Mr. Humphrey / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): Thank you.
Unknown (possibly a doctor or intern) / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): 23.
Unknown (possibly a doctor or intern) / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): People have been accidentally shot in the head with nails 23 times.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): One of those attempts at suicide doesn't count.
George O'Malley / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Oh, so he pointed a nail gun at his head on purpose?
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): That makes me feel better.
Alex Karev / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): So, uh, Gray and Stevens really walk around in their underwear?
George O'Malley / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): I mean, not all the time.
George O'Malley / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): I mean, some of the time, you know, but not all the time.
Alex Karev / Dr. Alex Karev OR Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Sexy underwear?
George O'Malley / Dr. Isobel Stevens OR Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Yeah, I mean... And they just, uh, let you look at them?
George O'Malley / Dr. Isobel Stevens OR Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Well, uh, yeah.
Alex Karev / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Like sisters?
George O'Malley / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): No, what?
George O'Malley / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Not like sisters.
George O'Malley / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): No, I don't think of them as sisters.
Alex Karev / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): But they're not coming on to you.
George O'Malley / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Not exactly.
Alex Karev / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): They don't expect you to do anything.
George O'Malley / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): No.
Alex Karev / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): But?
George O'Malley / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Like sisters.
George O'Malley / Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Just like sisters.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Is he prepped?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): I think they're doing it right now.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You think?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): He's having a prostate biopsy.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Trust me.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): If you'd been in there, you'd know.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): OK, Mr. Humphrey, we're going to get started.
Mr. Humphrey / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Get her out of here.
Mr. Humphrey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): I want her out of here.
Mr. Humphrey / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Just get her out of here.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Just you go.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Now.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey OR Zona (PVM): Just go now.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Jorge, relax, relax, Mr. Humphrey.
Javi (Jorge's partner) / Zona OR Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Will he be able to see again?
Derek Shepherd / Zona (PVM): We won't know until the nails come out.
Javi (Jorge's partner) / Zona (PVM): Did he tell you he takes photos?
Javi (Jorge's partner) / Zona (PVM): Beautiful photos, says Javi.
Javi (Jorge's partner) / Zona OR Zona OR Zona (PVM): I just got him a new digital camera and now he can't stop, you know?
Javi (Jorge's partner) / Zona (PVM): He always has it out, always taking pictures of me.
Cristina Yang / Zona (PVM): Jorge said he's been having headaches.
Derek Shepherd / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Can you tell me about them?
Derek Shepherd / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Have they been recent?
Javi (Jorge's partner) / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Um, I'm not sure.
Javi (Jorge's partner) / Mr. Humphrey OR Zona (PVM): Maybe the last couple of months.
Derek Shepherd / Zona (PVM): Have you seen him experience any dizziness or disorientation?
Javi (Jorge's partner) / Zona (PVM): Yes, yes, I have.
Derek Shepherd / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): OK.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You want to tell me what that was all about?
Alex Karev / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Nothing.
Alex Karev / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): It was probably just crazy or something.
Hospital Intercom: Dr. Campbell to oncology.
Cristina Yang / Unknown (PVM): Yes.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): Bethany Whisperer.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Isobel Stevens OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): What?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): Bethany Whisperer did a new Bethany Whisperer lingerie ad.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): He saw it in a magazine.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Isobel Stevens OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You got time to pose for a magazine?
Dr. Isobel Stevens: No, the shoot was last year.
Dr. Isobel Stevens: It just came out.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Isobel Stevens OR Dr. Isobel Stevens OR Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): So because he saw you in a thong.
Dr. Isobel Stevens: No, it wasn't a thong.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Isobel Stevens OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Now you're hiding out in the hallway.
Dr. Isobel Stevens: I just think it might be easier if you sign another interview.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Easy is not in your job description.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You are a doctor.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): He is a patient.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): He's your patient.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Biopsy these.
Dr. Preston Burke: If they come back positive, I expect to see you in surgery.
Dr. Preston Burke: Hey, you on this, you understand me?
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Vertiginous or lightheadedness?
Patient: Lightheaded.
Relative of Patient / Zona OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Sometimes he'd have to brace himself to get out of bed.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Could be a million things.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Simple orthostasis.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Isobel Stevens OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): What?
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): What made him fall downstairs with a nail gun?
Patient: He said he tripped.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Just because you hear hoofbeats, don't assume zebras.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Mr. Humphrey OR Zona (PVM): Something caused him to lose consciousness and fall down the stairs.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): He could have a tumor.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Look, I have no idea why this guy is still alive, let alone moving and talking.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Not a clue.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Let's just get him through this before we start digging around for something else.
Unknown / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Shepard.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): 23 cases?
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): One was attempted suicide.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Yeah, that doesn't count.
Ellis Grey / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Talk to me about procedure.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Biggest problems were bleeding and infection, but the odds improved to shorter surgery times.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Bottom line was, get them out quickly and watch for bleeding.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): I got it.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): In other words, I'm on my own.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): You coming?
Alex Karev / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Dude, I don't need an escort.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Go.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Go ahead.
Dr. Richard Webber / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Well, well, well.
Dr. Richard Webber / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Dr. Bethany Whisperer.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): That's so nice.
Patient's Husband / Jorge Cruz OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): She had this thing, red, when we met.
Patient's Husband / Jorge Cruz (PVM): Red car, red dresses, red hats.
Patient's Husband / Jorge Cruz (PVM): Personally, I hated the color.
Patient's Husband / Jorge Cruz (PVM): Too obvious, you know?
Patient's Husband / Jorge Cruz OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): But a couple of years ago, I took her up to the mountains.
Patient's Husband / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): And she was in her red dress.
Patient's Husband / Jorge Cruz OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): And there was this field of red poppies, I think.
Patient's Husband / Jorge Cruz OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): And she jumped out of the car and ran into them and started laughing, laughing at all of the red.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Isobel Stevens OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): The good news is it hasn't spread from his prostate to his lymph nodes.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): With a radical prostatectomy, we could probably get it all.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Isobel Stevens OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Good prognosis.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Spare some nerves, give him a chance at a normal sex life?
Older Male Patient / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): Young puppies like to take chances with cancer.
Older Male Patient / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): Old dogs like me, we do what works.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): Yes, sir, of course.
Older Male Patient / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): We on the schedule tomorrow?
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Uh, 10 AM.
Older Male Patient / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): Good.
Older Male Patient / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): Maybe I can squeeze in a round.
Dr. Preston Burke / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): An ass who deals in asses.
Dr. Preston Burke / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): We call him Limp Harry.
Dr. Preston Burke / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): He never spares the nerves.
Dr. Bailey / Jorge Cruz (PVM): As you can see, the patient has shot seven nails directly into the skull.
Dr. Bailey / Jorge Cruz (PVM): without doing significant damage other than the optic nerve.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): And we may be able to save that.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): The idea is to remove the nails at exactly the angle they entered.
Dr. Bailey / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Any wiggle and we risk doing more damage than when they went in.
George O'Malley / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Where are they?
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Move over.
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): They're just pulling them out.
Alex Karev / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Hey, I heard you got a whipple.
George O'Malley / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Yeah, maybe a whipple.
George O'Malley / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Burke has rung my butt off.
Alex Karev / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Oh, man, look at those films.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): It's Hellraiser.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Shell phone.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): There you go.
George O'Malley / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): There goes the third grade.
Unknown (off-screen or authority figure) / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Dr. Yang.
Unknown (off-screen or authority figure) / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Fisher's sailing for their mission.
Dr. Bailey / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Did you put in the blood work?
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Oh, right before I got here.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Take her to radiology for the MRI.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Beat me when you're done.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You want the Whipple, right?
George O'Malley / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Yeah.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Isobel Stevens OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): Here.
George O'Malley / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): I'm actually out of the grocery money.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Isobel Stevens OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): When are you going?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Isobel Stevens OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Okay, seriously, George, please don't... Yeah, can we not talk about it here?
George O'Malley / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): What, tampons?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Did you not hear a word I said?
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): You're a man, we know.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Talk about shrinking the salamander.
Dr. Meredith Grey: I always divided surgeons into two categories.
Dr. Meredith Grey: Those that remember the name of their patients and those who didn't.
Meredith Grey / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): They all remember their surgeries, of course.
Meredith Grey / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Every damn suture.
Cristina Yang / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): But the good ones remember their names, right?
Meredith Grey / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): I didn't say that.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Now, some of the best ones, you know, distance themselves on purpose.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): They believe that the personal stuff clouds the medicine.
Izzie Stevens / Elizabeth Fallon OR Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Hi, Liz.
Liz's Husband / Elizabeth Fallon OR Elizabeth Fallon OR Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Hey, bud.
Liz / Elizabeth Fallon OR Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): I'm waiting for the blood.
Izzie Stevens / Elizabeth Fallon OR Elizabeth Fallon OR Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): I'm sure this baby can see you.
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Hey, Liz.
Liz / Dr. George O'Malley OR Elizabeth Fallon OR Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Hey.
Izzie Stevens / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): You're looking good.
Liz / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Oh, you liar.
Liz's Husband / Elizabeth Fallon OR Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): How you doing, honey?
Liz / Elizabeth Fallon OR Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Oh, fabulous.
Liz / Elizabeth Fallon OR Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Just fabulous.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Hey, Liz.
Liz / Dr. George O'Malley OR Elizabeth Fallon OR Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Hey.
Alex Karev / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Hey, Liz.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Bleeding?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): It's clean.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): All right.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Way to go, team.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Good job, everybody.
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): Thank you.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): I don't think we made it worse.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): The big question is the optic nerve.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Mr. Humphrey (PVM): We'll know in the morning.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Should I order the MRI?
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): It needs to stabilize.
Dr. Derek Shepherd / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Mr. Humphrey (PVM): We'll do it tomorrow.
Liz / Elizabeth Fallon OR Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Is it over?
Liz's Husband / Elizabeth Fallon OR Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Hey, is it over?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke OR Elizabeth Fallon OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Yeah, it's over.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Hey, does Burke have a Whipple scheduled?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Dr. Burke, I wanted to know if you've seen Nurse Fallon's labs.
Dr. Preston Burke: I have.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): They're getting worse.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): The stent doesn't seem to be helping her jaundice.
Dr. Preston Burke: No.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Should we be doing something?
Dr. Preston Burke: We are.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Oh, I noticed you didn't have the Whipple on the board.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Do you want me to schedule it for you?
Dr. Preston Burke: I want to see the results of her biopsy and have a look at her overnight labs.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Overnight?
Dr. Preston Burke: You're on call, right?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Um, sure.
Dr. Preston Burke: Well, good.
Dr. Preston Burke: Stick with her.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Well, you're doing the surgery, right?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): You're still doing the Whipple?
Dr. Preston Burke: A woman has pancreatic cancer, Dr. Yang.
Dr. Preston Burke: We're going to do something.
Cristina Yang / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Okay.
Elizabeth Fallon / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Kiss the baby for me.
Preston Burke / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Well, get some sleep, Liz.
Elizabeth Fallon / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): OK.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Bye-bye, Liz.
Preston Burke / Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Mr. Humphrey OR Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): See you later.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley OR Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Thanks, Liz.
Elizabeth Fallon / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Bye-bye.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Bye-bye, Liz.
Preston Burke / Zona (PVM): Take care.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Yeah.
Cristina Yang / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Your mom's a bigger woman.
Liz Fallon / Mr. Humphrey OR Zona (PVM): You were her scrub nurse.
Richard Webber / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Liz Fallon, come in.
Liz Fallon / Zona (PVM): Meredith Gray.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Yeah.
Liz Fallon / Zona (PVM): She wanted me to send her regards.
Meredith Grey / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Doesn't sound like her.
Liz Fallon / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Excuse me?
Liz Fallon / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Of Alice Gray, I know.
Liz Fallon / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Didn't have regards for anyone except Ellis Gray.
Liz Fallon / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): But you know that already, don't you?
Liz Fallon / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Where is she now?
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Traveling.
Liz Fallon / Mr. Humphrey OR Elizabeth Fallon OR Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Traveling?
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Yeah.
Liz Fallon / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Huh.
Liz Fallon / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Is she practicing?
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Not so much.
Liz Fallon / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Oh.
Liz Fallon / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Doesn't sound like her either.
Liz Fallon / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): She was all work, just like me.
Liz Fallon / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): She never left the hospital.
Liz Fallon / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): But you know that too, don't you?
Liz Fallon / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Is she well?
Meredith Grey / Zona (PVM): She's fine.
Liz Fallon / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): Good.
Liz Fallon / Zona (PVM): Just wanted to send her regards.
Liz Fallon / Zona (PVM): Take care.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Yeah.
Meredith Grey / Zona (PVM): I think these were taken at the old house.
Liz Fallon / Mr. Humphrey OR Zona OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): There's you and your scrubs.
Liz Fallon / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Who is that?
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): That's dad.
Liz Fallon / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Who?
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Your husband, Thatcher Gray.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey OR Zona (PVM): You called him Thatch.
Lexie Grey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Thatch.
Lexie Grey / Zona (PVM): That's the red wagon he got me for my birthday.
Lexie Grey / Mr. Humphrey OR Zona (PVM): I'm about four years old in this photo.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey OR Zona (PVM): This is your family.
Lexie Grey / Zona (PVM): Sure.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Saw Liz Fallon at the hospital today.
Lexie Grey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Liz.
Lexie Grey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): I love her.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): How is she?
Lexie Grey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Is she still a scrub nurse?
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): She was excellent.
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): I reminded you before you went.
George O'Malley / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): I forgot when I got there.
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): No, no.
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): You were so passive aggressive.
George O'Malley / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Naked.
George O'Malley / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I am naked in the shower.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): Just tampons, George.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): I really needed tampons.
George O'Malley / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): God.
George O'Malley / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): I'm not riding in the same car with him.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Isobel Stevens OR Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Unless you're going like that, you're not riding with me.
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Where are the tampons?
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): He didn't buy them.
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): You didn't buy them?
George O'Malley / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Men don't buy tampons.
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): You know what?
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): You're going to have to get over the man thing, George.
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): We're women.
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): We have vaginas.
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Get used to it.
George O'Malley / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): I am not your sister!
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Grilled cheese again?
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Cold pizza.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Is he awake?
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Even better.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Really?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Let's see.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Hey, how are you this morning?
Elizabeth Fallon: Tell them what color my dress is, Jorge.
Jorge Cruz: I'd know the answer to that even if I couldn't see.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Go ahead and check it out if you like it.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): I'm taking the elevator.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): You take the stairs.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): I was going to anyway.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): Good.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): Hold it.
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): Thank you.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Isobel Stevens OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): What?
Dr. Burke / Mr. Humphrey OR Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): You don't wake a patient like that.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey OR Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): What do I have to do to get through to you?
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Give me some slack.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): I was on call last night.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): I didn't get much sleep.
Dr. Burke / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Oh, stop whining.
Dr. Burke / Elizabeth Fallon OR Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): You'd rather be here and you know it.
Dr. Burke / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): What you got waiting for you at home?
Dr. Burke / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Boyfriend?
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): No.
Dr. Burke / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): A girlfriend?
Dr. Burke / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): A pet?
Dr. Burke / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Family?
Cristina Yang / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): A bed.
Dr. Burke / Elizabeth Fallon OR Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): You got plenty of beds here.
Dr. Burke / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): I don't feel sorry for you.
Dr. Burke / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): This is who we are.
Sona / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): This is our lives.
Jorge Cruz / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): You tell her, Dr. Burke.
George O'Malley / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Excuse me.
Izzie Stevens / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): What's going on?
Izzie Stevens / Elizabeth Fallon OR Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): George, stop.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): We have Bethany Whisperer in our locker room.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh, boy.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I guess they do airbrush out the tattoo, don't they?
Dr. Isobel Stevens: You want to see it?
Dr. Isobel Stevens: You really want to see it?
Dr. Isobel Stevens: Fine.
Dr. Isobel Stevens: Let's look at that tattoo up close and personal, shall we?
Dr. Isobel Stevens: And what are these?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): Oh, my God.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): Breasts.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): How does anybody practice medicine hauling these things around?
Dr. Isobel Stevens: And what have we got back here?
Dr. Isobel Stevens: Let's see if I remember my anatomy.
Dr. Isobel Stevens: Glutes, right?
Dr. Isobel Stevens: Let's study them, shall we?
Dr. Isobel Stevens: Gather around and check out the booty that put Izzy Stevens through med school.
Dr. Isobel Stevens: Have you had enough or should I continue because I have a few more very interesting tattoos?
Dr. Isobel Stevens: You want to call me Dr. Model?
Dr. Isobel Stevens: That's fine.
Dr. Isobel Stevens: Just remember that while you're sitting on 200 grand of student loans, I'm out of debt.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): I'll take her down.
Dr. Burke / Jorge Cruz (PVM): Can you tell me what you had for breakfast on Monday?
Jorge Cruz: Cheese omelet.
Dr. Burke / Jorge Cruz (PVM): And on Sunday.
Dr. Burke / Jorge Cruz (PVM): And on Saturday.
Dr. Burke / Jorge Cruz (PVM): And on Friday.
Jorge Cruz: Sona gets up every morning and makes me a cheese omelet.
Sona: It's the only thing he likes.
Jorge Cruz: It's the only thing you know how to cook.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Okay, well, things look good, but I need Jorge to get an MRI this morning to check for residual bleeding.
Elizabeth Fallon / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): Okay?
Elizabeth Fallon / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): This is who I was.
Elizabeth Fallon / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): It has nothing to do with who I am now.
Elizabeth Fallon / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): I'm a physician, a surgeon, and I am just as qualified as any other intern on this floor.
Elizabeth Fallon / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): So you're just going to have to get over your chauvinist crap and allow me to do my job.
Jorge (Patient) / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): I'm sure you're a very good doctor.
Elizabeth Fallon / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): Then what is your problem?
Jorge (Patient) / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): I fantasized about you.
Jorge (Patient) / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): About the woman in this photo, whoever she is.
Jorge (Patient) / Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): I'm not proud of it, but it's a fact.
Jorge (Patient) / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): Do you know what they're gonna do to me today?
Jorge (Patient) / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): I have cancer.
Jorge (Patient) / Dr. Alex Karev OR Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): and they're gonna lift up my legs and expose me to the world and cut out my prostate and my nerves and effectively neuter me.
Jorge (Patient) / Dr. Alex Karev (PVM): So is it so hard to understand that I don't want the woman who's in that photo to witness... my emasculation?
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Have you seen her overnight labs?
Elizabeth Fallon / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): I have.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Did you check her liver panel?
Elizabeth Fallon / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): They're not good.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): No, they suck.
Elizabeth Fallon / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): She's choking on bile.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): She's jaundiced.
Elizabeth Fallon / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): A very sick woman.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Why haven't you scheduled the Whipple?
Elizabeth Fallon / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Are you her surgeon now?
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): I'm her cruise director pushing her around all day.
Elizabeth Fallon / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): The woman is circling the drain.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): We need to do something.
Elizabeth Fallon / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): I'll take a look at her biopsies.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): What are the biopsies?
Elizabeth Fallon / Dr. Preston Burke OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You know, enough.
Elizabeth Fallon / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): You know, I...
Elizabeth Fallon / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): You know what I think?
Elizabeth Fallon / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): I think you never intended to do the Whipple.
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): I think this entire thing has been bull, and you're behaving like the only reason she's in this hospital is to die.
Cristina Yang / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): There.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): It's a tumor.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Midline of the hypothalamus.
Alex Karev / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Damn.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Best practice?
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Probably to remove the tumor.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Probably because I can't get it all.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Mr. Humphrey (PVM): 99%, but not all of it.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Radiation and chemo, you're looking at maybe five to ten good years.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): You haven't heard the downside.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): See, the tumor is located in the part of your brain where your memory and your personality resides.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): And because of the fuzzy edges of this type of tumor, I have to cut out a lot.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): All right, you stand a good chance of losing your memories, of losing who you are.
Patient's Family Member / Zona (PVM): Is there any other way?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Mr. Humphrey (PVM): The alternative is a gamma or cyber knife treatment with focused radiation.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Mr. Humphrey (PVM): It's less evasive, this little chance of memory loss or him losing himself, but it would only give Jorge maybe three to five years.
Patient's Family Member / Zona (PVM): Three to five years?
Meredith Grey / Dr. Derek Shepherd OR Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): This is an incredibly difficult decision.
Richard Webber / Zona (PVM): I told my mother about you.
Richard Webber / Zona (PVM): She remembers you very well.
Meredith Grey / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Of course she would.
Richard Webber / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Ellis Gray never forgot a thing.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Oh!
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): I'm sorry.
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): It's not really funny.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey OR Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): It's not funny, but... What's her diagnosis?
Meredith Grey / Zona (PVM): Alzheimer's.
Meredith Grey / Zona OR Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Early onset.
Cristina Yang / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): And she doesn't want anyone to know?
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): No.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey OR Zona OR Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): She's in a nursing home, and I'm the only person she'll allow to see her.
Cristina Yang / Elizabeth Fallon OR Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): But if I know Ellis Gray, she made the nursing home sign a contract to that effect.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): You know my mother well.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey OR Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): What a bitch.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): The woman's life was this hospital.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Isobel Stevens OR Mr. Humphrey (PVM): It was her home.
George O'Malley / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): It's a sweet thing for them to do.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): It's a waste of a bed and it's a waste of my time.
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Who are we talking about?
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Miss Fallon.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): They brought her here to die.
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Wouldn't you want them to do the same thing for you?
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): No.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): You know what?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): I'd want the doctors to do everything they could.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): I'd want them to cut me open until the minute I die.
Izzie Stevens / Zona (PVM): Sometimes doing everything can be worse than doing nothing.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey OR Mr. Humphrey (PVM): You are eight feet tall.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Your boobs are perfect.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Your hair is down to there.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): If I were you, I would walk around naked all the time.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): I wouldn't have a job.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): I wouldn't have skills.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): I wouldn't even know how to read.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): I'd just be naked.
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Humphrey OR Zona (PVM): It's makeup.
Izzie Stevens / Zona (PVM): It's retouching.
Cristina Yang / Zona (PVM): You get that we hate you, right?
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Bailey again?
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): You know what?
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Any patient who spanks his doctor's pictures forfeits his rights.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): You're seriously not going to give up the prostatectomy, are you?
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Izzy.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): You know, sometimes it's actually, you know, painful to be around you.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Where the hell have you been?
Dr. Miranda Bailey: When I page, you answer.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: It's not that difficult to understand.
Nurse / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): O'Malley answered his page.
Nurse / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): He's doing your prep.
Hospital Intercom / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Dr. Hammond to OR Room 3.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Isobel Stevens OR Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): If I hear the words Bethany Whisper one more time... I can't.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): Okay?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): I just...
Cristina Yang / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): I can't.
Sona Cruz / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): He doesn't want me in there.
Doctor (possibly Miranda Bailey) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): No, what he wants is to not have cancer.
Doctor (possibly Miranda Bailey) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): What he wants is to be saved.
Doctor (possibly Miranda Bailey) / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You want to stay in the scrub room, that's your choice.
Jorge Cruz / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): All right.
Doctor (possibly Miranda Bailey) / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): We're hands on.
Jorge Cruz / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): I want the surgery.
Doctor (possibly Miranda Bailey) / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): They want you to cut it out?
Jorge Cruz / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): It's their decision.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): They were never gonna operate.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): You could've told me.
Preston Burke / Mr. Humphrey OR Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): What fun would that have been?
Preston Burke / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Think of it as a hazing ritual.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Mr. Humphrey OR Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Well.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Liz, don't talk.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey OR Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Don't talk.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey OR Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Liz?
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Liz, stay.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Liz, stay with me.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Stay with me, Liz.
Elizabeth Fallon: Zona.
Doctor (possibly Miranda Bailey) / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Let's go.
Doctor (possibly Miranda Bailey) / Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Push Effie into actual pain.
Doctor (possibly Miranda Bailey) / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Preston Burke OR Elizabeth Fallon OR Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): Somebody pays work.
Doctor (possibly Miranda Bailey) / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Preston Burke OR Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Okay, go.
Doctor (possibly Miranda Bailey) / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): She's DNI.
Cristina Yang / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): She's DNR.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Do not resuscitate.
Unknown / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Preston Burke (PVM): Dr. Yang.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Come on, people.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Push another epi.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Come on.
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): You need to consider what you'll lose.
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Humphrey OR Zona OR Zona (PVM): What good is five years if he doesn't joke about your omelets and he can't remember seeing you in that red dress?
Zona (Jorge's wife) / Zona OR Zona (PVM): It's still five more years.
Izzie Stevens / Zona (PVM): You don't understand.
Zona: He'll be there, but he won't be Jorge.
Zona: He won't even recognize.
Zona: This is our business.
Zona: You have no idea what this will do to you.
Izzie Stevens / Zona (PVM): Isn't five good years better than 10 bad ones?
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Derek Shepherd (PVM): Meredith, what the hell are you doing?
Dr. Meredith Grey: She needs to understand.
Zona: I do understand.
Zona: You think that I'm being selfish, that I don't want to give him up.
Zona: I don't.
Zona: This is Jorge's decision.
Zona: And if that means 10 bad years for me, fine.
Zona: I'll give him those years, because I will give him whatever he wants.
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Look, I am so sorry, Zona.
Izzie Stevens / Zona OR Mr. Humphrey OR Zona (PVM): Just please forgive her.
Izzie Stevens / Zona OR Mr. Humphrey (PVM): She's an intern.
Zona: And if he doesn't remember me, if he doesn't remember what we are,
Zona: He's still my Horty.
Zona: And I'll remember for us both.
Miranda Bailey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): OK.
Miranda Bailey / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): All right.
Miranda Bailey / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Five, three, one, two.
Dr. Victor / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): What the hell are you two doing?
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): We lost Pulse.
Unknown (likely a doctor or nurse) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): One, two.
Unknown (likely a senior doctor) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Let her go.
Unknown (likely a doctor or nurse) / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Where's that Abby?
Unknown (likely a doctor or nurse) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): She's DNR.
Unknown (likely a senior doctor) / Elizabeth Fallon OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Let her go down.
Unknown (likely a doctor or nurse) / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Three, four, five, one, two.
Unknown (likely a doctor or nurse) / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Do not resuscitate.
Unknown (likely a doctor or nurse) / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): All right.
Unknown (likely a doctor or nurse) / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): It is on her charge.
Unknown (likely a senior doctor) / Elizabeth Fallon OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Let her go down.
Unknown (likely a doctor or nurse) / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Where are they?
Unknown (likely a surgical resident or intern) / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): He's resecting the prostate, coming up on the distal nerve.
Unknown (likely Izzie Stevens) / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): You said I am not your sister.
Unknown (likely Izzie Stevens) / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): Do you feel like I was emasculating you?
Unknown (likely Alex Karev) / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): No.
Unknown (likely Alex Karev) / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm too masculine to be emasculated.
Unknown (likely Izzie Stevens) / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): I'm sorry.
Unknown (likely Alex Karev) / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Guess you put Dr. Model to rest.
Unknown (likely Izzie Stevens) / Dr. Isobel Stevens OR Dr. Miranda Bailey OR Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): Guess I did.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Dr. Victor, I'm sorry, but these are viable nerves.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Isobel Stevens OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): We should save them.
Dr. Victor / Dr. Isobel Stevens OR Mr. Humphrey (PVM): It'll take at least an hour longer, and we might not get it all.
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): I know they call him Limp Harry.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): But his prognosis with chemo is nearly as good, and frankly, if you're worried about missing your tea time, I'd be more than happy to finish.
Dr. Victor / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Dr. Stevens?
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): Can we help you?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): I'm sorry, Dr. Bailey.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): Dr. Victor, I agree with her.
Dr. Victor / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): You just can't...
Cristina Yang / Dr. Isobel Stevens OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You have to save the nerves.
Dr. Victor / Dr. Isobel Stevens OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): What?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): The nerves.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): You have to save them.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Isobel Stevens OR Dr. George O'Malley OR Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Dr. Stevens, I can handle this.
Dr. Isobel Stevens: No, you told me the most important thing is giving the patient what they want.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): What Humphrey wants is his erection.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): She's yours.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Isobel Stevens (PVM): You get her out.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Can't do that, sir.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You know how these young puppies are.
Miranda Bailey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): I'm going to tell Richard about both of you.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): You do that.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): In the meantime, let's pretend it's you on this table and give this a try.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey OR Elizabeth Fallon (PVM): Look me in the eye and tell me you don't find me attractive.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Look me in the heart and tell me you won't go.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Look me in the eye and promise no loves like I love.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): Look me in the heart and I'm very broken.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. George O'Malley (PVM): You ever called one?
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Time of death, 1143.
Dr. Meredith Grey: I wish there were a rule book for intimacy.
Dr. Meredith Grey: Some kind of a guide that could tell you when you've crossed the line.
Dr. Meredith Grey: It would be nice if you could see it coming.
Izzie Stevens / Zona OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I'll get it.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): Better go.
Dr. Meredith Grey: But I don't know how you'd fit in on a map.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Miranda Bailey (PVM): Of course.
Dr. Miranda Bailey: Now, you know every time he gets a rise, he'll be thinking of you.
Miranda Bailey / Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): You take it where you can get it.
Miranda Bailey / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Meredith Grey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): And keep it as long as you can.
Dr. Meredith Grey: And as for rules...
Dr. Meredith Grey: Better not be using my toothbrush.
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Humphrey OR Dr. Meredith Grey (PVM): I'm not.
Dr. Meredith Grey: Maybe there are none.
Dr. Meredith Grey: Maybe the rules of intimacy are something you have to define for yourself.
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Humphrey (PVM): Good night.