What are you doing?
Eating cereal.
I got us a chicken for dinner.
Chicken? Seriously?
You're not gonna be hungry now.
You're doing it all
wrong, again, as usual.
I'm not. I'm cutting from
the media steinum out.
You can't see the media
steinum without your glasses.
Damn. Where are my glasses?
No, put it down. Put it down.
Right here. Right here.
Move.
What would I do without you?
Starve.
Damsel in distress.
Come on.
Put her on a monitor, order a
portable chest. Gonna cut your top.
Between my ninth and
tenth intercostal spaces.
No hemo or pneumothorax,
vitals are stable. Pull it.
- I wouldn't.
- Mind your business.
- Who is this guy?
- Get this thing out of me.
I screwed up in
front of the chief.
I messed up a suture and now he's
looking at me like I am number 12.
Mer, please, no one gets
to see me like this. OK?
Yang! What the hell
happened? Get her on a monitor,
- order a portable chest...
- I did.
- Check her respiratory funct...
- I did. See?
Breath sounds clear and equal.
Quiet. What would you
advise as course of treatment?
We leave it in until we get
the chest X-ray and CT back.
- I'm fine.
- What about infection? This is melting
- dirty roof water
into her body.
- Pull it out!
Leave it. You get stabbed in the
chest, lucky enough to still be breathing,
you leave the knife in until you
figure out what's going on. Leave it.
- Take it out.
- Leave it.
Since you know so much,
teach your interns to treat you.
This is an opportunity
to get back to the basics.
I need to check
on Vincent Kenner.
Kenner is your
responsibility now.
Bear in mind he is my patient,
and I am not about to lose
another trauma case
today. Keep that man alive.
Can I get a word
with you, Dr. Hunt?
Think you'll be able
to restore her memory?
I was able to suction blood
and remove the pressure.
Hopeful. Not
certain, but hopeful.
Fifteen blade, please. Ow!
- Something wrong, Dr. Shepherd?
- Oh, my God.
Dr. Hahn asked
about teaching before.
When you get a surgeon a
blade, make sure it's handle first.
Suction the bleeders while
I clean and get a glove.
- He's really gonna be OK?
- Except for his voice.
His abdomen's definitely
tender. He needs another CT.
Michael, the insurance,
it's a mistake, right?
It's gotta be a mistake. Write down
a name and a number and I'll fix it.
Everything will be fine, right?
Everything's gonna be fine?
Maybe later would be better.
Sarabeth, come on, honey.
- What's going on?
- We're going ahead
with the freezing.
Without my consent?
No, I don't think so.
Wanna be the doctor who
doesn't give his all to keep
- a man from being
wheelchair-bound?
- Get out!
Don't take orders
from civilians.
- You arrogant...
- Shepherd.
Now this patient is
stable, he may never walk.
If you try this, he could throw a
clot, have organ failure and die.
We're going ahead
with the freezing.
Ever since this morning, you've
been pissing on everything with a pulse
trying to prove
you're not number 12.
And you're not.
But right now, with this
decision, you act like number 12.
Good luck with the
patient, Dr. Torres.
The chief's under the spell of
some insane man in camouflage.
He saved my patient's life. He'll
never talk again but, still, life saved.
What happened to your hand?
Scalpel. Rose. Not intentional.
She's a dead mouse
on the kitchen floor.
At some point you gotta
pick it up and throw it away.
- Want me to look?
- Mer's gonna
take care of it.
I'm a renowned plastic surgeon.
- Grey's a resident.
- She gives me sex.
Especially when I'm wounded.
Oh! Oh...
Is this positioned right?
If I'm getting a mammogram.
Lower, to the right.
- Two, what are you doing?
- Draping so your parts
are safe.
Get away from my parts.
Oh. Gentle, gentle, gentle.
- How are you doing?
- Please take my films
'cause my interns are idiots!
How's Mr. Kenner?
- Stable.
- You cannot let him die.
- I'm doing my best, hold still.
- I am. Just shoot it.
Hold still because I
wanna ask you a question.
What?
Did you mean what you
said about me and Derek?
Well, this is not
fair. I'm impaled.
I know I talk about it too much.
I've gone soft and gooey and disgusting
and if I had to listen, I'd puke too.
But you said what you said
because you were mad, right?
Not because you meant it?
Just take my X-ray and...
It doesn't matter what I say.
Of course it matters
what you say!
Of course it matters.
You stop... Oh!
Stop taking my picture,
and take my picture!
Anna.
Are you feeling OK?
Her world is about to fall
apart and she has no idea.
It's all my fault.
What should I do?
I know I'm a terrible
person, but what should I do?
She should hear it from you.
You're her best friend. Even if it's
the most terrible thing in the world...
you should tell her.
Hey.
Callie's gonna freeze her
patient. Wanna go check it out?
Hello? Alex? Why
are you ignoring me?
I'm hoping if I wait long enough
you'll be as annoyed by the sound
of your voice as I am and shut up.
OK... Did I do something?
- You know what you did.
- No. I don't.
- Alex, just tell me,
what did I do?
- Shut up.
I had a bad night
and cried like a girl.
I'm over it. You
need to get over it too.
That chill you'll
feel is cold saline
rushing through your veins to
lower your core body temperature.
And if it works, I walk?
If it works, the hope
is that you walk.
Wow... OK...
I'm getting cold.
His temp's still 96.8. Shall
we lay another cooling blanket?
Up to you, Dr. Torres,
you're taking point.
That's what the chief of a
number one teaching hospital does,
he hand picks talented surgeons and
lets them take point. Right, Dr. Bailey?
- Couldn't agree more.
- Warm and toasty's
what I'm feelin'.
His pulse is falling.
Are you sure?
- Down to 52.
- It's normal for his pulse to fall.
How much longer do we got?
Not too much longer.
You're doing great.
- Keep thinking
warm and toasty.
- OK. I'm trying.
Good.
Number 12, my ass.
You wanna hear
how I cut my hand?
It's a good story.
I am not sure moving in
together is a good idea.
OK. Fine.
- Fine? What does that mean?
- It means that I know you.
- Didn't believe
I'd let you move in?
- I believe you believe it.
Look, I'm gonna move
very slowly. Baby steps.
No sudden moves. You're
like a deer in the woods.
OK, I built the
house of candles.
It's unprecedented in
the Meredith Chronicles.
- Fine. Let's move in together.
- Fine.
Unless you wanna go
ahead and get married.
Gotcha. Wanna know
where I learned that?
Goes with the story
of how I cut my hand.
What did you say to Alex?
I... I didn't say anything.
I just said that I think it's nice
that you two are friendly again.
Why can't you mind your own
business? I should have never told you.
Can't keep anything to
yourself unless it's for Cristina.
Izzie.
- Marriage?
- Not funny.
Dr. Bailey.
- Yeah?
- Mr. Briar's abdomen
is more tender.
I know I'm supposed to get a CT,
but if we start the surgery after midnight
he's not covered and we're
bankrupting him. I say we skip the CT.
You say? You say? No,
you don't say. You ask.
And the answer is we don't skimp on
medicine to save money. Get the CT.
Doing great. Giving you more sedative
and a paralytic to stop your shivering.
OK. OK.
- We'll need to intubate, Bailey.
- - Coming down.
One, two and three.
And down.
He's down to 90 degrees.
I think that's too low.
- Is that too low?
- You did all the research.
I think it's too low.
- Oh, God.
- OK, so, what now?
Is this going to resolve? Did they
recommend lido or amiodarone?
Dr. Torres?!
- Dr. Torres?
- He's
barely got a pulse.
Uh, should we do CPR?
No! Let's try to avoid jostling
Shepherd's spinal decompression
unless absolutely necessary.
- Crap.
- His heart is likely to stop.
- Soon. What are you
gonna do, Torres?
- I don't know.
I don't know.
How is he?
Given him medication to
keep his blood pressure up,
but Betty's husband is not as
stable as we'd like him to be.
They're freezing Phillip.
Freezing him.
To try to help him
walk again. I don't...
They explained it
to me very well...
And Betty's having
surgery on her brain.
And poor Vincent here
is barely hanging on.
- And Michael...
- It's all right.
We'll survive. We always do.
I wish he would just look at me.
Sarabeth...
Michael lost his job
eight months ago.
- What?
- The firm let him go.
He just...
He couldn't bring
himself to tell you.
He just felt like
such a failure.
What...? I don't...
Why do you... How
do you know this?
He told you.
Sarabeth...
Anna...
Have you been sleeping
with my husband?
- I'm sorry...
- He's in V-fib. Code blue!
Get them out of here, please.
You started him on ECMO? You're
taking out his blood and replacing it?
It was the only thing to do.
We don't want to jostle his spine.
This'll give his heart rest.
We need you to monitor him until we
get him back on. Now are you in or not?
I sent Michael down for the CT.
I was hoping we could start the
surgery. Get him in under the wire.
But it's almost midnight, so...
It doesn't matter, I
don't care. I don't.
Do you know anything
about Betty's husband?
He... I think he was dying.
Have you heard anything?
No, I can find out.
Why do men cheat?
My husband slept with my friend.
He lost his job, and then
he slept with my friend,
all the while telling
me he loves me.
Why?
Maybe he was low.
He was down and he didn't
want you to see him like that.
In pain. Weak. As
less than a man.
He has his pride
so he turned away.
It's not right, but it...
It doesn't mean he
doesn't care about you.
I swear it doesn't.
♪ And I told you to be patient ♪
♪ And I told you to be fine ♪
♪ And I told you to be... ♪
- All right, we all ready to wean?
- - Let's do it.
It looks like he's tachycardic.
Should we shock him?
Give him adenosine?
Normally I'd say yes,
but this man's an ice cube.
Torres, in any of your research, was
there anything to suggest what to do?
I mean, um... I think
I messed up here.
I don't... I don't know. Maybe
he would've been fine on his own.
- Maybe...
- All right, look at me. Look at me.
Focus. You're trying something
new. Nothing wrong with new.
Breaking new ground, pushing
boundaries comes with the job.
So, Dr. Torres, take a breath,
stop panicking and just tell
us. What did your research say?
My research showed that...
That arrhythmias can
occur at a certain threshold.
His appears to be between
- 91.5 and 92 degrees.
- He's around 90 right now.
We could use the ECMO
to help bring him back up.
Yes, but not too quickly because
that can cause problems of its own.
All right, looks like we
have some warming to do.
What do you see?
Uh, it kinda looks
like it's hitting nothing.
Oh. It looks like it's hitting
nothing because it's hitting nothing!
- So what does that mean?
- What do you mean,
"What does that mean?" Don't
you know how to read an X-ray?
- You always read them.
- Oh, get out.
All of you just get out and
find me someone with a brain.
Those your interns?
Seem pretty scared of you.
I am not scary.
What are you doing?
- That's my icicle.
- Yeah.
You took out my icicle.
I didn't give you
permission to do that.
So?
Cristina.
He died.
- Patient still alive?
- He's stable.
Let some soldier talk you into
something that could've killed a man.
- He deserved the chance.
- No way of knowing
- if it helped or hurt.
- He deserved a chance.
He deserved the best, the most
that this hospital could give him.
I've let a lot of things slide
over the past few years.
I've been...
- soft - This was not
about you being soft.
I think it's the fact that Meredith is
here, that Ellis's daughter is here.
Chief...
Vincent Kenner.
We gave him 31 units of
blood, fresh frozen plasma,
multiple liters of LR... We
did everything we knew to do,
we couldn't bring him back.
You don't know
how to do anything.
None of you.
You're halfway through
your second year of residency,
and you walk around here like
it's your God-given right to be here.
Well, it is not,
Dr. Grey, I assure you.
You are here because I allow it.
You are here to do what I say.
And the one thing I asked you to do...
- You can't even save...
- Richard!
We can't save everybody.
We should try harder.
♪ I'm sure we'll grow ♪
♪ But we'll never bloom again ♪
Michael, Sarabeth is here.
He's a little tired. The CT showed
the hematoma's getting worse,
so Dr. Bailey and I will be
taking him down to the OR soon.
But he wrote you this letter.
I'm not interested.
"Sarabeth."
Sorry. That wasn't
me, that was the letter.
"I know you hate me."
Again, not me. The letter.
I'm just gonna read.
Um... "I know you
hate me right now.
And you have every right to.
I betrayed you. I
betrayed our marriage.
But I had lost my job and I couldn't
tell you, so I told Anna instead,
which was wrong and stupid.
I've wanted to tell you a million times.
And let you know how truly sorry I am.
But now I have no voice,
so I'm begging you, please,
if you could just listen with
your heart..." That is so poetic.
That was me, sorry,
not him... Sorry.
"If you could just
listen with your heart
when I tell you that I know
you can't forgive me right now,
but I'm gonna do everything in
my power to make it up to you.
But no matter what happens,
no matter what you decide to do...
I'm going to love you
until the end of time."
That's it. I'm done talking. Well,
he's done. He's done. The End.
♪ How my thoughts
They spin me round ♪
They let me down ♪
♪ How my thoughts
They spin me round... ♪
Betty?
She's not awake, but I
can take you to see her.
- And her memory?
- We don't know yet.
Oh, no. Oh, please don't say it.
- I'm sorry, Vincent...
- Oh, God.
- Oh, God, no.
- Very sorry.
- Sarabeth...
- Don't, don't, don't. Just... don't.
Sarabeth...
Vincent's dead and Betty...
We don't know if
she's gonna be OK,
- and Phil and Michael.
- Don't you mention
his name to me.
Sarabeth.
More bad things have
happened to us today
than have ever happened before.
We've been blessed. Until today.
I took it for it granted.
I took you for granted.
We've been friends for 50 years.
Ever since we were little girls.
And I made one
awful, awful mistake.
- But I need my best friend.
- You slept with my husband...
- Please...
- I'm going to go see Betty.
I'm gonna see my friend.
♪ Then there's you ♪
♪ Then there's you... ♪
Sorry about teasing Alex.
I forgive you.
♪ You know I know
a bit too much... ♪
Tell me about trauma surgery.
Trauma? Quick and dirty.
No time to make things
pretty, and no time for mistakes.
Drop your pants. You
need a shot of cefazolin I-M.
No time for mistakes, huh?
So, what, you don't
make mistakes?
I make mistakes, people die.
I'm the best surgical
resident in my program, and...
Today I killed a man
because I couldn't do a stitch.
In the field, you do what you
can. Work with what you have.
It's about somethings, not being
the best. It's about saving lives.
I make mistakes. Guys
die by my hand, good guys.
Guys who are fighting
for their country in a desert.
And I don't know
everything. Nobody does.
So I make mistakes. And I learn.
And the next time I don't
make that mistake again,
so the next guy,
that guy? He lives.
Mistakes are how you learn.
Hi, Betty. How are you feeling?
My head...
hurts.
What's going on?
Betty, you and Vincent
were in a car accident.
Vincent... I'm so
sorry. He didn't make it.
No, no, please. No.
No... He's in the other car,
he's gonna be here any minute.
♪ Today you're gonna leave
Just like you did the day before ♪
Oh, my head...
♪ You disappear
into the corner store ♪
It hurts.
What happened?
♪ I could swear that I saw you ♪
♪ Slip out the back door ♪
Well, you look pretty stable,
which is good because I can't let you
go into your next surgery until
you're feeling strong and stable, OK?
It happens, people
make mistakes.
They sleep with the wrong
person and they hide it,
but if you ask me it's the part
that comes after that matters,
the part where
you make it right.
I think you're off
to a good start.
- ♪ Stay ♪
Karev. Michael Briar
ready for his ex-lap?
- He was ready an hour ago.
- And I'm ready now. Book the OR.
Fine.
- Dr. Karev,
what time is it?
- It's tomorrow.
His insurance expired.
- I'm sorry about the hand.
- These things happen.
Not to me they don't.
Or they didn't before
you existed for me.
Before you existed, I was good.
Every doctor wanted
me in their OR.
I was known as a
damn good scrub nurse.
And now I'm the crazy
girl out of Fatal Attraction
who goes around
stabbing surgeons.
Sorry.
I'm so... I'm sorry.
There's an opening in peds. I
start on their service tomorrow.
Again. Very sorry
about your hand.
What's...
What am I doing here?
Where's Vincent? Did
something happen?
I can't... I can't
tell her anymore.
- I won't.
- I know.
Why don't you two take a break.
- Check on things.
- I don't want her
to be alone.
I'll sit with her, I don't mind.
Sarabeth, Anna.
Am I in a hospital?
Oh, honey... There's
been an accident.
Where's Vincent? Is he OK?
Your husband is on his
way, he'll be here any minute.
- He's on his way now?
- Yes.
- Oh.
- He's just around
the corner.
If you watch the door,
you'll see him any minute.
- You'll see him.
- Oh, good, he's...
- He's on his way?
- He's on his way.
- Around the corner?
- Yes. Around the corner.
♪ Say you're sorry
That face of an angel ♪
♪ Comes out just when you... ♪
It's better for her.
Thank you.
♪ As I paced back
and forth all this time ♪
♪ 'Cause I honestly
believed in you ♪
Come on, let's go
check on our husbands.
♪ Holding on The days drag on ♪
♪ Stupid girl, I should have
known I should have known ♪
♪ That I'm not a princess
This ain't a fairy tale... ♪
Karev, I think
that clock is wrong.
I know it says 2:30am,
but I'm pretty sure it's
actually only 11:58pm.
- Can you fix it, please?
- Set it back?
Set it back.
It's important that the official
hospital record shows the right time.
And the insurance
company needs it too.
And I say it's only 11:58pm.
♪ Baby, I was naive ♪
♪ Got lost in your eyes and
never really had a chance ♪
Scalpel.
♪ I had so many dreams
about you and me ♪
♪ Happy endings Now I know ♪
♪ I'm not a princess ♪
You know, you'd
be good in the field.
Now you've got this
battle scar, you'd fit right in.
- Right.
- I'm serious.
You should ditch this
place, go for the adventure.
You telling me this place
gives you a rush, a high?
Yeah. Yeah, it does.
Dr. Hunt, there you are.
How's the gash on that leg?
Uh, Dr. Yang took good care
of me. Excellent care of me.
I made a few calls. They speak very
highly of you at Maryland Shock Trauma.
I also heard a story that
you constructed an OR table
from a exploded humvee in
the middle of the desert. True?
Had to be innovative in
the middle of the desert.
Have to be
innovative everywhere.
How would you
like a job, Dr. Hunt?
Uh, appreciate the offer, but
I'm due to go back to the sandpit.
Finish my tour.
Well, good luck to you.
♪ I'm gonna find
someone someday ♪
♪ Who might actually
treat me well ♪
♪ This is a big world
That was a small town ♪
♪ There in my rearview... ♪
What?
♪ Disappearing now ♪
♪ And it's too late for
you and your white horse ♪
♪ Now it's too late for
♪ To catch me now ♪
I... I don't even know you.
So?
♪ Try and catch me now ♪
♪ It's too late ♪
♪ To catch me now ♪
It might've been the
hypothermia treatment.
- Or my surgical skills.
- We'll never know.
What's going on?
Phillip can wiggle his toes.
Say it.
- Don't make me say it.
- Please? Say it. Say it for me.
Even though it's
technically not true yet.
We made a man walk.
- We made a man walk.
- We made a man walk!
What a nice way to wake up.
Did you sleep with Meredith?
Yeah, I did.
Why?
I... I mean... Sorry.
Were you in love with her?
Thought I was.
But I was too
scared to admit it.
I did know that she
did not like me that way,
and I did it anyway.
And I shouldn't have because...
I'm...
Besides just
being so selfish, I...
You know, take advantage of her
that way, to want her to want me like that
when clearly she...
Like I said, I made
mistakes the last year,
but I'm trying to
get back on track.
- I gotta do that by myself.
- The only reason I...
I wanted to help...
is because I feel like
you and I are more
than just roommates.
We are more than just roommates.
We are?
Yeah, we're friends. I mean, right now,
you're probably one of my best friends.
Best friend.
I'm not an experimenter.
I don't like to experiment.
But then you showed
up, and we did it together,
and the experiment
was kind of a success.
Oh.
Oh!
Look, I've never
done this before.
I... I've never kissed a girl.
I'm not sure I even
like kissing girls.
I don't, actually,
I just...
like kissing one girl.
You.
I don't have anything
to compare it with.
I... You're the only
woman I've ever kissed.
- So you're freaking out too?
- A lot of therapy time.
I don't do therapy.
I just get all... Ah!
And then I get
all clingy, and...
OK, you don't need
to know that yet.
So...
Does this... This kind of
makes us virgins, doesn't it?
I guess, in a way, it does.
Virgins.
Hey, we can be scared together.
Kind of virgins, and, yeah,
we can be scared together.
- OK?
- Yeah. Thanks.
You said Derek and I
would never make it.
And then I was karmically
impaled for saying it.
But you're right.
People don't have
happily ever afters,
people barely have ever afters.
So why would Derek
and I be any different?
Mer. Why do you
care what I think?
Because you're my person.
And if I'm going to do this
with him, be whole and healthy.
Be a warm, gooey person
who lives with a boy...
I need you. I need you on board.
I need you to cheer me on.
Because you're the
only one who knows me...
darkly.
Really knows me.
I need you to pretend that I can
do this, even if you don't believe.
Because if you abandon
me now I will never make it.
I'll never get my happy ending,
- and that's just...
- Life.
I'm saying please here.
I think you and
Derek will make it.
You'll make it work.
Are you just telling
me what I want to hear?
I am your person.
I'm on your side.
Once upon a time,
happily ever after.
The stories we tell
are the stuff of dreams.
♪ So if another door closes ♪
♪ I hope you see
the window opening ♪
Fairy tales don't come true.
♪ Don't waste your
days Life slips away ♪
See? I told you I would
show you my dress.
You look better than a bride.
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Can't you see we're
all crashing in slo-mo ♪
♪ Holding to this
wheel we know ♪
♪ What's the use? Don't
want to be sleeping too long ♪
♪ Why can't we
try to fly ourselves ♪
♪ back to an old skin? ♪
♪ Making do is no way to live ♪
♪ What's the use? ♪
♪ We're only here
then we're gone ♪
♪ Gone, gone ♪
Reality is much stormier.
♪ So if another door closes ♪
♪ I hope you feel the window ♪
♪ Opening ♪
Much murkier.
♪ As people hurrying
down the lines ♪
♪ Don't waste your
days Life slips away ♪
Much scarier.
♪ Like butter from a knife ♪
Listen up, people!
Listen up.
We used to be the best
surgical program in the West.
An upstart program
that no one ever heard of
that blew everyone
out the water.
And then, overnight, we got old,
entrenched and sloppy,
just like everyone else.
We've been resting
on our laurels.
You have all been failing.
Failing to take initiative, failing
to ask the tough questions.
Failing to practice your skills.
Failing to give opportunity
to practice skills.
And I let it happen.
So you have not
failed, we have failed.
Well, it stops.
And it stops now.
People sliding over general surgery
as though they'll never see anything,
but a heart or a brain through
the course of their career.
As though blood from the heart doesn't
make its way through the whole body.
Or the nerves don't
travel past the brain stem.
It's shoddy teaching, and it
makes for shoddy surgeons.
We've failed.
Get it? We all have.
And it stops now.
The surgical training protocol
is officially changing, people.
The bar has been raised.
Consider yourself on notice.
Reality. It's so much
more interesting
than living happily ever after.