What happened?
Betadine, saline
and a suture kit.
- What happened?
- She cut herself. An accident.
- I've got this.
- How much blood has she lost?
- Alex.
- She's fine. I've got this.
Given the situation,
I'd understand if you didn't
want to proceed with surgery.
But we did learn from Jeremy,
and the formulation of
the cocktail will be adjusted.
We have not had
a positive outcome.
Liz?
I want to take her home.
- I understand.
- No. I want the surgery.
Honey.
- That's the grief talking.
- I want the surgery today.
Well, there are no other
clinical trials out there.
No one else has any answers.
- Dr. Shepherd has worked
hard on this.
- Meredith.
We're not letting
you have surgery
because you want
to die with Jeremy.
If I go home, I die.
I die in a few
weeks, a few days.
I don't want to lose you.
Mom, you won't.
Because I'm not finished.
Daddy. He loved me.
Yeah, you know,
Jeremy really loved me.
And he'd be so mad
if... if I just gave up.
Please. Do the surgery today.
Lola, Andrew's asking for you.
Could you come with me, please?
Hey, um, is... Is he OK?
No, he's not OK. He's
stuck in a block of cement.
Actual hardening-by-the-second,
concrete cement.
How could he be OK?
Wow, you care about him.
He's my friend.
I... I know I told you he
wasn't, but he's my friend.
I think he's more than that.
And I think you're too proud
to admit it to your friends,
and maybe to yourself.
Mommy, I have a
boo-boo. Kiss it better.
He is in pain, he is scared,
and he needs someone
he knows to hold his hand.
Lola, hold my hand.
Screw what they
think. This matters.
They don't.
I can't help him.
You're gonna hate
yourself for this.
Later.
You're gonna hate yourself
for this, and you'll be right.
- Don't think this looks right.
- Cristina is dyslexic,
but she got straight A's during
school and has a Ph.D. Amazing.
Eight letters of recommendation.
This look right?
How you found 'em?
Izzie went to college at
night. Six years to graduate,
volunteered as a candystriper.
Patients wrote letters of rec.
Gotta get outta here.
And Alex, he wrote
this essay to get in,
this moving, beautiful essay
about how his grades
weren't that good.
He was suffering
from testicular cancer.
Ow! What?
He lost a ball. I've
seen him naked.
He has two mangerines,
two pouch potatoes. He lied.
- Stop telling me information.
- One point. Just one point.
- How can they keep you back?
- Forget about it!
Photographic memory! I can't.
- We'll get it right with Beth.
- She lost the love of her life.
- You encourage her to surgery?
- Encourage her not to?
Not me with the
big ego, it's you.
You backed me into a corner.
- What was I supposed to do?
- Derek.
I can't She's a kid.
She's a kid who's gonna
die without surgery.
She'll die with surgery.
What you and I do.
We kill things over and
over and over again.
We've killed 12 people,
and now, because
of you, I will kill a 13th.
Surgery's over, we're done.
Don't wanna work with
you, see you, talk to you.
We're done.
OK, Andy, we're ready to begin.
Wait. Is she...?
- Lola?
- She... I couldn't find her.
She went to eat or something.
We need to start the catheter.
OK. Now, you're gonna
feel some pressure.
She didn't go to eat. She
just didn't want to come, right?
Lola likes to hang out with me.
Or she did... used to.
Before I did this.
Once, she almost...
There coulda been a kiss,
but I chickened out.
Well, maybe you don't
need to be kissing her.
No, I do. I do. I do
My whole life is
about kissing her.
Catheter's in.
Guys are on their
last piece of cement.
Thank God. The
hard part's over, right?
- The hard part's over?
- - Get a crash cart ready.
I've got calcium,
D-50 and insulin.
- Ready.
- The hard part is over?
OK, there is a chance
that when the nice
gentlemen take off
the final piece of cement
there, on your abdomen,
the toxins that have been
building up underneath
the concrete will rush to
your heart, and you'll crash.
You... Your heart will stop,
and you'll stop breathing.
But, no, there's no
need to make that face
because we will
restart your heart,
and we will put in a tube
that will breathe for you
and rush you to the OR.
We are good at what we do.
Just, if you see the
warm, welcoming light,
do not go into it.
Let's go.
OK, we're gonna
do this on three.
- OK. One.
- Watch the leads.
Two.
Three.
- There he goes.
- Clear his airway.
All right. One.
Two. Three.
- Easy, easy, easy.
- Push the lidocaine.
- Bailey.
- Got the intubation.
Go.
I don't know what you mean
when you say she didn't want to die.
When you were sitting on
the floor with your mother,
what did she say to you?
She told me to be extraordinary.
She said that she had failed,
but that I should
be extraordinary,
that I shouldn't
depend on anyone.
"Be an extraordinary
woman," is what she said.
And so you became a
surgeon, just like her.
- Yes.
- Which means you have the tools
- to figure this out.
- But I just...
You need to work this through.
I promise you, when you
do, you're gonna be glad.
♪ I'm not sure why it
always goes downhill ♪
- My head is exploding.
- Make it unexplode.
- Are... Are you mad at me?
- No.
- Why talk to me in that voice?
- There's no voice.
There's a voice.
And I did you a favor.
You didn't do me a favor.
You made it clear
that I'm still me.
The almost guy.
All that separates me
from the rest of my class
is one point?
It would've been OK if it was
50 points or ten points, but one?
That means it was right
there, it was in my hand,
and I let it slip away.
I didn't want to know
that. Do you get that?
That knowing that if I had just
checked A instead of B, that...
that one point separates
me from freedom.
I have been running my tail off,
busting my ass to make
up for one lousy point,
- ♪ to sing these doubts away ♪
- proving...
♪ Water keeps on
falling from my eyes ♪
You didn't do me a
favor. Don't kid yourself.
At least now you know
you have what it takes.
- Yeah.
- ♪ Heaven knows ♪
This arm's almost bandaged,
then we're gonna move
to the other one, OK?
OK.
I've prescribed her
Alprazolam and Clonazepam.
Psych will be down, but
it'd be good to keep her calm.
She doesn't need any
drugs or any psych.
She needs a psych
consult to be admitted.
- Not admitting her.
- Not taking her.
I was watching her every minute.
You shouldn't have to watch her.
You're not on today so she
was admitted under my name,
which means I decide
the treatment plan.
- She needs to be put on hold...
- Damn it!
Leave us alone,
you stupid bitch.
♪ It would be a
lie to run away ♪
You're supposed to sit down.
That's what the breaks are for.
We're on our feet.
Rest your legs.
My legs are good.
Inappropriate, don't you think,
thinking about
sex during surgery?
Just saying what I've
been witnessing all day.
This poor kid's entire body
was encased in cement.
His legs are crushed,
his vessels and nerves
cut off completely,
and still... I was turned on.
This entire time I've been
turned on because of you
- and your dirty talk.
- It wasn't my dirty talk.
It's what I was
dirty talking about.
- What?
- Erica. You and Erica.
No. That's...
- No.
- Callie.
- What?
- It's OK.
I wish I was all
someone thought about.
You had 14 letters
of recommendation.
Cristina had eight, Meredith
had four, Izzie had ten.
But you had 14. The
words used to describe you...
Nobody had
recommendations like yours.
People said the
others were smart,
they said they
were hard workers,
they said that they were
good. But your letters?
They said you were great.
They spoke of kindness,
attention to detail.
They talked about how hard
you try, and that you never give up.
They painted a picture
of the kind of doctor
that I hope to become.
It was an honor to
read those letters,
because now I know that what
separates you from the others
isn't one stupid point.
What separates you from
the others is greatness.
So don't you dare let
one point hold you back.
- I'm covered in blood. Talk -
fast. Alex brought Rebecca in.
She tried to hurt herself.
He's taking Rebecca home.
- And?
- She needs to be admitted.
- She needs a psych consult.
- And?
- Can you just do your job?
- I am doing my job.
I'm helping a 19-year-old man that I
promised would get to live, get to live.
That's my job as a surgeon.
I took my son to
daycare when I came in.
My job as a mother.
I'm asking you,
what are you going to
do about your patient?
My job as chief resident.
- How about you do your job?
- I can't.
- I don't know what to do.
- Stevens. She's your patient.
He's... her loved one. Come
on, you know what to do.
It's just hard to do it.
- OK, I'll try.
- No, you don't have to try.
You're a doctor trained by me,
with all the skills
that God gave you.
You have everything you need.
Each one teach one.
- Where are we?
- Sloan, Hahn and Torres
are done.
- We're up.
- Unclamped the vein.
Blood flow is good to the liver.
Right, chief?
Absolutely right. Good job.
Good. Then we're ready to...
I think I liked it better
when you were saying
boring science stuff.
I'm never good enough.
No matter what I
say or what I do.
I never wanted to do this.
This clinical trial is
making me a failure.
I fail her over
and over and over.
You mean "them."
When you say, "fail her,"
you mean, "fail them."
The patients.
♪ I've been walking
in the same way ♪
♪ As I did ♪
♪ Missing out the
cracks in the pavement ♪
He's gonna need an
embolectomy. Call Hahn back here.
A clot in the right
pulmonary artery.
I could get to it.
- Hahn will assess him.
- I can get to it.
The lung retracts, leaving
the area for embolectomy clear.
He's already severely
compromised. We'd waste time,
time his brain
won't be perfusing.
It'll take me seconds.
I've done it before. With Burke.
I promised this kid he'd live.
Dr. Bailey, take over CPR.
Yang, I'm right
here if you need me.
♪ Ooh, the people I've met ♪
Ten-blade.
♪ Are the wonders of my world ♪
♪ Are the wonders
of this world ♪
You don't have to do this.
- Come on. What are you, scared?
- Yes.
- ♪ I love to see everybody ♪
- Me, too.
- ♪ In short skirts,
shorts and shades ♪
- So let's just leap. OK?
♪ I like it in the city ♪
- ♪ When two worlds collide ♪
- OK.
♪ You get the people
and the government ♪
♪ Everybody taking ♪
♪ Different sides ♪
- What happened?
- He threw a PE.
Yang would be the best
person to open him up?
- She's a cardiac savant.
- Is that why she went through
- the fourth intercostal space?
- Couldn't get in through fifth.
Gauze pushing the diaphragm up.
This could be
easier under fluoro.
Already had the
TEE. I'm doing fine.
Reach it better...
Forget it. I'll do it.
- Gown, please.
- I've got this.
- If you had done it...
- Shut up and let me work.
♪ Of my world ♪
Let her work, Dr. Hahn.
Shepherd scheduled
two craniotomies
for the clinical trial today?
- Yes, we lost the first one...
- I told Meredith one patient.
Dr. Grey said she
cleared it with you.
Did she?
- I... Sir, I might be mistaken.
- I don't think you are.
- She's holding steady.
- The ICP's 13.
- We'll see.
- Derek.
She's still alive.
We've gotten this far.
- She's still alive.
- For how long?
- You can go.
- I'll stay with her.
No, it's just... I'll
do it. You can go.
Yang flew solo,
and you should be
celebrating because that means
you're doing your job.
Teaching her how to save a life.
Residents are like puppies,
eager and enthusiastic,
and you need to learn how to
teach without crushing their spirit.
Now you want to work
here with my residents,
then you need to do better.
You need to be a better teacher.
Don't make me
regret backing you up.
No, sir. Absolutely not, sir.
- Thank you, sir.
- Puppies.
Rebecca.
This is Dr. Shapiro from Psych.
He's gonna be examining you.
- Iz...
- Ask questions while Karev and I talk.
- What did I tell you?
- She's my patient.
I decide her treatment. I am not
releasing her without a consult.
If you try to take her without
my OK, I will have you arrested.
- You can't have me arrested.
- Try me.
Look, Iz, you're worried. I
see that, and I understand.
But you're being a
little unreasonable.
- I've got this.
- No, you don't have it. I have it.
- I'm taking her home.
- No. No!
- You gonna bodily restrain me?
- I will if I have to.
- Hit a woman?
- If I have to.
Alex, she's sick. She needs
help you cannot possibly give her.
- I can take care of her.
- No, you can't.
You have no idea. You could
do damage by taking her home.
I can take care of her.
I've done this before.
- Alex...
- She's just going through
a bad patch.
People go through a
bad patch. All right?
I can feed her and I
can... I can change her,
and I can bathe her
and I can watch her.
Until the bad patch is over,
I can take care of her.
I took care of my mom,
and I can take care of her.
- You've done this before.
- I've done this before.
I have done this before, Izzie.
But I was a kid then,
and I'm a man now,
so I'll be better at it.
- I have done this before.
- Stop.
You don't have to say anymore.
- You're here early.
- I never went home.
You'd want to
monitor your patient.
I figured you were tired.
- How is he?
- His vitals are stable.
He received 16 liters
over the first 24 hours.
I changed it down
to 125 cc's per hour.
Urine output's at
37 cc's per hour.
He had some anxiety at
3am, and then again at 5am,
which I treated with
diphenhydramine.
- Good. Good job.
- It's not a good job.
- O'Malley?
- It's not a good job for me.
Sitting by his bedside
recording urine output
and giving antianxiety
meds all night.
It's not a good job for me.
Running labs for Meredith
Grey, that's not a good job for me.
It's not a good job
because I'm better than that,
and you know I'm
better than that.
Maybe if I wasn't good at my job
or maybe if I had struggled
and was lagging behind...
My personality, I'm not Karev,
I'm not Yang, I'm not Meredith.
I'm not hardened,
I get that. I get it.
I don't have the
personality of a surgeon.
Maybe that's why
you made the mistake
of not thinking that I
deserve a second chance
when everyone else
around here has gotten one.
But, sir, it is a mistake
because I'm excellent.
I'm excellent at my job.
And I did fail my test,
but I deserve a second chance.
OK.
- OK?
- OK, you can retake the test.
OK.
She hasn't woken up yet.
Sometimes it takes
longer with brain surgery
for the body to recover.
But she could not wake up?
- Could she die?
- That's a possibility,
but I'd rather not worry
about that until we have to.
- When?
- When what?
When will we have to
start worrying about that?
Still here. Sleep in
the waiting room?
Look, I like him.
All right, I do. But he
doesn't need to know that.
- Nobody needs to know that.
- He needs you,
and you're worried
about your friends?
What do you know?
Do you know what
it'd be like for me,
for him, if they
knew? Think it's easy?
I think it's better
to be honest.
He's alive. Barely,
but... he's alive.
I, uh, called your husband.
He says he took the baby
and left you two months ago.
He says...
You have something called underlying
borderline personality disorder,
which means you were
fragile to start with, so this...
This has probably been
coming on for a while.
Probably since
your... your accident.
Then they changed your face.
I helped change your face.
You couldn't...
You need help, Rebecca,
and I can't give it to you.
So you're gonna stay here
tonight, and tomorrow...
Tomorrow, they're gonna
transfer you to a psychiatric facility.
I think that's better.
I'm sorry.
I really tried.
I wanted to be better for you.
I know how hard it is
for you to trust people,
and I wanted to be someone
you could depend on.
I'm sorry.
It's OK. You tried.
So you convinced Shepherd
to do the second surgery
without my approval.
- So?
That's how you speak
to the chief, "So?"
My mother tried to kill
herself after you left.
Did you know that?
- Did you know that?
- I didn't know that.
- I'm sorry. I didn't know.
- She was a brilliant surgeon.
How could you do that to her?
She was a talented, gifted,
extraordinary surgeon.
Meredith?
- Tell me.
- She was a surgeon.
An excellent surgeon.
If she was really
trying to kill herself,
she wouldn't have slit her
wrists. She knew better.
She would've taken the
scalpel, cut her carotid artery.
Would've taken seconds to
die. She didn't really want to die.
She was an excellent,
gifted, extraordinary surgeon.
- Didn't want to die.
- What did she want?
She wanted Richard to come back.
And why didn't he come back?
Well, because he
never knew about it,
and she was too stubborn to ask.
- What does that mean?
- Well, that part I don't know.
Could you tell me
that part for once?
I can.
It means that you are a gifted,
talented, extraordinary
surgeon, exactly like your mother,
but the difference is you get
to learn from her mistakes.
Be extraordinary.
She wasn't talking
about surgery.
No, she wasn't.
She wasn't talking
about surgery at all.
Well, do I or do I not
keep my promises?
You do.
And remember what I said
about the bigger picture?
Yeah.
He's been waiting his
whole life for that, huh?
Yes, he has.
- Are those Beth's films?
- Yes.
These are from two days
ago, and these are from today.
Would you hand me
the calipers, please?
This one is smaller than that
one. The tumor's shrinking.
- The virus is working.
- Oh, my God.
- You have to go tell Derek.
- No. You have to tell Derek.
It's the kind of news he'd
want to hear from you.
Rose.
Congratulations on your
major medical breakthrough.
It's the stuff of legends.
- Hey!
- Take the sparkle pager back.
- I am drunk on the power.
- Where is it?
I think it might
actually be mystical.
- Have you seen Derek?
- Nope.
Um... You paged, Dr. Yang?
Grab that banana from my cubby.
You... You want
me to peel it for you?
I want you to learn running
whip stitch. I'll teach it.
Take the needle.
- Chart.
- Here you go.
Thank you.
Hi.
Hey.
You're alive.
Yeah. I'm alive.
Not just for show anymore.
No.
That's not sanitary.
A little closer
together. Try again.
- Dr. Yang, thank you for...
- Uh-huh.
How'd it go?
- Awful.
- Yeah.
OK. Um...
These are for you.
Why give me your
keys to the clinic?
I'm not giving you
my keys to the clinic.
I'm giving you the clinic.
What?
I've seen the bigger
picture. I love the clinic.
I love what it means,
I love what it is.
But I don't love it as
much as I love surgery.
I don't love it as much as
I love being chief resident.
I don't love it as much as I
love my husband and my child.
I have seen the bigger picture,
and I can't do everything
and still have everything.
So I have to... let
some pieces go.
This piece. This is your piece.
I've watched you earn this piece
the hard way, the awful way.
Knowing that I can give the
clinic to someone like you.
You have grown into a
fine doctor, Izzie Stevens.
Thank you.
The Denny Duquette
Memorial Clinic is in your hands.
You make me proud.
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- Derek!
- He's not there.
- ♪ Ooh ♪
- Oh.
♪ I'm leaving tonight ♪
I'm not a bad man.
I know I'm the villain in your
story, but I'm not a bad man.
♪ I close my eyes slowly ♪
♪ Flowin' away slowly ♪
So you want to finish
what we started yesterday?
Or you can finish
what you started.
♪ Here's my life ♪
♪ I know I'm getting older ♪
- I'm growing.
- ♪ Ooh ♪
- Go. Get outta here.
- ♪ Ooh-ooh ♪
♪ All my love ♪
- ♪ It is ♪
- Hey.
♪ It is all my love ♪
I wanted to see if you
wanted to grab a drink.
- I can't find my keys.
- Maybe we could, um...
♪ Ooh, it is ♪
- Something I wanted
to talk about.
- I had the damn keys.
I put them in this bag,
but I can't remember...
- This whole thing with Yang...
- Erica.
- What?
- I'm saying something here.
♪ And I know
someone is out there ♪
♪ Lead the way ♪
- I just... I wanted to say...
- ♪ Lead the way ♪
♪ Show me the answers ♪
- ♪ I need to know ♪
- I just wanted to say...
♪ What I'm gonna live for ♪
♪ What I'm gonna die for ♪
- Meredith!
- ♪ Who you gonna fight for ♪
♪ I can't answer that ♪
♪ What I'm gonna live for ♪
♪ What I'm gonna die for ♪
- Richard?
- I want to come home.
- Richard!
- I am a good man.
I'm a good man.
I spend my days being a
good man for the hospital,
for my residents,
for my patients.
I'm a good man who made
one mistake with a woman
20 years ago.
I am a good man for
everybody but you. I know that.
Don't you think I know
that? But I am a good man.
And I am your husband...
- ♪ All my love ♪
- and I love you.
- ♪ It is ♪
- Now, I am not
asking you to come home.
- ♪ All my love ♪
- I'm telling you.
I am your husband, and I
want to come home to my wife.
♪ I know it is a
life to live lately ♪
- ♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
- ♪ Yeaaah ♪
Well...
- ♪ No, no, no ♪
- it's about time.
♪ Yeaaah ♪
♪ What I'm gonna live for ♪
- ♪ What I'm gonna die for ♪
- Meredith.
♪ Who you gonna fight for ♪
♪ I can't answer that ♪
♪ What I'm gonna live for ♪
- ♪ What I'm gonna die for ♪
- I'm retaking my intern test.
- Oh, my God.
- I talked to the chief,
made my case,
I'm taking the test.
Lexie, I know I was mad before,
but thank you,
thank you, thank you.
Thank you. Get out the liquor,
'cause we are celebrating.
♪ And now I found
a place to go ♪
♪ I've said goodbye
to all my troubles ♪
♪ 'Cause now I've
found my place to go ♪
- I'm sorry.
- Whatever.
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
- ♪ Oh ♪
- ♪ Ohhh ♪
Not whatever.
I'm sorry.
About Rebecca and your mom.
- ♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
- I'm sorry.
- ♪ Whoa, hey, yeaaah ♪
♪ No, no, no, no ♪
- Alex.
- Please.
- Just this once.
- ♪ What I'm gonna die for ♪
- ♪ Who you gonna fight for ♪
- Just for this one night,
please.
- Please.
- ♪ What I'm gonna live for ♪
♪ What I'm gonna die for ♪
♪ Who you gonna fight for ♪
♪ I can't answer that ♪
- ♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
- ♪ Oh ♪
- ♪ Yeaaah ♪
♪ No, no, no, no ♪
♪ What I'm gonna live for ♪
♪ What I'm gonna die for ♪
♪ Who you gonna fight for ♪
Please. Please.
♪ Whoo ♪
♪ Oh ♪
- ♪ Oh ♪
We goin' home.
Home to Daddy.
Yeah. Yeah.
Meredith?
Stupid, corny, idiotic.
I cannot believe I did this.
Stupid loser. Son of a... I
could be at home instead of...
- Stupid brain man.
- Meredith.
Where have you been?
I've been waiting
and waiting for you,
and I did this
stupid, embarrassing,
humiliating, corny thing,
and I was gonna
tell you that this here
is our kitchen and
this is our living room,
and that's the room
where our kids could play.
I had this thing, "I was
gonna build us a house,"
but I don't build
houses. I'm a surgeon.
And now I'm here feeling
like a lame-ass loser.
I got all whole and healed,
and you don't show up.
It's ruined because
you took so long.
And I couldn't even find
that bottle of champagne.
♪ I can pretend ♪
♪ 'Cause I've
studied the masks ♪
This is the kitchen?
- ♪ But I don't wanna play ♪
- Living room?
Little small.
I think the view is
much better from here.
And that's the room where
the kids are gonna play?
♪ I don't wanna stage ♪
- ♪ A single piece for you ♪
- Where's our bedroom?
I'm still mad at you, and
I don't know if I trust you.
I want to, but I don't know
if I do. I'm just gonna try.
I'm gonna try and
trust you. I believe that
we can be extraordinary together
rather than ordinary
apart, and I wanna be...
♪ Oh ♪
♪ You, you keep me warm ♪
- ♪ You, you keep me warm ♪
- I have to go.
What?
In order to kiss you the
way I want to kiss you,
in order to do
more than kiss you,
I need to speak to Rose.
I want my conscience clear
so that I can do
more than kiss you.
Stay here.
Don't move.
- Wait for me.
- ♪ I don't wanna stage ♪
♪ Any theater for you ♪
♪ I don't wanna play ♪
♪ A single piece ♪
♪ For you ♪