Rreviously on "Grey's Anatomy"...
- This where Georgie lives?
- Oh, George.
O'Malley!
Callie, she dumped me.
Don't chase me anymore unless
you're ready to catch me.
You erased my name from Burke's
humpty dumpty surgery.
What I don't know is why.
- You okay?
- Absolutely.
Stop worrying.
Nobody has to know.
I saw you there, at the nursing
home with my mother.
She lights up
when you're around.
Meredith,
I want to start over.
You're not going to retire.
I need more time.
I don't have
any more time to give.
- It's about your dad, George.
- My dad?
Many people don't know
that the human eye has a blind spot
in its field of vision.
There's a part of the world
we are literally
blind to.
What did I say?
- Seriously?
- Seriously.
- Seriously. We're taking it slow.
I can take it slow.
I can take it incredibly slow.
We're taking it slower
than that.
We're starting fresh.
And startign fresh
means no sex because...
Because we started with sex
last time,
and it didn't go very well.
Plus, the waiting is fun.
And we need fun.
From now on I want to be
bright and shiny.
Bright and shiny, huh?
The problem is,
sometimes our blind spots
shield us from things that really
shouldn't be ignored.
Mom.
The nurses tell me
you haven't been eating.
No time.
I've been in the O.R. all morning, and I've got
back-to-back surgeries the rest of the day, so...
Look, I'm sorry that I haven't been
visiting, it's just that I've been...
I don't have time
to coddle you right now.
I'm trying to save lives here.
Do you understand?
Do you?
Dr. Grey.
Chief.
Richard.
For me?
You shouldn't have.
The nurses said
she hasn't been eating.
Oh, you wonderful man.
I'm interrupting.
- I'll... I'll go.
- No, chief. Uh...
You stay and I'll go.
Sometimes our blind spots
keep our lives bright and shiny.
Today is the day, people.
Today is the day
when dark-and-twisty Meredith
disappears forever
and bright-and-shiny Meredith
takes her place.
You're probably not gonna wanna
be friends with me anymore
because the sheer intensity of my happiness
is gonna make your teeth hurt.
But that's okay
because life is good.
Life is good.
What's going on?
George's dad
got admitted last night.
- Oh, my god. Is he okay?
- Oh, no, he's fine.
He, uh, passed out,
- hit the floor and fractured his clavicle.
- Yeah, but his clavicle's fine.
Callie said it's gonna be fine.
Are those his A.M. Labs?
Yeah, complaining
of severe abdominal pain.
He doesn't have
peritoneal signs. That's good.
Has anybody seen...
I was just looking at it.
Don't you think me reading it
is more important than you reading it?
Sure. Fine.
He's gonna be fine.
You're on scut today.
You'll be distracted.
No, I won't.
Family  members do not treat
family members. Scut.
I'm scrubbing in on a surgery
with Dr. Burke this morning.
Of course you are.
Karev, Sloan. Grey, Pit.
Stevens, shadow Karev.
And let me remind you again
of the rules of your probation.
I think she knows the rules,
Dr. Bailey.
No touching patients,
no talking to patients,
no rolling your eyes at the patients
or your superiors.
Hey. Good morning, Addison.
What's that supposed
to mean?
It is a greeting...
used in civilized cultures
by their civilized inhabitants.
You're smiling.
Yeah. It's called happiness.
I understand why
you wouldn't recognize it.
Whoa, whoa.
Wait, wait, wait.
We're, uh, being mature
about this?
Yes, we are going to peacefully coexist
in this hospital,
unless you've reconsidered
moving back to New York.
Okay, then.
We peacefully coexist.
- Interesting.
- Yes.
We're adults. We're educated.
I think we're capable of many, many things.
Come on.
Let's shake on it.
So I'm still wearing
the rings.
Well...
I think they're stuck.
Have you tried soap?
I hear it's good and slippery.
You are
a very strange person, Derek.
I am just bright and shiny, Addison,
bright and shiny.
No, so then I just... I popped
his shoulder right back in.
He didn't even flinch.
Your brother is hard-core.
- George?
- Callie, what are...
It looks like you've got
a full house, Mr. O'Malley.
Just waiting on the wife.
She's in D.C.,
Uh, chaperoning a field trip.
Yeah, she's coming in today.
His clavicle's still hurting,
so I added P.R.N. morphine
every four hours.
And I've scheduled your
endoscopy for this afternoon.
- An endo-what?
- Scope.
That's like... like a camera.
- That sounds dangerous. Is that dangerous?
- No, it's not dangerous.
Okay, I didn't ask you.
I asked the doctor.
Yeah, let the doctor speak, Georgie.
White coat.
Let's  look at the white coat.
What about an x-ray? 'Cause I had
that once, and I feel like he...
- Shut up, both of you. Shut up.
- O'malley.
What?
Since we're all...
Well, she's not talking to you.
Ah, excellent.
My invaluable intern.
Is it "bring a hot blonde
to work" day? No one told me.
Sexual harassment.
Dr. Stevens is
shadowing me today, so...
Which one of these cases
do you need us on?
It's a really tragic one.
I found out just this morning
that I have over two weeks
worth of dry cleaning
that needs to be picked up...
Stat.
Cool. That's it?
See? We're like a well-oiled
machine, you and me.
I also need you twoto get me
a sandwich from that
pathetic excuse for a deli.
You know the one I like, Karev.
Oh, but go easy
on the mayo this time.
I think you're trying
to kill me.
I don't see why I can't at least help
with my dad's endoscopy.
What about "no working with family"
do you not understand?
- I'm not asking to do the pro...
- Fine.
Pick an intern.
What?
I'm being kind. You want an intern
assigned to your dad's case?
Fine.
Who do you want?
Right now.
Pick an intern.
Excellent.
Now we want to place a
partial occluding clamp on the aorta.
Slowly.
Good.
Now make sure
all the grafts are de-aired
before you remove the venous
and aortic cannulas.
He's letting her decannulate
the heart by herself?
Freakin' unbelievable, huh?
What do we have?
Mia Hanson... 5-year-old female,
crush injury to the abdomen,
blunt trauma to the head.
B.P. 90 over 60, pulse 110.
- How was she injured?
- Backed over by her mom's S.U.V.
She's, um...
Her blood type is A-negative,
and she's allergic to penicillin and,
um, wheat.
I am so sorry, Mia.
I am so sorry, baby.
- Has she had anything to eat today?
- Uh, cereal this morning around 6:30.
Okay, Mrs. Hanson, we're going
to take care of your daughter.
I am Mrs. Hanson.
Mia is my child.
Anna is just the nanny
who ran over my daughter!
I'm gonna examine your neck, okay?
It's okay, Mia.
My name is Meredith.
And Dr. Shepherd and Dr. Bailey
are just trying to see where you're hurt,
- Okay?
- What the hell happened?!
She ran over Mia in the driveway.
- She what?
- Mia wasn't supposed to be
in the driveway. Mrs. Hanson told me
to go get some milk, and I...
- I didn't see her.
- How do you not even see a child
- standing in the driveway?
- Shh.
And  where were you?
- What?
- What were you doing that
you couldn't watch Mia
for five minutes?
- I was supposed to be in Court.
- Oh, you're on the phone.
I was letting them know
that I was going to be late.
- Instead of watching Mia!
- Oh! Oh, so now this is my fault?
It's the car's fault, okay?
S.U.V.S have blind spots
the size of jupiter.
And yelling and fighting and placing blame
is not gonna help your child.
- Is she gonna be okay?
- She has blood in her ear canal.
We need to get her upstairs
for a C.T.
- Okay, ready?
- It's gonna be okay, baby girl.
Get away from her.
- Now. Get out!
- What?
Come on, let's get her up.
I can't believe you...
You just decannulated a heart
all by yourself.
I didn't decannulate
the heart by myself.
I assisted Dr. Burke,
who decannulated a heart.
Why are you being modest?
Modest looks weird on you.
It's no big deal, George.
How's your father, O'Malley?
Anything new?
He needs an endoscopy,
and, uh,
Bailey won't let me be the intern
on this case. She said I could pick someone.
I was wondering if Cristina
could be the intern on this case.
- Why?
- That shouldn't be a problem.
Uh, uh, yes it is. We have a
carotid endarterectomy scheduled at noon.
I'll push it.
-  O'Malley's father deserves the best.
- Thank you, Dr. Burke.
Not a problem, O'Malley.
Your dad better get something
interesting wrong with him real fast.
You're sick.
She's a...
sick, horrible person.
Tell me again why you put up
with this crap?
Because one of these days, he's gonna
crack and let me in on a case.
You sure you want to do
plastics that badly?
There you are.
What, did you go all the way
to New York for my pastrami?
Extra spicy, extra lettuce,
light on the mayo.
Mark...
What are you doing?
Lunch.
Want my pickle?
Seattle Grace
is a teaching hospital
and part of your job is to teach.
Your interns aren't your slaves.
Fine.
No pickle for you.
- Did you see that?
- Hmm?
Sloan. He's using his interns
to pick up his dry cleaning and his lunch.
I've got to do an endoscopy.
What  the hell is going on
with the men in this hospital?
How you doing, Mr. Jeffes?
Oh, Frank's doing okay.
He'd be doing a lot better
if the twins were even.
Uh, twins?
Frank's new pecs.
Who is Frank?
You're looking at him.
Frank, these are interns.
I'm supposed to be teaching them.
Apparently,
this is a teaching hospital.
Karev?
Yeah, uh...
Frank Jeffries is post-op day three
for pectoral enhancement surgery.
There was a slight complication
when a seroma formed.
What is a seroma?
Build up of blood and fluid
under the skin.
Sorry.
And that concludes today's teaching.
A tube was inserted into Mr. Jeffries' chest
to drain the excess fluid.
I want you to monitor him,
check the tube for fluid output
and change his dressings.
Dr. Stevens...
I guess you can
watch.
Actually, dr. Stevens is
an excellent doctor.
Yeah,
that's what I hear.
You decannulated a heart
this morning.
- Yeah, I didn't decan-
- Yes, you did.
And when Burke and I
were fishing, I...
I noticed something weird
with his hand, like
- it had a spasm...
- I'm sorry.
Why are you even saying that?
That is not funny.
I didn't say it was funny.
I said it was weird.
And him letting you
decannulate a heart,
that's weird.
You should sit with your father. 'Cause if
you want something to worry about,
- you should worry about him.
- My father is fine.
He's good,
I have a good,
Don't... This is Burke.
Did you think that...
I want Anna.
It's okay, Mia.
Mommy and daddy are here.
and we are just going to take
some pictures.
Okay? This is a big camera.
I don't like it.
Grey...
keep her still.
Mia, baby...
It's okay. Mommy's here.
Where's Anna?
You need to lie very still, okay?
I want Anna.
How about I sing you
the good night song?
And you pretend it's bedtime
and stay super still, okay?
Okay.
Good night, Mia
good night, mommy
good night, daddy
- No, you're singing it wrong.
- I am? I'm singing it wrong?
I want Anna.
She's in the waiting room, honey.
I'll, I'll get her.
John!
Let's all sing it together, okay?
No. I want Anna.
So now... but you pick...
you pick a car.
Okay. Um...
1968 mustang gt
390 fastback.
That's interesting.
No, that is hot.
That is very hot.
Car.
Hey, Georgie.
How's dad?
Fine. They're not done yet,
but I'm sure he's fine.
Can I talk to you,
Dr. Torres?
Sure.
Excuse me.
What are you doing?
- I'm talking to your brothers.
- You don't have to do that.
It's okay. I don't mind.
I'm pretty sure Ronny and Jerry
both have a thing for me.
I was gonna go with Jerry
until he went all 1957 bel-air.
- I was like, "really?"
- Thank you
for trying to help out with my family,
but it's really not necessary.
George...
I'm kidding about your brothers.
Come on.
Callie, I'm serious.
I can handle my family
on my own.
You broke up with me,
remember?
We may have to do
a partial nephrectomy.
Do you think
you can save Mia's kidney?
Only if we can control the bleeders.
Here, cauterize as I go.
Thank you.
You poor baby.
It's not gonna be an easy recovery.
Well, with parents like that,
she didn't have it easy
to begin with.
People do the best they can,
Dr. Grey.
They don't know
their kid's blood type.
They don't know her favorite song.
People want high-powered careers,
I get that,
but they should think twice
before having kids.
Oh! I... I'm sorry.
I didn't mean...
What, that I should be home
with my baby
instead of here with this little girl
and a surgical intern
who can't cauterize the bleeders?
- Dr. Bailey...
- If I were you, Dr. Grey,
I would keep my eye on the surgical area
and my mouth shut.
O'Malley.
How's it going with your dad?
Good. The chief's doing an endoscopy
on him, so he's in good hands.
That was an amazing surgery this morning,
the way you let Cristina
decannulate that heart.
She shows tremendous promise
in cardiothoracic surgery.
She said she didn't do it.
Probably didn't want
to rub it in.
Make anyone jealous.
We're talking about Cristina.
Everything all right
with you?
Sure.
It's fine.
'Cause if anything ever wasn't,
you know you could talk to me, right?
You've been through a lot lately,
getting shot...
All that...
It can't be easy.
Yeah.
Has it not been easy?
It's  fine.
- Send my best to your dad.
- Okay.
- Hey.
This civil and mature thing,
how far does it go?
Meaning what?
Meaning is it pleasantries in the hallway,
or do we actually interact?
Oh, I don't know.
That sounds drastic.
I'm worried about Richard.
He seems down to me.
Well, he's separated from his wife.
That usually doesn't make a person giddy,
except in my case.
I think he could use somebody
to talk to.
- So talk to him.
- No, I think we both should.
You know, so it's clear that
he has people to turn to.
Because he's a little depressed?
Well, because I don't think
he's spoken to Adele in weeks,
and he's our friend, and
he has always been there for us.
When you get divorced, doesn't that mean
your wife is supposed to stop nagging you?
Maybe if you took the rings off
it would help.
Are you gonna come with me
to see the chief or not?
Fine. Yes. Okay.
Thank you. Let's do it.
And I will try soap.
- For the rings, I mean.
- Okay.
Oh, yeah.
That's what I'm talking about.
Oh, look at you.
Do they still look lopsided?
I mean, from the seroma.
No, it looks like most of
the swelling has gone down.
Yeah?
Oh, yeah.
Hey, uh,
Dr. Stevens, would you
take a look at the twins?
Frank would like
a woman's perspective.
You're just looking.
Nice.
It looks pretty even to me,
very defined.
And the redness should go away
in a couple of days.
Good.
Frank got them for his girlfriend.
He doesn't want her to see 'em
till their perfect.
Your girlfriend asked you
to get pec implants?
Oh, no. No, no.
Frank's girlfriend joined a gym,
got a trainer named Lars.
What kind of name
is that, Lars?
So you got fake pecs 'cause you're jealous
of a guy with a fake name?
Well, uh,
my last girlfriend Veena...
left me for a guy with hair
so I got plugs...
too late.
This time around, Frank's not
taking any chances.
Frank sees the signs of discontent,
Frank's fighting back.
Oh, yeah.
I don't know.
I just don't get the whole
fake boob thing, no offense.
Oh, these are, these are
top of the line.
I mean, they... they look real,
they
feel natural.
No, really.
Feel 'em.
Really.
Come on. Feel them.
Very solid.
And real.
- I don't know about that.
- Well, compare them to his.
- I'm not involved with this.
- Come on.
Don't be such a baby.
This...
this is why
I don't work with interns.
Mrs. Hanson.
Is she all right?
Yes, we were able
to stop the bleeding.
Dr. Shepherd has ordered
an M.R.I. of her skull fracture.
Hopefully she won't need
any more surgery.
- Oh, thank god!
- Uh, she's in recovery.
- Dr. Grey will take you up to her.
- Thank you.
Can we wait just a minute? My husband
went downstairs to use a landline.
- His battery died.
- Sure.
So
Mia, she's okay?
Oh, she is.
Yeah.
She, um...
keeps asking, uh, for Anna.
We fired Anna.
Oh.
She just seems
very attached to her.
That's my fault,
according to my husband,
because I'm a working mother.
He's a working dad, but apparently,
that's not the issue.
I love my job.
I love Mia more.
She is my baby.
She's my...
I love my daughter
and I love my job.
I'm not good at the mom stuff,
but
I'm good at my job.
Why bother having a kid if you're only
gonna see it on weekends and holidays?
You might as well just get a cat.
I talked to Burke.
I think he's fine.
You did what?
What's wrong with Burke?
Nothing's wrong with anybody.
Do you know he let her
decannulate a heart this morning?
You decannulated a heart
this morning, by yourself?
Bitch.
No, not by myself.
Now she's lying about it.
Yang decannulated a heart.
Why is Alex not surprised?
Izzie isn't either.
Last week, Izzie was digging through crap.
This week, she's fondling man-boobs.
No decannulating hearts
for Izzie.
Why aren't you bragging about
decannulating a heart?
- I didn't decannulate the heart.
- Izzie and Alex do not believe you.
Okay,
what are you two doing?
Izzie and Alex have a patient who
speaks about himselfin the third person.
They thought it was annoying at first,
but now they kind of like it.
Good. Is it gonna stop soon?
Wow, what happened?
This morning you were all "bright and shiny"
and asking to be kicked in the face.
I am.
I'm bright.
I'm shiny.
Yeah.
Izzie thinks this whole
bright and shiny thing is getting old.
Alex agrees.
We think you're depressed.
- Both of you?
- Yes.
Well, for the two of you to agree
on something, I must damn near be suicidal.
- We agree on things.
- We agree on this.
So...
Start talking.
Adele and I...
She wants me to step down as chief,
retire.
You, retire? That's crazy.
What would you do?
Uh, spend a little more time
with his wife, perhaps?
- She's being unreasonable.
- She wants to know that
- his marriage is a priority to him.
- She's using his work as an excuse.
Or he is. Some men use work.
Some men use other women.
- Some women use other men.
- I've been visiting Ellis Grey.
I was lonely, and you had checked out
and I was lonely.
I work, I visit Ellis.
That's my day.
- You gave up on us first. I was there.
- I make time for Ellis.
- I don't make time for Adele.
- There's something driving a wedge
between Richard and Adele.
Now maybe you don't see it, but I do,
- and so does Adele.
- Maybe he sees it
- and doesn't want to do anything about it.
- He's gotta do something about it.
That's what marriage is built on, change.
Change is what keeps marriage alive.
The man has a right to do whatever
he wants to do...
- Stop...
- Sorry.
helping me.
Look, I miss my wife.
I want her back.
I don't want my marriage
to be over.
Richard...
your marriage isn't over
until you decide it is...
- Right.
- Until you decide that the...
the sacrifice just isn't worth it.
Right.
Come in.
Oh, Yang.
What is it?
O'Malley.
Yeah.
I have your father's
test results.
You gotta ask for it.
Hey, we've been waiting here forever.
Where's the doctor?
Uh, Dr. Webber will be in
in a couple of minutes.
Won't tell you anything, huh,
not till you're a real doctor?
I am a real doctor.
Ronny!
I just...
I'm just not dad's doctor.
What is it, Georgie?
Let's just wait for Dr. Webber.
No, I think
he's expecting you to tell him.
- But he's coming. He said he's coming.
- He's coming in later. You should...
- I mean, you should tell your dad.
- What's with the whispering?
The biopsy results were abnormal.
Well, is abnormal bad or...
just different?
Georgie?
Sir...
you have cancer
in your esophagus,
which has spread
to your stomach.
We need to operate
to remove it,
and you'll need to undergo
chemotherapy and radiation.
I'm sorry.
They're gonna try
to operate soon.
This week, I think.
It's a stage 3
metastatic cancer.
So...
And my... my brothers...
And, uh...
Callie slept with Sloan.
I just can't...
I can't...
I can't deal with...
with any of it.
I spent the entire day worrying
about Burke, like
there was something wrong with him.
But there's nothing wrong with Burke and...
God, my dad has cancer,
I can't even look him in the face.
Cristina had to tell him
wh-what was wrong.
Cristina.
Nobody gets it right
with their own family.
I certainly don't.
Yeah.
Yeah...
Callie slept with Sloan?
I don't get you people.
Us with the boobs?
- We make a lot of bad decisions.
- Yeah.
Dude,
I still can't believe you
went through all this for a chick.
What, you never did
anything crazy for love?
Not like this.
You have a girlfriend?
No.
Dr. Stevens?
Frank can sense the vibes.
I'm not talking about this
with you.
What, she left you for another guy?
Frank's hit a nerve.
It's more complicated
than that.
Uncomplicate it then, man.
Grand gestures is what
I'm talking about.
Be like Frank. Just figure out
what she wants and make it happen.
Just forget all about
the other guy.
Trust Frank.
Frank knows.
Hey, what do we got?
The second M.R.I. Report
shows bleeding in Mia's brain.
Damn it.
I need to go in,
try to relieve the pressure.
- Two surgeries in one day?
- But she's tough.
And right now we don't have
any other options.
Here.
Not so bright and shiny.
I thought the cancer
was in my gut.
What are we looking
at my heart for?
Your E.K.G. showed some abnormalities,
so we just want to make sure
your heart's healthy enough
to support you
through the surgery.
You're a smart girl.
Yes.
George told me you were the best intern
I could have on my case.
He said that?
He said you were the best intern
in the hospital.
Said you keep everyone
on their toes,
even him.
Dr. Yang,
you should take a look
at this.
You paged me?
What is Burke doing
in there?
I did a pre-op echo.
His aorta valve is leaking.
He won't make it through the cancer surgery
unless we replace it.
It's just
a valve replacement, George.
It's gonna be fine.
Burke will do it.
Burke will do it, and
you will clear his schedule.
If someone is gonna operate
on my dad's heart, I want it to be Burke.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
It's gonna be fine.
It's a valve replacement.
It's Preston Burke.
If someone's gonna cut your
dad's heart apart, you want it to be him.
What?
- What's wrong with Burke's hand?
- Nothing.
- He's gonna operate on my father.
- George, Burke is fine.
- Your dad will be fine.
- You're lying.
Burke is hiding something,
and you're helping him.
Leave me alone.
You wanted to see me, chief?
It's about your mother.
Um...
I... I know your relationship
with her is, uh...
complicated.
And I know you know that
she and I...
- were...
- Chief,
it's okay.
What really matters
is that you make her happy,
and my father couldn't
- and I couldn't, so...
- Meredith, I...
I can't see your mother
anymore.
I need to make...
I need to try to make
my marriage work.
And if I'm gonna do that...
I have to stop seeing
your mother.
I see.
She...
She's an extraordinary woman.
She worked so hard,
she sacrificed so much, and to see it
end like this,
Take good care of her
for me.
We got it from here.
Yo.
Okay, Frank.
Time to take the tube out.
Izzie,
- put on some gloves.
- What's going on?
Alex, what are you doing?
You ready to take out
Frank's boob tube?
What about the rules?
What if Sloan finds out?
Screw Sloan.
She knows
what she's doing, right?
I promise you, Frank, the twins
are in excellent hands.
Grand gesture.
Frank gets it.
What's he talking about?
Nothing.
You sure about this?
Oh, yeah, he's sure.
Looks like we can
safely evacuate the clot.
Want to cook the pumper?
Did you ever think about
having kids?
Derek and I talked about it,
but I wasn't ready.
I love kids.
I'd have a dozen.
Believe me, one's enough,
unless you plan
to put away your scalpel.
That's why
god invented nannies.
I wish it were that easy.
What do I do with these,
hock 'em, keep 'em?
My mom says post-divorce
wedding rings are bad juju.
- Your mom says juju?
- She does.
So,
what would your mom do?
Burn 'em
bury 'em.
You want 'em?
I want some rings,
just not bad juju rings.
Then again, my mom's kind of insane.
Hey, don't talk smack about your mom.
Miranda.
Yesterday,
I left
for work early,
and Tuck's favorite food
was strained peas.
Nasty green gunk, but he loved them,
ate them for breakfast.
I got home after a 15-hour shift,
and he doesn't like strained peas anymore.
He only wants carrots.
Life moves so fast.
- Everybody moves on.
- Yep.
Where you going?
I'm not ready to move on.
Do you know why I picked you
to be my dad's intern?
Because you are a robot.
You're a freakin' robot in a white coat
who never makes a mistake,
and most of the time, I appreciate that.
Most of the time,
I really feel like I have something
to learn from you. But right now,
right now,
I need you to try, just for a minute,
I need you to try to be a human being.
Thank you, Alex.
I can't believe you let me help.
Alex is cool, you know that?
Alex is the coolest.
Oh, Alex knows it.
- Izzie isn't so bad herself.
- No, Izzie is rocking.
Izzie is back in the game.
I can't.
Alex, I'm sorry.
Hey, Mia.
Can you say something
for me?
I need to hear
how great you talk.
Can you say my name?
Can you say Meredith?
Wh-where's...
Anna?
That was great.
Guess who's here.
Mom and dad.
Hey.
How's my baby girl, huh?
I want Anna.
Anna.
Diane, wait.
Diane, where are you going?
So we'll do the thing
with the heart tomorrow?
Maybe tomorrow.
Uh, maybe in a couple of days.
I don't, I don't know
quite yet.
But, uh, Dr. Webber and Dr. Burke said
we should get to it quick.
And we will get to it
as quick as we can.
I just want to make sure
that we do it right.
I just don't understand why
they're operating on his heart
when the cancer
is in his gut.
Yeah, it's complicated.
You know what I was thinking?
Maybe the tests are wrong.
Okay? Maybe it's not cancer.
'Cause, 'cause, 'cause cancer
runs in the family, right?
And no one else in the family
has cancer.
It is cancer.
Okay? It's stage 3 metastatic
- esophageal cancer.
- Meta-whatic?
Metastatic.
It's, uh,
when the cancer cells have migrated
from their point of origin...
Okay, you're talking doctor now, George.
Just talk english.
I am talking english,
you're just not listening!
No, you're just not saying
anything that we understand!
Boys.
Imagine your dad's like a...
like a vintage car, okay?
And, uh...
his blood's like
gas flowing through the fuel lines.
The cancer cells are like the gunk
that builds up in there.
- And fouls up, fouls up the plugs.
- Exactly.
Once the gunk starts circulating, it can do
a lot of damage to the whole engine.
The carburetor, everything.
It's... it's like the engine
had already blown a gasket
even before
all the other damage started.
Good night, mummy,
it's time
to say good night
good night, Mia...
good night
When it comes to our blind spots...
daddy,
it's time to say goodnight.
maybe our brains aren't compensating.
Maybe they're protecting us.
I'm glad you came to visit.
But you can't stay.
I'm expecting someone.
Actually...
mom, he's not coming.
What?
The chief.
Richard.
He's not coming tonight.
It's... in fact, it's just gonna
be me for a while.
- He's gone back to Adele.
- Yes.
Of course he has.
Mom...
He's afraid,
afraid to be happy.
And I'm all alone.
Now I have to raise
my daughter alone.
How am I expected
to do that?
Mom...
You did the best you could.
That's all anybody
can do.
How am I looking?
Good. You're ready
for surgery.
That's good, I guess.
I don't know how I'm gonna
tell my wife about all this.
40 years, we've been
married,
and now...
cancer and a heart condition?
She was always
telling me
how I should eat better
and take better care
of myself.
I guess I should have listened.
George...
is the best.
What?
He's the best...
intern.
He's a good doctor
and he's a good person,
and
whatever happens,
I just thought you should know that.
that you raised a good person.
Thank you, Dr. Yang.
I didn't know you still felt
that way about me.
Me neither.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
Alex gets it.
Alex is sorry
he's such an idiot.
Can Izzie buy Alex a drink?
Alex would like that.
Izzie can.
I know what time it is.
I don't care if he's sleeping,
just wake him up.
He could sleep late.
No, wake him up.
Okay.
Now.
No, uh, put the phone
to his ear.
Hey.
Hey, tuck.
It's mommy.
Them that's got shall get
them that's not shall lose
so the bible says
and it's still is news
mama may have
papa may have
but god bless the child
that's got his own
All the strong get more
while the weak ones fade
George knows.
Empty pockets don't
ever make the grade
mama may have
papa, he may have
but god bless the child
that's got his own
I may not be cut out
for bright and shiny.
I'm not either.
We can be dull
and lifeless together.
I am glad
you're in my bathtub.
A crust of bread
and such
Me, too.
You can help yourself
but don't take too much
mama may have
papa may have
but god bless the child
that's got his own