Previously on Grey's Anatomy:
- Who's Mark?
- Derek found us in bed together.
- How come you forgive her?
- I didn't forgive her.
Denny, this is Dr. Stevens. She'll
be tending to you prior to surgery.
That guy Alex, you with him?
- No.
- I won't have to fight him for you.
Where is my husband?
Got into a car accident
trying to get here.
- This is our son.
- He's beautiful.
He broke up with me for a girl
who doesn't know he's alive.
You, Meredith Grey?
Never gonna happen.
You look sad.
I saw my father for the first time
in 20 years.
- Is there anything that you need?
- I don't need anything from you.
You could just try
telling her how you feel.
I will never stop loving you.
OK, so sometimes
even the best of us make rash decisions.
Bad decisions.
Decisions we pretty much know
we're going to regret the moment...
the minute especially...
the morning after.
I mean, maybe not
"regret" regret because at least,
you know, we put ourselves out there,
but still,
something inside us
decides to do a crazy thing,
a thing we know will probably turn
around and bite us in the ass.
Yet... we do it anyway.
I'm coming, Doc. Just hang on.
Just hold it until I get there, please.
- I'll walk him.
- No, it's my turn.
No, it's OK. I'll walk Doc.
You just sleep.
The good... fresh outdoors.
Spring morning.
- You just sleep.
- OK.
- Unless you wanna talk.
- Oh, God. Here it comes.
I'm not saying we have to talk. I'm just
saying if you want to talk, we could.
I can start and you can talk about
anything at all you want to talk about.
It's too early for me to interpret
"girl flip-out" into conversation.
It's just that usually you start
yelling when you get mad.
Mark showed up and you haven't yelled
yet and I'm trying to give you a chance.
- Just go. Yell.
- I don't wanna yell.
- You don't wanna yell? You?
- I just wanna sleep.
Doc, he wants to pee.
Preferably not inside this trailer.
OK.
You could yell if you want to.
I can take it. I'm ready.
All right. I'm going.
I'm going. Come on.
What I'm saying is...
we reap what we sow.
What comes around, goes around.
Morning. Morning.
What? So, I slept with him again.
So I'm a big whore. A big horny whore
who can't get enough.
Can we get over
the shocked silence already?
It's karma. And any way you slice it...
What's going on?
... karma sucks.
50 bucks says O'Malley caught
her doing Mark Sloan.
There's something going on.
Look at them.
All right.
He walked in on her doing McDreamy.
Did I just call that dude McDreamy?
- Oh, you know you did.
- Awesome. You are ruining my life.
- Uh-huh.
- Get a room.
- Guys?
- Excuse me.
Sorry.
What's going on?
- Nothing.
- You know we're gonna find out anyway.
- If you tell us, we can help.
- There's nothing to tell.
That means there's something to tell.
- Come on.
- There's nothing to tell.
Well, how about gardenias?
Like masses and mountains of gardenias.
- Are we worried about bees?
- That's why I love him.
- No gardenias.
- Who would like to present?
Keith Paulus. Admitted last night
with chest pain. Status: post acute MI.
No family or personal history
of heart disease.
- No cardiac risk factors.
- Healthy as a horse.
A horse who's in bed
after just having a heart attack.
Any minute, I think you're gonna
tell us that this was a false alarm.
- She talks when she gets nervous.
- I understand.
Mr. Paulus, unfortunately the scan
shows a mass around your heart.
A very, very large mass.
Mass. OK.
Is that code for tumor?
OK, that's absurd. He doesn't
have a tumor. He's incredibly healthy.
We won't know
without further exploration
which is why
I'd like to do an angiogram today.
OK. Good.
Did Meredith say anything to anyone
about anything?
- No. Are you going to dish?
- No. No.
Then leave me alone. I'm working.
Good. Because I don't
want to talk about it ever.
- Fine. Then don't.
- I'm just saying.
Why are you...? That's weird
You need to throw up again?
There's no shame in needing to throw up.
Dad, I don't need to throw up.
Shawn Begleiter, 11 years old. In
for vomiting after a minor head injury.
Oh, I wouldn't exactly say minor.
- He was hit with a baseball.
- Playing first.
This little dolt Harry Doppelhammer
hit this line drive
when Shawn wasn't looking...
This is my fault. I shouldn't
have let him play Little League.
- It's clearly a dangerous sport.
- Rick, let's let the doctors talk.
Michael, I'm telling them what happened.
Shawn's going to be OK. Right?
Yeah, we have to keep a close eye
on him. OK, recommendations?
It could indicate anything from a
concussion to intracranial hemorrhaging.
I'd start with an H and P,
do a thorough neuro exam, and get a CT.
- Good.
- Sure you don't need to throw up?
Dad.
- Tucker.
- Dr. Shepherd.
How um... How are you feeling?
I'm feeling great. I get to go home!
That's fantastic.
Is Miranda going to meet you there?
- No, I'm driving him there.
- Oh, thank God.
- Are you OK?
- I need a consult.
- I'm not working.
- Miranda. I need a consult.
- Oh, no.
- Please don't say that.
Addison, I'm so, so sorry.
You have poison oak...
where nobody wants to have poison oak.
-  Like I was saying...
- Oh, God!
... payback's a bitch.
It's official, my friend.
You get to go home.
I can't thank you enough.
I thank you, my wife thanks you...
and my son thanks you.
Where is your wife?
You can't drive for another six weeks.
Dr. Shepherd's a stickler when
it comes to patients' recovery. I know.
Hey, Richard.
Wanted to stop in
before Bailey took you home.
Well, she's here somewhere.
Your wife came in earlier.
Said she needed a consult.
Consult?
Bailey's on maternity leave.
It seemed like some kind of personal
consult. It's OK. I don't mind waiting.
- All right. I'm back.
- Oh.
You didn't make a chart? Please tell me
you did not make up a chart?
I did not make up a chart,
so we are officially stealing
this calamine lotion and these gloves.
You take it up with the chief.
- I cannot take this up with the chief.
- I'm kidding.
Did I make jokes
when you were in the stirrups?
No, you did not. And I'm apologizing.
Oh, my.
- What?
- These blisters are growing fast.
- I gotta give you a shot of steroids.
- Steroids?
I have never seen
a case a poison oak this bad.
Ew! Girl, what did you...
Oh, for the love of God!
Miranda, the calamine!
Right. Sorry.
- What happened with you and O'Malley?
- Nothing.
Whatever it is, I've done worse.
How do you know I did something
and George didn't?
Because Bambi looks pissed
and you look guilty.
Here we are! Come on, buddy.
Let me help you up there.
There you go.
Fine, I did something.
A terrible, terrible something.
One time I put a raw egg in my sock
drawer for a month,
then I smashed
it in my teacher's grade book.
- Ew!
- My dads were really mad.
Well, what I did was worse than that.
- Cool.
- Stop pouting.
- I'm not pouting.
Oh, please. I don't even have to look
at you. I can feel you pouting.
Whatever Meredith did,
it wasn't on purpose, so get over it.
I am not being inappropriate. He's
acting like she's skinned his puppy.
- Yang, this is not nice.
- I'm not a nice person.
If you knew what she did
you would understand.
No, I don't understand.
I don't wanna know.
What I want
is to analyze this angiogram,
book this sucker into surgery
and excise his cardiothoracic mass.
- Doesn't look like a mass to me.
- That's because it's not.
What we thought was a mass
is actually a coronary artery aneurysm
with a fistula
into one of your heart chambers.
Is that, uh, easy to fix?
Before you answer that, I want you
to know that we're getting married.
We're getting married
and we're not so young,
so we've been waiting
a long time for this.
I have my dress and everyone's coming
and it's supposed to be
the happiest day of our lives.
I'm telling you this because
you have this look on your face,
this dark, ominous look,
and we're silver-lining kind of people.
So I just thought it might help
if you knew that.
Dr. Yang? Would you close the door?
Well, we can...
We can operate on the aneurysm,
try to repair it,
but this type of lesion
is extremely delicate.
Chances of it rupturing
in surgery are high.
What keeps if from rupturing
if I'm just walking down the street?
Nothing. The risks are high either way.
This isn't happening.
This can't be happening.
- It's OK, Amy.
- No, it's not.
I know it's a lot to process,
but if we're going to operate,
we need to do it as soon as possible.
- We're getting married.
- Honey.
We're getting... We're getting married.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
They seem like a really nice couple.
They don't seem like they deserve this.
- They never do.
- Really?
I guess I just think...
I believe in karma.
You know,
good people deserve good things.
At least I thought
that's the way the universe worked.
How can you think that
and practice medicine?
Why...
I'm not saying that everybody who
gets sick or everybody who dies is bad.
I'm just saying that
I think that there's a balance.
Or there should be a balance.
There should be some sort of balance.
Good God, O'Malley,
what the hell did Grey do to you?
What do you mean
when you say blood in the ventricle?
Oh, my God! His brain is bleeding?
There's no need to panic.
It's a small amount of blood.
These injuries often resolve themselves.
But what if it doesn't?
Will he lose IQ points?
He's very smart. That's important
to him. He likes to be smart.
Should we sue that little brute
that hit the ball?
- Or the coach, should we sue the coach?
- Shawn loves the coach.
- Shawn's brain is bleeding.
- Rick...
Dad. I'm fine. Jeez.
Yeah, he's awake, alert, minimal pain.
These are good signs.
I just want to monitor him for 48 hours.
OK. Good.
Hear that Shawn? Good signs.
That means, honey,
you shouldn't be scared.
- I'm not.
- I am.
We know.
They paged you too?
Must be something big.
- Nobody paged me.
- They didn't? Can you tie this?
- Nobody paged you either.
- Yes, they did. I just got a...
Did you page me? Alex...
Ooh!
- You free tonight?
- I might be.
- Are you still working with Meredith?
- I'm trying to kiss you here.
Did she say anything about her and
George? I'm starting to get worried...
35-year-old male, shortness of breath.
- Pulse is rapid and irregular.
- Oh, my God. It's Denny.
- What?
- It's Denny.
- What'd he get in the field?
- He's my patient until I sign him over.
I know him. He's on top of the list for
a new heart. That makes him surgical.
Dr. Burke's on his way,
so you'd better start signing.
What did he get in the field?
40 of furosemide. Rhythm didn't change
after six of adenosine.
- What do we got?
- It's Denny.
Transplant candidate, acute dysrhythmia
and CHF. Vitals all over the place.
- His heart rhythm is a mess.
- He's in heart failure.
Bisoprolol can reduce mortality.
What about ACE inhibitors? And digoxin.
Somebody load him with dig!
Slow down. He's holding on.
Barely, but he's holding on.
There has to be something more
we can do.
The best we can do is get him up to CICU
and see if his heart will stabilize.
- Izzie, we should go.
- No, you go. I'm gonna stay.
- No. Yes, yes.
- I see you.
No, you don't.
Your husband was discharged
over an hour ago.
- I'm not here.
- Go home.
You're not working.
You're on maternity leave.
Exactly.
- Have you made your decision?
- Oh! Uh, about the surgery?
Um... No, we're still...
We're still talking about it.
We were thinking maybe we should
wait until after the wedding.
- So how is he?
- He's pretty much the same.
- Well, that's good, right?
- Uh, no. Not really. It...
With your condition,
you're gonna be OK until you're not.
If you opt against the surgery
and leave, it's just a matter of time.
You might make it to your wedding,
but you might not.
You're just gonna be OK until you die.
What...
You're trying to comfort me?
No. I'm trying to convince you
to let Dr. Burke operate.
So that he can die today?
He might die today anyway.
But Dr. Burke is the very best.
And he's your very best chance.
...5.0. WC: 13,700.
Stevens, everything all right?
Oh, it's just...
It's just not fair.
You know, it's really not fair.
We treat... jerks all the time.
Patch them up, send them off, whether
they deserve it or not. No big deal.
But Denny...
He's a good guy, Dr. Burke.
He's a really good guy with a bad heart
and all we can do for him is wait.
Believe me, I know.
I've been treating Denny a long time.
He didn't deserve this.
He deserves the best cardiac care
and we're giving him that.
You really like him, don't you?
He just...
He just doesn't deserve this.
OK.
All right. How's that?
Is that ice pack helping?
I don't know. I don't think so.
Mind if I ask
how exactly this happened?
- I slept with Mark!
- Oh! And he had poison oak on his...
No! I slept with Mark a year ago.
And, apparently, this is what I get.
Yeah. But how did you...
I live in a trailer.
I have Meredith Grey's dog.
And I went outside to throw a stick
and I had to pee. So I squatted.
I didn't want to go inside
and wake up my husband
because the way he's been looking at me,
I just wanted a few minutes of peace.
- This is what I get!
- No, no, no. Don't cry.
Don't cry. Please don't cry!
Please don't cry!
Stop! You're gonna make me...
lactate.
- Can you give some gauze? Here. Quick.
- I'm sorry.
Just stop!
Can I help you, chief?
Dr. Bailey...
I don't know what you're doing in there,
but whatever it is...
Oh.
Oh, no. Um...
Dr. Bailey, uh, I'm... sorry.
Carry on.
OK, fill me in.
I was doing his routine neuro check.
I noticed he was altered.
Most likely a clot. Acute hydrocephalus.
- We need to relieve the pressure.
- Cranial access kit's ready.
Cranial access?
Access to Shawn's brain?
- Debbie, get them out of here.
- Gentlemen.
- Rick...
- We're not going.
I'm about to drill a hole
into your son's skull.
He's our son. We're not leaving.
We are not leaving his side!
15 blade. I want a catheter ready to
drain as soon as I penetrate the dura.
Do not panic. I want the drill.
Almost... OK.
Look at that. OK. Catheter quickly.
- Pupil's reactive.
- Pressure stabilizing.
- Is he OK?
- I want neuro checks every hour.
- We're in the clear for now.
- In the clear?
- You guys did well.
- I have a headache.
Welcome back.
911.
Dad, you look white. Are you OK?
Oh, great.
Yes.
You got here quick.
We gotta get his heart rate
under control. Push 300 of amiodarone.
- Status?
- Atrial fibrillation.
His heart's beating too fast.
If we can't slow it...
It'll give out.
All right. Let's try synchronized
cardioversion. Push five of morphine.
Izzie?
- You're awake.
- Hey.
I was hoping I might get to see you.
You're working us pretty hard.
The things I have to do
to get a girl's attention.
Denny, we're about to send
electric currents through your body.
Hopefully, the shocks will be enough
to slow your heart rate.
- I'll be here the whole time.
- Is it going to hurt?
- It won't be fun.
- Maybe you oughta hold my hand then.
- Mind if I handle the paddles?
- Be my guest.
- Ready?
- Yeah. Hit me.
Clear.
No change. Try it at 100.
Clear!
Holy smoke!
Denny, you are a lucky man.
Oh, Doc. I oughta kick your ass,
making me yell like a baby in front
of the girl I'm trying to impress.
Oh! Jeez!
Take care, man.
Dr. Bailey. Dr. Bailey!
Didn't you hear me?
- I'm a little distracted right now.
- Oh, yes. I've been paging you.
I'm not on call. I'm on maternity leave.
I've been paging my wife as well.
You know where she is.
Just because I know
doesn't mean you should.
There's some things you don't get to
know. And, really, you don't wanna know.
You have to tell me where she is.
I saved your husband's life.
- She saved my baby.
- So baby trumps husband?
Baby trumps husband?
Hey, Amy.
The website said
that you should save your receipts.
- I'm sorry?
- Just in case something happens.
You know, to have them.
I have all of ours right here.
I've got, you know,
I've got my dress and the band
and I've got the ballroom deposit
and honeymoon.
My mom said I shouldn't keep them.
Said it was bad luck.
It was... It was tempting fate.
This isn't your fault.
You have a life. You fall in love.
You make plans. You have fantasies.
And none of them
involve all of them ending
in a blink of the eye.
- What are you doing?
- Hiding.
All right. So you slept with O'Malley.
Get over it already.
- He told you?
- Uh... no.
Oh, I was just kidding. I mean,
it's not like I should be surprised.
Why not?
Because when your life is sucking,
you get drunk and sleep with
inappropriate men. It's your thing.
Whatever. I find it charming.
You sleep with inappropriate women
when you're sober.
One inappropriate woman.
And Izzie forgave me for that.
- O'Malley won't get over this.
- She hasn't forgiven you.
- Yes, she has. We're together.
- No, you're not.
Izzie will never see you the way she
saw you before you slept with Olivia.
Why are you trying to piss me off?
You're suggesting it's forgivable
for you to sleep with Olivia,
but not for for me to sleep with George.
- You told him? I...
- George!
When I am wrong about someone,
I am really wrong!
- No, George! It's not what you think.
- Dude, chill.
You chill! You chill!
I'm not gonna chill!
- George. I...
- What's going on?
- Fetus is freaking out.
- Why?
You think that someone is...
your friend.
And that at the very least
she will respect your privacy!
- What's going on?
- He's freaking out.
- She can see that.
- Why is he freaking out?
- George, can we at least talk?
- I don't wanna talk. Not to you!
I wanted to keep my mouth shut!
And if you hadn't been running away
from me, you would know that!
OK, you're right, but can we talk now?
You want to talk now because
you told everyone that we had sex!
- You had sex?
- You had sex with George?
- You didn't tell them?
- No.
- Damn it!
- George!
George!
Go away.
He's gonna be OK, right?
He dislocated his shoulder.
He's gonna be fine.
That's not exactly what I meant.
Meredith,
if you can't make this right,
if you can't fix this with George...
Just so you know,
if it comes to choosing sides...
I'm on his.
He's the weaker kid.
I mean, even I don't beat up
on weaker kids. It's cheap.
I did a terrible thing.
I didn't...
He's been in love with you since day
one. There's no way you didn't know.
- We all do terrible things.
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
- George O'Malley?
- Uh, hi.
Dr. O'Malley.
The heart-in-the-elevator guy.
- Yeah, that's me.
- That was amazing.
Uh, thanks.
I dislocated my shoulder.
- Yeah.
- Oh!
- I can see that.
- It's really not so bad.
Yes it is. Pick your poison.
Uh... No painkillers, thanks.
- Bold choice.
- No. Officially I'm on duty.
- And planning to stay?
- Mm-hm.
Bolder choice.
All I need is help...
popping it back in.
- You got into a fight?
- I fell down some stairs.
- Where? At your girlfriend's?
- Wha...
- No, I'm single.
- Single, huh?
Hurts less if you don't see it coming.
- All set?
- All set.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
- Bye.
- Don't.
- Don't?
Don't be nice to me.
I did a terrible thing.
- We all do terrible things.
- No. I...
I did a thing
that I can't even believe I did and...
I was sad and...
I'm pretty sure
I'm gonna lose all my friends.
You won't lose me.
- You're not my friend.
- Yes, I am.
Well... I could be.
I'm a very good friend.
No. We can't be friends.
We could be friends.
You'd be lucky to have me.
How? How can we be friends?
We could uh...
hang out.
I walk Doc every other morning,
Tiger Mountain trail.
We could meet,
have coffee, watch Doc play and...
discuss the complex nature
of our existence.
- Right.
- We could. Might be fun.
- I could be your friend, Meredith.
- No. We can't be friends.
Just adding nitro.
Your blood pressure's stable now,
your CHF is improved
and the atrial fibrillation resolved.
- I like the way you say fibrillation.
- Fibrillation.
- Tease.
- How are you feeling?
You, uh... You believe in karma?
Um... Actually, I do, yeah.
I think you might be mine.
You must have been
very, very good to deserve me.
I must have.
OK.
- I wouldn't do that.
- Dr. Bailey...
If she wants privacy,
we will give her privacy. Understood?
- Dr. Bailey paged me.
- She did?
- Yeah.
- I did. And I'm still not here.
I'm still on maternity leave
and I still need privacy.
Come here.
No peeking, no pulling the curtain.
Stand there. Let her talk to you.
Understand?
- Is this really necessary?
- Do you understand?
- I'm not mentally challenged.
- I'm not sure about that. Let her talk.
- Addison, this is ridiculous.
- Stay where you are! Promise!
OK, I promise.
I'm going to show you something
and when I do,
you do not get to laugh
and you do not get to gloat.
- Why would I gloat?
- I have poison oak.
What?
Mm. You do indeed have poison oak.
So are we even yet? Is this bad enough?
Have I repaid my debt to society, Derek?
- Let's take a look.
- Ow!
Oh.
Good morning, Tuck.
Let's take your daddy home.
Hm? Oh...
She really didn't tell you about it?
No. God, is that a bad thing?
She tells you everything. It didn't
matter enough to her to talk about it.
OK, George. The pity thing? Not good.
If you want crappy things
to stop happening to you,
then stop accepting crap
and demand something more.
Hey, Amy.
Oh, could you tell Dr. Burke
that Keith is gonna have the surgery?
- Great.
- Where are you going?
Um, I...
I'm not strong enough for this.
Amy, I know it's hard, but your fiancé
is going in to surgery.
You're gonna want to be here
when he wakes up.
No, I won't. Um...
He's not my fiancé anymore.
- You're leaving him?
- I'm not strong enough for this.
So the "in sickness and in health"
part of your vows...
you were planning to leave those out?
Please try to understand.
I don't like that I'm not strong enough.
I just know that I'm not.
- George, he's crashing!
- What?
His aneurysm may have blown.
Page Dr. Burke!
OK, everyone.
It's actually
a coronary-artery aneurysm.
- He's gonna live?
- Burke's a miracle-worker.
D'you know this guy's fiancée left him?
Sounds like he dodged a bullet.
I don't think
he's gonna see it that way.
If she can't love him back
the way he loves her...
then she doesn't deserve him.
- You heard about me and Meredith?
- Well, everyone heard, George.
You were yelling about it
in the hallway.
Must have sucked. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
If I made you feel anything
like I'm feeling right now...
I'm sorry.
That's nice to hear.
- How's that?
- It was good. Really good.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Because, uh... I could do it again.
I like doing it.
- No, it's good.
- I could do it until you...
No, it's OK. I'm ready.
- Ow!
- Oh, I'm sorry.
OK. It's OK.
- There.
- Right there?
Meredith.
George.
- What's wrong?
- Oh, nothing.
Nothing's wrong.
Why would you think anything's wrong?
- You're crying.
- No. It'll stop. Just ignore me.
I can't ignore you.
Yeah, yeah.
It's fine. It's fine. Just...
It's OK. You're almost done, right?
No.
- George.
- Meredith...
George, please.
Sleeping with me
is really this awful for you?
No, George! It's not!
It's not you!
George!
There's a suitcase in the hall.
I was just getting my shirt.
- There's a suitcase...
- Yeah, uh...
I don't live here anymore. Excuse me.
Why?
I just wanna know why you...
- If you didn't want to...
- I didn't know I didn't want to.
You were there.
And you were saying
all these perfect things and I was sad.
And so I thought, maybe...
Maybe I've just been overlooking
what's been in front of me.
And if I just give it a chance,
because you're George
and you're so great...
I didn't know I didn't want to
until I knew I didn't want to.
Yeah.
OK.
Can we please just go back
to everything the way it was?
I don't know how to go back.
No. I'm done.
We're done.
One way or another, our karma...
will leave us to face ourselves.
We can look our karma in the eye
or we can wait for it
to sneak up on us from behind.
- You ready?
- What?
Aren't we...
I thought we had plans for tonight.
Oh. I forgot. I'm sorry.
- Rain check?
- Sure.
Amy?
She's not... here.
But you are. That's what's important.
She left?
She really left.
Who does that?
What kind of person does that?
One way or another
our karma will always find us.
- Hey.
- Hey, yourself.
Wow.
I gotta say, not exactly how
I'd envisioned our perfect first date.
Are you kidding?
Do you know how hard I've had to work
to get a cute boy in bed before?
You think I'm cute.
OK. Shut up and drink your juice.
And the truth is, as surgeons...
we have more chances than most
to set the balance in our favor.
- George?
- Dr. Torres.
Callie.
- You going on a trip?
- Sorta.
Well, in that case...
Give me a call
when you get back in town.
No matter how hard we try,
we can't escape our karma.
It follows us home.
He's your friend
and he needed our help.
- Are his problems surgical?
- No.
Then, technically,
he doesn't need our help.
- You're a good person.
- I am not.
- Good night.
- Oh, good night.
Good night!
I guess we can't really
complain about karma.
It's not unfair, it's not unexpected.
It just... evens the score.
Good boy. Good boy.
Even when we're about to do something
we know will tempt karma
to bite us in the ass...
Well, it goes without saying...
- So...
Just friends.
... we do it anyway.
www.tvsubtitles.net