Previously on Grey's Anatomy:
I did a terrible thing.
- Sleeping with me is this awful?
- No, George!
I grew my hair for her.
I could be your friend.
- Why do you think she cheated on you?
- I was just a little absent.
Give me a call when you're in town.
I thought we had plans.
Not how I envisioned our first date.
Can we please just go back
to everything the way it was?
- I don't live here anymore.
- Your friend needed our help.
- Good night.
Good night.
As doctors,
patients are always telling us
how they would do ourjobs.
"Just stitch me up,
slap a Band-Aid on it and send me home. "
It's easy to suggest a quick solution
when you don't know much
about the problem,
when you don't understand
the underlying cause,
orjust how deep
the wound really is.
So, your friends,
are they still mad about
this bad, horrible thing you did?
The very horrible bad thing
I won't tell you?
- Yes, they are.
- Whatever it is, I don't want to know.
Even if I beg, don't tell me.
- OK. I won't.
- Good.
OK. Although we are friends.
- True.
- Technically, you tell friends stuff.
You come to me with a problem,
I give you the answer.
After, maybe we celebrate
the moments of our lives.
I will keep that in mind
next time I do a horrible thing.
Don't you have any problems
you want to tell me about?
Truthfully? This moment in time,
I don't have any problems.
Not a single one.
The first step toward a real cure
is to know exactly
what the disease is to begin with.
That's not what people want to hear.
Morning.
- How many miles was that, Dr. Burke?
- Five.
Five. Five miles in 50 minutes.
- Nice.
- We can get it closer to 45.
- Pancakes?
- Uh, top cupboard.
- What's wrong with your hair?
- Leave the man alone.
He's got issues.
And if he wants to cut his hair
to get over those issues,
that's his business, his thing.
It's my thing. Coffee?
Oh, cappuccino.
Ooh, excellent. Cappuccino.
We're supposed to forget the past
that landed us here,
ignore the future complications
that might arise,
and go for the quick fix.
- Is George having a nervous breakdown?
- Burke says he's got issues.
You should see them, like, doing things.
Like running and... cooking and talking.
They're like bonding.
And you're afraid Burke will realize
he makes a better girlfriend than you?
You know,
just go and apologize to him.
- I've tried.
- Try again.
Things can't stay like this.
They suck like this.
What's with O'Malley's hair?
He looks like a hobbit.
- He's just trying a new look.
- You didn't call back. You avoiding me?
Why would I be avoiding you?
Denny Duquette, aged 36.
37 in three weeks.
37 in three weeks. Has difficulty
breathing and chest pains.
- Breath sounds?
- A little junky.
He has a build-up of fluid.
Did you just call me a junky?
That's not very nice.
Denny, your congestive heart failure
is getting worse despite the meds.
All right. So how do we proceed?
Doctors, how do we proceed?
Titrate up his nitrate drip,
then diuretics.
ACE inhibitors, beta-blockers
and start dobutamine.
I want his ins and outs recorded and
one of you monitoring him at all times.
- I'll stay.
- Me, too.
Mr. and Mrs. Gibson,
Dr. Montgomery-Shepherd.
I'll be covering for Dr. Pollack.
Mrs. Gibson had a preterm, premature
rupture of her membranes at 28 weeks.
She's confined to bed rest for
seven weeks and has a low-grade fever.
Can't you just schedule a C?
Believe me, I am ready
to have this baby.
You and me both.
I want to get your blood work
before we make any further decisions.
I have to pee. Again.
Come on. Here we go.
I appreciate you
taking over my wife's case.
- Dr. Pollack says you're the best.
- It's my pleasure, Mr. Gibson.
He didn't mention that...
I mean, you bear a striking resemblance
to a young Catherine Deneuve.
Oh, you never heard that before?
Eh, no. I'm sorry.
- I have to say, it's a first.
- Been told I look like Halle Berry.
Beautiful.
Beautiful. Well, Ms. Deneuve.
Of course, you are, too,
but by extension.
Right. We'll be back in later
to check on your wife.
Look forward to it.
- ER needs a consult.
- O'Malley, Grey, you go take that.
- What about Mrs. Gibson?
- I'll take care of her.
- Uh, do they really need both of us?
- I guess you'll find out. Go.
- Are you taking him to the nursery?
- It's full and Tucker's out of town.
- You brought your baby to work?
- Uh, yes, Chief.
You're not taking him into surgery.
- I don't have anything scheduled.
- Yet.
I can't solve a problem
until there's one to solve.
- Are you saying there's a problem?
- Is there a problem, Richard?
No.
You know, at some point
you are going to have to talk to me.
I'm going to take the stairs.
- You paged?
- Just got a new patient.
Looks surgical, maybe neuro.
Doesn't look neuro to me.
- Not him.
- Oh no, I'm fine. It's my wife.
This is so embarrassing,
but we didn't know what else to do.
We were at the Hotel Monaco
having brunch. We had some mimosas.
Can we skip that part?
Can we pull this out and just go?
I'm fine, really.
Sylvia was giving me
some special attention.
- Under the table.
- Dear Lord.
Oh! OK.
Sweetie, they're doctors.
They've heard it all.
- Absolutely.
- While I was down there
it was like a shock
went through my body.
- And she... clenched.
- Clenched?
- My jaw. It just shut.
- Oh, and I panicked.
I grabbed the fork off the table
and it was just instinctual.
It doesn't hurt that much.
We just didn't want to pull it out.
It's in pretty good.
No, you did the right thing.
Pulling it out could cause more damage.
I want to do an X-ray
to make sure no nerve
or major blood vessels
are being compromised.
Did you get your injury checked?
Doctor says I'm fine.
It's just bruising.
I want to find out
what caused the clenching.
- Do you have a history of seizures?
- No, nothing like that.
It may... It may have something
to do with her brain aneurysm.
- Kyle. I don't want to do this now.
- It's not on there.
Can we just take this fork out and go?
No.
- She was diagnosed six weeks ago.
- Your doctor didn't recommend surgery?
All the surgeons say it's inoperable.
That's why Kyle and I
are here in Seattle.
The Space Needle.
- I've always wanted to see it.
- We wanted to see it together.
Do an MRI.
It's good to see you.
- What do we got?
- Tachycardic in the 140s.
Systolic dipped to the 60s.
Last was 72 over 40.
- Can you turn that off? Turn it off!
- OK.
Dr. Bailey?
- Here. Take him.
- Uh, what?
- Watch him.
- No, you don't want to do that.
Yang, I have a patient.
I need to operate
on that patient right now.
- We could page the chief.
- I'm not paging anyone.
I'm going to do the surgery.
Cris, I...
I need you to help me, Cristina.
I... I...
OK.
You watch from the gallery.
You both can.
- Hey.
- You didn't call me.
- I did, I did.
A few times.
I just hung up every time.
Nice, very stalker-like.
Goes with the hair.
I thought it would look good shorter.
It is shorter.
- I make you nervous, don't I?
- A little.
- That's good.
- That's no... What?
Hey, are you busy?
No.
Want to see something really cool?
Whoa.
Excellent, right?
- It is. How did you do that?
- After hockey practice.
I didn't have my glove on.
I was drinking from the goalie's bottle.
This asshat crashes into the net,
my hand gets tangled in the mesh
and I start hearing pops, big pops.
Dr. O'Malley, what do you see?
Ooh, dislocation of the PIP joint,
multiple fractures.
- That must really hurt.
- It's just a finger.
Last season I took a puck to the face,
broke two teeth.
Oh.
Orthos love hockey season.
It's Christmas every day.
Can we just put it in a splint?
I got a really big game this afternoon.
Um... do you know what you're doing?
I mean, have you ever done this before?
Have I ever pulled a fork out of a neck?
Hmm. Right.
OK. Let's just do it.
- Honey.
- Huh?
- Talk to me. Distract me.
- OK. Think about Paris, huh?
- And the food and the wine.
- Uh-huh.
And the long walks we'll take together.
And the Champs EI... What?
- The Champs Élysées.
- Yeah.
- More food, more wine.
- OK.
- That's it?
Oh, my God,
I didn't even feel anything.
You're amazing. She's amazing.
So... how much do you know
about this Dr. Shepherd?
- Kyle, no.
- What?
I do not want another MRI.
I want to go to Paris.
I made a few calls.
He has an incredible reputation.
Please, Kyle.
Let's just live our lives.
I want to go crazy.
I want to crawl underneath the table.
I want to go to Paris
while we still can.
Dr. Shepherd
is an extraordinary surgeon.
If he thinks he can help, a
second opinion couldn't hurt, could it?
It won't be a second opinion.
It'll be a fourth opinion.
And when Dr. Shepherd says
there's nothing more he can do,
we'll be devastated all over again.
I just want to spend
what little time we have left in Paris.
So do I. But I don't want to go to Paris
and wonder if we should have listened
to the amazing girl
who took the fork out of your neck.
- You're not Izzie.
- Sorry to disappoint you.
Not disappointed. Just saying.
- Where is she?
- Oh, she's busy with other patients.
I'm afraid you'll have
to make do with me.
Look, man, I'm sure you're...
I'm sure you're a fine doctor.
You're just...
You're just not as much my type.
No offense.
I'll just have to settle
on being Izzie's type.
So you...?
- You two...?
- Yeah, yeah.
Pretty much. You know.
Congratulations.
~ A, B, C, D...
Oh, gross.
~ E, F, G
~ This really couldn't suck any worse...
Dr. Yang?
- Oh, uh, Dr. Webber.
- What's that smell?
Uh, it's feces. It's baby feces.
We've had an incident, sir.
Are you having trouble
with the diaper, Yang?
- It looks like you're having trouble.
- No, sir.
I've got an MD from... Stanford
and a PhD from Berkeley.
I can handle this diaper.
Unless you want to.
Uh... no.
It's all right, it's all right.
You carry on.
Carry on.
- Can we stop for a moment, please?
- Sure.
I can walk.
- OK. The wheelchair is just protocol.
- Yeah, well...
I'm way past caring about protocol.
I just want to feel
my body move while I can.
You seem incredibly OK
with your prognosis.
I'm more than OK.
I'm a little in love with my prognosis.
It woke me up.
It woke my marriage up.
I've been sleepwalking about 15 years.
And now... I am wide awake.
I'm having this MRI for Kyle.
He's not ready to let go.
But me and my aneurysm?
We're good friends.
- Hey, I've been looking for you.
- Hey. Look.
- Look at the size of this aneurysm.
- Oh, it's big.
- Are you going to operate?
- I'm definitely intrigued.
- Do you know who Catherine Deneuve is?
- Um...
Yeah. Actress. French. Hot.
One of my patients, her husband,
said I looked like her.
Isn't she blond?
Yeah, I... guess. I don't know.
I don't know.
Anyways, uh...
- OK, you're busy.
- Bye.
I'm not just
another pretty face, you know.
- Got it going on up here as well.
- So you keep telling me.
Yep. I probably know...
hundreds of words.
Really? Hundreds?
Wow, you're a real brain trust.
Ouch.
Well, I'm highly competitive.
Screw.
S-C-R-E-W.
- That's 25 points. Thank you very much.
- Wait a second now.
You didn't tell me we were playing
naughty word Scrabble.
- We're not. You just have a dirty mind.
- Oh, it's filthy.
You're the one that put down "screw".
- I was referring to hardware, not sex.
- Oh.
I guess maybe sometimes it's, uh...
hard to tell where you're...
coming from.
What do you mean?
Alex, uh...
He may have said something
about you guys...
um, being together.
Well...
he had no business telling you that.
And besides,
it's not even true, so...
So you're not together?
No. I mean...
Yeah, a little, but...
Not really. So...
No.
OK, well, sweet. Thanks, uh...
Thanks for clearing that up.
Denny, what is it? Don't panic.
Just try to breathe.
Page Dr. Burke!
Just breathe. Just breathe.
Take it easy.
He had flash pulmonary edema.
I switched him to nesiritide,
started milrinone and put him on BiPAP.
- That's a good call, Stevens.
- Good call.
- Bad news, right?
- It's not good.
The fact is, Denny, you need a new heart
and you're running out of time.
So... what's behind door number two?
I would like to install
a left ventricular assist device.
It's a battery operated machine
to help your heart pump.
Battery operated?
I knew it. You people
are trying to turn me into a robot.
It's all part of your evil plan
to take over the hospital.
It's a bridge to transplant, Denny.
It'll keep you alive
while we wait for your new heart.
That easy, huh?
- No catch?
- There are some risks.
Increased damage to your platelets
and increased bleeding.
If you do choose the assist device,
you may not leave hospital
until you get a donor heart.
Any other options?
I'm going to need time to think.
Don't take too long, Denny.
- Always happy to get this page.
- That's not why I paged you.
Oh, what you paged me
to the on-call room to talk?
No, I paged you
to the on-call room to yell.
Why the hell
did you talk to Denny about us?
Oh, you never talk to Denny
about personal stuff?
Not about our sex life, Alex!
That is between us.
So none of your friends know
we sleep together?
Are you saying
you and Denny are friends?
- I'm not friends with patients.
- You're an ass.
You feel threatened by him.
That is why you did that.
You're his doctor and he's your
half-dead, soon to be all-dead, patient.
How could I possibly be threatened
by that guy?
I can't believe you just said that.
Someone's got to.
I'll schedule the surgery for your son.
In the meantime,
I'm sending Heath home
with a prescription for hydrocodone
to control the pain.
I get that this is a bad break,
but it doesn't hurt much.
I'm telling you, I can handle this.
Here's what I'm thinking:
we put a splint on my finger
so I can jam it into the glove,
play today and I'm all yours.
- You are not playing today!
- Heath, your mom is right.
Thank you.
Did you hear that? I'm right.
- Your mother must be proud.
- Scouts are coming, college scouts.
I could get a scholarship today!
If I cut that bandage off
we risk permanent damage to your finger.
I'm with you, but I'm sorry.
There's no way we can put your finger
into a glove today.
There must be something you can do.
I need to play this afternoon.
This game is what
I've been training for my entire life.
This is my chance to go to college,
it's my whole future.
Honey, you can go
to community college.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- Ooh. That sucks.
- Yeah.
Oh, Dr. Montgomery-Shepherd.
- Are those my wife's test results?
- Yes, they are actually.
There's no infection.
I'm scheduling a C-section
this afternoon.
I was actually going to go up
after lunch and tell her.
- Mr. Gibson...
- You do look like Catherine Deneuve.
I'm talking to you about your wife...
- giving birth to your baby.
- I know.
I'm sorry. May I?
Listen, I don't mean
to focus on your looks.
You seem very kind, intelligent.
You're a doctor.
I don't mean to objectify
or harass you in any way.
I'm usually not this awkward, but...
you're just
so extraordinarily beautiful.
I understand if a woman like you
doesn't want to eat with me.
So, uh... Well, anyway.
No, no.
- Really?
- Yes, stay. It's fine.
All right.
You going to eat that pudding?
- Take him.
- Bailey gave him to you.
She's only in surgery
for another half hour, hour tops.
- Take him.
- You're a liar and you smell of vomit.
Really? Because I think
she smells like poo.
This is why some species
eat their young.
- Have you talked to Meredith yet?
- Tomorrow I am going to buy a T-shirt
that says,
"Stop asking me about Meredith".
I'm going to wear it every day
until people stop asking me.
At least they won't be asking you
about your hair.
Oh, come on. Meredith, stop him.
What should I do? Knock him down?
Do you know he cut his hair
over my bathroom sink today?
George is a good roommate.
You can tell him what's annoying you.
No, he's not my room... This is why
I shouldn't have given up my place.
He would still be our roommate
if Meredith would apologize.
I have apologized.
I've apologized sincerely.
And you know what?
It takes two to make
a stupid sexual decision. So, whatever.
Oh!
Oh, I just miss when we all got along.
- Can't we just go back to that?
- Well...
Excuse me.
I have to check on a patient.
Awesome. Awesome.
Thanks, Alex. Thank you. Oh, yeah.
OK. Shut it.
Shut it. Shut it.
They have no right to be mad at me.
- It's none of their business.
- I agree.
You don't even know
what I'm talking about.
You're mad at your friends
for being mad at you.
I hate them. I do.
What the hell did you do?
I'm not telling you.
You know, as a friend, you suck.
Does Addison know we're friends?
Did you get Sylvia Booker's
blood work back yet?
I'm going right now.
- Dr. Bailey?
- What is it, Yang?
Uh... he's crying.
Let me hear him.
- What?
- Let me hear the baby cry.
Um...
That's cry number four.
You need to feed him.
Oh, God! Oh...
- A double-barrel what?
- It's a double-barrel brain bypass.
I'm going to use two scalp arteries
to redirect the blood flow in your brain
around the aneurysm.
- How come no one else mentioned this?
- This surgery is rarely performed.
I have performed one
and I've watched one.
But I don't want
to understate the risks.
- Risks?
- The risks are that the aneurysm
- could rupture on the table.
- But there's a chance it could work?
No.
Hell, no.
I'm leaving
and we're going to Europe.
We've always wanted to see it,
we've never had the time.
This is the time.
We're going. That's it.
- Dr. Shepherd? Can I get a word?
- Yes.
- I'm sorry if my wife offended you.
- Oh, no. No offense at all.
Um... I didn't notice her.
- I'm sorry? I...
- For 15 years, I didn't notice her.
When we got married,
she was everything.
Somewhere along the way, I stopped
noticing her, stopped seeing her.
And since she's been sick,
she's all I see.
And I hate that that's what it took.
I hate it and I'm sorry.
But I love her.
And I don't want her to...
I don't want my wife to die.
Please talk to her.
Dr. Shepherd, please.
OK.
I had a lunch date
with my patient's husband today.
He paid attention to me, Miranda.
For a whole half hour.
Addison, you're not going
to fix the problems with your husband
by having meals with someone else's.
I mean it.
Oh, please eat. Eat!
I'm begging you to eat.
It's yummy food. Yummy.
Bailey, breast... milk.
- Food, come on!
- Well, look at you.
- You find this amusing?
- You don't?
You know what? I can't help you.
I cannot help you
if you don't want to eat.
If you're going to keep on crying...
Then eat.
O'Malley, you're a natural.
You have nieces and nephews?
- Babies just like me.
- It speaks to a good bedside manner.
- Keep it up.
- Thank you, sir.
Hey, is that Bailey's baby?
Oh, he is so cute.
Hi there.
I scheduled the Mercer kid's surgery
for tomorrow. Do you want in?
Oh, no, I want in, on any surgery.
- I'll do it.
- Who are you?
I'm Cristina.
- Sorry. I only need one.
- Oh. Well, absolutely. I'm in.
Oh, and George? This is
the last invitation I'm extending.
So... the ball's in your court.
- OK.
- Seriously?
- Seriously.
Nice. Think she has
a couch you can sleep on?
Mrs. Booker.
I'm waiting for my husband.
He's bringing the car.
Mrs. Booker...
I know you're worried
about the surgery.
No I'm not. I'm not worried about it
because I'm not having it.
You're not having the surgery
because of the medical risks?
No, I'm not having it because...
because for the first time in 12 years,
I have a great marriage and a life.
And I want to live it.
You have weeks.
If this surgery is successful,
you're looking at decades.
I don't think you understand.
I'm not crazy and I don't want to die.
I don't want to go back to being Kyle's
bed warmer in a flannel nightgown.
- Can you understand?
- I understand you're tired of settling.
So don't.
Fight.
Fight for your life,
fight for your marriage.
Let me operate.
And make a decision right now
that you'll never settle again.
The LVAD will inhibit
organ deterioration,
allow you to get off the meds you're on
and give your heart
a much-needed rest.
Izzie.
I'm just...
I'm so tired.
I appreciate that.
But the LVAD also has
increased survival rates
over conventional therapies
and I think that you need...
Hey.
Having this surgery...
it means I don't get to leave here.
And you know
how much I hate hospitals.
I do know.
But as your doctor, I can't
support you making any other decision.
This surgery will allow you more time
and we need more time.
We?
We, your doctors...
need more time.
And we need more time.
So... you'll be here?
Every day.
And as an added bonus,
it'll really piss off Alex.
Yes, that it will.
OK.
OK?
OK. OK.
- Heath.
- I told you I couldn't miss my game.
I made two goals and one assist
and there were scouts!
- What did you do?
- I cut off my finger.
It's OK. I saved it
so you guys can sew it back on.
There's deep tissue infection here.
Not good.
He said he found out
how to do it on the Internet.
Who puts up Web pages
on how to cut off your own finger?
He's got a passion and he sacrificed
for it. You got to respect that.
No... you don't.
Thank you, Bokie.
He cut off his finger.
A finger... Sorry.
...that would have healed
in a few months.
Sometimes you can't wait.
You just want the pain to stop.
So you cut it off.
End the problem. End the pain.
That doesn't... end the pain.
I mean, if it's that painful...
to start with,
then even if you cut it off,
there's always going
to be that... phantom pain.
Your ex did a real number on you, huh?
- You're quitting your job?
- Absolutely.
And we're selling the house?
And we're moving to Paris
and we're spending that nest egg now?
- Promise?
- I promise.
- And, baby?
- Yeah?
If I die...
promise me you'll do it anyway.
I promise.
I'm sorry.
This is as far as you can go.
Sylvia, please don't die.
I'll do my best.
I fed him.
Oh, God, there's poop everywhere.
Wait.
- Go back to sleep, Cristina.
- Oh, good.
I know you're the boss of me
and you could destroy my career
and make my life a living hell
and torture and all of that.
But, just in the future...
I don't baby-sit.
Fine.
I read that a patient's heart
can remodel itself
and they can be
weaned off the LVAD.
It's not likely in Denny's case.
His heart is too weak.
I just wanted to make sure
everybody was doing OK.
Everything's fine.
Thank you so much.
Oh, yeah, right... Thank you.
When you put your freshly severed finger
into a grungy, bacteria-filled glove,
- you got a severe infection.
- What?
No, the Internet didn't say
anything about infection.
We didn't realize how deep the infection
had gone until we were in there.
- There was too much tissue damage.
- The infection was caused
by a methicillin-resistant
staph bacteria.
It's spreading. We'll be lucky
if we can preserve enough muscle
for you to have any hand function.
What does she mean?
You may never regain
complete control of your hand.
No. That's wrong.
You're wrong.
Ronnie Lott played for the 49ers
when he cut off his finger.
He could still play.
I got the directions off the Internet.
- My poor baby.
- Mom, stop, they're lying!
They're trying to scare me.
I'm sorry. I really am, but...
your hockey career is over.
Mom.
Mom, they're wrong, right?
- They have to be wrong.
- Sweetheart.
I got the directions off the Internet.
Is there any evidence
of vasospasm or bleeding?
- No, it looks good.
- So do you think they'll move to Paris?
I hope so.
That was amazing.
It was, wasn't it?
Yeah.
Meredith...
You know I was kidding this morning?
I mean, you can tell me
about this horrible thing.
Come on, you can talk to me.
As a friend?
As a friend.
There's a line
between friends and "not" friends.
And if I tell you this...
If I tell you this horrible thing,
you have to react as my friend,
not my "not" friend.
I can do that.
All right, you tell me what's wrong,
I'll tell you how to fix it.
- OK. You're ready?
- I'm ready.
I slept with George.
And... it was a horrible mistake.
And now everything has changed.
And I don't know how to repair it.
I don't even know where to start,
but I just know that I have to. And...
Say something friendly.
You tell him that.
You find George and you apologize.
That's what everyone says,
but he won't listen.
Make him listen. You tell him.
Just tell him again and again
and again until he listens.
How do I do that?
You do what I do.
Use the elevator.
You're trapped.
And you don't have to talk.
I'll do the talking.
George,
I am truly, very deeply sorry.
And I'm not going to make excuses.
I'm just sorry.
Look, I know you're going to get
off this elevator and not look back.
I know that, but, George,
we're friends, real friends.
That means,
no matter how long it takes,
when you finally do decide to look back,
I'll still be here.
As doctors, as friends,
as human beings,
we all try to do the best we can.
Hey.
- Don't you have somewhere to be?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I'm there.
But the world is full
of unexpected twists and turns.
And just when you've gotten
the lay of the land,
the ground underneath you shifts
and knocks you off your feet.
If you're lucky, you end up
with nothing more than a flesh wound,
something a Band-Aid will cover.
- Hi.
- Hey.
But some wounds are deeper
than they first appear
and require more than just a quick fix.
What?
I was indifferent.
You know,
in New York before Mark.
I was just indifferent towards you.
Yes.
I was absent.
I'm partly to blame
for what's happened to our marriage.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I'm working on it.
OK.
With some wounds,
you have to rip off the Band-Aid,
let them breathe
and give them time... to heal.
www.tvsubtitles.net