Previously on
"Grey's Anatomy"...
When I told you I was
done trying to compete?
That was me breaking
up with you.
I broke up with Finn.
- Yeah.
The patient died last month
from complications following a heart transplant.
- Denny.
Are there any questions for me?
I got shot. I'm not fine.
You're not fine.
You quit being a surgeon.
You'll stand on my right side,
I'll look at you,
and you'll know to slide in to
do the sutures we've practiced.
Nobody has to know.
To make it...
really make it...
as a surgeon...
it takes
major commitment.
We have to be willing to
pick up that scalpel
and make a cut that may or may
not do more damage than good.
It's all about
being committed...
because if we're not...
we have no business picking up
that scalpel in the first place.
Put Burke in O.R. 2 tomorrow at
10:00 A.M., the usual scrub team.
And get rid of his
valve replacement at 2.
That's no-- that's no good.
- Yang,
Brought you a latte.
You're not scrubbing in.
But Burke always
lets me scrub in.
Hey, Yang, uh, can i get in on Burke's-
- No, no, okay?
No residents.
Burke says you crowd him,
so just go away.
Make sure you put the instrument
tray on his left-hand side.
He needs the extra elbow room.
And remember, O.R. Two.
No gallery. Burke was specific.
Dr. Burke's become very specific
since coming back to work, hasn't he?
Do you want me to tell
him you said that?
Burke's back, and suddenly
Cristina's running his board?
Who does she think
she is--Bailey?
She's helping him.
Bull. She's taking advantage.
She gets out of rounds, she scrubs
in on every surgery Burke does,
she's ordering around
third-year residents.
You guys are overreacting.
I'm so sorry.
It's completely illegible.
I mean,
why don't you just write it properly?
She is writing on
the O.R. Board.
Maybe I should
sleep with Burke.
You've been busy.
Yeah.
Derek hasn't called yet.
I told him I broke up
with Finn a week ago.
He still hasn't called.
Hey, do you want to go grab a drink, catch up?
- Uh, no, I can't.
I have to study up for
Burke's surgeries tomorrow.
She's busy.
Callie.
Hey, talk to me.
Hey, how about talking to
me instead of ignoring me?
Callie.
- George!
Well, that's talking.
That's a good start.
Oh!
Oh, god.
Hey, stranger.
Oh, Nancy.
You don't call first?
Hi. You know, I...
Meredith.
Oh, Meredith.
Wait. Let me explain. Meredith.
Oops. I take it that was the slutty
intern you cheated on Addison with?
She's not slutty.
What are you doing here?
You bailed on Thanksgiving
and Christmas,
and you live in a trailer,
and you're getting a divorce.
And then there's the slutty intern.
- I really don't like you.
You love me.
Feeling good. Really good.
Good.
- Good.
Yeah, first day back.
It's big. Kinda nervous.
But feeling good.
Do I look okay?
- Great.- Great.
I want to get off
on the right foot.
Gotta  get my I.D.
renewed, new time card,
sign some papers with legal,
and then I'm back.
I'm really back.
- Yeah.- Yeah.
This is me--human resources.
See you guys on the floor.
Yeah.
Okay, I'll be Cristina for
you if you'll be Izzie for me.
Deal.
Derek had a woman in
his trailer last night.
She was ugly, very ugly.
Except she was tall
and beautiful.
And he was naked.
Oh, uh...
McDreamy was doing the
McNasty with a McHottie?
That McBastard.
How--how was that?
That was good.
- Cristina enough? Really?
Yeah.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Yeah, 'cause-- -
Channeling Izzie. Go.
Okay, uh, Callie...
She won't forgive me.
Um... She won't talk to me.
She dumped me.
Which is, uh...
I don't care about,
you know, at all.
Good, because you
deserve better.
You do.
You are George.
I mean, seriously.
Seriously.
Was that Izzie-optimistic?
- That's very Izzie.
What the hell has
happened to us?
We are now the people that the
people we want to be with avoid.
We have careers to think about.
We don't need attention
from men with perfect hair.
You know,
we should make a pact.
There's no more dating.
No more Derek. No more Callie.
Just 100% focus on our work.
They're dead to us.
- They are freakin' corpses to us.
Preston Burke.
What a pleasure.
I have read so much about you.
Well, thank you.
Pruitt  Byrd.
Medivac brought him in this morning.
He presents with a
primary cardiac tumor.
We've been told Pruitt needs a
"cardiac autotransplantation".
A cardiac autotransplantation?
A humpty dumpty surgery.
- Yes, I know what it is.
Mrs. Byrd,
this is a very complicated surgery.
You'll need thorough testing.
- Oh, already done.
Mr. Byrd is a
perfect candidate.
You understand what this
surgery entails? We have to--
we have to remove his heart,
cut it open,
scrape out all the tumor and then
put his heart back together again.
Which is risky.
But possible.
- Which is why we're here.
I want the very
best for my Pruitt.
The best.
- She means you.
I know that, however--
- I've scheduled Mr. Byrd
for surgery this afternoon.
Just trying to be as
efficient as possible.
Legal cleared Stevens.
Explain her parameters and
make sure she understands.
What, Stevens is being
assigned to me again?
She's your intern.
But I-I didn't think that--
wouldn't be better for her to
start fresh with
another resident?
You don't want her, huh?
- I... want her to succeed.
There's still a good deal of
fallout after the Duquette M&M.
There's been talk.
Look, I don't need to tell you that
there are doctors in this hospital
who have concerns
about your judgment.
Concerns about my judgment?
- Stevens was your mistake.
Do you, sir?
Do you have concerns about my judgment?
Do you?
You're not gonna put
those concerns to rest
by avoiding taking
responsibility for Dr. Stevens.
She's your intern... again.
Transfer from Mercy West.
Noelle Labatt, 32 weeks along,
pregnant with twins.
One appears to be developing
more slowly than the other.
Hi.
- Hi, there.
Greg Stanton. This is my fiancée,
the future Mrs. Stanton--uh, Noelle.
Greg, I promise you, you're the only
person who cares if we're married
or not.
They said at mercy that
we had to come here
because her condition
could be serious.
I-is it serious?
- I've got to say, at first glance,
you don't seem emergent enough for Mercy
to send you over here in an ambulance.
You're not in labor, you're not
bleeding, your vitals are fine.
They said I need a specialist
because of my thing.
Your thing?
- Two uteruses?!
Ms. Labatt, uh, Noelle was born
with two uteruses. Uh, uteri?
Uteruses.
- Uteruses.
That's very rare.
I'm here. Hi. Hello.
That paperwork took--
Well, forever.
But I'm all do with it now,
and can I just say how...
really grateful
I am to be back?
You understand there are
rules to your probation,
a protocol to follow?
Yeah,  I know. Legal already took
me through lots of that stuff--
the mandatory counseling,
the extra lab hours,
the volunteer work with
transplant patients.
That's the stuff you're
doing for the chief.
I'm talking about what
you're doing for me.
Okay, uh...
what am I doing for you?
Okay, let's start with
what you don't get to do.
You will not interact
with any patients.
You will not be alone
You will be seen and not heard.
You will perform no procedures.
The O.R. is off limits.
No pre-op, no post-op,
no anything have to
do with an "op."
You have no authority,
you have no opinions and you
have no choice in this matter.
Am I understood?
Is... there anything I can do?
I want to be useful.
Well... I can't use you.
You've got to earn back the right
for any of us to trust you again.
Until then, you will be shadowing
a different doctor each day.
Okay, well, who am I with today, Dr.
Montgomery, you?
Dr. Bailey, you paged.
Dr. Grey.
Meredith?
You're to make sure that
Stevens observes only.
You want me to...
Wait, Meredith...
Meredith  is the boss of me?
Grey's Anatomy - Episode 306
Let the Angels Commit
I'm sorry, about this.
It's not your fault.
Hey, you want me to
fetch you some coffee,
rub your feet maybe?
I did not ask for
this assignment.
I'm fine with it.
Really, it's fine.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
- Dr. Stevens--
Hey, Dr. Shepherd.
- Welcome back.
Okay.
Uh, Meredith, Meredith--
- Sorry, it's not like I can leave.
I gotta stay by my boss' side.
Okay, the trailer sucks,
but in the light of day,
the land's nice.
Seattle's pretty
in the daylight,
plus you have your
thing for ferries, so...
- Ferry boats.
Right. Whatever.
Dr. Stevens, uh, Meredith,
this is my sister Nancy.
Oh, hi.
Sister?
Yeah.  Mm-hmm.
Oh. You're one of
Derek's sisters.
Yeah, well,
I knew you didn't think I was the wife
seeing as you
already ran her off.
Nancy is visiting
from Connecticut.
She's on her way home now,
straight back home.
Well, it was nice to meet you.
- Okay.
McDreamy's sister's McBitchy.
You put me in charge
of your schedule.
To make sure that I didn't
get a surgery like this one.
Only a handful of people
do humpties, Burke,
and you're the best
one on the west coast.
Well, he can go to Houston.
- Hey, you want--
You want to tell
that to the chief?
Pruitt needs this surgery.
He'll die without it.
You didn't tell me.
You told the patient we
were doing the surgery,
but you didn't tell me.
I have been doing
that all week.
Are you up on the humpty?
Do you realize what this entails?
I have done my research.
Stop worrying.
We are a well-oiled machine.
Uh, Dr. Burke.- Yeah.
I understand there are some
doctors in this hospital
who have concerns about
my judgment since Denny.
Well, everybody loves a scandal.
- So you think it's just gossip,
not actual concern
about me as a doctor?
Sure. Sure.
'Cause...
Ow. Iz,
set me up for debridement and dressing.
It was stupid. I know better.
When I'm studying for the bar,
I'm a mess.
I can't focus on
anything for weeks
but torts and real property
and constitutional law.
Uh, the biosynthetic ones.
We never use those.
We do now. Sloan changed
the burn protocol last week.
I was about to start a practice test,
and I wanted some tea,
so I put on a pot of water and
hit the timer and just forgot.
Half an hour into my
section on contracts,
the smoke alarm was blaring,
and well, you know the rest.
So you're gonna be a lawyer?
All I have to do is
pass the bar exam.
I failed before,
but this time I'm ready.
I'm gonna pass.
Good for you.
That was just mean.
Kathleen called and told me to find
out why the slutty intern's panties
were hanging on the
hospital bulletin board.
Four sisters--four sisters
and not one brother,
and you wonder why
I don't call more.
Feel free to explain about
the panties at any time.
Nance, you know what?
It's great to see you.
Really great to have you here.
But I have a job, you know?
I have patients.
I have a mother at 35 weeks with twins.
Where is her O.B.?
Well, her O.B. should be on a plane
back to Connecticut where she belongs.
Okay, so we've covered the trailer. We
still need to cover the slutty intern
and the divorce.
You know what? You sound more
and more like mom every day.
Take it back!
So two uteruses...
that's pretty cool.
And you're engaged.
That's also cool.
Well, Greg talked me into it.
Oh, man, from the first moment
I saw Noelle, I was ham.
Did you just say "ham"?
- You're either ham or eggs.
Here we go.
- You gotta ask yourself in every situation,
are you the chicken
or are you the pig?
Sorry, pig or chicken?
Look, you got a plate of ham and eggs,
all right?
Now--now the chicken is
involved in the meal,
but the pig--
now the pig is committed.
So the question is--
are you involved or are you committed?
Ham or eggs.
Karev, you free?
Absolutely, sir.
Great, take this.
I'm on hold with the D.M.V.
Some mix-up about switching my
license and registration to Seattle.
Take care of that for me?
Thanks for thinking of me, sir.
O'Malley, how's it feel to
be the new gynie grunt?
Oh, I got a patient who was born with
and is pregnant in two uteruses.
Two uteruses. Jealous?
No. No, I'm--I'm--
I'm busy. I'm on hold.
Oh.
- Yeah, important business.
Right.
- For Sloan.
Right, it's super important,
I'm sure.
Noelle Labatt, room 2314.
Two, two, two, two, two, two
Hang on.
Can I see that for a sec?
Did I just hear him
say "two uteruses"?
I'm sorry. You-- you must be...
Nancy-pants?
Hey, loser.
I wish Derek had told me
you were coming to visit.
Oh, like he tells you
anything these days?
Yeah, well,
I'm working on that.
What are you doing here, Mark?
Are you trying to torture him?
He's my family, Nancy.
Plus, I needed a
change of pace.
Plus, I slept with my
tennis partner's wife,
and he went out
and bought a gun.
There it is.
Oh, my God. Nancy!
Let me guess.
Did mom send you out?
I hear Derek's trying to
ban you from Seattle.
Did he also tell you that he's living in a trailer?
- Yeah.
Derek.
Oh, Derek.
I want to see the two uteruses.
Yeah, um, find me later.
I miss her.
Yeah... me, too.
The diesel pushes past
cornerback Don McNeal.
He's at the 30.
He's at the 20.
He's at the 10.
Touchdown, washington Redskins.
I'm sorry.
One of the twins gets rowdy,
and Greg gets carried away
when talking to the baby.
He's decided that the baby is
into sports, of all things.
Well, she's daddy's
little girl.
I can tell, see,
because when I talk to her--
yeah, the rhythm in your voice,
it helps calm her. Sure.
I  read a couple of articles
on that recently, actually.
Dr. Karev, I knew you secretly missed my service.
- Right.
Greg, Noelle,
I have very good news for you.
According to our tests,
the babies are both perfectly healthy.
But they are substantially different
sizes for a very unique reason.
The test indicate that the babies
have two different due dates.
According to our calculations,
the larger baby, your son,
was conceived a full six
weeks before your daughter.
I...
- Oh, God.
I-I don't--
I-I don't understand.
That--that can't be right.
That's impossible.
No, actually,
it's quite possible.
Our tests are extremely accurate
in predicting due dates.
But we broke up.
Yeah, see, she, um, she got pregnant.
I wanted to get married.
She didn't.
I gave her an ultimatum,
and she left me.
Greg, I am so sorry.
I am so, so sorry.
I mean, we were barely speaking
six weeks after the conception,
let alone having sex.
Or at least I
wasn't having sex.
It was one night, Greg.
It was one night.
I-I didn't think that this could happen.
It was nothing.
I can't believe you did this.
I can't believe
you didn't tell me.
Oh...
- God, I can't believe this.
He's not the father
of both babies.
I just accidentally broke the news of
my patient's infidelity to her fiancé.
And yet no one is questioning
your competence as a surgeon.
No. What?
I need a button.
I'm down to my last clean shirt,
and I'm missing a button.
Adele always
handled my buttons.
Have you called her?
- Adele?
Oh, no, no. I wouldn't want to bother
her with something as trivial as
a button.
I don't suppose either
of you would want to...
I'm sorry.
I have two uteruses
I have to attend to.
I have many skills,
many skills, surgical skills.
Your button ruptures its oesophagus,
I'm your woman.
Otherwise...
I hear you burned your hand
because you were studying?
I can't even be allowed to warm soup
within five days of taking the bar.
So you burned your hand while you were-
- Burning my soup.
And when you grabbed the pot-
- Dropped it, obviously. I mean,
it was literally red hot.
You must have held on to it
for a little while, though.
This burn's extremely deep.
Oh, yeah. No, that's right.
I held on, and then I dropped it.
There are some deep partial
thickness burns here.
Give her a gram of
cefazolin and a tetanus.
It's too bad, really,
that I did this to my hand.
I'm supposed to be taking
the bar again friday.
This burn is bad,
but we'll get you fixed up.
You'll be fine to take
the test on friday.
I will?
She's lying.
Something's off about Gretchen's story.
- Izzie,
you're only supposed
to be observing.
I am observing.
I'm observing closely.
And I'm telling you something is off.
Did you see her reaction when Sloan told
her he'd be okay to take the test again?
That was not relief.
That was panic.
It's okay to be nervous about being
back here at work, about failing,
but you haven't even been
back a full day yet,
and already you're pushing to bend the rules.
- Meredith,
Meredith, this is
so not about me.
This is about our patient.
I am worried about our patient,
and get off your
high freakin' horse.
This is my patient.
Try to remember that.
Fine. Whatever.
- Iz.
A humpty dumpty surgery?
B-burke's doing a
humpty dumpty today?
Um, yes.
Well, I've never seen a
humpty firsthand before.
Yeah, me neither.
Uh, what are you doing?
Scrubbing in.
You'll let Burke know?
Sure.
I know you're not talking to me anymore,
and that's okay,
but there's something
I'd like to explain.
All you have to do is listen.
You and me,
we're like ham and eggs.
I was the chicken.
I just want you to know that
I know that I was the chicken.
You put yourself out there
and you were committed,
and I was just putting
the eggs on the plate.
Not the ham,
because you were the pig.
I was involved,
but now I'm committed.
Did you just call me a pig?
- No, it's a metaphor.
Calling me a pig?
The point is,
you're not the pig anymore.
What I'm trying to say is I'm the pig.
Now I am the pig.
I am the pig.
I've been waiting for you guys for
a half an hour in the cafeteria.
Since when do we eat
in a patient room?
Izzie, meet really old guy.
We found him a
couple of days ago.
He sleeps all the time.
It's quiet in here.
Nobody bothers us.
No, what are you doing?
It turns out I'm
not doing anything.
I'm literally not
allowed to do anything.
I knew coming back was gonna be an adjustment,
- No.
- but this is just--
- What are you doing right now?
- Eating my lunch.
- Okay, if you want to socialize
or talk about your day or get
in a quick therapy session,
you know, go do it over there.
Seriously?
Good-bye, Izzie.
- Okay, fine.
So, O'Malley,
your chick with the two uteruses?
You're on scut--
glorified plastics scut.
You are in no position to
mock me or my uteruses.
Any cervical changes
on the ultrasound?
Why do you care?
- I don't.
I'm so glad to be back. Yay!
I'm not complaining about you.
You and I are fine, boss.
This is weird.
I called callie a pig.
To her face?
What happened to the whole
she's a corpse thing?
I just can't get over how much
everything around here has changed.
How many times?
- Just one time.
I get one, too, then.
- Deal.
Gin.
What was, uh, with that,
with Meredith?
We have a thing.
Wait, you have a thing with
Meredith and I don't know about it?
I live with you.
I see you every day.
It's a work thing.
- Okay, you know,
the whole point of hanging out with
really old guy is that he doesn't talk.
The man is sedated.
This is supposed to
be a quiet place.
See? Changed.
She's changed.
Everything's changed.
I gave the other nurse a list of
his medications this morning.
My husband needs his pills.
He needed them hours ago!
Oh, oh, okay.
Why don't you check on the meds again?
I have checked on them.
- No, meds, pharmacy, now.
Just... I'm sorry. I am sorry.
It's fine. It's fine.
I was never a yeller before.
I'm becoming this horrible person who
yells at people who are just trying to
do their job.
You are just looking
out for your husband.
You do exactly what it
takes to protect him,
and that does not
make you horrible.
It makes you smart.
He said he was leaving.
He said he wasn't coming back.
- She's hyperventilating,
and the baby's had
some bradycardia.
Noelle, I need you to
get back into bed now.
Is Greg out there?
Did he leave?
Like really leave?
Just take deep breaths.
I always give him such a hard time,
you know, about everything.
Like he likes weddings.
I hate them.
He loves kids, and me,
they scare me to death.
Noelle, have you had any cramping,
any contractions,
any pressure at all?
But I can't do
this without him.
We'll get past this, right?
We have to get past this. Aah!
Damn it. All right, Noelle,
I need you to get into bed, okay?
Why, what's happening? Ow!
Stay on your left side,
and whatever you do, do not push, okay?
Okay, I need slow,
deep breaths.
So tell me about
the slutty girl.
Fine, the slutty intern.
It was the slutty part
I had a problem with.
Kathleen says she's
not even single.
She is single.
She's wonderful. She's smart.
She's a lot of things.
And she's none of your business, Nancy.
Wow, I've never seen you
like this over a girl,
even Addison.
I've never been like
this over a girl,
especially Addison.
Oh, don't be bitter.
I mean,
shame on Addison and all that,
but he's Mark, Derek.
What did you expect?
He's just... Mark.
And who hasn't gone there
once or twice, right?
What'd you say?
Oh, come on.
Everybody sleeps with Mark.
It's practically
a rite of passage.
Derek, I get it, okay?
I get that they made a terrible mistake.
- It wasn't a mistake.
Nancy, it wasn't a mistake.
It wasn't just one night.
It was months.
They were together for months.
Didn't you know that?
No, I had no idea.
Then shut up about it
and eat your lunch.
Derek's sister is in town.
Cristina, are you mad
at me or something?
Because I have been trying to talk...
- Everything is not about you, Meredith.
Okay, what is going on?
Because George and Alex are saying--
- I-I don't care.
What is your problem?
- I just...
I have bigger things
in my life right now.
What?
Nothing.
10 blade.
Hey. Hey, Dr.
O'malley. Can you, uh,
can you tell me what's
happening in there?
I thought you left.
She thinks you left her.
This is all a lot to digest.
I mean, our daughter,
my--my little girl isn't
even my little girl anymore.
Noelle is in there freaking
out because you left.
Just tell me if she
is okay, please.
She's gone into premature labor.
Dr. Montgomery-Shepherd--
Dr. Montgomery is about to
do an emergency c-section
on one of the babies to try to
stop the labor on the other.
Wait, so you're delivering one
of the babies right now, today?
In just a few minutes.
The boy or the girl?
Greg...
Ham or eggs?
You say you want a
career in plastics,
and yet you can't tear yourself
away from the baby catchers
long enough to actually
show me you want it.
Being on hold with the D.M.V. has
nothing to do with a career in plastics,
Dr. Sloan.
Only it does, because being on hold
with the D.M.V. has to do with me,
and I have everything to do
with your career in plastics.
Tyler... Addison Montgomery needs
two units of b-positive blood in l&d.
Stat.- I'm on it.
So the biosynthetic dressing should
ensure that you won't need skin grafts,
and that's good news.
If I did need grafts,
would that take long?
I mean, I mean, like how long would
something like that take if--if I had
needed them?
Uh, that would just depend on
the severity of the burn, really.
Oh, so more severe
than this one?
It would have to
be more severe?
Just to make sure I have
everything accurate,
uh, you burned your hand...
we've been over this,
haven't we?
Uh, I'm sorry. I--
- Look, I have a test on friday,
and I have work to do.
So I have to-- I-I want to go home.
I'm really ready to get
out of here now, okay?
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to--
Gretchen, did you burn
your hand on purpose?
Izzie, you heard what Dr.
Bailey said.
It's okay if you did.
It's just, did you burn your hand
to get out of taking your test?
I can't fail that damn
test one more time.
I just... can't.
It's all anyone in my family,
in my life--
it's all they talk about.
It's all I'm known for.
"Oh, Gretchen, the failure."
Can you imagine failing the bar
exam five times? Five times.
I mean, that's absurd.
I mean...
that's just, uh...
that's pathetic.
I cannot sit for two and a half
solid days of testing again
just to prove to
everyone... again...
how pathetic I am.
Not... when...
you feel that pathetic
all by yourself.
I've completed the incision.
I'm going to ask you to move
the top uterus to the side
so I can reach the
one underneath.
Got it.
Now I don't want to alarm you or make
you nervous in any way, O'Malley,
because you seem like
a decent person, but
I've got about 120 seconds to
get baby one out of uterus one
while you're
holding uterus two,
and if you so much as hiccup,
you could tear the uterine wall
and kill this woman's child.
So do what you can to be careful, okay?
- Okay.
Wow. Look at that.
- Amazing, huh?
Applying the final
hemostasis suture.
Great. Don't be afraid to--
- grab a bigger piece?
Got it.
Hmm. Good. Very nice, Dr. Yang.
Applying pressure.
- Gently.
It was attached to the
interventricular septum.
Are you gonna use
a graft to repair?
Somebody's been doing their homework.
- 4-0 prolene, please.
Thank you very much, Boki.
Ready to perforate
uterus two. Scalpel.
Wait. Wait, Dr. Montgomery.
My baby's moving.
It's really moving.
I can't hold it.
I need you to hold her still if
I'm gonna do this c-section.
I'm trying.
I mean it, O'Malley.
- What should I do?
It's really moving.
I can't hold it.
I need you to keep her still.
You're sending her into distress.
You have to get that baby to stop moving.
How do I do that?
Talk, O'Malley.
- Alex.
Karev, back away
from the table.
Talk to it, to the baby, to calm it down.
- Karev.
Talk about what?
October 30, 1974--
It's the fight known as
"rumble in the jungle".
World heavyweight champ George
Foreman is pitted against Muhammad Ali
his first major fight after three
and a half years out of the ring.
It's working.
- Foreman is favored to win.
He's younger, he's stronger...
- Scalpel.
But he's not prepared for what Ali
would later call the rope-a-dope.
It all started in
the second round.
Foreman comes out swinging.
Ali's backed up against the ropes...
That's not gonna stay on.
You're giving it too much slack.
You're blocking my light.
Think of it as a
basic corner stitch.
I can figure out how to sew on my
own buttons, thank you. I am surgeon.
Right.
Oh, for God's sakes.
You sew this on for me,
and I'll get rid of Addison and Sloan.
Really?
- No.
Oh, fine. I'll do it anyway.
So I heard you've got a
sister wandering the halls.
She planning on
moving here, too?
God, I hope not.
Derek, I know it's
been hard on you.
He was like my brother.
I have four sisters...
four very annoying sisters.
Mark was my brother.
It's--it's hard.
Divorce isn't all it's
cracked up to be, huh?
I just want it to be easy.
I want it to be
over and move on.
But...
- But you're in a surprising amount of pain.
You and Adele?
I'm sewing on a button for
the first time in my life.
What does that tell you?
- Technically, I'm sewing.
I'm just saying.
Dr. Sloan.
So we're clear,
you knew when you stepped
into that surgery,
you were forfeiting your
future in plastics, right?
But, Dr. Sloan--
- I need my phone back.
Well done. You really prepared.
Yes, I'm always prepared.
Couldn't do it without you.
Thank you.
Dr. Burke, uh,
could we have a moment alone?
I just-- I didn't realize
that you were one of them,
one of the doctors around
here with doubts about me
or my abilities.
- Miranda, I'm not.
My name was erased from the board.
I have to assume that was you.
Dr. Bailey--
- I just--
I just--
I just need to know why.
I need you to tell me why you
didn't want me in on your surgery.
I'm afraid I just
couldn't use you.
I understand.
Oh, you should've seen that.
Two uteruses.
So unbelievably cool.
And a cute baby to boot.
Well, I'm glad you're
enjoying your trip.
Relax, Derek. I'm going.
I'm on a plane in two hours.
So... you're gonna report back to mom that?
- That you're you.
Still running in circles around
all the women in your life,
but that's to be expected with
four sisters and a dead dad.
I'm not running
around in circles.
Derek, can you even remember
the last time you were alone?
You've never been single, ever.
I mean, you're fine,
but you're not happy.
And you're not gonna get happy
until you get some space.
Just get away from Addie,
away from the intern,
just away.
Figure out what you want.
Kathleen's the shrink,
Nancy, not you.
I gotta go.
Nancy...
Thanks for flying out here.
It was, uh...
Thanks.
Where are we going again?
We need to go upstairs.
Okay.
Wait. Wait. Where are we?
We're on the psychiatric
floor, Gretchen.
We need to place you
on a 72-hour hold.
No, I'm not crazy.
You can't--no. I'm going home.
Gretchen.- No,
you have to let me go home. Please.
I'll just--I need to
go back home. Please.
If you go home, you're just
gonna hurt yourself again. Right?
Isn't that your plan, so that you
won't have to take the bar exam?
You need some help, Gretchen.
If the idea of taking an exam makes
you hold your palm to a burner,
you need some help.
Everyone needs help
from time to time,
someone to look out for them,
make sure they're okay,
make sure they're ready.
I have that.
And you need that right now.
I'm not crazy.
- I know.
I just... didn't want to fail.
I know.
What happened?
Are my babies okay?
- The surgery went very well.
You have a healthy baby boy.
And the labor stopped
on your little girl.
She's gonna be just fine.
- And Greg?
Has Greg come back yet?
No, Noelle, I'm sorry.
Greg isn't here.
I want an update every half-hour, and--
- What happened?
My babies?
- They're just fine.
You're just coming out
of anesthesia, Noelle.
Everything went very well.
Is Greg back yet?
I'm so sorry, Noelle.
He's not here.
And be sure to alert me
to any fetal distress.
What happened?
Your babies are
healthy, Noelle.
Everything's okay.
Is Greg back yet?
I'm right here.
Hi.
I saw our son.
He's amazing.
But how's our little girl?
You look like you could
use a little cheering up.
Not from you.
Oh, if I recall,
I was pretty good at cheering you up
One, two...
yep, three very cheerful times.
Dirty. It was not
"cheerful." It was dirty.
And like I said, no.
So your sister really
doesn't like me, huh?
Sorry. It's just, she's...
from the east coast.
Well, I--
you know what?
I shoulda called.
But you didn't.
I want us to work, it's just--
it's complicated.
I think I need a
little time to...
take some space.
Yeah.
To clear my head.
Yeah. I... okay.
Okay.
There are times when even the best
of us have trouble with commitment.
Dr. Stevens.
I was just looking at Dr. Grey's
evaluation on your first day back
to work.
I get daily report cards now?
She had a lot to say.
Yes, Sir.
It was a difficult catch.
Nicely handled.
Good work.
Welcome back, Dr. Stevens.
I was rude to you before.
I'm sorry.
I understand what you're trying to say.
You're the... pig.
You are committed.
Only we broke up.
And I've been wanting to hear
this from you for how long?
And--and you wait until now to say
it to me after we've broken up?
I'm out of my element here.
I break bones for a living.
I-I used to live
in the basement.
Most days I wear last
night's eyeliner to work.
I don't give a crap what
other people think about me
because I am a happily independent,
successful woman,
and I like it that way.
Only when you say stuff like this,
it just...
it just-- it makes things too hard.
So please...
don't chase me anymore...
unless you're
ready to catch me.
And we may be surprised by the
commitments we're willing to let slip
out of our grasp.
Commitments are
complicated.
I'm here for you,
whatever it is.
Whenever you're ready,
I'm here.
Thank you.
We may surprise ourselves by the
commitments we're willing to make.
True commitment
takes effort...
and sacrifice.
Which is
why sometimes...
we have to learn
the hard way
to choose our commitments
very carefully.
Brought to you by :
Raceman and Bemused
www.FOROM.com