Previously  on "grey's anatomy"...
you and red make a pretty good team.
- Don't tell sloan.
- Oh,she and sloanaren't happening.
- I'm not what you're looking for.
- What are you talking about?
Once a man-whore,always
a man-whore,right?
I keep telling her there's more
to life than surgery and career.
Mother. it has to be small.
Make an appointment at city
hall,and that'll be that.
I don't know if I wanna keep
trying to breathe for you.
I'll go.
He said he spent the day in the clinic when he
spent it doing god knows what with izzie stevens.
You're gonna transfer to mercy west?
I mean,no offense. Today was awesome.
It's just you're not my girlfriend.
Okay?
the dream
is this--
that we'll finally be happy
when we reach our goals.
Find the guy,finish
our internship--
that's the dream.
Then we get there.
And if we're human,
we immediately start
dreaming  of something else.
It's 3:00 in the morning.
What are you doing up?
- I can't sleep.
- What are we watching?
- Why can't you sleep?
- No reason.
Because if this is the dream...
then we'd like to wake up...
now,please.
okay.
Cristina,stop lurking.
Come and say good
morning to your guests.
Good morning,mother.
Uh,good morning,missus...
mama.
What...
what's
every--
everyone doing here so early?
Early?
Darling,by the look of the calendar,we
should've been here six months ago.
She doesn't understand what
goes into planning a wedding.
Breathe.
Sip...
and breathe.
The police haven't found
anything on our jane doe.
Well,I believe she
calls herself ava now.
Yes,well,she doesn't seem to
be getting her memory back.
Well,now that the rest of her medical problems
are taken care of,I'll see what I can do.
- That'd be great.Thanks.
- Has anybody seen addison?
- Uh,she's gone.
- Gone?
- She took a leave of absence.
- Why?
- I mean,did she-- did she tell you
why? - What'd you do to her,mark?
She didn't give a reason.
Did she tell you where she was going?
all she said was she needed some time,
"to be happy and free,"if
I recall correctly.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.I'm sorry. it's just...
um...
where I come from...
elevators tend to be
this kind of aphrodisiac.
you know?People get on 'em,and
they just get all horny.
Oh,no! No,no.
Not that I'm,uh,not that
I'm talking about you and I.
No. I'm--I'm just
saying,it--it's a relief.
You know,to be on a not horny elevator.
You know? Just get on...
and ride...
without the sex.
right?
oh,my god.
I'm becoming a crazy freak...
a crazy,inappropriately chatting freak.
becoming?
seems like you're already there.
hey.
Oh,hi.
Hello.
Someone have bones that
need resetting or...
bridesmaid.
Excuse me?
Bridesmaid.
My mother and...
burke's mother have been
talking on the phone,
and now they are here...
- with me.
- to plan the wedding.
Oh.
Cristina led us to believe
that you were friends.
- okay. I guess.
- Good.
It's settled.
uh,whoa. Wait. Um...
what are you--
are you--are you...
you actually asking me to be--
to be one of my bridesmaids?
- did you get any sleep?
- I did,actually,
after I evicted a raccoon who chewed
his way into the luggage compartment.
- The trailer.
- Yes.
So while you were sleeping...
when I drowned,
it was different for
you than it was for me.
Something happened to me.
And I really don't know how to
explain it without sounding like...
I just-- I
feel different.
I wanna be better at
everything,and I wanna let you in.
I swear.
Did you practice that?
with hand gestures,but I dropped those.
Just,now is not the time
to give up on me,okay?
That's what I'm saying.
Okay.
- Okay?
- Yep.
Oceanside wellness group.
Uh,yes. You're confirmed
for tuesday at 4:00.
Oh,no.No,ma'am. No,I'm not a doctor.
yeah,I don't know what you should
do about the itchiness "down there.
" Okay.Okay. Okay,bye.
Hi.
I,uh,
I think I'm in the right
place. I'm looking for,uh...
maya,is that you?
Addison!
Oh,my god.
You got so big.
What are you,like,45 now?
Maya,you're gonna
be late for sch--
addison.
Naomi.
Surprise!
Oh,I got lost like eight times,
smell like someone who's been
driving in car a for two days,
and I think I just had some kind of
psychotic break in your elevator,but,um...
surprise!
maya,go get your backpack.
so...
- what do you want,addison?
- I miss you.
Really?
'Cause I haven't heard
from you in over a year.
Unless you count the
christmas card,which was nice.
I know,I know. I'm sorry
about--I'm sorry about that.
I left you messages on
your pager. I e-mailed you.
I had some really special
conversations with your voice mail.
Can we just let this go? I've been
having some rough times lately,okay?
- I got divorced.
- So did I.
Oh,my god.
You and sam?
addison.
- Bye,daddy.
- Bye,baby.
- Hey.
- sam,I'd say good to see you,but...
- yeah.
Your face is everywhere.
"body language"?
uh,yeah,I just-- I had a few
thoughts,I wrote 'em down,and that'S...
and now you're the
common man's medical guru.
Hey,dell,can you push my
appointments back an hour?
- Oh.
- I have to rescue cooper.
This is addison.
Addison,this is our shrink.
Violet. Hi.Bye.
- What did cooper do this time?
- What does cooper always do?
a woman.
I'm his colleague,not his chauffeur.
So this is,uh... co-op medicine,huh?
Yeah,doctors working together.
It's me,naomi,
we have a pediatrician,a shrink,an
alternative medicine practitioner--
- could--could you excuse us
for just a minute? - Sure,I can.
- Good morning,naomi.
- Oh,shut up.
So you two still work together?
hey,pete.
Who is that redhead with your ex-wife?
She's hot.
Possibly insane,but hot.
Don't even think about it.
You work with your ex-husband
in a shrine for your ex-husband.
It's actually a good book.
And we're friends. We stayed
friends even after we got divorced.
It's very healthy. We're healthy.
What happened between you and sam?
Addison,you and I were close in
med school. It was a long time ago.
Oh,naomi,
come on.
You can't stay mad at me forever.
I know you.
- You got fat.
- I did not.
- Your hair looks hideous.
- It does not.
And you're getting really,really ugly.
I've missed you,too.
so...
why are you really here?
You're a fertility
specialist,one of the best.
- You want to have a baby?
- I want to have a baby.
www.ydy.com
proudly presents
sync:gagegao
¸¡¸¡ www.ydy.com
Crey¡¯s
Anatomy Season 3 Episode 22
susan grey.
You sure you're in the right place?
I have reflux...
acid reflux.
And the,uh,hiccups come and go...
when it gets really bad.
they've stopped a few times,but
lately it's been getting...
worse.
- have you had chlorpromazine?Here you go.
- Thank you.
Um,isn't that the crazy person's drug?
it's used as an anti-psychotic,
but it's helpful with hiccups.
and if we don't stop these
soon,you will be a crazy person.
ah.
okay.
Hey,how is meredith doing?
I know they have that big intern exam
coming up,and she's been really busy.
I tried to call,but...
uh...
hey,no hiccups.
chlorpromazine.
You know,I'm not getting any younger,you
know?And I always planned to have one,
it's just--well,now clearly,a
man is not in the cards for me.
I mean,this is addison
post mcdreamy,post mcsteamy.
- You know,I just have to...
- mcwhat?
Forget it. You know what?
Let's never "mc" anything.
A baby,that is...
my answer.
Find a sperm donor,have a baby.
My new
dream--a baby.
A baby's not really an answer. It's
more of a crying,puking,non-answer.
- Yeah,but you did it.
- Yeah,with a husband.
Yeah,but you did it. You
got married,you had a baby.
You're my example.
Okay,we should check your F.S.H.
And your estradiol levels,and we should
probably do and antral follicle count.
Holy crap.
I'm gonna have a baby.
ooh. The treadmill,huh?
Okay,what's going on?
I tried to take it up to ten and do
the hilly terrain mode,which you can do,
but only if you're an olympian,so
I paused and I went flying off.
No. I mean,what's going on with
you pushing yourself this hard?
This is your fourth sports
injury in three months.
I am a sexual person.
I'm a normal sexual person.
I like sex. I need sex.
And he won't do it. He
won't have sex with me.
He just... won'T.
I'm hoping you're talking about your husband. Well,I'm not
hoping because of the no sex part-- it's been 18 months.
-Vit's been 18 months.
- Wow.
18 months!
Do you have any idea what that is like?
My husband won't do it.
- So you know what I do?
- Uh,you run.
I run. I run so I won't
sleep with someone else.
I run so I have someplace
to channel my energies.
I run so I won't pick up a tire
iron and beat my husband to death.
I need sex!
- You'd do it with me,right?
- Hmm?
I think you need to spend
some time with our therapist.
hey!
hey.
thanks for the ride.
- hey,have you been crying?
- Where's your car?
- Were you crying?
- You wanna walk?
I met a girl at a bar...
on the internet...
and she borrowed my car.
- did you file a police report? She might bring the car back.She was gorgeous and hot and s
-
okay,cooper,cooper,cooper.
All right,so you meet a strange
woman on the internet again.
You bring her back to your
apartment to have sex with you again,
and she steals from you again.
What does that suggest to you about you?
That I'm an optimist.
That I believe in magic.t
there is a soul mate...
out there waiting for me.
oh,violet...
allan's not worth it.
You deserve better.
I know that. I do.
I'm not...
I'm not crying about him. I'm not.
don't look at me. Look over there.
I switched my hours at the clinic
so I can go to the bridal shop.Yay!
Did she cheer? She just cheered.
- Someone's not being very bride-
- I am not a bride.I am a surgeon.
Don't tease the caged animal.
You're not excited?
I'm excited. I love weddings.
Weddings are all about
hope and the future.
Okay. I rescheduled an A.C.L.
Repair,but I wanna be clear.
I will not be wearing pink or baby
blue. I do not do flowers in my hair.
And I will never be seen
with a bow on my ass,okay?
See? She's got the right attitude.
thank you very much.
Hey.
hey.
Hi.
I--I'm here with susan.
She's down in the clinic.
- The clinic?Is everything okay?
- yeah.
Callie's a bridesmaid?
Yeah.Yeah,ca--yes,of course.
Callie's a bridesmaid.
- fun.
- yeah.
Yeah.
You gotta do it. That kid of yours
is gonna need you on your feet.
She's cute,huh? She's
a cute shriveled kid.
She's cute.Come on. Let's keep walking.
so... where is she?
Red--I thought
that was on.
- walk.
- Gossip.
Oh,you called it.
She was too serious
about the whole thing.
- And alex is a rolling stone.
- I was being thoughtful.
Yeah,right.And dumping red
after one night is sensitive?
Come on. You need to buff up.
So did she just take off?
What'd you say to her? Did she cry?
ow.
Idiot. You divorced naomi?
Look,just mind your
own business,ok--ouch.
Moron.She is my best friend.
Stop hitting me on top of my head.
- Did you
cheat?Di- - okay.
two things I learned way
back in kindergarten--
one,keep your hands to yourself,
two,he who smelt it dealt it.
- That makes no sense.
- Yeah.Well...
you cheated.
You cheated on your husband
with his best friend.
There.Smelt it,dealt
it-- it works.
You're using fart logic.
Hey,if you want details,go see
naomi. She won't talk about it.
- Well,then you get no details.
- I'm on her side.You know that.
- That's why you get no details.
- Oh,details!
Woman,be quiet.
I've missed you.
Yeah.
Well,you know,naomi's known you longer,
so she gets custody
of you in the divorce.
yeah.
so,uh,other than project
baby,this is strictly a vacation.
I am here to read trashy
novels and go to the beach.
Okay,nobody over 30 goes to the beach.
- You should stay here at the practice,
- hang on.
see how we work.
it's more fun than a stuffy hospital.
and we have an empty office.
Nai,are you trying to lure me?
look,maybe. We do have
sunshine and cute boys.
Yeah,speaking of which,cute boy behind
the desk is tracking you with his eyes.
- No,he's not.
- Oh,cute boy wants naomi.
okay,maybe you should shut up... and
go get some coffee or something...
please.
- You have to stop that.
- Stop what?
You cannot  watch me like that. It'S...
not something you can
do. I won't allow it.
You can't make rules about my eyes.
- that's enough!
- no!
- Did you hear that?
- all of you,just stop it!
Did you hear that?
- What was that?
- Did I just hear--
- I'm the father of that child!
- No,I'm the father!
- If it's anybody's baby,it's mine!
- Stop it!
- calm down,everybody!Just--
- hey,hey,hey,hey!
A little help here. A little help.
- oh,my god,cooper!
- cooper!
Oh,Dr.Freedman!
- Oh,god!
- Oh,that's great.
- Really great.
- You gotta be kidding me.
- you could've called.
- Oh,it's such a silly problem.
- Hiccups?
- We didn't want to bother you.
well,it's not silly if you can't sleep.
Chlorpromazine is good,but it
doesn't always work long-term.
we've had some good result
with endoscopic gastroplication.
We put a tube down your throat
and sew together the
bottom of your esophagus
to protect it from the
acid in your stomach.
It would be an outpatient procedure.
I'm sold. Ready when you are.
You're sure that that's not-- just think of it like
breathing into a very expensive brown paper bag.
okay,let me see if I can
explain this to everyone.
So carol was married to rick.
Carol is now married to doug.
Keith is lisa's husband.
- Uh,I'm rick's husband.
- Life partner.
- You're just mad I left you for a man.
- I'm lisa's husband.
- And lisa is the-- surrogate carrying
my child. - surrogate carrying my child.
- Our child.
- you are not the father!You don't know that,rick!
- I am so sick of you!
- Hey,hey!
O-okay,okay.
Let's all try to remember that
we are in a place of healing.
Uh,lisa...
h-how are you feeling?
guilty. Guilty is how she is feeling.
wh-why is that,lisa?
Because the same week that I
brought her here to be inseminated,
she had sex with him...
and him...
and him.
And we have no idea who the father is.
yeah,she,um,really gets around.
Okay,how does this happen? How do you
pick a super freak for a surrogate?
I-I screened her. There was
nothing thereto indicate she was--
sex crazed?
- Insatiable?
- Cooper-like?
Ooh. Okay.
The point is,everybody's
flipping out over nothing.
Medically,it has to be rick's baby.
We implanted lisa with a fertilized
embryo from carol's egg and rick's sperm.
Then rick implanted some more
of his own for good measure.
- before he decided he was gay.
- I've treated doug.
I have him on valerian
root for anxiety and stress.
And I knew he was fooling around,but
with his new wife's surrogate?
Can I just,uh...
I think the more pressing issue,uh,here,
is that,uh,lisa's had no prenatal care.
- She took off right after
her,uh¡ª -  sex-a-thon?
Hi.We haven't officially met.
Cooper. Pediatrics.
Hi.Uh,yeah,she...
left town,and,uh,she and the
baby need a complete workup.
Um,who's your usual G.Y.N?
Uh,she left the
practice rather suddenly.
I didn't do anything.
Well,look,I would be happy to
examine her. Trashy novels can wait.
Have you ever thought of...
plying your trade in
sunnier climes,addison?
"Sunnier climes"?
Now we see why he has
to type to pick up women.
Hey!
Besides,we have a very strict
no consorting rule here now.
I didn't do anything.
I can't wait to tell meredith her
stepmom hiccupped through the whole thing.
She should be here for this.
Susan asked her to be with her father.
She said he's having a lot of anxiety.
And...
meredith is supposed to help with that?
you know there's nothing to worry about.
what I...
what I worry about is molly living in a
new city alone with a baby most of the day.
That's hard. And lexie,who'S...about
to start her residency.
She's a really good
student,but it's grueling.
I know.
You know. Right.
And... I worry about you,too.
How you're getting on,your
mom-- none of that was...
simple.
Susan's really on you to talk to me,huh?
I got to admit,I'm envious...
that she's getting to
know you,and I'm not yet.
I think she may be faking these hiccups.
To get...
us in the same place?
I guess I'm just not very sexual.
He's having an affair. He's
not in love with me anymore.
That's not true,honey. I
love you.I love you so much.
I-I want to do it.
I just want to want to do it.
Okay,paul,I'm gonna give you
some homework for next session.
Homework?
- Have sex with your wife.
- Yay!
- Well,but- -
no matter what.
Whether you're in the
mood or not,have sex.
Do it in the bed,do it on the
kitchen floor. Do you have a pool?
- Yes.
- Okay,do it in the pool.
Have sex. No pressure,no
judgment,no expectations.
Have sex. Just...do it.
- We do need a new G.Y.N.
- Right.
And addison seems...
oh.Nuh-unh.No.Absolutely not.
- What?
- Addison is a nice person.
She is a decent person. She is a person.
- I'm lookin' for a person.
- Man,you're just looking.
At least I'm trying.
Dr.Feelgood.
- Hey.
- I love you.
Hi. Thank you.
Okay,dr.Feelgood, this
is what I'm saying.
Your career is taking off,girls like
that are throwing themselves at you.
- You should be celebrating.
- Celebrating? I just got a divorce.
You got a little tiny dog,and you
cook it chicken,and you talk to it.
- That's not normal.
- Hey,easy.All right?
I'm alone because I choose
to be. It's--it's a choice.
So you're saying that you're not
interested in addison,but I can't have her.
See,addison isn't the
type of woman you have.
She's a marriage woman. All right?
- She's gonna want a commitment,and
you- - hey,I do not sleep around.
No. You are a serial
monogamist,all right?
You--you date a girl,you romance a
girl,and then when it's time to commit,
- you cut and you run.
- I do not.
Linda,uh,karen,uh,julie.
Then there was
tricia,amy,carrie,the other linda-
- we can't forget- -
fine. I won't ask her out.
Good boy. That's a good boy.
and the week before I implanted the
embryo,you slept with how many,three?
Three men.
We're almost done here,lisa,and
then we'll do the amniocentesis.
- You're on carol's side.
- I'm carol's doctor.
You came to us.You applied to be
a surrogate. It was your choice.
I know.I
just--
I was about to hand my body over to a
baby that's not mine for nine months,
which is a big responsibility.That...
hit me-- the
responsibility-- and I just...
they all wanted me.
me.
And f-for once,I just
stopped thinking and I just...
I did something wild.
- dr.Montgomery,is something wrong?
- I'm gonna run some more tests.
You promise me you'll take it easy.
I have a stack of dvds to watch,and I
expect your father to feed me by hand.
So just call if you have any questions.
It was nice t-talking with you.
- Bye. -
Bye-bye.
any news about mercy west?
Uh,there's a spot.
There's a lot of takers,but
they said it looks good.
- So after the intern exam-
- I'm not an unfaithful guy.
I'm not a cheater.
You think it'll happen
again if you stay here...
- no.I don't know.
- With me?
George.
I have to go.
- sam.
- Yeah.
So paul and kathy,I gave them an
assignment. I told 'em to do it.
- He didn't rise to the occasion.
- Nothing?
- No wood.
- Not even a twig.
There's gotta be something
physical going on,right?
Because the only other option-- that
he just doesn't love her anymore--
- I mean,that's just...
- not the only option.
I mean,did they meet in the
drama department in college?
Could be a thyroid thing,anemia.
Could be a bunch of stuff.
- Have you checked for extreme ugliness?
- Okay,not funny.
- Will you get back to me...
- yes,I will.
- With what you find soon?
- Okay.Yes.
And,cooper,you know what?
- Ugly people have sex,cooper.
- Ew.
- Ugly people are people,too.
- Okay.
hello?
Hello?
you fill out this E.E.G. Request on ava?
Yeah,you asked for it.
I asked you to run labs on her every
other day. What the hell is this?
Shepherd's doing a full neuro
workup. Just get the hell of my--
go ahead. I would love to
have an excuse to lay you out.
I didn't do anything.
Whatever you didn't do sent
addison running for the hills.
Okay,this guy is 6'2",dark
hair,green eyes,totally healthy.
He plays the violin,and
he's a physicist.
That is good sperm.
Geeky,but,uh,good.
Lisa has extra donors if
you want to borrow one.
Her tests come in yet?
No,tomorrow. I don't want to ring
any alarm bells till we're sure.
What about this guy? He's a
marine biologist.Good hair.
Are you sure you want
to do this,have a baby?
Your life is really gonna change.
That's why I'm doing this.
I want my life to change. I need...
my life to change.
I mean,look,you have
maya. You're family.
You did everything the way you
were supposed to. You didn't wait.
Maybe I should have.
Waited.
What do you mean?
addison,I did everything exactly
the way I was supposed to.
After college,I never dated anybody
but sam,because he was the one.
I never had sex with anybody but
sam because cheating is wrong.
I had a baby because...
that's what you do when you get married.
I never made a single mistake.
I did everything right.
And then sam comes home
and says he wants a divorce.
So all those photos you're...
busy admiring,all they are are
reminders of all the stuff I didn't do.
I'm 38 years old,and I
don't know how to have fun.
That's not lucky. That's sad.So just...
shut up about lucky!
Poor...
sad... dried up naomi.
Shut up.
Poor little,special
talented doctor girl.
let's make a
made-for-tv movie...
about the poor little,dried
up special girl who has no fun.
I could put you out. You'd
have to sleep in the car.
I just...
I just wish I'd been
a little more like you.
What,an adulterous bitch
who forgot to have kids?
Violet?
- Allan.
- Hey!
Great to see you.
- How you doing?
- I'm great.
Really. I'm really wonderful.
Well,I saw you and I--
I didn't want to be rude.
So I hope it's okay.
you know,it's just... it's
really wonderful to see you.
You look,uh...
you look really wonderful.
They didn't have the gouda you
like,but they had a camembert-
- hi.
- Hi.
This is violet.
Violet--oh,violet.
Hi. Nice to meet you.
I-I'm cami.
- Okay.
- Allan's wife.
god,I still can't get
used to that word--wife.
- yeah.
- Wife?
- How long have you been married?
- Newlyweds-- eight weeks.
Oh.
Congratulations.
We'll see you.
nice to meet you.
hey,addison,uh,latte? Or
ac--more of a cappuccino.
- Lisa's baby has something called placenta accreta.
- Is that bad?
The placenta abnormally
attaches to the uterine wall.
It makes delivering dangerous
for both mom and baby.
- But there was something else.
- That's not enough?
The baby has some genetic markers
that don't match carol,just lisa.
What? The
embryo--
- did not implant.
- This is lisa's baby?
Which also means that the paternity
is once again up for grabs.
- Good luck.
- I'm off to the beach.
Uh,you can't leave. Someone
has to tell the patient.
Honestly,I
ha--I have...
low people skills with anybody over 12.
It--it's true. An internet
hooker just stole his car--
violet! Privacy.
She was not--
she just...she borrowed my car.
she--she
borrowed it.
Borrowed.
911 turbo,hand-sewn leather seats.
911 turbo with hand-sewn leather seats.
Who does that to a 911?
A chick. A crazy chick.
- But she was so hot.
- A crazy hot chick.
I loved that car.
That was a single man's car.
That's the point. I mean,I-- I
thought maybe I was done being single.
I thought she was gonna be
the mother of my children.
What was her name again?
Sexyboobs316.
are you... dude,are you crying?
No.
You better be crying about that
car and not over sexyboobs315.
316. 316.
I can'T.I-I can'T. I'm gonna hurt him.
Let's just say he's crying
over the car and the woman.
All right? There we go.
Let it out.
let it out.
Uh,cristina?
That's a pretty one.
Moves very well in it.
Looks quite natural.
- You paged?
- I need you over here.
Should I be seeing you in
the dress before the wedding?
You think I'm wearing this?
- well,it is very feminine.
- Exactly.
Do you know your mother booked
a chapel that sits 200 people?
Okay,how did i get bridesmaids,huh?
freakin' stupid cotton-candy
colored bridesmaids?
No offense.
what happened to our small ceremony?
What happened to you
and me at city hall?
I didn't--I didn't
think you were serious.
I am not wearing this.
Oh,I gotta get to the hospital.
You know,we should,uh,give
'em some privacy.
What?
Oh! Oh,you want me to
go over there with you...
- by myself.
- Yeah.
You want a big wedding?
You want the chapel,you want the
guests and me in a white dress?
Well...
yes.
I'm a traditional man,cristina.
- Are you kidding me?
- No.
The saleslady has another batch
of dresses for you to see,cristina.
Oh,thank you... mama.
Cristina has certainly
made quite an effort.
Tried on,I would say,over
a hundred dresses,
and that certainly could
not have been easy for her.
Yeah,mama,I know she seems
disinterested in wedding planning.
But cristina...
she's not cold.
- I know she seems
cold-- - preston...
if you think cristina is
right for you,I trust you.
I trust your instincts.
and the baby-- the,um,the
baby isn't even mine?
- Honey,calm down.
- Calm down?
You mean I can keep
this baby if I want to?
Uh,legally,yes.
So who's the father?
We won't know the paternity of
the baby till after lisa delivers.
More urgent at the moment
is the placenta accreta.
The fact is,lisa is at risk of having
a life-threatening hemorrhage and
the baby could deliver preterm.
So you're saying they could die?
There is a risk of death,yes.
Lisa,I know you're scared.
If you do go into preterm
labor,you'll have a c-section.
And they'll monitor it
and control it so that
they have a better chance of
saving your uterus and your life.
And you'll save us,me and the baby?
Well,I have...
I have to get back to
seattle. I have a practice.
But I can refer you
to someone local who--
no,I want you.You be there.
I thought kathy was coming
to the appointment today.
oh.
Just--kathy didn't
come home last night.
And,you know,I don't
blame her,but it's just...
what--what if she's
with some guy right now?
Some guy--some--some
guy who can...
- who can bring it?
- Okay.
Let's not get ahead of
ourselves. It's okay.All right?
There are plenty of medical reasons
for low sex drive. All right?
Sorry. Sorry.
- Honey...
- where were you?
I was out.
All night?
And I had a chance to cheat,believe me.
But I passed. Okay?
I passed up being with someone who actually
wants to be with me because I am stuck with you.
you're crying?
Okay,let's--let's all
just calm down here.
All right-- I'll be
in the waiting room.
Oh! She's starting to hate me.
What am I gonna do if
little paul can't perform?
Okay.
Don't talk about your penis
while you hug another man.
I'm sorry,man.
- It's okay.
- I'm sorry.
- Let's draw some blood.
- Okay,let's draw some blood.
What's in L.A.?
What?
For addison.
Any idea...
what she might be doing there?
naomi and sam are down
there,I guess. I don't know.
You all right?
We were gonna try.
We were gonna make a go of it...
as a couple.
She bet me I couldn't go
60 days without having sex.
Oh.Let me guess. You couldn't do it.
No,she couldn'T.
She didn't want to be with me.
I thought she did.
I thought she might.
But she didn'T.
And I caught her. You know...
sleeping with somebody else?
oh,that must have been so hard for you.
not that I can't relate.
So I told her I did it.
You told her you did it?
I told her I lost the bet. I
told her I slept with someone.
I figured if she didn't want to be with
me,she shouldn't have to feel guilty about it.
Selfless.
- That'S...out of character.
- Yeah.
Anyway,uh...
I was just wondering if
you knew what was in L.A.
No.
okay,now I am going to the beach.
Wait,addie.
Your test results came back in.
Oh,good. Because,um,I picked a donor.
I think I'm gonna go with physicist guy.
Your F.S.H. Level is high.
Well,they're high this month.
We can do,uh,ovarian stimulation.
And your antral follicle
count is only two.
That could be due to stress.
Addison,I'm sorry.
I did all the tests.
There's no fertility potential here.
okay. Uh...
this is good. This is,um...
oh,this is just... perfect.
- Addison-- - I
have the great guy.
I don't have a baby because
I'm focusing on my career.
And then I have the other guy. I don't have
his baby because he's not the great guy.
And now I don't have the
great guy or the other guy,
and I'm finally ready to
have a baby,and I can'T.
That is so...
exactly what my life is.
- Addie,there are other options.
- Yeah,I know about the options.
I'm so sorry.
I know how much you wanted this.
It's okay.
I just,um...
I just didn't realize I
was out of time,that's all.
Addie,please
stay so we can--
no,it's okay.I'm fine. Thank you...
for telling me.Thank you.
I will see you at home.
looks like you had a bad day.
Okay...
enough.
Okay? Not today.
This is not a good day. All right?
So why don't you just...
shut up?
Shut up!....
all right,then.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:¸¡¸¡ gagegao
Greys Anatomy
Season03 Episode22