previously on grey's anatomy...
last night,you and shephard did it.
meredith,what does this mean?
uh,i had panties on
Here I thought I was a surgeon,but i'm not.
- she cut the his IVAD wire.
- so i quit.
it's time for you to make a choice-- me or this hospital.
good-bye,richard.
you live here?
i'm not crazy or anything.
i just spend so much time here in the hospital.
- are you gonna tell shephard about...
- not yet...
what does this mean?
it means you have a choice.
at any given moment,the brain has 14 billion neurons firing at a speed of 450 miles per hour.
we don't have control over most of them...
when we get a chill-- goose bumps,when we get excited-- adrenaline.
the body naturally follows its impulses,
which i think is part of what makes it so hard for us to control ours.
it's enough muffins.
we don't need all these.
no more muffins.
of course,sometimes we have impulses we would rather not control...
what are you doing?
just because you can't touch doesn't mean you can't enjoy.
that we later wish we had.
mama.
daddy.
oh,my-- preston.
mama and daddy?!
is this a new service the hospital is providing?
i told you to guard the door!
i had a code blue.
i had parents walk in.
- we saved the guy's life.
- whatever.
- you know,i want my 20 bucks back.
- sorry.
bought everyone coffee...
to celebrate saving the guy's life.
yeah,i want my 20 bucks back.
it's not tyler's fault you're a dirty,dirty stripper.
- you heard.
- everyone heard...
stripper.
oh,oh,you're one to talk,sleeping with two men.
wrong.
i'm not sleeping with either one of them...
not until i pick one.
if i haven't made a decision by the end of the day,i'm flipping a coin.
a girl can only hold out for so long.
oh,and somehow i'm the dirty stripper?
you two have time to round,or are you too busy getting naked on hospital property?
no,i wasn't naked.
i-i wasn't naked.
you've got a coffee stain on your shirt.
you had a bed on your couch.
hope you're not planning to see patients in your sweat suit
actually,um...
i need the day off.
a day off,for what?
for drinking.
i am feeling the need to do some drinking.
actually,i'm feeling the need to do some crying,but my tear ducts seem to be too proud,
so i'm going to do some drinking instead.
- what,no laboring moms today?
- no.
because i think god knows that...
i need to dosome drinking today.
you wanna ta about it,addie,or you just wanna be glib a little longer?
why are you living in your office?
marriage...
is hard.
well...
thank goodness mine seems to be just about over.
ms.seabury,what-- what are--
no,i'm--i'm sorry. you cannot be eating.
what is all of this?
this is chocate raspberry souffle cake.
it is the best thing i've ever tasted in my life.
except for maybe the banana cream torte there.
it's pretty stunning,really.
bakeries deliver.
did you know that?please,grab a fork.
ms.seabury,you're scheduled for surgery this afternoon.
we push the surgery a little.
tomorrow,maybe?
oh,my god.
you've gotta taste this.
ma'am,you have an aggressive form of lung cancer.
the sooner we get you into surgery,
- the better your chances--
- the better my chances of surviving.
so i heard.
it's all very aggressive.
i mean,it's very...
it's funny.
i have never smoked a cigarette in my life.
i have never smoked pot.
i've never drank.
before today,i hadn't had a dessert in ten years.
i am the picture of health,and i have lung cancer.
i mean,come on.
it's absurd,right?
i'm sorry.i think i'm on a sugar high.
i'm sorry.
o'malley,reschedule her surgery for tomorrow and get her a psych consult.
yes,sir.
and no more food deliveries.
okay.
you do it.
so,um...
um,dr.bailey?
surgeons don't say "um," o'malley.
you want to be a surgeon,learn to speak like one.
look,he wants you to talk to the chief about izzie,see if she can come back.
she's just baking-- a lot of baking-
and it seems a waste for all her talent and medical skills to go into muffins.
- we just thought u might be willing to help.
- stop...talking.
well,good morning.
benjamin,ruth.
good morning,dr.shepherd.
it doesn't feel like a very good morning to me.
i have to have brain surgery today.
pretty scary.
plus,my sister is nervous.
when she gets nervous,she sweats,and the windows in here don't open,so it's pretty rank.
benjamin.
was i rude,ruthie?
let's let the doctors talk.
benjamin o'leary,32,
in for the removal of a brain tumor that's pressing on his frontal temporal lobe.
clearly,it's affecting his impulse control.
it makes me say everything i think,which apparently is annoying.
this doctor looks annoyed,anyway.
although,it's hard to tell 'cause she always has kind of a pinched,uptight look on her face.
am i annoying you?
it's fine.
you can't say it's fine.
he doesn't perceive sarcasm or irony.
if he's annoying you,you have to tell him.
maybe i'm not annoying her,ruthie.
- no,you are.
- dr.yang.
- he asked.
- okay,benjamin,dr.yang--
pinched and annoyed though she may b-is nna prep you for surgery today.
do you have any questions for me?
is that blonde your girlfriend?
'cause the way you keep looking at her,you might as well just mount her right here and now.
i'm sorry.
was that rude?
i'm proud of you all.
you make me proud.
you reflect on me well.
grey,if you think you can keep your clothes on long enough to follow up the labs,
i'd appreciate it. karev,cover the pit.
wait,the pit?
i'm--i'm off gynie?
dr.montgomery-shepherd is out sick.
you can cover the pit,or you can...
you can tell me whose damn panties are on the bulletin board!
yours?
this is a hospital,people.
serious work happens here.
we save lives he-- oh,something funny?
whose are these?
this is bad.
this isn't good.
well,you better claim them.
- she thinks they're mine.claim them!
- no!
yeah,i know it's one of you.
it's always one of mine.always.
so tell me,which one of you left your damn drawers on my surgical floor!
oh,no.did i leave my underwear lying around again?
i am so sorry,bailey.
it's,uh,it's my bad.
o'malley,yang,prep your patient for surgery.
karev,pit.
grey,charts.
all four of you,do not make me regret setting you loose in this hospital.
o'malley,what do i mean by that?
you mean check with you before we cut any wires or steal any hearts.
are you trying to be clever?
- no,ma'am.
- better not be.
holy crap.the nazi's definitely back.
and louder than ever.
oh,mrs. burke.
hi,i'm cristina.
i-i may have said that earlier,but i was,um--
did i hear you refer to miranda bailey as a nazi?
what?
oh,no.
oh,uh,uh,i mean,yes,but--
you do understand that the nazis were responsible
for the worst genocide in the history of man?
and a racist genocide at that.
i would think that as a woman of color and as a doctor,no less,
that you would think twice before using that word as a punch line.
i'll think about that in the future,mrs. burke.
mrs. burke?preston's mother?
yes.oh.and you are?
derek shepherd.i'm the surgeon who operated on your son.
oh,thank you.
brilliant surgeon.
and a handsome man,too.
your mother must be very proud.
do you mind,dr.shepherd,if i borrow your young intern for a quick cup of coffee?
- i'll bring her right back.
- oh,no problem.
dr.grey can cover for cristina.
- i'm sorry?
- uh,dr.grey is very busy.
she has charts to do for bailey.
bailey's on the warpath.
uh,not the german warpath.
it's a hospital warpath.
it's--it's--
i'll take care of bailey,okay?
enjoy your coffee date,ladies.
- very nice meeting you.
- thank you.
i'll,um...
i just have this one quick-- i will meet you in the cafeteria in a couple of minutes.
is that--is that all right?
- yes,i look forward to it.
- oh,good.
well,this is a change from the elevator,
i mean a little more public.i like it.
you're married.you're married,and you said things to me.
yes,i said things to you.
normally,i would like the things you said to me.
normally,i would even think the bulletin board thing was funny.
bulletin board?
what are you talking about?
but you're married,which makes none of this normal.
it makes me a home wrecker.
and i hate the fact that i'm a home wrecker.
meredith,i'm not gonna pressure you.
take all the time you need.
but just so you have all the information,
my home was wrecked well before you came into the picture,
and i am just now done trying to rebuild it.
- you're done?
- i'm done.
whatever you decide,i am ending it with addison...
today.
you have said this before.
i know,but this time i mean it.
i'm gonna come clean just as soon as i see her.
- you are?
- i am.
you guys should think about getting a hotel room or something.
your mother wants to have coffee with me.
- and?
- and...she thinks i'm a racist.
oh,and a stripper.
she thinks i'm a racist stripper.
oh,come on.
what's funny?
this is not funny.
it's kind of funny.
she's just my mama,cristina.
your "mama"?
you'll love her when you get to know her.
everybody loves my mama.
you will save me from this,okay?
you will save me from this or...
you will save me.
hey,uh,chief,you haven't heard from addison,have you?
she's not answering any phones.
actually,she needed a day off.
something about finding another woman's panties in the pocket of your tux.
oh,that's-- that's not how i wanted her to find out.
you don't leave another woman's panties in your tux unless you want her to find 'em.
- i know,i know.
- look,i know a thing or two about affairs.
i even know a thing or two about affairs with women named grey.
it's not an affair.
see,i was gonna tell her.
addison--i was gonna tell her today.
i was gonna end it.
- look,give her some space.
- no.
- give her some time.
that's not it.
no.
no,i gotta-- i gotta talk to her today.
if something's over,it's just gotta be over.
meredith,she's-- she's not an affair.
ruthie,i don't think i want this surger you have to have the surgery,ben.
right.
you're very pretty,but you look kinda tired,
and i think maybe you should change your hair conditioner.
- that was rude,benjamin.
- it is?
no,actually,it's true,and it's refreshing.
- do you have sex with that brain surgeon?
- benjamin.
it's okay.
nope,i haven't.
not today,anyway.
i would.
he's hot...
and arrogant in way that's still sexy.
i would totally have sex with him if i could.
looked like you could.
so what'the holdup?
are you trying to seduce me?
i was just wondering--'cause i got a lot of work to do-- mm-hmm.
but,uh,i was just wondering about,uh,the panties-- the panties that are yours--
and how they ended up on the bulletin board.
black,lacy panties on the board.
- you are trying to seduce me.
- no.no,i'm not.
i'm just wondering how,uh,panties that i haven't seen before--
and i've seen your panties a lot of days in a r now--
i'm just wondering how black panties that apparently belong to you
and i've never seen end up on the bulletin board.
wow.
you're jealous.
no.no,no,no,no,no.no,no,no.i'm not--
- yeah.yeah,you are.
- i'm not jealous.
no,i'm-- is that my pat-- ms.seabury?
ms.seabury?
hey.stop.get...
- i'll tell him.
- what?
- i'll tell him the truth about the panties.
- don't you dare.he is jealous.
so you and o'malley,huh?
how'd that happen?
i don't know.
you're a surgeon.how'd that happen?
karev,she's a resident.
she outranks you.
you don't get tosk personal questions.
- it's fine,dr.bailey.
- he's my intern.
i say it's not fine.
are we clear?
no.
what's not clear?
what's not clear to me is why you won't talk to izzie.
- that's what's not clear.
- really?
you want to push me on this today?
today you want to push me?
what do we got,jill?
harley hernandez,14,was street luging when he lost control and hit a car.
witnesses say he was catapulted at least 20 feet into the air,
landed on a pile of tree trimmings.
broken pvis apparentas are,i would gu and then suddenly--wham.
it's all right,harley.
you're at the hospital.
we're gonna take care of you now,okay?
hospital?
what's the matter with me?
you're an idiot.
that's what's the matter.
- dad.
- sir.sir,please back away.
your friends are idiots,and you don't use the sense god gave you!
that's what's the matter with you!
sir,you're blocking our path.
please!
you okay?
sorry about that.
- sir,ir.
- you son of a bitch.
- where's my son?
- we took him in there.
- he was blocking the paramedics.
- no,he is terrified.
his child is a tree!
alex,listen to me.
you will not get physical with another human being on my watch ever again,
you will not question my authority,
and you will not defend your little girlfriend for killing a man!
are we clear?!
she's not my girlfriend.
as you know,i'm sure,he graduated first in his class from tulane.
i-i did know that.
actually,i graduated first in my class at stanford.
so you are planning to pursue a less time-consuming specialty--
obstetrics,perhaps,or family medicine?
oh,i'm in the surgical program.
but after you're married.
married?
uh,i'm sorry.married?
come,cristina.
you must have considered the possibility.
you're no spring chicken.
i don't know a young woman who wouldn't want to marry my preston given half the chance.
he's handsome.
he's brilliant.
he is the best thing i've ever done in my life.
he is the most important thing in the world to me.
oh.okay.
oh,burke.
burke.burke's here.
preston is-- preston burke is here.
oh,what a surprise.
my two favore ladi in one place preston,what on earth are you doing out of bed?
oh...well,i...
i wanted to get some,uh,i-- stretch my legs,mama.
but you're not suppose to stretch your legs.
you're supposed to be resting.
right.
but i wanted to have,uh,some air...
some stretching,some air and some coffee.
anybody want any coffee?
we already have coffee.
- please have a seat.
- right.just a second.
- you did this.
- did what?
cristina,listen to me.
it's not that i don't like you.
i think you're a very smart,very attractive young woman.
- but you're selfish.
- i beg your pardon.
oh,you pulled him out of aickbed because you were uncomfortable.
that's selfish.
you're selfish and my son is giving.
and the combination,well,it's not gonna last,not much longer.
hey,hey,hi.
all right.all right.
i brought you a scone,mama.
his kidney's gone.
there's no way to save it.
just focus on keeping the renal artery under control.
i have another bleeder.
okay,pace yourself,everybody.
we got long way to go.
- we have enough blood standing by?
- yes,sir.
is that a tree?
his mother rivals my mother,and that is saying something.
they're ating around both othem,
dark and evil.
you're blocking my view,george.
i miss dirty stripper cristina.
she was fun...
a lot less angry.
next time i see her,if she even looks at my sideways,i'm telling her what i think.
she wants to call me racist?
- wh--
- yeah.okay?
i'll call her sexist.
change my career after i'm married?
what is this,1953?
if she comes at me,i'm goin' there.
i think you should.
i think we all should just go there.
you know,tell the truth,spit it out,go with your gut,follow your instincts.
i miss philandering whore meredith.
she was trashy and much less idyllic.
do women have two sets of panties?
you know,two sets they wear for different occasions?
i made a choice.
i'm picking derek.
finn is great.
but derek is...
derek.
and...
- i'm following my gut.
- yeah,whatever.
i-i want my patient back.
you know,the one you stole after...
mama cornered me?
well,that's fine.
it's my day to check on izzie anyway.
you paged me?
your patient was caught hoplifting chocolates from the hospital gift shop.
what?
i'd never done that before.
it was exhilarating.
and now she's planning to leave.
leave?
you can't le-- she can't leave.
you're sick.
you should be sleeping and resting.
- and preparing for death?
- preparing for surgery.
- there's a difference.
- maybe.maybe not.
that's what they mean when they give you a 60% chance of surval.
it means that 4 out of 10 people die whether they have the surgery or not.
i have lived my entireife pent-up,repressed,stifling every impulse,
foowing every rule,and now i'm done.and you know what?
you should be,too.
we should all be done.
- so you're leaving?
- i'm claiming my life,doctor.
i can't do that from a hospital bed.
and you know you'll die.
maybe.
but at least when i do,i'll know that i have lived.
oh,god,this is good.
izzie?
wow.
okay.
- finn.
- hi.
wh-what are you doing home?
i thought you were working.
i am.
i'm--i was.i-i still am.
i just came home to check on izzie.
oh,so did i.
i brought her lunch.
you brought izzie lunch.
when my wife died,uh...
there really wasn't anything anne could say,but,uh...
the bringing of food actually helped.
it w the only thing that helped.
- you brought izzie food.
- yeah.
even though you didn't think i was here.
is--is that okay?
yeah.
it's amazing,actually.
you're amazing...
sweet and thoughtful and sensitive.
meredith,i don't want to pressure you.
you have a decision to make,and i want you to take all the time you need.
but i do want to make one thing clear.
what's that?
i'm not all that sensitive.
so...
have a nice day of work.
mr. hernandez.
h-how is he?
is he okay?
i mean,you've been operating for hours.
there is extensive damage.
we've had to remove one of his kidneys and a portion of his bowel.
but the tree's out.
i mean,you got it out,and he's okay.
okay,mr. hernandez,the branch actually is still there.
we're operating around it,which is part of what's taking so much time.
his mother's not here yet.
i mean...
you think-- you think he'll be okay by the time she gets here?
i-i'm sorry,i do have to get back in there.
but i just wanted to give you an update.
that he's still alive.
yes,that he's still alive.
okay.
izzie.
how you doin',sweetie?
- i brought you some muffins.
- okay.
i made a lot,and i was...
running out of room,and i thought maybe...
you would like some.
i'm a good baker.
yeah.
absolutely.thank you.
dr.stevens.
please don't call me "doctor."
okay...
please don't call me "mrs. shepherd."
that's funny.
- she's drunk.
- this is true.
so did you know about the slutty sex your slutty friend had with my...
super slutty husband?
you should have a muffin.
they're really good,and...
they'll help you.
i may be beyond help
yeah.me,too.
don't let hedrive,joe.
good.
but i knew.
i knew that you...
she's still here.
never leaves.
she never even pees.
i'm not entirely sure she's human.
finn brought izzie lunch.
oh,you went to see izzie?
yeah,she wasn't home.
but i'm taking that as a good thing,'cause at least the baking has stopped.
but my point is that finn brought izzie lunch.
he's that guy-- the guy who brings your roommate lunch when she's sad.
so,uh,you didn't end it?
he's the guy who brings your roommate lunch when she's sad.
so i'm gonna end it with derek.
whatever.
you know,i am not selfish.
i am by his side.
i-i took off all my clothes this morning.
that's not selfish.
and i'm going in for surgery.
selfish people don't save lives.
for surgery.
- george.
- what?
you're flirting with that nurse.
i'm young.
i'm healthy.
i got a life to live.
is this about the panties?
are you still jealous?
i'm not jealous.
i'm just living my life.
do you have a boyfriend?
he's gonna keep asking till you answer.
yes,i have a boyfriend.
can you look here?
if i had a boyfriend,i would definitely not be as angry as you.
why are you so angry?
is it because you're frigid?
or he's frigid?
- or--
- nobody's frigid.
my boyfriend's mother called me selfish,okay?
are you selfish?
- 'cause you do seem kind of self-obsessed to me.
- ben.
hey,i'm a surgeon.
in order to be a surgeon,a certain amount of self-obsession is necessary.
my boyfriend gets that.
if his mother doesn't,it's her problem.
i used to have a boyfriend.
when i got the tumor,he understood.
he tried to understand.
he loved me.
but his mother didn't.
my offending everyone offended her.
and he said he didn't care what his mother thought.
but in the end,he did care.
'cause now it's two years later,and i'm having brain surgery,
and only my fat sister ruth is with me.
benjamin...
that was kinda rude.
sorry.
when the tumor's removed,is it gonna bring his old personality back?
if we get the tumor out and benjamin lives,anything else is icing on the cake.
i'm locking down the external fixator.
there's no active bleeding,and the trajectory is clear.
karev,i want you to hold pressure on the liver.
put your hands down in here,and don't move.
you with the saw,
don't make aove until we get our hands on every vital organ around the tree trunk.
the parents-- have they said their good-byes?
mom's not here yet.
and the father was too busy blaming him to say good-bye.
speak when you're spoken to,karev.
i've had enough out of you today.
all due respect,dr.bailey,i think you got me mixed up with izzie stevens.
all right,everybody.
take your positions.
cut carefully.
we'll get this thing out in pieces.
you see that right there?
it's too close to the cavernous sinus.
suction.
i've got a bleeder.
the brain is starting to swell.
- v-fib.
- his heart can't take it.
yang,get in there with those paddles.
move.now.go.
clear.
renal artery's collapsed.
i thought you had that.
hepatic artery's gone.
b.p.is dropping.
all right,he's bleeding.
damn it,he's bleeding fast.
laps.
- come on.come on.
- no change.
epi and atropine are in.
- still in v-fib.
- shock him again.
i've decided that i'm gonna get really fat,
just as a stopgap,just until i figure out another plan.
i'm gonna eat all of these muffins,and i'm gonna get really,gloriously fat.
it's over.over.over.
i'm talking about the last third of my life,miranda.
how can that just be over?
how does that just end...
over a skanky pair of panties and...
- a bad tux?i am desir,amanda
- miranda.
right.
joe...
i'm desirable,right?
i have a boyfriend.
be that as it may,i don't need me to tell you how wildly attractive i am-- wildly attractive.
you are...
and your wildly attractive cab is here.
it is?
you told me to call you a cab at 10:00.
it's 10:00.
i guess that's for the best,huh?
i would say so.
hey.
can i buy you a drink?
i have a lot of them.
i'm trying one of everything.
hey.
hey,aren't you the cake lady from this morning?
aren't you supposed to be having surgery?
oh,well,that hasn't been decided yet.
so you're a doctor?
yes,i'm a doctor.
does that mean you can't drink with me?
not at all.
joe.
george...
you're gonna kill someone.
what are you doing?
i'm workin' it.
callie can be bad,so can i?
hey,watch it.
george...
callie is hot.
she's,like,really sexy,like,almost dirty-hot,and she's hot for you.
maybe you could keep using the darts as weapons,
or you could go get lucky with the sexy,hot,dirty girl.
where is hgoing?
to get laid.
god,you know,there is something wrong in the world when bambi's getting laid,
and i can't get five minutes alone with burke.
- what are you doing?
- day's over.
flippin' a coin.
call it.
the brain surgeon should be heads.
right.
choice made.
oh,that's it?
you're gonna base your choice on flipping a coin?
i'm taking a cue from benjamin.
impulsive,hont-- it's my new motto.
benjamin died.
he wasn't impulsive,meredith.
he wasn't honest.
he was sick and brain damaged.
and now he's dead.
mr. hernandez.
uh,may i?
you--you okay?
your son,he's gonna be fine.
he was off with his friends.
i let him go off with that thing.
i knew better.
his friend,he has this driveway up on a hill.
i just keep picturing him.
i keep picturing him going down that hill and...
and i didn't stop him,and i shouldstopped m.
kids spin outta control sometimes.
they...
spin outta control.
- you can't--
- yes,you can.
you can control them.
it's your job as a parent to control them.
ever sincehe divorce,i only get to see him every other weekend.
i never woulda bought him that luge.
i never woulda let him go off on his own that way before.
i went soft.
i went soft when he needed me to be the father.
i wish i'd had more fun.
i didn't want to be a ut.
didn't want to be a tramp.
didn't have any fun.
my ex-husband,he had fun--
all sorts of fun with all sorts of women who were a lot more fun than me.
nobody ever called him a slut.
why is that?
men can do it,but women can't.
women can.
i know some who do.
not without getting called names.
what do you care what people call you?
i get called an ass.
i don't care.
i don't think you're an ass.
i don't think you're a slut.
do y have a girlfriend,alex?
no,no girlfriend.
so you're single?
s,definitely.
- i'm single.
- i'm single,too.
and i'm very bad at this,never having had any practice.
so,um,i am...
i'm gonna go into the bathroom,and if i find myself alone in there after two minutes,
i'll just touch up my makeup and come back out.
but should you have any interest in fulfilling the wish of a potentially dying woman,
you know where i'll be.
getting some exercise,dr.torres?
Yes, yes, sir. Chief whatever.
- hi.
finn.
derek.
thanks for coming.
both of you,thanks for coming.
so here's the thing...
i like you.
and i like you.
and i thought i had a choice to make.
i thought i had to decide.
but i think i owe myself the chance to consider my options.
- options?
there's this thing that allows for the considering of options.
in the olden days,they called it dating.
- dating.
- yes.
i'd like to try that.
- you wanna try dating.
- yes.
- both of us?
and i understand if you're not up for it.
but i really hope you are.
you bowing out?
no.you?
i don't think so.
you're here first,you get all the best cases.
trauma comes in the middle of the night,you get first dibs.
exactly.
yeah,i respect it,i do.
and also,i can't have it.
and you know that.
you're throwing me out?
got no choice.
this violates all sorts of codes,and you know it.
so i have to go,but you're allowed to live in your office?
you noticed that,huh?
yeah,i'm pretty observant.
guess if i'm throwing you out,i have to follow my own rule.
okay,i'm jealous.
but i have a right to be jealous,because i don't want other guys touching your panties.
great.
that's great.
- you might wanna clear that up.
- yes,sir.
You heading out,dana?
gotta get back to the hospital,joe.
gotta go kick this cancer's ass.
okay.
Joe, ??
hey,alex.
uh,about today--
dr.bailey,you were right.
i-i shouldn't be getting physical with patients.
the body is a slave to its impulses.
i don't know if it's gonna get y better,mama.
well,i do,baby.
i do know.
cristina,it's late.
preston needs his sleep.
but the thing that makes us human...
i'm sorry,mrs. burke.
i was just coming in to see if either of you needed anything before i went home for the evening.
is what we can control.
we're fine.
good night,preston.
sleep well.
hang in there.
after the storm...
after the rush...
after the heat of the moment has passed...
- the panties?
- yeah.
- not mine.
- yeah?
- the jealousy?
- yeah.
insanely hot.
what's with the suitcase?
we can cool off and clean up the messes we've made.
i'm busy,you guys.
leave me alone.
izzie.
i went soft.
i...
had a baby,and i swore it wouldn't change me,it does change you.
i got tired,i got busy,and i stopped teaching.
i stopped teaching when you needed a teacher the most.
- you couldn't have stopped me.
- yes,i could've.
you couldn't have stopped you,but i could have.
and in the past,i would have.
i went soft.
and i'm partly to blame for what happened,so...
i want you to come back.
you will talk to thief.
we'll work it out,because you're talented,and you're capable,and we all make mistakes,
and-- and it's enough muffins.
we can try to let go of what was...
i thought you were room service.
i feel terrible.
i'm not proud of what i did.
you deserve better.
and i'm sorry about the...
sorry about the panties...
and the prom.
i-i'm sorry i did that.
yeah.
i'm sorry you did that,too.
our marriage is over.
yeah,i guess it is.
it's a my fault.
god,this is incredibly sad.
i'm incredibly sad.
and then again...
oh.
well,this is awkward.
i feel much better now.