Previously on Grey's Anatomy:
- The best breakup.
- She's doing McDreamy.
- Norman is an intern.
- I'm your sister.
You're not a girl I ever
wanted to have to know.
- Because our dad chose you.
- My niece's cancer's back.
She's 17 years old
and she's going to die.
Alex, I'm sorry. I can't.
I slept with Izzie.
In life, only one
thing is certain,
apart from death and taxes.
No matter how hard you try,
no matter how
good your intentions,
you are going to make mistakes.
Callie?
You're going to hurt people.
You're going to get hurt.
And if you ever
want to recover...
You haven't said anything in...
♪ We trick the train
to stay on track ♪
♪ I don't have to
leave the living room ♪
♪ To have a good time ♪
♪ We're going way out now ♪
Just say something.
Please. Anything.
There's really only
one thing you can say.
♪ At the end of your luck, so ♪
I forgive you.
- ♪ We getting on ♪
- What?
You made a mistake.
♪ Uh, oh, oh Uh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
But we took vows.
Till death do us
part, so I forgive you.
♪ When you're on my block
At the end of your luck, so ♪
♪ We getting on ♪
Izzie, why aren't you
picking up your phone?
I just talked to Callie and...
- George!
- I got to find Izzie.
- Rounds in five minutes.
- Right after I find Izzie.
♪ We getting on ♪
You wanna go away
with me this weekend?
Why would I want
to go away with you?
Because of this.
We didn't go away when we were
a couple. Now we're not a couple.
Not-couples have
no reason to go away.
You're not paying attention.
I'm talking about 48
uninterrupted hours of this.
♪ Deep holes and deep creases ♪
- Where would we go?
- Wine country.
Sounds like a couples place.
There's wine. There's
country. We wouldn't see it.
We'd be in bed all weekend.
- Oh, a weekend of sex.
- Now you're paying attention.
I'd have to get
someone to cover for me.
So you're in?
Forty-eight uninterrupted
hours of this? I'm in.
♪ Uh, oh, oh Uh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
Oh, great.
I'm stuck in the pit protecting
smackheads and gangbangers
from my interns, and
you're getting McDreamied.
Smackheads and
gangbangers at Seattle Grace?
- I hate interns.
- Lexie's not that bad, is she?
Oh, are we not
hating her anymore?
Oh, no. We still
hate the idea of her.
We realize we don't have a
reason to hate the actual person.
She's an intern.
That's reason enough.
I think you may be the new Nazi.
- Damn right.
- I don't see any charts.
- Will you work for me Saturday?
- What's in it for me?
- What do you want?
- Take Norman today.
- Who?
- The World's Oldest Intern.
He's only going to slow me down.
- Ageist.
- Deal?
Fine.
- Rounds!
- I still can't find Izzie!
I'm gonna have to put you in
the clinic if you miss rounds.
The clinic!
Miss Sayles? I'm
Dr. Bailey. You are...?
Uh... the boyfriend.
Who warned her not to
read on the StairMaster.
That's how I did
this. I fell off last night.
I took a ton of ibuprofen,
but when I woke up this
morning, it was huge and hideous.
How much ibuprofen did you take?
I usually take some every
day because of the gym.
So I doubled the dose,
but it did nothing for me.
OK, let's get some X-rays...
Can I just get a shot of
cortisone or something?
I'm supposed to meet
my trainer at noon.
Uh, Miss Sayles,
I can't treat you
until I find out what's
wrong with you.
- Have you seen Dr. Stevens?
- Check the pit.
Right.
What time do you
think we'll be done?
Just so I can tell my trainer.
Lexie! Sorry. Uh, have
you seen Dr. Stevens?
- No, you see Dr. Yang?
- No.
She told me to meet
her, she's not here.
Don't wanna give her
reasons to hate me.
Going to answer every question.
I'm not going to take her crap.
Three! Incoming! Let's move!
- Got hit during a scrimmage.
- You the coach?
- He's my dad.
- And coach.
He was charging the receiver.
He had his head down,
couldn't see the other guy.
I had my head down because
the guy blocking me was holding it.
You could've
gotten past that guy!
I need you to leave the room.
Cut him out of his equipment.
Dr. Grey, I need you to help
stabilize his neck and his head.
It's very important that
you not move your head.
I need you to keep perfectly
still. Do not move. Relax. Good.
- O'Malley, what's the hurry?
- I can't talk! I got to find...
O'Malley?
Sorry. I... I just
got to find Izzie.
She's at the third
floor nurses' station.
- Thanks.
- Oh, when you find her,
tell her Dr. Torres
is looking for her.
I know charting doesn't
seem as exciting as surgery,
but it is every
bit as important.
Believe me when I tell you,
people, penmanship saves lives.
What kind of doctor
doesn't pick up their phone?
Is that a seven
or is that a nine?
If I have to ask myself
that in an emergency,
your patient is dead.
You killed him. With
your handwriting.
Think about that.
Callie. Hey.
- We have to talk.
- OK.
- Um, about...?
- George told me.
- He told you...
- Everything.
Cafeteria. Noon.
You and me. Be there.
Dude. Is she going
to kick her ass?
- She forgave you?
- She said I had a rough year,
that people make mistakes,
and that I made a mistake.
Oh, so now I'm a mistake?
Back off!
- She said that. I didn't.
- What did you say?
Didn't expect her to forgive
me. I expected rage... bloodshed.
She's saving her rage
and bloodshed for me.
- She's gonna kill me.
- She wouldn't.
She breaks bones for
a living. She's crazy.
No, she's not crazy.
She is if she thinks I'm
not going to put up a fight.
I can't believe that kid's dad.
His son is paralyzed, and
the guy's still riding him.
Focus more on medicine,
Three, and less on the tragedy.
- Three? Is that a nickname?
- You could say that.
So how would you
proceed, Dr. Grey?
Oh, um... You won't
be able to operate
unless you realign
his spine, would you?
- How would you do that?
- Traction halo?
Very impressive, Dr. Grey.
Your intern year's
off to a good start.
How's it going? How
are you and Meredith?
Yeah, it's weird. The
whole family thing.
Plus I think she
might still hate me.
- She doesn't hate you.
- Really? Did she say that?
See if Mrs. Cooley's
dressings needs changing.
Why don't you go see
if Mrs. Cooley's dressing
- needs changing?
- Certainly.
Dr. Sloan, Dr. Norman Shales.
- Dr. Shales. Call me Mark.
- Thank you.
I thought you
were on my service.
I am. He's my intern.
I know, right? Like,
"Seriously, you're an intern?"
But it's seriously
true. Seriously.
Glad to have you aboard, Norman.
He the one you call
McDreamy or McSleazy?
Or Mc... Wait a
minute, what is it?
- We have labs to deliver.
- Yeah.
Labs and discharges.
This one's being
discharged to hospice?
When there's nothing
else we can do.
We tell someone they're dying?
Don't worry. I'll teach
you the protocol.
McSteamy! He's the one
you girls call McSteamy!
You paged me, Dr. Bailey?
- I didn't know you were...
- I'm in the clinic. Or I was.
- What do you got?
- Ruthie Sayles.
She twisted her ankle
falling off the StairMaster.
She crushed it. We should
book an OR right away.
You don't think we
should run tests?
Find out why Ruthie's
bones are fragile?
She's osteoporotic. I see it
in older women all the time.
Now you're seeing
it in a 28-year-old.
Right. Call me when
you get the test results.
I can't talk about it with you.
- Well, is she all right?
- Yeah.
When giving a
patient the bad news,
be polite and
detached, but not cold.
- How can you be detached
but not cold?
- Show you care
without actually
allowing yourself to care.
If you get too emotional,
then they get scared.
Then they get
emotional and that's bad.
- Seriously?
- Stop the "seriously."
Oh, uh, I'm sorry.
It must be hard being
older than most of us,
but I think you're
going to go a lot further
if you just let everything else
go and focus on the medicine.
McDreamy and the
Other Grey are bonding.
Over their mutual
Meredith Grey-ness.
- What are they saying?
- I don't know.
He's making me
deal with his patients
while they focus on
what's important: You.
Cristina!
What was I saying?
How important it was
to focus on the medicine.
Oh, just give me the chart.
We're going to apply a halo
which uses weights and traction
to pull your spine
back into place.
- Traction?
- Like at the gym.
Stretch your body using weights
till the spine pops in position.
Unlike at the gym,
Dr. Shepherd needs to
attach the traction device
directly to your head
- by screwing two bolts
into your skull.
- It sounds painful.
Painful is if he
doesn't fix your spine.
Painful is you never walk again.
OK. We going to
do this thing or what?
- Told you not to get emotional.
- I couldn't help it. What now?
Go apologize one last time.
Once again, ma'am,
we are very, very sorry.
Very sorry.
And now?
Now we slowly and
respectfully back out of the room.
Alex, I need a favor.
I don't have time for
favors. I'm working here.
Well, what are
you doing at lunch?
According to my interns,
watching Torres kick your ass
- up and down the cafeteria.
- How do they know?
- It's true? What'd you do?
- Nothing.
- Dude.
- - We need a little help here!
Thank God! Somebody I know.
Will somebody please make
sure they page my husband?
- Is that...?
- The Chief's niece.
Camille Travis, 18.
I've tried intubating.
Some kind of obstruction.
Sats staying down, 82 percent.
- Somebody get me a cric tray!
- How many crics have you done?
- Including this one? One.
- It's the Chief's niece.
- Pulse is weaker.
- We better not screw up.
- What are you doing?
- - Trying to help her breathe.
She just slit her throat!
I need suction.
Get the retractors.
You didn't hit an
artery, did you?
- No. Not on purpose.
- Oh, God. Oh, God.
Get the tube.
Oh, God.
- Sats are going up.
- Oh, we did it.
Richard!
What the hell are
you doing to my niece?
The one thing this child did
not need was another surgery.
- She wasn't breathing, Chief.
- Didn't know what else to do.
You did the right thing.
But Camille was diagnosed with
ovarian cancer when she was 14.
She's had both ovaries removed,
a hysterectomy, and now...
- There it is. The mass.
- No wonder she couldn't
breathe.
I can take it out, but we won't
know how many more there are
until we do further studies.
I'm so sorry, Chief.
She beat it twice before.
She'll beat it again.
I just had to tell a 48-year-old
woman that she's going to die.
I wish I could tell a 24-year-old
woman she's going to die.
I have gone out of my
way to be nice to her.
And she talks about
me behind my back?
- When were you nice to her?
- I was nice. Once.
- My point is...
- Hey, Meredith. Hey, Norman.
- What's up, Lexie?
- Come on, Norman.
Dr. Shepherd asked that we
meet in Adam's room in ten minutes.
You could acknowledge
that you heard me.
You're using the
Grey sister angle
to get in good
with the attendings.
I get that. But you're
here on my license,
so if you do anything, like
kill someone, it's on me.
The rest of the day
you're gonna hug the wall.
Not say anything.
Not do anything.
You're an intern.
Are we clear, Three?
Lexie.
- What?
- It's Lexie. Or Grey.
It's not "Three." I have a name.
Blood tests show
low electrolyte levels,
low calcium and low vitamin D.
- Have you been dieting?
- She just lost 40 pounds.
Will told me if I ever got
back down to a size four,
we'd move in together.
- How romantic.
- We just needed motivation.
I told him I wouldn't live with
a smoker, so he quit smoking.
The problem is,
even if Dr. Torres
is able to repair your fracture,
it won't do any good unless
you're eating more, and
working out less. Am I right?
Dr. Torr... Hey,
are you all right?
Uh... Dr. Bailey's right.
You won't operate unless
she puts on a bunch of weight?
- No, but...
- Why are we talking about this?
We came here to get her
leg fixed. So fix her leg.
OK.
How did that
discharge-to-hospice patient go?
Not great.
There was crying and
tears and more tears.
Tears? Really?
He's such a tough old bird. I
thought he'd take it like a man.
"He'd take it like a man?"
- What? I'm sexist now?
- No. "He" as in "him?"
- Joel Hanson in 2212?
- Not Gretchen Bitzer in 2213?
Oh, dear. I thought
that two was a three.
Did you and your
intern tell a woman
who came in to have
her moles removed
- that she was dying?
- Oh, dear.
I mean, crap. Oh, crap.
Hear that? Like a weight room.
There's nothing to be scared of.
He's been weight
training since he was eight.
What did I say about
you and the wall?
Dr. Yang. This is still a
teaching hospital, isn't it?
Yes, sir.
Need to get a closer if you
want to learn something.
OK, Adam. I'm going
to attach the tongs now.
I need you to stay perfectly
still during this procedure.
Let the weights do all the work.
You're going to feel a little pressure,
but you shouldn't feel any pain.
All right. Here we go.
Imagine being 14 and having some
doctor tell you you've got cancer?
- What do you do with that?
- You fight.
Camille's a fighter. You
two have that in common.
- Hmm.
- What's it going to be?
Stevens gets bones broken or
Torres gets taken to the trailer park?
It's not happening. But if it
does, will you pull her off me?
Tell me what you did?
You have to promise not
to say anything to anybody.
- Swear.
- I swear. Jeez.
I slept with George.
I'm a terrible person.
Which is why I'm gonna let
her get one good punch in.
Maybe two, I deserve it.
- No, one. Then pull her off me.
- You slept with O'Malley?
- You said you
wouldn't say anything.
- I won't.
Believe me. This...
I'm embarrassed for you.
You had one job. One
job. Read the charts.
You want to yell
at me some more?
I'm an intern.
According to Dr. Bailey,
yelling is how we learn.
- I'm not a good yeller.
- I'm sure it takes practice.
Perhaps Miss Bitzer will
show us how it's done.
- Let me do all the talking.
- Miss Bitzer?
- Gretchen?
- She left about an hour ago.
- She's gone? Left the hospital?
- Mm-hmm.
Feel like yelling now?
Your CT results show that
not only is the cancer back,
it's spread to your
chest, lungs and throat.
We have options
though. We can operate.
We can be even more aggressive
with the chemo and radiation
- than the last time.
- I just want to go home.
We can try to
treat you at home...
No, you don't understand.
I don't want any treatment.
- What?
- - Camille, don't say that.
I've tried, Mama. It's not
working. I can't do it anymore.
You can and you will.
You have no choice.
I'm 18 now, Aunt Adele.
I do have a choice.
You may be 18, baby girl,
but you are clearly not capable
of making life and death
decisions for yourself now.
- Tell her, Richard.
- No, you tell her.
Tell her how the radiation
almost killed me last time.
How I got hepatitis and
my kidneys shut down
and my skin was so
raw I couldn't be touched.
- Camille.
- I'm dying. We all know that.
I don't want to spend what
time I have left in this hospital.
I want to spend
time with my friends.
I want to sleep in my own bed.
And I want to be home.
So, please. Don't be
my doctor right now.
Be my uncle who loves me.
Let me go home.
Try not to move your head.
I'm trying, but...
I don't know how much
longer I can take this.
You'll take as much as they give
you. Come on, you can do this!
- Another few pounds.
- Maybe we should...
- No one asked you.
- I... I can't.
- Please take it off.
- Push through it!
OK, one more plate.
You're strong. You can
handle this. Want to be a quitter?
- Do you? Do you?
- That's it. That's 20 pounds.
You did it. Right? I
told you, you could do it.
Get him out, please.
Somebody, get him out.
- Adam, I'm just trying to help.
- Please get out! Get out!
Calm down. Try not to upset
him. Adam. Adam, calm down.
- Adam? It's OK.
- What are you doing? Don't touch him!
The slightest movement could...
Put his hand down. Gently.
I'm so sorry. I forgot...
Step away from the
patient and leave the room.
Get out right now or
I will throw you out.
Dr. Grey, take over for
Dr. Yang. Dr. Yang, a word.
You are a resident now.
Your job is to teach
interns, not abuse them.
Until you learn to be less
competitive and selfish,
you will not assist on my
surgeries. You will observe them.
- But she...
- You can go.
Arlene, she's just tired. She
doesn't know what she's saying.
But she's right. She's
not going to get any better.
We don't know that, Arlene.
There's always a chance.
Not if she doesn't
get treatment.
You've got to talk to her.
You... You have to convince her.
She loves you. She trusts you.
She's the closest thing we have
to a child of our own, Richard.
I'm begging you,
please, save our baby girl.
Again, Miss Bitzer, it's very
important that you call us back.
You idiots still can't find her?
I called her home,
her cell, her next of kin.
I don't care if you have to call
every Bitzer on the planet. Find her.
I am really so very
sorry about this.
It's not entirely your fault.
You're an intern. I
should've checked.
I was distracted by things I
shouldn't be distracted by.
For what it's worth,
Lexie Grey is a good girl.
She's very sweet.
I don't think she would say
anything untoward. Or uncool.
I have Bitzers to call.
But you could take
the... Norman? Norman?
- I'm not a bad resident, am I?
- Don't ask. I lost a patient.
- You killed someone?
- Lost. Literally can't find.
Oh. Shepherd says I'm
selfish and competitive.
What is wrong with that? I kick
ass. I'm an excellent resident.
I'm not. In addition to losing
my patient, I also lost my intern.
Turned around, he
was gone. AWOL.
What's wrong with these
interns? We weren't like this.
- We were great interns.
- I was great. You were good.
- You guys seen Callie?
- No. Ooh!
Is it time for her to grind
your bones into dust?
You don't think I can take her?
- You really doing this?
- You heard?
- Whole hospital heard.
- That explains the line.
- What are you fighting about?
- You don't want to know.
I'm just saying, whatever
it is, it's not worth it.
Actually, it is. Some
things are worth fighting for.
- O'Malley.
- Picking up labs
for Ruthie Sayles.
Who's your money on?
Guess you got to back the wife?
- What are you talking about?
- The fight? Torres vs. Stevens?
What they fighting about?
Oh, Winnie, it's just a rumor.
Callie's way too
mature for that.
That's not what my buddy
in the cafeteria just said.
- O'Malley! Your labs!
- I'll be right back!
I learned how to fight
in a trailer park, OK?
Where'd she learn to
fight, boarding school?
Not quite the same thing.
I'm a street fighter. I got some
bad ass in me. I can take a girl down.
Izzie.
Punch with your left, protect
your face with your right.
No, protect your surgeon
hands. Your face can heal.
♪ Tell me we're
knockers to bite ♪
♪ And out of the
beats of tomorrow ♪
Here we go.
♪ Tell me what
beat fills the night ♪
Stevens.
Let's do this.
Let's go. Let's go!
- Go where?
- You know. Go.
I wanted to talk.
You want to talk? You
don't want to kick my ass?
You thought I was
going to fight you?
- Excuse me.
- Sorry.
- A forfeit. Torres forfeits.
- Oh, my God.
You were very ghetto-fabulous.
Oh, my God.
- What happened? There a fight?
- No.
Guess they realized they
were fighting over nothing.
What do you think is a better
weekend getaway? Napa or Sonoma?
Hope you don't mind
if I kill your girlfriend.
First of all, she's
not my girlfriend.
Second of all, I mind.
Interns shouldn't
talk to patients.
- Well, that's how they learn.
- Which means I have to teach.
I have to deal with their
problems when they screw up.
Meredith rarely screws
up. She's not an intern.
- So Napa or Sonoma?
- Sonoma.
Smaller hotels, fewer tourists.
And Meredith?
She's still an intern.
Don't kid yourself. She's
green. She's a baby.
The only difference
between her and that old guy,
is that you're not
sleeping with the old guy.
- Sorry. I'm late.
- I was explaining the surgery.
Since your bones
have splintered,
Dr. Torres will place
metal plates and screws
to hold the ankle together.
- How long will the recovery be?
- Hard to say.
You'll be in a cast
eight to 12 weeks.
- Three months?
- Right, Dr. Torres?
- Longer if she doesn't eat.
- What? She eats.
Not enough to keep
her bones from snapping.
- You don't seem concerned.
- What is your problem?
I'm not the one who
has to live with you.
- Dr. Torres.
- You do have a problem!
In here. That's good. In here.
Ruthie was going
into surgery tomorrow.
That's before she
started vomiting blood.
- She's got a bleeding ulcer.
- How did we not see this?
She came in with a broken ankle.
Her malnutrition and the amount
of ibuprofen she's been taking?
- She's lucky to be alive.
- Why'd she do this to herself?
People are stupid and
just want to be loved.
It's the only reason
anybody does anything.
Asystole!
OK. Start CPR.
- You think he'll walk again?
- It's not impossible.
Got a bleeder.
I need you to cauterize
the vein, Dr. Grey.
Oh, OK.
I, um... I can't find it.
I can't see where it starts.
It's coming too quickly.
Suction around it. You have to see
where the bleed's coming from first.
Follow the flow to the
source. Good. Now bovie it.
- Got it.
- Good job.
Dr. Yang, if you
don't mind stepping in.
- Dr. Boler,
extension 4271.
- Dr. Grey?
Norman! Where have you been?
Do you think you can cut out
on me in the middle of a crisis?
I went...
Where did you go that
was important enough
to disappear in the
middle of a shift?
- Miss Bitzer's apartment.
- To Miss Bitzer's apartment?
Told her she had a bill
outstanding. She's right behind me.
But if I may say so, your
yelling's improved remarkably.
- Thank you.
- I'm sorry I missed your calls.
I didn't mean to
cut out on my bill.
It's just, I got a
lot of living to do
and not a lot of
time to do it in.
- Actually...
- Quit my job.
Dumped my boyfriend, told
my boss he could shove it,
and bought a ticket to Iceland,
where the sun never
sets, which is fine by me.
I'll sleep when I'm dead, right?
You're, uh, not going
to die, Miss Bitzer.
I'm not?
There was a mix-up with
your labs. You're going to live.
Hopefully a very
long, healthy life.
I quit my job!
I broke up with my boyfriend!
I gave up my apartment!
Do you know how hard it is to
find an apartment? With parking?
I thought you quit smoking.
Wasn't that the deal? Ruthie
loses 40 pounds, you quit smoking?
My girlfriend's in surgery.
She'll forgive me for smoking.
No. No, she won't
because she's dead.
Ruthie's dead.
Dr. Bailey tried to
stop the bleeding,
but because she's been
starving herself and overtraining,
her heart couldn't
take the strain.
You think this is my fault?
She wanted to lose the weight.
- I wanted her to be healthy.
- She was healthy 20 pounds ago.
You wanted her to be hot,
especially if you were
gonna move in with her.
- I loved her.
- You didn't love her!
You didn't want to be alone, or
maybe she was good for your ego
or maybe she made you feel
better, but you didn't love her!
Because you don't destroy
the person that you love!
- Callie!
- Get her away from me, man!
Give me some excuse to kick
somebody's ass because I'm dying to!
- Dr. Torres! Dr. Torres!
- Don't touch me!
Sir, we are so sorry for your
loss. O'Malley, please take him.
Sir, why don't you
come with me? Come on.
I'm going to ask you one
last time, are you all right?
- I'm fine. It's nothing.
- Really?
Because "nothing" almost
cost you your career just now.
The mass we removed
from your throat
was so big you couldn't breathe.
Camille, what took
you so long to come in?
I knew the cancer wasn't gone.
It's never been gone. It's
never going to be gone.
And, don't tell my
mom, but the truth is,
I was hoping it would kill me
before I had to come back here.
I'm just so tired,
Uncle Richard.
I am so, so tired.
♪ If you don't know ♪
♪ Who I am ♪
♪ If you can't see
that you need me ♪
What I have here is a
plan to keep you alive.
It involves 12 oncologists,
eight new drugs,
six experimental treatments
from three different continents.
I have no idea if it'll work,
but as your uncle, I'm
begging you to take it.
Because I know
for a fact, the world...
my world, is a better
place with you in it.
However, as your doctor...
I promise to do
whatever you want.
I just want to go home.
Then let's get you home.
♪ Take it away
in just one flight ♪
♪ And you can't say
that you see me ♪
Callie. Callie,
wait! Please wait!
Please.
♪ If you don't know who I am ♪
I'm sorry about the cafeteria.
I didn't know that you
wanted to talk to me.
I thought you wanted to kill me.
♪ You can't see
that you need me ♪
I'm sorry about everything.
With George, I...
I'm really sorry.
I feel terrible.
♪ If neither one of us ♪
♪ Can be found ♪
You feel terrible?
You took advantage.
He was your best friend.
I tried to trust you.
I'd convinced myself
that it was all in my head.
That I was crazy.
But I wasn't, was I?
Then you pull that
in the cafeteria?
You humiliate me by getting
in bed with my husband,
you have to humiliate
me at work too.
George may be the one
that broke his vows, but you?
We're women, Izzie. You
did this to another woman.
You took something from me.
You stole something from
me, like a petty little thief.
You are the one who
should be humiliated.
should be ashamed.
You are the one who should...
Don't you dare come
to me for forgiveness,
you traitorous bitch.
What, I'm invisible now?
What do you want?
So you hate me now
too. Well, join the club.
You and O'Malley? O'Malley!
What? What is it that I
did that is so horrifying?
- I fell in love, Alex.
- He's married.
Yeah. So?
You're carrying a big old
torch for Ava or Jane Doe
or whatever you call
her and she's married.
So what gives you the
right to judge what I do?
Why do you even care?
You told me you
weren't ready yet.
After Denny... to
be with anyone.
And then O'Malley? O'Malley!
Then you tell me, like I'm one
of your chick friends. Come on!
Miss Bitzer, I just wanted
to apologize one more time.
Oh, and I just wanted to
say thank you, Dr. Grey.
And you too,
Dr. Shales. Bless you.
Bye-bye.
- She's not going to sue?
- Nope.
Our lawyer talked
her into settling.
Seattle Grace bought
that woman four bedrooms
and three and a half
baths in Reykjavik.
- I'm so sorry.
- Tell the Chief.
- I'm writing you both up.
- It wasn't Norman's fault.
He's my responsibility. I'm
the one you should write up.
That's very noble
of you, Dr. Grey.
Stupid, but noble.
For the record, I don't
think you're stupid at all.
- I find you quite smart.
- Oh.
What did you say to Camille?
Adele.
I've already lost one baby
and now I have to lose Camille?
I am not going to use Camille
to try and make up for the fact
- I never gave you children.
- I never asked you to.
I asked you to talk to
her. To convince her to...
I can't do that.
I can't do that, Adele.
I can give her all the
options in the world,
but I cannot make her
do what I want her to do.
I'm her doctor.
I thought being a doctor
was about saving lives.
After all these years of
choosing your job over your family,
the one time I ask you to do
your job to save this family...
Adele, I'm sorry.
I'm truly, truly sorry, but...
So am I, Richard.
Callie.
You can't just forgive me.
What I did to you?
It's unforgivable.
That's how it works. That's
what "I forgive you" means.
No, see, I think it means
you don't forgive me.
You don't know
how to talk to me.
Look, you don't... You
can't even look at me.
You're so angry that the
only way you can deal with me
is to say you forgive me and...
What, we pretend
it didn't happen?
It happened. And
you don't forgive me.
You're right.
I don't.
So, I got Alex to cover for me.
I can leave right after
I round on my patients.
- Have 48 uninterrupted hours.
- Yeah. Um...
You know, maybe this
is not a good weekend.
What did Lexie say about me?
She didn't say anything.
I did all the talking.
- Don't blame her.
- You're friends
with my sister now?
I mean, you talk to the
other Grey about me?
You know what I talked
about with the other Grey?
All the things this
Grey won't let me say.
You can say anything to me.
I want to marry you.
I want to have kids with you.
I want to build us a house.
I want to settle down
and grow old with you.
♪ Yeah ♪
I want to die when I'm
110 years old, in your arms.
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
I don't want 48
uninterrupted hours.
I want a lifetime.
♪ I know you think
I'm like the other man ♪
Mm-hmm.
Do you see what happens?
♪ I'll free your mind
and I'll bless your soul ♪
I say things like that
and you fight the urge
to run in the
opposite direction.
It's OK. I understand.
I didn't, but now I do. I do.
You're getting started and I've
been doing this for a long time.
Deep down...
♪ It's destiny that
you're next to me ♪
you're still an intern.
- And you're not ready.
- I'm not ready right now.
But things could stay the way
they are, and I can get ready.
- I'll get ready.
- Things can stay
the way they are.
We can still meet in
elevator, the on call room.
And maybe you'll get ready.
And I'll wait.
I'll wait until you're ready.
♪ Like the old song says ♪
OK, then.
Yeah. But what if
while I'm waiting,
I meet someone who is ready
to give me what I want from you?
What if you do?
♪ Baby, baby when
the sun comes up ♪
I don't know.
♪ I'm gonna be holding you ♪
♪ It's destiny that
you're next to me ♪
♪ I'm in love with you Oh,
and, baby, when I wake up ♪
Forgive and forget.
♪ I'm gonna be there with you ♪
That's what they say.
♪ A new day rise I
wanna look in your eyes ♪
♪ When the sun comes up ♪
I just wanted to say,
thank you for saving
my ass today in surgery.
Well, that's my job, Three.
Now where are
Adam's post-op labs?
It's good advice, but
it's not very practical.
I'll get them, Dr. Yang.
♪ I'll hold on to the memory ♪
♪ All day ♪
When someone hurts us...
we want to hurt them back.
♪ Listen here, girl ♪
Come in.
♪ I know your pain ♪
♪ And I know you never
thought you could love again ♪
♪ But I know the way ♪
Keep it down, will you?
When someone wrongs
us, we want to be right.
Without forgiveness, old
scores are never settled.
♪ You'll still be here ♪
Old wounds never heal.
♪ When the sun comes up ♪
And the most we can hope for
is that one day we'll be
lucky enough to forget.
♪ Oh, baby when
the sun comes up ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah Yeah, yeah ♪