Previously on "Grey's Anatomy"...
You people are taking a test
that will determine the course
of your entire medical careers.
You want a big wedding ?
Yes.
I know you think I have feelings
for you, but I don't.
Search and rescue found
those lost climbers.
One's still missing.
Tell me the truth. Do you remember ?
Do you know who you are ?
He's making his recommendation
to the board tomorrow
for chief of surgery and chief resident.
- You're adopting ?
- She hasn't actually picked us yet.
This heartburn, it's like it...
Oh, no.
Fourth climber.
Is that an ax in his head ?
- If Richard finds out that you're
carrying another man's baby...
- Somebody help !
Being chief is about responsibility.
Every single surgical patient in the
hospital is your patient,
whether you're the one
who cut them open or not.
Come on. She's lost a lot of blood.
The scalpel stops with you.
Start 2 large bore I.V.S
and bolus 2 liters L.R.
You need to be able
to look at a family...
Ready ? One, two...
and tell them your team did everything
they could to save someone's child...
get me a stat E.K.G. And a
portable chest, Brooke.
She's 34 weeks pregnant with twins.
Their husband...
you guys, why don't you go have a seat
- in the waiting room ?
- We're not leaving her.
Their wife.
What happened ?
I don't know.
I found her unconscious.
You get caught up...
taking care of other people'families.
She's lost blood, a lot of blood.
And the responsibility,
it makes you...
I didn't even know she was in the
hospital. What was she doing here ?
You take care of other
people's families...
and you sacrifice your own.
I thought I was gonna hate this party
game thing, but it's kinda great.
Can we set her on fire after ?
No, we cannot.
Okay, these wedding vows
are not all gonna fit on here.
Okay, then write smaller.
Be still, please. "Vow"
just became "cow."
You don't need vows on your hand.
When you get up there,
just speak from the heart.
Izzie, the heart is an organ.
It pumps, it circulates blood,
it gets clogged from time to time.
It does not, however, speak.
It doesn't have tiny little lips on it.
Well, you're all "glass totally empty."
I'm gonna like being married.
It's the wedding part that's ridiculous.
- Party's over.
- Damn.
Hey, mine didn't go off. Piece of crap.
You can do this, right ?
Become a piece of chattel ?
Sure. Looking forward to it.
I mean, no matter what, you're
walking down that aisle today.
I need you to go down that aisle.
Is the toilet paper cutting off
your circulation ?
You marrying Burke, it's a sign.
It's a sign that people like
you and me can do this...
be healthy, be happy.
You marrying Burke
restores my faith in me.
I get it. My wedding's about you.
- Yes.
- Okay.
You can do this, right ?
I can do this.
Okay.
They found the fourth climber.
Vitals are stabilizing
after fluids, but...
- I thought he was dead.
- He was according to his friends.
Did the C.T. show a bleed ?
We haven't done a C.T. yet.
I don't understand. You said
there's a head trauma.
There's been a little head trauma.
ice ax to the head.
What the hell happened
up on that mountain ?
That's a good question.
You don't think it could be
uterine cancer, do you ?
It runs in the familly.
No, it's not...
she was in earlier. She was
in a fender bender.
My wife came into my hospital,
and you neglected to tell me ?
Doctor-patient confidentiality.
We're still married.
She's unconscious. There are medical
decisions to be made.
- Legally I have a right to know.
I have a right...
- She might...
be having a miscarriage.
She's pregnant.
I need to know what time
your chest pain started.
I don't know.
Yesterday afternoon.
What time exactly ?
This is important.
Around 3:00.
What's wrong with me ?
I'm gonna explain everything
to you. I promise.
But right now we need to get you
up to the surgical floor.
Surgery ? But...
- What about my babies ?
- I think those babies are coming out
today.
But I-I haven't decided. I...
I haven't chosen the parents.
I need time to decide.
You don't need to decide
anything right now.
Right now the most important thing
is making sure that you are okay.
All right ?
Burke.
Ah, I've got a surgery, but it shouldn't
be more than four hours, five tops.
I can scrub in.
How's Rina ?
I need to get a C.T. angio, but I'm
pretty sure it's a tear in her aorta.
Her heart is about to blow.
Most dissecting aortas burst
within 48 hours.
Which means we have less than 12 hours
to fix it before she's dead.
- So you need me to get the babies out.
- So I can save her life.
You have an aortic dissection ?
Hey, I promise I will make it
to the chapel in time.
I...
Okay. Listen up. Uh, O'Malley,
you're with Shepherd and Sloan.
Stevens, you're with Burke.
Karev, Addison. Go.
Grey... you are with the chief's wife.
- The chief's wife ?
- Is pregnant.
Yes, I did say pregnant. I recommend
that you lose the shocked look and try
for something a little more dignified.
Go.
Who am I on ?
Uh, I didn't page you. Go home.
Get some sleep.
Yeah, but I'm here already, so...
You're getting married
in less than 12 hours.
Give us room.
Well, uh, Burke's getting married, too,
and he gets to operate.
There's only one Preston Burke.
There's only one Cristina Yang.
I've given you the day off,
the whole day.
It's a kindness. Take it.
It's your wedding day.
- There'll always be more surgeries.
- But...
really, what would you rather be doing,
preparing a patient or preparing
for your wedding ? Go home.
Saison 3 Episode 25
"Didn't we almost have it all ?"
I never got the sense you really
wanted the job.
Seems to me you got in the race
to play out some kind of unfinished
business you had with Derek.
I was in this to win, sir.
I don't know if he's your new chief,
but if he is, he got there because
I made him fight for it.
You made them all fight for it.
So I'm not gonna be chief.
No you're not.
They recovered Lonnie's body ?
Not his body. He's alive.
So why don't you tell me what really
happened up there on the mountain ?
W-we're half way up this ice wall.
There's a...
there's a ledge
a couple of huned feet above us.
We figured we'd set up the tents,
wait out the storm.
Only Lonnie's insisting
we go down the mountain.
I told him, we gotta dig in, sit tight.
He started freaking out, keeps saying
down's the way to go.
And then he starts climbing down.
We were tied together.
- And just like that...
- We're falling.
I swing out with my ice ax,
just trying to catch a rock.
And I clip Lonnie in the
back of the head.
Ax just...
snags.
We thought he was dead.
It was an accident.
What happened ?
You've been unconscious for a while.
- What about...
- He knows.
Adele, you lost a lot of blood.
I'm gonna try to find a heartbeat.
You should prepare yourself.
Heartbeat.
It's a little slower, than I'd like,
but once we tank you with
liquids and a transfusion,
it might get stronger.
I've gotta rush off to surgery, but I
will back with you the minute I'm done
- Okay ?
- Thank you.
Okay.
Adele, why didn't you tell me ?
Come on, Richard.
What do you think you would've done,
congratulate me ?
I'm sure you have work to do.
I'm good right here.
The peds resident's on call. He'll be
in the O.R. for Rina's delivery.
Great. Just make sure
they notified the nicu.
Hi.
Sorry for interrupting. The nurse
said that you're Dr. M-Montgomery.
Yes. Can I help you with something ?
I'm Jeff Pop
Rebecca's husband ?
Rebecca?
Rebecca ?
Hi, Jeff.
You...
your face...
but it's you.
I'm so sorry, baby.
I should've never let you go.
I'll never let you go again.
- Hey.
- I have a surgery.
- I heard you're the best man.
- Yeah.
- Maid of honor, best man, kinda perfect.
I know I haven't been myself lately, but
I'm me again, so I was thinking maybe
you should sleep over, because
the me that I am is horny for
the you that you are.
I met a woman last night.
- You met a woman last night ?
- At Joe's.
Nothing happened.
She was pretty, I noticed,
and we talked.
- You met a woman last night ?
- Yeah.
- So should I be worried or something ?
Should you be worried
that I met a woman ?
No.
Should you be worried that,
for me, flirting with that woman
was the highlight of my week ?
Yeah, you should be worried
or something.
I don't understand.
It's not you.
No, I understand that part. What
I don't understand is why.
I need this job,
Richard. I need it more than the others.
- Addison...
- No, I need a reason
to stay here.
I need a reason to get up in
the morning. I need to wake up
and not care that it's raining
or that I'm 39 and alone.
I need the job, Richard.
That's why.
If you need a job to give you a life,
you either need a new job
or a new life.
I'm thinking four hours tops
to repair this heart,
if all goes well.
You're a lucky man, Burke.
Cristina's great.
She's there, she's sure.
She's willing to commit.
You're a lucky man.
And you're not ?
There he is.
T-minus five hours.
And how's the best man ?
Up to the challenge ?
I was an excellent best man.
You know, the worst case scenario
is I sleep with your wife in ten years.
Okay.
I just checked. Chief resident
hasn't been posted yet.
No, no. I wasn't looking
- for chief resident.
- Yeah, you were.
Yeah. Okay, I was.
George...
- Hey.
- What I'm about to say is, is crazy.
And, I-I-I am not responsible.
I-I am saying this against my will.
Because I am a surgeon,
okay ? I-I-I love my job. I love
my life exactly as it is.
Okay ? Exactly as it is. Do you
understand what I'm saying ?
Not really
I-I have no desire to house a human
being in my body for 9 long months
and then...and then...and then push it
out and raise it. Okay ? None.
Zero.
- Okay.
- Except housing a human
for nine long months is all
that I can think about.
It... it... the thoughts are invading the
surgeries that I love, and it's... it's...
it's... it's hormonal.
It's... and horrible.
But it is happening...
to me.
You want to have a baby ?
Apparently.
There's a guy with an ax in his head.
- Right.
- So go.
I'm a freak. Just go. Just run. Just...
- thank you.
- Please.
Go. I'm fine.
Take your pill... and drink your water.
Richard, you know you wanna go out
that door and start bossing some
- people around.
- Take your pillule Adele.
See ?
I can do my bossing
right from this chair.
Go ahead, Richard, ask.
- I know you are dying to know whose
baby th...
- not really my place.
Mrs. Webber...
your room is ready.
Excuse me, but
what do you want to do about the
announcement for chief of surgery ?
Look, I will be right back.
I promise.
We've met before.
You probably don't remember.
You were little.
My husband always flirted
with your mother.
I didn't want to see that, so...
I watched you a lot,
watched you grow up.
You turned out well.
I'm sorry about your mother.
I'm...
sorry about my mother, too.
It wasn't your fault.
Maybe it wasn't anyone's fault.
You get married at 25 thinking,
this is it, happily ever after.
Maybe there is no happily ever after.
It's stunning.
It's a little...
Is it supposed to be so tight ?
Well, it's a choker.
It's beautiful.
It's really, really beautiful.
I just don't know if it's me.
Five generations of Burke women have
worn this on their wedding day.
It's a way of...
joining our family,
becoming a Burke.
A Burke.
I'm afraid I missjudged you early on.
I thought you were selfish.
But you've given way to Preston's
ideas about the wedding,
and you've been flexible
about the things that are...
most important to him.
And that is wonderful.
It's just...
what were you planning to do
about your eyebrows ?
N-nothing.
How's she doing ?
B.P.'s 92 over 56.
How'd the reunion go with
Jane Doe's husband ?
Whatever. He cried like a baby.
She looked bored.
Don't go overboard with
compassion, Karev.
She's not even sure if she wants
to stay with the guy.
- It's complicated
- It's not actually...
complicated.
- They're married.
- She took a vow.
You don't mess with vows.
Married is married.
Game over. So freakin'over.
Just an opinion.
Pressure's dropped to 60.
She's bleeding out. Addison,
how much longer ?
Rupturing the membrane now.
- I just need 2 minutes
to get these babies out.
- Make it one.
She's flatlined. Stevens,
start compressions.
Got the first one out. Clamp.
Come on come on.
- Second baby's out. Okay, go.
- Boki, 10-blade.
Poor guy... he just wanted to climb
a mountain, and he ends up with an
ax in his head.
Well, he shouldn't have tried
turning back.
The group is going up,
you move with the group.
- Okay, drill, please.
- He panicked.
You have a right to turn back
if you're scared.
No, you don't.
You chose to climb a mountain.
You can't change your mind
in the middle of the climb.
- Okay.
- Now we pull it out ?
Ah, yeah, but the ax went in as they
fell, so there will be some tearing,
it should be a shallow wound,
- and it should come out easily.
- You got it ?
All right, everybody. Here we go. Ready?
Okay, one, two... three.
That's strange.
One... two. Three !
- That's a clean cut.
- I thought you said there was gonna
be tearing.
I know. It doesn't make sense.
You are a lucky guy.
Yeah.
Or the ax didn't go in there
by accident.
It's probably unfair,
but I hold you to a higher standard.
And you let me down this year, Preston.
After you got shot,
the tremor...
this job is about making
the tough calls.
Sometimes the toughest call
you can make
is admitting when you're
in over your head.
You don't do that.
You know a lot, Preston.
You're one of the best surgeons
I know...
one of the best men.
But you're not perfect.
You don't know everything.
I want to give you the job.
I want to.
But I can't.
Preston.
I have a wedding to get to.
Thank you.
Yeah. The babies are doing great.
They're in the nicu.
How are you doing up there, Preston ?
- Close call, but she's stabilized.
- Good work, Dr. Burke.
We may actually get you to the church
on time. You nervous ?
No, not really.
More, uh... excited.
Except by my vows. I wrote them myself,
and... I don't know.
They may be too...
- I want'em to be right.
- Well, let's hear'em.
What, now ?
Hey, you've got a room full
of women. Try it out on us.
Cristina...
I could promise...
to hold you...
and to cherish you.
I could promise
to be there in sickness and in health.
I could say...
till death do us part.
But I won't.
Those vows
are for...
optimistic couples,
the ones full of hope.
And I do not stand here
on my wedding day
opmistic
or full of hope.
Okay, um...
I am not optimistic.
I am not hopeful.
I am sure.
I am steady.
And I know.
I am a heart man.
I take'em apart.
I put 'em back together.
I hold them in my hands.
I am a heart man.
So of this I am sure...
you are my partner...
my lover...
my very best friend.
My heart... my heart... beats for you.
And on this day,
the day of our wedding,
I promise you this...
I promise you
to lay my heart in the palm
of your hands.
I promise you...
me.
Too trite ?
- Because I can rewrite it...
- No.
No. It's...
I think I speak for...
every woman in this room
when I say dump her.
Dump Yang and marry me.
Hey.
- Hey. Oh, god. Did I miss a page ?
- No, no, no, no, no.
Everything's okay.
What ?
Is this really what you want ?
'cause if it's really what you want,
we could do it.
- Really ?
- Yeah.
- Okay, wait. Really ?
- Really.
Oh, my god.
Oh, my god. Really ?
She looks like Rebecca.
Well, at least what Rebecca
used to look like.
But still.
Around the eyes.
Yeah.
I thought I'd give her some space.
She seemed a little overwhelmed.
The ferry crash was on the news
everywhere.
Your wife goes missing...
how could you not look for her ?
I thought she left me.
We got into a fight that night.
She was trying to tell me how
unhappy she was and...
I shut her down.
Yeah, I didn't look for her when she
was missing, but what's worse is...
I didn't see her when she was there.
I can't imagine what it must have
been like for her,
what her face must have
looked like all broken.
She was beautiful.
I love her.
You know ?
Meredith.
You are not gonna believe...
Derek met a girl...
in a bar.
And he flirted with her.
And he told me.
You know, no big deal.
Just thought I should know.
Meredith.
I'm not exaggerating.
He didn't even hint. He just
flat out told me.
Meredith, you know how sometimes it's
about you, and sometimes it's about me ?
This is really, really about me.
Mama took my eyebrows.
She took my eyebrows,
and now I am a Burke.
Lonnie's stable...
but the damage he sustained
is significant.
But is he gonna wake up ?
Do you want him to?
What ?
The ax in his head was put
there deliberately.
I just wanted to give you three guys
another opportunity to tell me the truth.
- It wasn't...
- Shut up, Andy.
- But we can't just sit here...
- I said shut up, Andy.
Is that how you let him talk to you
at 14,000 feet ?
I have to talk to his family.
You guys can talk to the cops.
Dr. Bailey.
Yeah. What ?
Cristina needs to cut something.
I can't really explain it
in a way that won't make you glare.
But...
they took her eyebrows
and they called her a Burke.
She really needs
to cut somebody open.
Yang...
go... do...
getting married things.
Get out of this hospital.
I mean...
I...
you have to let me cut,
because I am standing here
eyebrowless with no dignity left.
I am a surgeon, dr. Bailey.
But right now I don't feel like one.
I feel...
like...
somebody else.
Do you know what that's like,
not to feel like yourself ?
What's going on?
She started cramping and then
she got really diaphoretic.
Alert O.B. to a possible D & C due to
an incomplete miscarriage.
Adele,
you could have a placental abruption
due to the trauma.
We've got to get you
to into an O.R. now.
Let's move, people !
Sir, dr. Shepherd is here.
Thank you.
Richard, are you sure
you want to...
you don't have to do this today.
Yes, I do.
She went into early D.I.C.
I gave her blood, platelets, F. F. P,
pregnancy at 52 is dangerous.
I tried everything. I
couldn't save...
I thought...
for a second, I thought I'd lost you.
Do you want to... call somebody ?
I can...
No, no one.
Well, the father of the baby,
maybe you want to...
He doesn't even know about it.
I didn't tell him.
I, um...
I think I misjudged him.
I thought he'd go running
for the hills.
But actually...
He's a much better man
than I thought.
He'll get over his initial judgments,
and he'll...
sit with you...
and he'll make you drink
your water.
Look
- Adele...
- It was a boy.
I'm sorry.
All right, dr. Leonard, would you please
close for dr. Burke ?
He has a wedding to get to.
One cut,
and then you're gone.
One.
But... I still have to...
Come on. You want your bride
waiting for you at the altar ?
They don't like that.
Let's go.
We gotta go now, Cristina.
Grey.
Put the scalpel down, Cristina.
You can still do this, right ?
What?
Hold on a minute.
I just wanted to make sure
no one's around so I can say this.
- I think we've said everything
we need to say.
- Shut up.
I am an optimist.
I am hopeful.
I am not sure.
- Look, I can do this myself.
- Let me speak.
Because I'm your best friend
and because I love you,
if what you want is to be with Callie,
then I will do everything
in my power to support you
and help you
make your marriage work.
But because
I'm your best friend
and because I love you...
I also
have to say...
that I'm in love with you.
I'm in love with you.
I can't promise the future,
I can't promise perfection because
we're us and I'm me
and who knows what will happen.
But in my heart...
I am sure.
I'm in love with you, George.
And I hope you're in love with me, too.
Say something.
What time is it ?
You got 30 minutes.
Oh, crap. I'm gonna be late
for my own wedding.
No, we're not.
Dr. Burke asked me
to check on you.
Let's see. Your, post-op x-rays look
good. We'll discuss releasing you.
- Any change in Lonnie ?
- Andy ?
Who are you?
He's my lawyer.
- That was fast.
- Don't you dare judge me.
You weren't there.
We thought... he was almost dead.
No way he was gonna make it.
He was in so much pain.
So I...
- picked it up...
- Andy, shut up.
- No !
I'm not gonna shut up.
I put him out of his misery.
And if I was back there right now...
I'd do the same thing.
He was my friend.
He is my friend.
I put him out of his misery.
Anyone got any deodorant ?
You're not putting my deodorant
in your hairy armpits.
Don't move.
You're gonna have a unibrow.
And I have some in my locker.
Uh, closed ? Open ?
Closed.
Perfect.
Dashing.
- Thanks.
- You look great.
- Moment of truth, people.
- Those our scores ?
Grey.
Karev.
Yang, Stevens
whoo-hoo !
O'Malley.
Yes !
right here, baby.
Yes. Thank god.
Did you pass ?
You bet your married booty, I did.
How'd you do ? Did you pass ?
Yeah.
- I'll talk to you at the church.
- Okay
- All right. Let's go.
- Excuse me.
Meredith.
I'll meet you at the chapel.
Iz, will you take the dress ?
- I'll be right there.
- Okay.
I like the suit.
- The suit is way better than the scrubs.
- Thanks.
Hey, uh, I passed
my intern exam.
- Good ! That's good.
- Yeah.
We got discharged,
me and the baby.
Oh, come on, you just
you just had brain surgery.
You're still...
you're still on antibiotics.
My body's been signed off on by...
plastics, cardio, orthopedics,
neuro and O.B.,
And my... and also, my teeth
got the blessing from...
wait, I can say this...
prosthodontics.
Yeah, but there's still your memory
you know how I know my memory's fine ?
Because I can say prosthodontics.
- Yeah, but the baby...
- Discharged, by peds.
Yeah, but...
I have every reason to go.
And and yeah, I'm scared.
And yeah, this is moving at warp speed.
And yeah, I'm freaking out,
but Jeff is good.
And Jeff isthe father of my child.
The man is out buying a car seat
right now.
And the minute he gets back...
I have every reason to go,
because medically...
there's no need for me to stay.
Medically.
Okay. Well, then
I'll just check the chart.
- Damn it.
- We got, uh...
what ?
Are you... Do I have to spell
everything out for you ? I mean,
Did you sniff too much glue as a child ?
I'm asking you something here
What do you want from me?
I want...
I want you to give me
a reason to stay...
a real reason.
I mean, Jeff's... Jeff's a decent guy,
a good, decent guy.
But to him, I'm Rebecca, and I don't
know if I am rebecca anymore and...
you know me. You knew... you knew
when I couldn't even speak who I was.
You... you named me Ava,
and I was more me
as Ava then I'll ever be as rebecca.
Look, I have every reason
to go back to my life.
And I will.
Unless... you...
Alex, I'm asking you to give me a
reason to stay here... A reason from you
Jeff loves you. He's a...
- He's a decent guy.
- Alex, give me a reason.
I think you should stay
with the decent guy.
If you want to break up with me
so you can see other women, just do it.
Don't tell me you met another woman.
Just end it if that's what you want.
I can't.
Sure you can.
Here's how it goes...
meredith, I don't want
to see you anymore.
Meredith, I don't love you anymore.
Meredith...
I do love you.
Don't you see ?
Don't you understand?
You're the love of my life.
I can't leave you.
But you're constantly leaving me.
You walk away when you want,
you come back when you want.
Not everyone,
not your friends,
but you leave me.
So I'm asking you... If you don't see a
future for us, if you aren't in this...
please... please just end it,
because I can't. I'm in it.
Put me out of my misery
I... I can't. I... I...
Cristina is getting married.
I have to go
make sure she gets married.
- Meredith...
- I really need to make sure
she gets down that aisle.
Let's go. We're running late.
You okay ?
I'm fine. I'm fine.
You need anything ? Need a mint, huh ?
A getaway car ?
If it's the chief thing, don't worry
about it. You deserve it.
Richard didn't pick me
to be chief.
We all assumed you...
- Well, who did he pick ?
- I don't know. It wasn't me.
You really don't...
look so good.
Meredith and I
may not make it.
I think I want it
more than she does.
It's all about you today.
- You really are a good best man.
- I try.
Cristina.
- Cristina ?
- I didn't run.
You look beautiful.
- I'm proud of you.
- Thank you.
Frankly, I always feared
you were too emotionally
stunted to settle down.
You can do this.
I've always found it confusing.
If you know both the bride and the
groom, which side do you sit on ?
I just look for the hottest chick
in the room and sit next to her.
- Stop.
- Wanna ditch the reception,
grab a drink instead ?
Stop it.
You don't want me.
- Maybe I do.
- No, you don't.
You want Ava.
She's not Ava anymore. She's Rebecca
now, and I barely know her.
Look at me.
You suck.
To me, you suck.
I kind of... hate you.
But, Alex,
we do not get unlimited chances
to have the things we want. And this
I know... nothing is worse
than missing an opportunity
that could've changed your life.
And no matter what her name is,
she'll always be Ava to you.
Dr. Bailey.
- You didn't go to the wedding either.
- No.
I am... so sorry, George.
So, um... what do I do now ?
You fail your intern test,
you have two options. You can...
walk away from being
a surgical resident altogether,
or you can start
from the very beginning.
Repeat my internship ?
No
I can't.
did I...
did I fail you, george ?
No.
I failed you.
Ooh. It looks so pretty
in there. I see Burke.
- Yang the twins looks nice in that dress.
- Thank you.
Sort of.
I gotta go. Congrats
- You're on call ?
- Wait, Alex. Did you see George in here ?
I don't see him.
He's, uh... probably gonna be late.
We had kind of a big, emotional day.
- Oh, really ?
- Yeah.
Did something happen
between you two ? I mean...
No. It's just that I was
named chief resident
Plus we decided to have a baby,
A baby ?
Yeah, we're trying.
We tried today, in fact.
- Wow.
- Yeah. Big day.
This is it.
- Okay ?
- Yeah.
- You have the bouquet. I have the ring.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- You remember your vows ?
- Yeah. Okay. I wrote them on my...
Oh, my god
I scrubbed in.
I scrubbed in, and the vows were
on my hand. I scrubbed off my vows.
Oh, okay.
Hello ? I... I scrubbed off my vows.
I... I can't... I can't do this.
I don't have any... I don't have
anything on my hand !
I should go see
what's going on.
Well, Cristina wouldn't be Cristina
if she didn't need a little push.
There are no words in my head. Okay ?
I have no vows.
- No vows.
- It's okay. It's going to be okay.
You know what ? Stop saying that !
Will you say sometng else ?
- Like what?
- Say something that is gonna help me.
Okay, okay !
Meredith, please. You know what ?
Say something.
Say... you know what?
I don't know what. Say... say... okay.
Say what I would say to you
if you were me.
- Okay.
- Good.
- Got it.
- Good, go.
Stop whining.
This is your wedding day.
You will go down that aisle
and you will get married.
If have to kick your ass every step
of the way to get you there,
you will walk down the aisle.
You will get married.
Do you hear me, Cristina ?
We need this.
We need you
to get your happy ending.
- Okay, I'm ready.
- All right, then.
My train.
I'll go.
Oh. I'm ready. I'm fine. I...
Meredith talked me down.
Really, I'm fine.
Go, go, go. I'll be right behind you.
I'm sorry.
I can do this.
You know, I had a momentary freak out,
but now I'm fine. I can do this. Go.
But you don't want to do this.
I'm up there waiting for you
to come down the aisle,
and I knew you don't want to come.
I know you don't want to come but that
you'll come anyway because you love me.
And if I loved you...
if I loved you,
not the woman that I'm trying
to make you be, not
the woman that I hope you'll become,
but you...
if I did...
I wouldn't be up there waiting for you.
I would be letting you go.
I am wearing the dress.
I'm ready.
And... and maybe I didn't want to
before, but I want to now.
I really think I want this.
And I really wish
that you didn't think.
I wish that you knew.
It's over.
You can all go home.
It's so over.
He's gone.
I... I... I don't think he's gone.
- Uh, his stuff is steel here.
- No, it isn't.
His trumpet was here.
His entire Eugene Foote collection...
vinyls and cds...
his grandmother's picture
was by the bed.
His lucky scrub cap was
hanging on the door.
He's gone.
I'm...
I'm free.
Damn it.
Oh, god. Get this off me.
Take this off ! Take this off !
Please, just...
I can't...
help me, help me, help me !
Ah, nice.
Do we get assigned lockers here or what ?
Dude, it stinks in here.
- What do you want ? It's a locker room.
- No, it's our locker room.
You guys, look, bloody scrubs.
Hi.
- Come on, you guys.
Let's, let's go check out the cafeteria.
- Yeah.
Hey.
Hi.
- We're the new interns.
- Yeah.
Well, you look seasoned and wise.
Um... got any advice ?
No.
Learn how to do an appendectomy
start to finish before your first day.
- You're leaving ?
- Yeah.
Better offer?
Just, uh... you know, life.
Yeah.
Anyways, uh, good luck with...
life, doctor...
My name is George.
I'm Lexie. Lexie Grey.
Congratulations.
You'll make a fine chief.
Derek ?
I'm not the best man for this job.
You're the best man for this job.
What are you talking about, Derek ?
A good chief learns from his mistakes.
I'm still working on that. But you...
if you had a chance to do it all over
again, you'd do it differently.
Go ahead.
Do it all over again.
Be the best man.
Merci à Raceman pour les transcripts
Synchro : ChipounetteF et Mickeyte
www.forom.com
http ://experts.heberg-forum.net/
See U next season !