When something begins,
you generally have no
idea how it's going to end.
The house you were going
to sell becomes your home.
The roommates you were forced
to take in become your family.
And the one-night stand
you were determined to forget
becomes the love of your life.
Hey. How long have you been up?
All night. I was
trying to figure out
how to get the tumor
out of Izzie's brain.
Then why are you smiling?
'Cause I figured
out how to do it.
Once Izzie's in the clear,
we go to the Bahamas,
and have our
wedding on the beach.
The One & Only Beach Club.
You're gonna actually have
drinks during the ceremony.
♪ It just might
change your day ♪
Sure you're OK to
be up and around?
Yes. I have good
days and bad days.
I don't want to spend our entire
honeymoon in a hospital bed.
- This is not our honeymoon.
- It totally is.
- I want you to meet my friends.
- I know all your friends.
You know all my doctor friends.
I'm a patient now. You
gotta meet my patient friends.
And they are gonna
love my new husband.
- Don't make a big deal.
- I'm not gonna make a big deal.
I'm a bride!
Iz, come on. I'm
getting her a real one.
I love this one. That
makes it a real one.
- Everybody, this is Alex. My husband.
- Hi.
Husband, this is Austin,
Star, Meg, Miguel and Alison.
Can you turn him around
so we can see the butt?
- Yes. Alex?
- What, are you kidding me?
Oh! A big trauma
just came in. That's...
- That's quality booty.
- Right?
- Congratulations, Izzie.
- Thank you.
So, uh, I had a good session
with my shrink this morning.
Did you talk to her
about your mom?
Have you seen your mom yet?
'Cause she lives
a few miles away,
and she thinks you're in Iraq.
- I am planning to see her.
- When?
Dr. Hunt? I'm not
on trauma today?
Follow me, O'Malley.
Lieutenant Lowell, I'm
Dr. Hunt, we spoke on the phone.
Major Hunt, it's good
to finally meet you.
My CO's told me a lot about you.
You shouldn't believe
anything Steve Mason tells you.
This is Dr. O'Malley,
you've met Dr. Torres.
I'm looking at Charlie's
scans, but not finding anything
functionally wrong with the leg.
Except I can't walk
or run or move,
really, without serious
pain. I've tried everything.
Medications, physical
therapy, nothing works.
Which could indicate
nerve damage.
Or chronic pain syndrome.
And we can look into pain
management, but surgically,
I'm afraid there's
nothing I can do.
Actually, there is.
You could cut it off.
You can cut it off, replace
it with a prosthetic leg
so I can get back to
Iraq, where I'm needed.
- Did you know why he was here?
- No.
Is it such an
unreasonable request?
Unreasonable? Cutting off a
viable limb is dismemberment.
That kid made lieutenant at 19.
He was planning on
spending his life in the military.
They'll take him
back with one leg?
There have been amputees who've
returned to duty with prosthetics.
- Voluntary amputees?
- Maybe, I don't know.
I have to turn this kid away?
His CO sent him here
because he trusts me.
We could get
another set of scans
and then try an
epidural for the pain.
Dr. Torres?
Fine. Do an MRI and an epidural.
I'll take a look at the scans,
but if the leg is healthy,
I'm not cutting it off.
- Dr. Bailey, you busy today?
- That depends.
You got any dying children
you want me to become
overly attached to
before they expire?
I have an eight-year-old
neuroblastoma patient
and he's gonna live.
I feel it in my bones.
So scrub in with
me and see the joy.
Dr. Bailey, may I borrow you?
- Who is Santa Claus?
- An old, white man
who lives at the North Pole
and enters people's
homes inappropriately?
No.
I'm Santa Claus.
All systems ready.
Oh, no, you did not!
Oh, yes, I did. The Da
Vinci S-I HD Surgical System.
Tell me you didn't
wait until I'd all but left
the general surgery
program to buy the Da Vinci.
Care to take it out for a spin?
Santa!
Hey. I was thinking, you know,
with Derek and
Meredith getting married,
they probably don't
want us hanging out
in the attic much longer.
So I was thinking I'd
start looking for a condo.
Perfect. Then you'd finally
have a place of your own.
Actually, I was, you know,
thinking maybe you'd, uh...
- you'd come with me.
- Absolutely.
I'd love to see it. I
am so happy for you.
How much of that did you hear?
The part where you asked
her to move in with you
or where she shot you down?
I was here for both.
And, by the way,
it's just way too early for
you to be moving in with Lexie.
You don't have to
do everything I do.
This is not about you.
I have my own future to
think about. Life is short.
Look at what's going
on with Stevens.
Don't worry about
Stevens. I got a plan.
You want to remove
her hippocampus?
One of them. It's a
common procedure.
Removing her hippocampus
could compromise
her memory, her speech.
She wouldn't be able
to practice medicine.
- I've performed this
hundreds of times.
- On cancer patients?
- No, but it's...
- If you do it,
I could lose my memory?
It's unlikely,
but it's possible.
And if you don't
do the surgery...
We could shrink
the tumor with IL2.
- If the tumor doesn't kill me first.
- - Why take the chance?
- Have you done a Wada test?
- - Putting her brain to sleep and asking her
to remember flash
cards is not an accurate...
But it would tell us whether
or not she could function after.
- As her physician...
- Fine, I'll do it. It's unnecessary.
The surgery is unnecessary.
She's having hallucinations.
Nice ring.
Alex outdid himself.
We're gonna have beautiful
kids, don't you think?
- Is four too many?
- Four is perfect.
Ideally, it would be
two boys and two girls.
One of which will
definitely be a tomboy.
And I should have
them close together,
though that might be stupid.
- Why wait?
- Exactly.
That way, if I'm not able to
practice medicine anymore...
- You won't want to.
- You don't think?
- Do you?
- I'm asking you.
Why do you keep agreeing
with everything I say?
Because I am
you. I'm your tumor.
You're talking to yourself.
- Right.
- At least until
you have surgery.
If you have surgery. Are
you gonna have surgery?
If Derek cuts the tumor
out, I could lose my memory.
And if he doesn't, I could
die. I don't know what to do.
- Alex, tell me what to do.
- I can't tell you what to do.
Of course. You're my husband.
That's what husbands
do. They stomp around
telling their wives
what to do. It's your job.
- My job is to support you.
- I don't know
what I want to do.
That's why I'm asking you.
OK, I have an idea.
Let's put it to a vote.
- All in favor of the surgery.
- We're not voting.
No one's voting.
- Opposed?
- I'm opposed.
- To voting.
- Just decide for me. Please?
You don't have to know
right now. Think about it.
I don't have time.
Captain Mason told
me you saved his life
four times in the field.
A couple in the canteen, but
don't tell Mace I told you that.
So you think I'll
get to go back?
Are you sure you want to?
I mean, why do you
want to cut off your leg
just to go back to the
war? Don't you have family?
You know what it's like to
have family who don't know you,
don't get you, maybe
don't even like you?
Yeah, actually, I have brothers.
Me too.
So there's that family,
the guys I grew up with,
and we've got nothing in common.
And then there's
my guys in Iraq.
My real family.
Whatever we got into,
we were in it together.
But here, I'm alone. I'm nobody.
And I've tried. I've
tried fitting in here.
I've tried being
a regular person.
I've tried getting a job,
but there aren't any.
There are a lot of things
I wanted to be in my life,
things I wanted to do.
But none of 'em's here.
This is Alison Clark.
She was referred
to me two years ago.
Mets in her
brain, liver, kidney.
She ended up
having five surgeries
and extensive
chemo, which worked.
But then...
- The mets came back.
- That's when I started
her IL2 therapy.
And now, after three
treatments in as many months...
- The mets are gone?
- The mets are gone.
Dr. Stevens should be patient.
She should give her
therapies a chance.
As surgeons, we like to cut. But
sometimes there's a better way.
Let me retract that small bowel
so you'll have
better visualization.
You know what,
chief? Thanks to Leo,
you don't have to.
- Leo?
- Leonardo. Da Vinci.
Watch this. See?
Five hundred and forty
degrees of wristed movement.
Can't do that with
a laparoscope.
Or in open surgery.
Feels pretty good, doesn't it?
Dr. Bailey? Are you
making lightsaber noises?
Uh, not anymore, sir.
You know, Dr. Chalikonda
at Cleveland Clinic is doing
single-incision
gallbladder removal
through the belly button. We
can try that on the next one.
- If you're up to it.
- Don't tease me, sir.
I'm not. Why should
Dr. Chalikonda have all the fun?
It's impressive, but it took
two years to get these results.
These were three months apart.
Izzie may not have three months.
That tumor could start bleeding
in three days. Or three seconds.
Since when are you
not about cutting?
It may not be in
the best interest.
Derek's not acting in
Izzie's best interests?
They're ready
for us in radiology.
OK, Iz, I'm going to show you...
a series of images you want me
to try to remember once
Derek puts the right side
of my brain to sleep.
Mm-hm.
- Hit me. Show me what you got.
- OK.
Is that a schnauzer
or a Scottie?
How specific do I need to be?
Dog is fine.
- It's either a 727 or a 747.
- Plane.
Ooh. A two-story
Victorian mansion.
We would also
accept the word house.
Schnauzer, 747, mansion,
schnauzer, 747, mansion.
Or dog, plane, house.
I'm putting the right hemisphere
of your brain to sleep now, OK?
Dog, plane, house,
dog, plane, house...
Dog, plane, house, dog, plane,
house, dog, plane, house...
OK. And now we wait for the
brain activity in that area to stop.
Dog, plane, house, dog, plane...
OK, Iz, are you gonna
tell me what you saw?
Show her the cards.
What's this?
Dog. Can you say "dog"?
- What's my name?
- Just stick to the cards,
Meredith.
You know my name.
You can say my name.
- This is what I was afraid of.
- OK. Who's Alex?
Iz, you don't have to speak.
Just nod your head for me
if you know who Alex Karev is.
The test impaired your
memory to such a degree
that I strongly recommend
you don't have the surgery.
Izzie, it was the
worst-case scenario.
- It has nothing to do with the surgery.
- - We don't know that.
I do know that not
operating is every bit as risky,
if not more so.
But it's up to you.
- What do you think?
- I think he's talking to you,
not me.
- I'll leave you two
alone to discuss.
- I'll come with you.
- I have a couple of questions.
- Alex.
Think about what you
want to do for a second, OK?
I'll be right back.
You are not having the surgery.
I need you to not
talk medicine to me.
Talk to me like I'm your friend,
like I'm the guy whose
cereal you eat in the morning,
and tell me what to do.
- Karev...
- Please.
Karev, I can't tell
you what to do.
What if it was Meredith?
What would you do
if you had to choose
between spending a few
more months with Meredith
knowing she was gonna die,
watching her hurt,
watching her sick...
or spending the rest of
your life with someone
who looked like Meredith,
but wasn't her anymore.
She's the one good thing
that ever happened to me.
The one good thing.
So I need to know what
to do. I need you to tell me,
what if it was Meredith?
I would ask her to
have the surgery.
You couldn't remember anything.
You didn't know my name.
You didn't know who Derek was,
you didn't know who Alex was.
- You couldn't remember
how to speak.
- Why don't I remember this?
The tumor is sitting right
in the middle of everything
that makes you you.
I was standing there talking
to you exactly like I am now,
only you weren't
there. You weren't you.
You were gone.
- So what do I do?
- Swender has a patient,
female, 22 years old,
metastatic melanoma.
- Alison Clark?
- After three months of IL2,
her mets were gone. All of them.
You're not having this surgery.
Don't do it. That's my vote.
Don't have the
surgery. I didn't.
I freakin' hate surgery.
I'm hallucinating, Alison.
I have really long
conversations with dead people,
and I see things that aren't...
Right now, I'm pretty certain
there aren't birds
flying over your head,
because this is a hospital
and that would be weird,
but that's what I'm seeing.
I have a brain tumor.
Am I really not gonna
let them cut it out?
I didn't let them cut out mine.
It's like, OK, one minute
I'm this college kid,
rowing crew and being an
idiot and forgetting my sunscreen
and thinking it doesn't
matter because I'm me,
and life has worked
out pretty well for me.
And then, the next minute
they're cutting into my body
every other week.
I had 15 surgeries.
And then I said enough.
Forget it. I'll row crew
in heaven, or whatever.
And then the IL2
worked. It worked.
I come here every three
weeks, I get my medicine, and...
I don't have a brain
tumor anymore.
Charlie, if we admit you, if we
do what you're asking us to do,
the pain in your leg,
there's no way of knowing
if amputation will cure it.
- But it might.
- Yes, it might.
And once I get the prosthetic...
It will be months
before I can even begin
fitting you with a prosthetic.
Which won't feel anything
like a new leg, by the way.
It'll feel like five pounds of
metal that hurts and pinches.
And what if the Army says no,
what if they don't
take you back?
- They will. Chances are...
- You want to take that chance?
You're asking me to
remove one of your limbs.
You think I don't know that,
you think I want to cut my leg off?
Of course not. Am I
sure about this? No.
The only thing I'm sure
about is I'm in hell right now.
That I'm sure of.
I've lost everything.
Everything I've worked
for, everything I care about,
and I traded it in for a
six-times-a-day pain pill habit
that doesn't work. So don't waste
both our time trying to scare me,
because you don't scare me.
After everything I've been
through, nothing scares me.
So are we gonna do this or not?
Dr. Robbins, Dr. Bailey just
performed Seattle Grace's
first single-incision
gallbladder removal.
- Oh, wow! Cool!
- Through the patient's
belly button.
- And now it's kind of creepy.
- No, you should've seen it.
No scars, no bleeding,
and about half the time
it would've taken
laparascopically.
You want to do one after lunch?
- I've got another colon.
- You don't mind?
Oh... So I guess I'm on
my own for this afternoon?
My neuroblastoma? No,
don't worry. You don't have to.
You'll have the rest of your
life to do neuroblastomas.
- Then I'll see you after lunch.
- OK.
- Chief?
- Yes, Dr. Robbins?
- Chief...
- Did you want
to tell me something?
I am going to cry.
I just want you to know that
I know it's going to happen,
and I just want
you to ignore it.
And I'm not crying
because I'm upset.
It's just what happens
when I get mad
- at people of authority.
- You're mad at me?
I am mad at you.
And I'm crying because
you're the boss, my boss,
which brings up issues
with authority and my dad,
who you remind me of.
Not that you're old. But
you command respect.
People respect you.
I mean, I know I do.
I know Bailey does.
Which is why I am mad.
Because it's wrong,
sir, it's wrong and mean
to use a robot to lure Bailey
back to general surgery.
I don't have a robot.
All I have are little kids.
They're not as fun as a robot.
And they're not shiny
and new and silver,
and they don't have things coming
out of their belly buttons but...
I will fight you.
And I will win.
- Sir.
- You think you can fight me
and win?
- Yes.
- Good luck.
Because I have something
you don't have. I have joy! Sir.
Dr. Toretto, pathology.
- What's going on?
- We're going over Izzie's
IL2 schedule.
Oh, for after the surgery?
I decided not to
have the surgery.
- What?
- Maybe we should come back.
Dr. Yang.
- You're having the surgery.
- What?
- Shepherd said this is
your last shot.
- But I just...
I am your husband, I say
that you are having the surgery!
What happened to,
"This is your decision..."
That was when I thought you
were gonna make the right one!
You chose wrong, so you don't
make this decision on your own,
you married me!
It's not just your life at stake
anymore! It's my life, too!
My life with you!
You can tell Swender
whatever you want,
but I'm telling Shepherd, and
you, you are having the surgery!
She's your friend, but
that doesn't give the right
to talk her out of a surgery
you know nothing about.
You're Swender's resident.
What you did was
inappropriate, it is unprofessional.
- You crossed a line!
- No, she didn't. I did.
I'm the one who convinced
Izzie not to have surgery.
I'm the one you should
be yelling at right now.
Well, I'm gonna go now.
Unless you wanna
apologize... OK.
My mother disappeared
right in front of me.
Everything she had,
everything she was,
her dignity, her memory.
In the end, she
wasn't even my mother.
Izzie is not your mother.
She doesn't have an
untreatable brain condition.
She has a tumor.
And it can be treated.
Don't make this personal.
- I wasn't.
- You went to Izzie,
as her friend,
and you made up
her mind for her.
As my resident, go
back there and change it.
Because this
tumor will kill her.
Quick consult, Dr. Yang?
What are you doing?
The reason I haven't told my mother
I'm back is part of me is still there.
I made a commitment to
the Army I wasn't able to fulfill.
If my unit hadn't been
destroyed, I'd be there.
No wonder I can't
sleep at night,
or look my mother in the eye.
You and I can't move forward.
My work there isn't done.
And until it is, I have
no business being here.
So... I've decided to go back.
I have to go.
- Cristina, come on.
- What am I supposed to say?
- I could use your support.
- You don't have it.
Dr. Torres? Dr. O'Malley?
I just wanted to apologize.
- It's OK.
- You don't have to.
I do. 'Cause you were
trying to do your job in there,
your job is to put people back
together, not take 'em apart.
I get that.
I know it doesn't make sense
to you that I want to go back
to a place where
people get hurt and die,
but we're there because
we're trying to help people.
Save people. The
same as you. It's my job.
It's who I am. It's...
If something happened and suddenly
you couldn't be a doctor anymore,
if someone told you you
couldn't do it anymore,
wouldn't you wanna do
everything you could possibly do
to be a doctor again?
We haven't been
married 24 hours,
and we've had our first fight.
That's a good sign. Fighting
leads to good make-up sex.
Are you watching birds
fly around my head again?
Am I, like, totally
Snow White right now?
- I just don't want to hurt him.
- He'll come around.
It might take a while, but
once that tumor disappears,
once you're back at work
cutting open other people,
he'll come around.
Is it hummingbirds at least?
I really like hummingbirds.
- We need to talk to Izzie.
- We are not talking Izzie
into having surgery because
your future husband is mad at you.
He has a right to be mad.
We didn't talk Izzie out
of the surgery as doctors,
- we did it as her friends.
- Our job as doctors
is to present the options,
answer questions and let the
patient decide the course of treatment.
- That's what we did.
- Right. Except I may have
presented her options as,
"You're having this
surgery over my dead body."
He has a right to be mad.
- Crap.
- Who is it?
Come on.
- Izzie, what...?
- What happened?
- I don't know. Where's Swender!
- Izzie, let me take over.
Yeah, Izzie, come sit down.
The vessels and
nerves are separated.
Skin flap is done.
Remind me again why I'm doing
this. Someone remind me again.
You don't know what's
gonna happen to this kid,
how many fights he could win,
how many lives he could save.
If you don't do this, he's
never gonna get the chance.
We're not doing harm. We're
not hurting him. We're saving him.
We're doing what he wants.
It's what he wants.
- BP's still dropping.
- We need more blood.
- We need to move faster.
- I'm done. I'm at the end.
I didn't see any
bowel perforation.
It's there somewhere.
Run it again.
- Dr...
- Run it again.
Yes, ma'am.
So much for IL2.
You think this is my fault?
- You think I did this to her?
- No, ma'am.
There is no cure
for cancer, Dr. Yang.
There's only us, the two of us,
right here, fighting this thing as
aggressively as we know how.
And sometimes that means pumping
toxins into the patient to kill the cancer.
And, yes, sometimes, not very often,
those toxins kill the patient as well.
Alison had three months to live
when she first came to see me,
and I have managed to
keep her alive for two years.
So I am not about to give up
on her, or the IL2, anytime soon,
and neither are you.
I wasn't asking you
to see the condo.
I was asking you
to move in with me.
If that's what you want.
- I do.
- You do?
- Yeah. Not right away.
- No, of course not. In like...
- a year. I'm sorry, what, now?
- Ten years. Oh.
Well, because I'll still be a
resident for six more years,
and then I'd want to get my
practice up and running, so...
- How about seven?
- How about five years?
- I'll still be a resident.
- So? Stevens and Karev
are residents.
Meredith's a resident.
Bailey's a resident.
All married, or soon to be.
And happily. Or whatever.
I'm sorry, are you
asking me to marry you?
No!
- Why? Would you?
- Um...
Should we be having
this conversation?
No, probably not.
OK...
Impressive work
today, Dr. Bailey.
Thank you, sir. It was fun.
Yeah, it was, wasn't it?
Sounds like you
guys had a good day.
How'd the neuroblastoma kid do?
Oh. He was awesome.
The surgery was easy,
he gonna make a full recovery.
That's kinda why I
wanted you there.
Because the kids you can save
almost make up for
the ones you can't.
Anyways, I'm gonna go
monitor him at post-op,
and then I'll tell his
family the good news.
Stop by, come see the joy.
OK.
♪ Angel wings spread
over water worn wishes ♪
♪ Guarding the dreams
and the things left unsaid ♪
♪ Here we are wandering,
aimlessly roaming ♪
We had to resect
part of her bowel.
Unfortunately, we weren't
able to finish the surgery
because she was too unstable.
Right now, she's on a ventilator
because she can't
breathe on her own.
But you'll be able to
finish the surgery, right?
Yes, if she stabilizes.
And then she'll be able to
breathe on her own again?
♪ I don't know whether
we'll end up together ♪
♪ But I always know ♪
Your daughter's heart
stopped during the surgery,
which means her brain
wasn't getting oxygen.
♪ When it's done, we will walk
where the road meets the sun ♪
So it's unlikely she'll be
able to come off a ventilator.
- ♪ Don't disappear ♪
- ♪ Darlin', I want you ♪
- ♪ Don't leave me here ♪
- ♪ And when the day comes ♪
♪ I'll meet you here ♪
♪ 'Cause I know that
wishes come true ♪
♪ Finding my way back to you ♪
Izzie?
Izzie. Izzie.
- You're paging me. Are you OK?
- No.
I don't know what to do.
I don't know if I should
have the surgery.
I'm gonna die either way.
You gotta tell me what to do.
- You know what to do.
- No, I don't.
- I don't.
- Yes, you do.
You're just scared to do it.
All this back and
forth, it's just fear.
But... you've already
made the decision.
You made it. You made
it the second you decided
to fight this thing.
♪ Where the road meets the sun ♪
♪ And when it's done ♪
Just look... look
where you started.
Look where you are now.
I mean, now you're
this incredible surgeon...
- and teacher.
- ♪ 'Cause I know
that wishes come true ♪
You're a doer, remember?
♪ Finding my way back to you ♪
You know exactly
what you have to do.
♪ Angels wings spread
over water worn wishes ♪
Come in.
♪ Guarding the dreams
and the things left unsaid ♪
♪ And when it's done ♪
You can do it.
You can cut into my brain again.
♪ When it's done, we will walk ♪
- ♪ Where the road
meets the sun ♪
- OK.
You can do it, but I don't
want to end up a vegetable.
- Izzie, you won't...
- No, just listen.
I want the surgery right now.
But, if something goes wrong,
I don't want to end
up on a ventilator.
So I'm signing a DNR.
♪ When it's done, we will walk
where the road meets the sun ♪
- Please.
- Alex...
You went crazy. When
Denny signed that DNR,
you went crazy. That what you
want? You want me cutting LVADs?
You want to wreck my
career? 'Cause I will.
I will freakin' cut LVADs
before I let you just... Wait! Stop!
You don't get to quit.
You don't get to quit on me.
Please. Tear it up.
The DNR. Tear it up!
Where your eyes are
supposed to be right now,
I see white, sandy beaches.
And there's an ocean
behind your head
and ghosts wandering in and out.
I can't live like this.
And I can't live...
If something goes
wrong in that surgery,
I don't want any
extraordinary measures
taken to keep me
alive. It's not what I want.
I went crazy when Denny signed
the DNR because I didn't understand.
I didn't understand,
but now I do.
And I need you to understand.
I don't want you to go crazy.
I want you to have
a brilliant career.
And I hope I get to be
here for it. But if I can't,
I just want to go
to the other side.
I don't know what's there,
but it's gotta be better
than hospital beds and tubes
down my throat. So please.
Please don't cut LVADs.
Just...
if it comes down to it,
just let me go.
And right now, kiss me.
Please just kiss me
and close your eyes,
because the beach
is so distracting.
I always thought it would be me.
I'd get Alzheimer's, like my
mother, and forget everyone.
Let's go to city hall tomorrow.
I don't want to spend another
day not being married to you.
OK.
It doesn't matter
how good you are.
Or how hard you work.
You can do all the research,
you can master all
the latest techniques,
I mean, you can be the best...
you can be the best
surgeon in the world...
but your patients
are still gonna die.
Because the next day or the
next month or the next year,
you know, they're just
gonna get hit by a car
or find a mole on their back.
And there's nothing
you can do about it.
I don't want you to die.
♪ For a while I had
nothing to hide ♪
You OK?
I cut off a healthy leg.
I just cut it off.
It was for the
patient's own good.
But still, I feel
like a butcher.
My miracle case is on life
support. I thought I had one.
One miracle.
I hate this job sometimes.
I don't know why we do this.
♪ Hold on to me ♪
Come on. Come with me.
OK. What are we doing here?
We came to see that.
- What?
- The joy.
It comes around rarely.
So rarely, we
forget it can happen.
But that... That's
why we do this.
The joy.
♪ Some things leave
me with nothing ♪
♪ I never meant to be mean ♪
♪ Hold on to me ♪
We spend our whole lives
worrying about the future,
planning for the future,
trying to predict the future.
Will you come with me?
As if figuring it out
will somehow cushion the blow.
But the future is
always changing.
We've got one
more. He's a doctor.
He says he needs to do it today.
Come in.
The future is the home
of our deepest fears...
♪ Put on a straight face
to argue a lost case ♪
- ♪ Sometimes it's hard
to let go ♪
- Owen?
- Hey, Mom.
- ♪ Hold on to me ♪
I'm home.
♪ Hold on to me ♪
and our wildest hopes.
But one thing is certain:
♪ Hold on to me ♪
When it finally
reveals itself...
Congratulations, doctor.
Welcome to the Army.
- The future...
-  Thank you.
Is never the way we imagined it.