Previously on Grey's Anatomy:
- I passed?
- You're not an intern
anymore.
George doesn't know I exist.
- Want to go on a date with me?
- - What if I'm not into it?
- I won't let you do this to me.
- - I know I'm being an ass.
I found a way to save lives.
I could find patients
for a clinical trial.
Tumor's shrinking,
the virus is working.
- You keep a diary?
- It's not mine.
- Whose is it?
- Your mother's.
"I am a rock, I am an island."
That's the mantra of pretty
much every surgeon I've ever met.
We like to think we're
independent. Loners. Mavericks.
That all we need to do our job is
an OR, a scalpel and a willing body.
Is Yang on call tonight?
Yeah, why do you think
it's so clean in here?
But the truth is, not even
the best of us can do it alone.
Surgery, like life,
is a team sport.
Can I just say, the whole
"taking it slow" thing?
Best idea ever.
- It really takes
the pressure off.
- Mm...
Yeah, we can just...
hang out without all the...
The expectations.
- Why rush things?
- Exactly.
And eventually you've got to
get off the bench and decide...
what team are you batting for?
♪ Sad boy, you
stare up at the sky ♪
- Hey.
One of the joys of co-habitation
is having breakfast together.
I can't because Bailey
paged us in early.
Guess you don't have time to look
at our work in a major medical journal.
They published
our clinical trial?
It's on the cover. "A new method in
treating inoperable malignant gliomas.
The Shepherd Method."
- What do you think?
- It's a picture,
a big picture of you.
- You're making a face.
- I'm not making a face.
I love that picture.
I have to go.
The Shepherd Method.
It's about time this hospital got
some good publicity for a change.
- I heard you found a donor.
- Yes, sir.
Last piece of the
puzzle fell into place.
This is the day, Dr. Bailey,
the day that Seattle Grace
comes back swinging.
Shepherd on the front
page of a national journal,
bragging rights
to a flashy surgery.
I don't see Mercy West taking on
a project of this magnitude, do you?
I'd rather wait to celebrate
till we pull this thing off.
Good call. We
don't want to jinx it.
Eat that, Mercy West.
God, I've been looking
everywhere for you.
I had an early
morning palatoplasty.
- See this? The Shepherd Method?
- Yeah, impressive. Listen, last night Erica...
Think they airbrush these pictures?
The man does not have one pore.
Could you focus? I
need you right now.
I'm a little exhausted, but if you
want to hop on and do all the work...
No. I need to talk.
Last night, Erica and I...
we...
We did it. Sort of.
- Congratulations.
- No. No, no.
It was not good, at all.
I choked.
I... couldn't go down there.
I tried, but it just felt so weird
and clinical, like gynie rotation.
I left this morning before she
got up. I couldn't even face her.
What if... What if me and
Erica, what if we are a mistake?
- Where are you going?
- I can't talk about this.
Come on! You love talking
about this stuff. Girl on girl, it's hot.
Two girls getting nasty
and loving it? That's hot.
One girl talking about how much
it sucked? Depressing, and wrong.
Just wrong.
The chief wants us to give
George one of our interns?
Except for Grey. She already lost
O'Malley. Dump your dead weight.
They're all dead weight. That's
why I need all four, not three.
George is filling out paperwork,
getting his real-life doctor wings.
Now would be a good
time to decorate his locker.
- Give me that coffee.
- - I don't want the credit,
but the clinical trial was my
idea. I had to beg him to do it.
It's OK you want
the credit. I would.
Screw the attendings, you get
screwed. They have the power.
You could screw interns.
I mean, date.
Residents could date interns
'cause we're non-threatening.
I read this study once, interns hardly
ever file sexual harassment claims
because we feel so weak and
powerless in the hospital environment.
Interns: the other white meat.
- Where are we going?
- You'll see when
we get there.
I'm on Dr. Sloan's
service today.
Everyone's off their
services. You're all with me.
- Where are we going?
- - You'll see when we get there.
See your locker? I
put a smelly candle.
Your scrubs are gonna
smell like cinnamon bun.
Dr. Sloan is doing a
transpalatal advancement.
Hahn said I could scrub
in on her aortic bypass.
I need to get to the clinic.
I'm the only doctor on call.
I've got administrative work...
Today is not about you. It is not
about whose services you wish to be on,
it's not about your career.
This is about me. This is a project
I've been working on for a long time,
and it's very important to me,
therefore it will be important to you.
The only way we can pull this thing
off is if we work together as a team.
So today you are not
15 individual doctors,
you are one team of surgeons
representing this hospital.
Is everybody clear on that?
Why would they need so
many doctors for one surgery?
Because it's not just one
surgery, it's 12 surgeries.
Six kidney transplants in
six ORs, all at the same time.
Paired matching kidney donation.
It's a six-way swap. Six people
donate kidneys to total strangers,
six people get kidneys
from total strangers.
Twelve people walk away happy.
- Paired matching
kidney donations.
- Otherwise known as...
A domino surgery.
Stan Mercer, 46. Chronic renal
failure secondary to high blood pressure.
His wife wanted to donate a
kidney to him but she wasn't a match,
so she will be donating her
kidney to Ms. Chen over there,
who is a match, while Mr. Mercer will
be getting a kidney from this young man.
Nice to meet you.
PJ.
Please.
Kurt Walling, 58. Chronic renal
failure secondary to diabetes.
His son PJ wasn't a match, so
Mr. Walling will get Ms. Herman's kidney.
- Thanks for
the kidney, Ms. Herman.
- Call me Lindsay.
We'll be pretty close
by the end of the day.
And so on. Why do
you still look stupid?
Maybe if we had a cheat sheet.
Ms. Herman gives her kidney to Mr. Walling.
His son's kidney to Mr. Mercer.
Mr. Mercer's wife gives hers to Ms.
Chen. Chen's sister gives her kidney
to Mr. Patel. Mr. Patel's wife
gives her kidney to Ms. Loring,
who came in with her cousin Ms. Gomez,
who's giving her kidney to Mr. Cross,
the professional flautist.
For those without a
photographic memory,
it's on a board in
the conference room.
Why do we have to do all
six transplants at one time?
So no one backs
out at the last minute.
Why would they? It's an
incredible thing to be part of.
Passing the
organ's kinda creepy.
That's why this whole
surgery is a house of cards.
If we lose one donor,
we lose them all.
So you will not only provide
excellent medical care,
but keep your patients happy. We
need to make sure this doesn't fall apart
before the surgery.
Any questions?
I heard when they did
the domino at Boston Gen
the residents got to keep one of the
dead kidneys in a jar as a souvenir.
- I want a kidney.
- Can I have a kidney?
- If they get kidneys,
I get a kidney.
- I asked first.
No one is taking
home a kidney in a jar.
Diseased kidneys are not tchotchkes
for your coffee table. Now go, go.
- Hey, you OK?
- Uh...
Bailey snagged all the
surgical residents and interns
so I'm stuck with the psych
interns. Not the sharpest.
You're busy. I'll be brief. I was
thinking if you weren't on call tonight
that maybe we
could go to my place,
order in dinner, rent a movie.
Tonight? You want to
get together again tonight?
- Well, I had a lot
of fun last night.
- Fun.
Anyway, just let me know.
OK, as you may know, one of
you is going to O'Malley today.
- Me! I'll go,
if you need a volunteer.
- I decide who gets to go
after I decide which one
of you sucks the most.
You better not suck on
purpose because I will know.
Would you like your book or some
music, something to help you relax?
- Maybe some water.
- How about some
ice chips instead?
Your ankles are looking thick.
My wife loves tracking
my fluid retention.
And Megan, will you please
come over here and tape the needle
- so we can start dialysis.
- Sounds just like
a real doctor.
It says here that you don't have a
loved one in the domino, Ms. Herman.
- No.
- So you're just
donating a kidney
- to a complete
stranger for nothing?
- It's really no big deal.
I have two kidneys and they
say you can live with one.
That's amazing what you're doing.
UNOS is always short on organs.
If everyone in
the world did this...
It'd be all peace,
love and unicorns.
- She gets it, Grey.
- I'm so sick of all
the "yay, you."
I totally understand.
The chief has got me doing
press all day with journalists.
- My face is hurting
from smiling.
- I already pushed that.
- Comes faster when I push it.
- - Oh, that Shepherd Method.
Funny.
I'll take the stairs.
- Are you bothered by this?
- - Why would I be bothered?
You can't call it the
Shepherd-Grey Method
because then people
would think you had help.
I have to give my
kidney to that old guy?
- Mr. Mercer
couldn't be more than 50.
- My son's 22.
To him, everyone over
40's on the brink of death.
- I turned 23 in August.
- That's right.
Maybe we could have a little
belated party here in the hospital.
We'll get an ice cream
cake, you used to love those.
Yeah, when I was seven.
I'm not here for a reunion. I want
to get this over with and get out.
So you are on dialysis
four times a week now?
They might as well chain me
to the machine at this point.
My kidneys are shot. I'm
living on borrowed time.
So I'm pretty lucky to have a
son who would do this for me.
You're lucky you're loaded.
When do I get the 10,000
bucks, before or after the surgery?
It's a Christmas gift.
It's October.
Dr. Bradford, labor and
delivery. Labor and delivery.
I see you two hovering.
Hypothetically, say a patient
was paying his son for a kidney,
what exactly would happen?
- Paying money,
for a kidney.
- Hypothetically.
Well, as someone who stole an
organ herself not that long ago,
you should know, what
would happen is your patient
would be out of the exchange.
Which means that this person,
since her husband's no longer
getting a kidney, would drop out.
Then they'd drop out,
then they'd drop out,
then the whole thing would
fall apart, that's what'd happen.
So if you both are suggesting
that's what's going on here,
you'd better be
damn sure about it.
It's just a gift, an
early stocking stuffer.
Most girls your age,
they're busy shopping.
You're in the hospital
giving a kidney to a stranger.
I'm not such a saint.
Your kidney may not go
directly to my husband,
but you're one of the
people saving his life today.
To me, you're Mother Teresa.
Honey, do you mind running and
getting a wet wash cloth for me?
- Excuse me.
- Thank you.
My mother invented the
Grey Method all by herself.
Maybe you should stop reading her
diary. It's gonna make you feel inadequate.
She's dead and in the
past and still outpacing me.
OK, see that intern over there?
- Is he clean?
- Huh? What?
I was thinking what Lexopedia
said. She may be onto something.
You're gonna
sleep with an intern?
It'd just be
scratching the itch.
It's been a long time.
I can't do this.
All these people telling me how
wonderful, selfless and giving I am.
I can't take it anymore,
especially not from her.
- Keep your voice down.
- Did you see her face,
thanking me for saving
your life? Stan, this is crazy.
You promised you'd tell her!
- Mr. Mercer, everything OK?
- I don't feel so good.
Tell her! If the past three years
have meant anything to you,
- you have to tell her!
- Stan?
I'm not an idiot. I know there've been
other women. I've told myself just sex.
It's just... My God, Stan.
She's giving a kidney for you.
That's not sex, it's family.
All right, his cardiac
enzymes and EKG look good.
He had an acute anxiety
attack. I can clear him for surgery.
I do everything for you.
I've given up my entire life
to get you to dialysis,
drive you to the doctors...
I didn't ask you
to do any of that.
I can drive a car, I
can pour my own juice.
- I got sick, not elderly.
- Well, don't worry.
I won't do one
more thing for you,
and that includes
giving a kidney.
Get on the phone with UNOS,
tell them we need a kidney
- that matches
Mrs. Mercer's antibodies.
- UNOS is a longshot.
It's the only shot we
have. Now go. Now!
She's barely a second-year
resident. I made the virus.
She assisted. When Michael Jordan
scores no one cares about the assist.
- I don't know. Scottie Pippen.
- You know what I mean.
These women, they
overthink everything.
Somebody's cranky today.
What's that, "experimental
treatments for cleft palates?"
You're working on
your own clinical trial.
- I'm just doing
a little research.
- Mm-hmm.
The very sight of me reminds you
that you've not made one worthwhile
contribution to medical history.
- Get out.
- You should read my article.
It'll enrich your life,
make you a better man.
I'm saving it for the bathroom.
It started as an office
thing. You know, light, fun.
And then one day you wake up
and this older guy is
all you can think about.
You'd do anything for
him, even give a kidney.
Why?
I could save his life, too.
She may be married to him,
but I'm saving his life today too.
So then he'll finally
have to choose...
her or me.
Apparently Erica loved
it. The non-sex sex.
- I think she might want more.
- Happens to me all the time.
I barely remember,
their minds are blown.
That's your sage advice?
I'm a world-class surgeon,
double boarded in plastics and ENT.
I have more meaningful
and worthwhile things to do
- than dispense sex advice.
- Like what?
- Nice.
- Come on. No, Mark.
- I need your help!
- Mm-hmm.
Excuse me.
What is going on?
We're trying to decide which
of our interns to give to George.
In front of us. They're
deciding in front of us,
- like livestock
at a state fair.
- I think I'll keep Lexopedia.
- She remembers many things.
- Mm-hmm.
And she bathes, which is
much more than I can say for...
stinky Two over there.
Well, Graciella charts like
crap, but she can put in a line.
Claire, on the other hand, nearly
castrated a guy with a catheter.
We can hear you.
I might dump Pierce.
- How does he suck?
- I just hate saying the name Pierce.
- Mmm...
- We should revolt.
They'd respect us more
if we didn't participate.
Yeah. You revolt first,
- and I'll follow.
- - Have you heard from UNOS?
They're still searching
for a match. So far nothing.
- I hope they come through. My guy needs a kidney.
- They all need kidneys.
If Derek needed a kidney
I wouldn't give him one.
He'd say he magically
grew it himself.
My guy's been sick for 15 years.
Can you imagine having your life on
hold like that? Plus he's got a crappy kid.
Hey! Did I say you
could put that down?
No, so pick it up.
- Weak. No stamina.
- Yeah, but he takes orders.
True, true.
- Is my husband getting a kidney?
- - What about my sister?
If she's not getting a kidney, I am
not giving mine to some stranger.
I will do my best to make sure
everyone gets a kidney today.
I'll update you as soon as
I have information. Please.
Sir, I've got this
under control.
I have Grey talking with UNOS...
We're being featured
on the national news.
All eyes are on Seattle Grace.
- Fix this.
- Yes, sir.
I've been poked and
prodded like a lab rat.
All for nothing?
We got to spend time with
each other. That's not nothing.
Oh, now you want to
spend time together.
Well, you're about 20 years
too late, so, yeah, nothing.
- PJ.
- - Do I still get the $10,000
if the surgery doesn't
happen? If not, I'm out of here.
- I have a life to get back to.
- Please. I need you.
If you could just be
patient a little bit longer.
I was gonna punch that kid.
What kind of a selfish idiot?
His father is sick, really sick,
all he cares about is his money.
The guy must've done something
bad to make the kid so angry.
Maybe he cares about his son
but the moron is too
emotionally stunted to let him.
OK. I'm not...
I'm trying to be... I am.
But this, right here? This...
This is exactly your problem.
You get all wrapped
up and involved
and you just... You start
caring about these people.
Your patient in
there, he's the moron.
His son's never gonna give him
what he wants. He'll be disappointed.
The sooner he gets that
the sooner you get it, and...
No. Go on, please.
Be a selfish ass. At least
then I know what to expect.
This being a decent guy one second
and total jerk the next is getting old.
So who's it gonna be? Pick one.
O'Malley. What's up, bud?
Hey. Missed you at lunch today.
It was an all-new level of hell.
I was busy doing my own charts.
The interns don't respect me.
I would respect you
if I was your intern.
They don't respect you because
they're not scared of you. Decimate one.
It's not rocket science. Two!
Who's getting Ms.
Herman's kidney?
- Uh... I can go check.
- Three.
- Mr. Walling.
- That's right. I totally forgot.
Oh, you forgot.
Like you forgot to do
your notes before rounds?
Or like you forgot to pull the
drain on my post-op SBO?
Or like you forgot to sign all
your dictations so all your charts...
my charts... are delinquent?
You forgot?
The only thing you can retain
in that pea-sized brain of yours
is what time lunch is.
Grey here is gonna
become a surgeon
while you dig ditches
by the side of the road.
It's brutal, but it's effective.
- I'm not gonna do this.
- Do what?
Have this silent fight. I'll write the
editors, have them print a correction.
The Shepherd-Grey Method.
I don't want you to give me
credit 'cause you're mad I'm mad.
Give me credit 'cause you think I
worked hard for it and deserve it.
You don't deserve
it. You're a baby.
You have the potential to be a
good surgeon, maybe a great one,
but you haven't scratched the
surface on what you need to learn.
It was my idea.
And I hate that picture.
To thoracic surgery.
UNOS doesn't have a match.
OK.
Uh, we can, um...
We've been stalling, we haven't released
anyone. I can talk to Mrs. Mercer...
You can't do anything that
could be seen as coercion.
- UNOS is very clear.
- But, sir...
The last thing we need is to lose
our status as a transplant center.
Let the patients go home.
It's over.
I've got a CABG in an hour.
Want to get some coffee?
I'm not cut out for this.
- Coffee?
- No, this, the touching
and the...
sex with a girl. I just... I can't
do it. I thought I could, but...
But you did do it.
I don't understand.
Oh...
It wasn't good for you.
I still can't believe it.
I got so close.
You'll be high on the transplant
list. Something else will come up.
It's not the kidney
I'm upset about.
Oh, your son.
We hadn't spoken in over a year.
It took me months to find him.
This was my chance
to get him back.
Right.
I know PJ can be selfish...
rude.
But it hasn't been easy for him.
His mom died.
I worked late most nights.
- I made a lot of mistakes.
- - You can't blame yourself.
Some people are just broken.
I guess you just try
not to care too much
and you can't be disappointed.
These are your discharge papers.
I'm sorry.
I don't know why.
I'm so sorry.
It's OK.
Now all you have to do is sign at
the bottom and you're free to go.
You must think I'm
a terrible person...
refusing to give my kidney.
- We're not thinking
anything, ma'am.
- He's taken everything.
My love, my pride.
My dignity. It's all gone.
But the one thing that he
doesn't have is the kidney.
And the thought of giving
him that last part of me.
You must think I'm
a terrible person.
I'm not allowed
to think anything.
There are rules that prevent
me from having an opinion here.
Good rules, rules
in place for a reason,
because giving an organ that God
put in your body to someone else
isn't something that you
can be coerced into doing.
It is a big thing.
It is an extraordinary thing.
It's a gift that must
be freely given.
And if you were to give it,
and I'm not asking you to,
but if you were to give it,
it's not just for your husband.
It's for five other people, people
that you don't know from Adam.
Our six donors are all
anesthetized and ready to go.
They'll be done first,
followed by the recipients.
Each pair will be color-coded
so as not to confuse them.
This surgery is a hornet's nest,
people, so work quickly but carefully.
Use each other,
operate as a team.
Let's go make medical history.
We're lucky as hell that
woman changed her mind.
Yes, we are. Yes, we are.
♪ These quiet times ♪
♪ That I like best ♪
Huh. Now that's what I
call a nice-looking kidney.
Put that on ice and start flushing
in the preservation solution.
♪ Falling on the fields
I catch you calling ♪
♪ Remember how it
feels These quiet times ♪
♪ That I like best ♪
♪ I'll catch you falling ♪
♪ When you least expect ♪
♪ When you least expect... ♪
You want to do the
honors, Dr. Yang?
Good.
Clamp coming off.
Oh! Oh...
That's quite a geyser of urine.
That means we did our job right.
You never get
tired of seeing that.
We're ready for you, Grey.
Walking with the kidney.
Five second rule!
Hold it still. I'm
gonna need more ice.
- And another tie.
- I'll get it.
No. You don't
touch anything else.
Someone dropped a damn kidney?!
I know. You don't want to talk
about it anymore. I know you're over it.
- For the love of God!
- Just hear me out.
I like to be good at things, OK?
I do not fail, I do not quit.
I like to be good at things,
and I want to be good at this,
so... I need you.
I need you to show me.
Show you?
Because you didn't
publish a big clinical trial
doesn't mean
you're not a genius.
Fine. Take off your pants.
Really? Oh, my God, thank you!
- Thank you so much.
- I'll show you
the Sloan Method.
Will never be in a medical
journal, but it should.
Shouldn't it be
pinking up by now?
It's just getting venous blood.
Let's check the backside again.
I think I see a
little pink, maybe.
All right, come on, come on.
All right.
Come on.
Come on, pink up.
Pink up, pink up, pink up.
Come on!
Yes! It looks good.
We have a live kidney.
Oh, come on, I am offering two
interns. Two for the price of one.
- I'll trade you Laura
for both of 'em.
- Leo drains pus and likes it.
I dropped an internal
organ. On the floor.
- It happens.
- OK, OK.
How about this: Four goes
to George. I get James.
Karev, you get
Two. Izzie gets Leo.
What are you people doing?
We were just... deciding which
of our interns to give to George.
Oh, you think I got
to choose my interns,
and I picked you people 'cause
you're all such a surgical dream team?
You, you're lazy. You, whiny.
Butterfingers over there,
downright depressing.
And you, Yang, you,
you're just annoying.
Choosing their own interns.
Wha...
Give me those damn cards.
O'Malley, you have interns.
What is it?
OK, open his fluids,
Karev. Push a gram of Mag.
Do a CBC and electrolytes.
Order a color flow doppler
- and do a full neuro workup.
- Think there's a bleed?
No way of knowing
until we evaluate.
Where's PJ? Where's my son?
♪ Come on, friends,
get up now... ♪
Stan had better
be dead right now.
He's doing fine.
He hasn't called my room.
He hasn't asked for me.
It's been three years.
I gave a kidney for him and
he still hasn't made a choice.
♪ And this part was for
her This part was for her ♪
♪ Does she remember? ♪
He hasn't asked
about you or called.
I think he's made a choice.
But I gave a kidney for him.
I gave a kidney.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
Hey, man, the nurse was supposed
to bring my dinner an hour ago.
- Your dad just had a seizure.
- OK.
- So what does that mean?
- It means something's wrong.
It means he could be dying, and
he doesn't know you give a crap.
Honestly he doesn't know and
maybe you don't, but if you do,
he's dying and you'll be
too late. He's asking for you,
you're gonna be too late, you're
gonna live with it the rest of your life!
You want to live
with that? Do you?
Alex!
♪ It comes and
goes in waves, I... ♪
So tomorrow we'll meet
one hour before pre-rounds.
Dude, that's like 4:00am.
Dr. Stevens never made us
come in before pre-rounds.
Yeah, O'Malley, you gotta chill.
They probably should
say Dr. O'Malley.
So those are your interns?
Did you even ask for me?
- What?
- I helped you study.
I helped decorate
your stupid locker,
I... And you don't even see it.
You don't see anything.
I am such an idiot...
and you are a jerk.
You didn't even
think to ask for me?
Screw you, Dr. O'Malley.
Mr. Cross, Mr. Patel, Ms. Chen,
Ms. Loring and
Mr. Mercer, they're all stable.
But Mr. Walling, he has
delayed graft function
- and God knows what else.
- The press will be
all over this.
I need you available for interviews
and photo ops. Wear your nice scrubs.
Did you hear me? Mr. Walling.
He has a serious complication.
His electrolytes
are off, crits down.
But you saved five other lives.
That's a pretty good
scorecard. Not perfect, but good.
I told you, I don't
want to see Stan.
I'm not taking you to see Stan.
♪ This is how the story went ♪
♪ I met someone by accident ♪
Oh, this is her. This is the
woman who gave me her kidney.
You made the family...
♪ Buried them away ♪
♪ You buried them away ♪
♪ I wish I could lay
down beside you ♪
♪ When the day is done ♪
♪ And wake up to your face
against the morning sun ♪
♪ But like everything
I've ever known ♪
♪ You disappear one day ♪
♪ So I spend my
whole life hiding... ♪
- How's she doing?
- I'm keeping
a close eye on her,
but so far she's
completely stable.
Come with me.
♪ Put a kiss on top of my head ♪
♪ Watch me wave ♪
This man is very ill.
Maybe dying.
He's got a perfect,
healthy donor kidney
that wasn't
dropped on the floor.
There's only so
much we can help,
and so much we can hurt.
Forgive yourself.
♪ But like everything
I've ever known ♪
♪ You disappear one day ♪
Visiting hours are over.
It's OK.
♪ Away ♪
♪ I woke up feeling
heavy hearted... ♪
Dad.
♪ The morning rain... ♪
♪ Although I wish
that you were near ♪
♪ That same old road
that brought me here ♪
♪ Is calling me home
It's calling me home ♪
Your urine output's up 25cc's per
hour. That should make you happy.
My wife would have been happy.
Who's gonna care about
my urine output now?
♪ But like everything
I've ever known ♪
Well, things are gonna
be a little different.
♪ So I spend my whole
life hiding my heart away ♪
Dr. Bailey, heard your big surgery
went well today. Congratulations.
The same to you. Must feel good
to see your name in print like that.
It would feel better if
Meredith wasn't so...
She's acting silly about the
credit. She's getting emotional.
That girl worked her ass off
for you and you got all the credit.
I would've gotten the
blame had we failed.
- But you didn't fail.
- Simple: I'm an attending,
- she's a second-year resident.
- Who you're living with.
That's not simple, it's messy.
If it were me I'd start
with "Thank you."
You'll be surprised
how far that one goes,
especially with us
silly, emotional women.
- Derek said I was a baby...
- What?
And that I had a lot to learn.
- Whatever.
- Not "whatever." He's right.
I did drop a kidney. Don't say
"it happens" because it doesn't,
- but I do hate when he's right.
- No, OK, he is not right.
Stop caring so much about what he
thinks. Makes you seem desperate.
- OK, to the one
trolling for interns.
- Yeah, I changed my mind.
Interns are weak.
I don't want weak.
You know, Burke was a man.
He was a man.
Joe, I think we
need another round.
Hey, Joe, how you
doing? Excuse me.
There you go.
- Is this for me?
- Yes.
Hey, honey, I bought you
roses. Let me back in the house.
- Oh, no!
- Oh, yes!
Holy crap, what
the hell is that thing?
That is a kidney in a
jar. How did you get that?
Being an incredibly important,
fancy neurosurgeon has its perks.
Thank you.
I couldn't have
done it without you.
Not one surgery,
not one patient.
I couldn't have done any
of it without you. Thanks.
Yeah, can you guys go and get this
thing out of here before people freak out?
- OK.
- Um... Are you gonna be OK?
- Yeah, yeah. Go ahead.
- Good night. Good night, Joe.
- Good night.
The thing about
choosing teams in real life,
it's nothing like it used
to be in gym class.
Being first pick
can be terrifying.
- Take off your pants.
- Excuse me?
Take off your pants.
We're trying this again.
♪ 'Cause none of it's easy ♪
♪ I know it wasn't meant to be ♪
♪ I know it's all... ♪
And being chosen last...
isn't the worst
thing in the world.
What?
I care about you.
I care about you, and
I'm not gonna go crazy,
and I'm not gonna
try to kill myself.
And I'm not gonna stop caring about
you no matter how hard you push me away.
- Shut up and
get out of my room.
- No.
I care about you...
and I know you care about me,
too, and it's not too late for us.
- Get out of my room.
- Admit it.
Admit that you care about
me, too. I know you do.
And I care about you.
I care about you.
I care about you. I...
So we watch from the
sidelines, clinging to our isolation.
- It glows.
- Yeah.
When my mother was a resident
she wasn't dropping kidneys.
- You're reading
your mom's diary?
- Mmm...
I'm not half the
surgeon my mother was.
♪ It's all you can do ♪
♪ Use what's been given to
you Live like you're dying... ♪
Because we know as soon
as we let go of the bench...
- Honey, you leaving already?
- There are no
real men left, Joe.
See ya.
Hey. Shot and a beer. Whiskey.
Know what? Better make it just
the beer. I start work tomorrow.
Someone comes along and
changes the game completely.