- Previously on Grey's
Anatomy: - I slept with Izzie.
George told me. Everything.
You named me Ava and
I was more me as Ava
than I'll ever be as Rebecca.
Dr. Hahn. I was
pleasantly surprised
to hear you were
joining us today.
You remind me of myself
when I was an intern.
Focused, intense. Cold.
- My mother's dead, isn't she?
- Yes.
Let's do this once. I'm
fine. She's cremated.
I picked out a beautiful urn,
she's hanging out in
the back of my closet.
Any more questions about my dead
mother or can we get back to work?
Pick me. Choose me. Love me.
You're the love of my
life. I can't leave you.
But you're
constantly leaving me.
Imagine my disappointment
when I wake up after five years
and discover that you're
no more than ordinary!
There's a reason surgeons
learn to wield scalpels.
We like to pretend we're
hard, cold scientists.
We like to pretend
we're fearless.
Pick me. Choose me. Love me.
But the truth is we become surgeons
because somewhere, deep down,
we think we can cut
away that which haunts us.
- What are you guys doing up?
- Couldn't sleep.
Weakness.
Frailty.
Death.
What is that?
My mother.
Happy freaking Halloween.
Yang.
You're moving out
of Burke's place?
Yes, sir.
My wife has filed for divorce.
I'm very sorry, sir.
At any rate, I need
a place to live.
And Burke's place,
I was there once.
I suppose actually
it's your place now.
No. It's still Burke's place.
Now, it's yours.
What are we looking at?
Meredith put her mom in a
baggie and brought her to work.
I had to get her out of my
closet. She was haunting me.
And now she's haunting us all.
- I'm putting her to rest.
- Meredith is cleansing.
In tribal culture when one
wants to cleanse the past,
one cuts off all of one's
hair and buries it in the earth.
You might try that too.
OK. Listen up.
Today's a holiday,
which means the
pit will be overrun.
You've got the usual
drunken stupidity.
And then you've
got Seattle's annual
chainsaw pumpkin
carving contest.
- I love this city.
- Stay on your toes,
stay on top of your interns, OK?
So we should
round before the pit?
Direct your questions
to Dr. Bailey, Stevens.
Oh, we're directing our
questions to Dr. Bailey?
Oh, not you. Just Stevens.
Why is Stevens directing
her questions to Dr. Bailey?
Because she's been
sleeping with my husband.
Alrighty, then. Have a good day.
OK, this is even more disturbing
than your bag full of mommy.
His medication was
due half an hour ago.
The man is living in the
hospital while he waits on a heart.
Erin, honey, I'm
thinking it's kind of hard
for anyone to take you
seriously in your mouse costume.
See, I work with
five-year-olds, Dad.
My costume is
appropriate. Hers is not.
Look, I'm just saying if you have
time for Halloween costumes,
you probably have time to
provide my father with basic care.
Hi. I'm Dr. O'Malley. I will take
care of your father right away.
Thank you.
You should always make
sure they have their meds
before you do anything else.
- There you go.
- Thanks.
- I like your costume.
- Oh.
Well, Dr. Yang said that...
Dr. Yang is screwing with you.
Oh! I knew it.
- Are you the doctor?
- Oh. I am.
Good. That's... That's good.
Is your leg hurting you?
It's not the leg, it's the foot.
And it's not hurting so
much as it's not mine.
Something happened.
I can't explain it,
but this foot does
not belong to me.
It's...
It... It... Well, it feels
like it's a corpse foot.
Did you lose feeling
in the foot? Is it numb?
No, it's not numb. It's just...
It's not mine.
Please. I'm not crazy.
I work in a bank.
I'm not crazy. Please.
I just... I need a surgeon.
I need you to get me a
surgeon who will remove it.
A surgeon who will
remove your foot?
A surgeon who will amputate
your seemingly healthy foot?
- Oh!
- Whoa!
- What is that?
- It's charts.
- Meredith?
- It's my mom.
- What?
- Had her in the cubby
and she was freaking people out
so I was gonna
put her in the car.
Think that's disrespectful?
To leave her in the car?
- Just a little...
- It's not that strange.
- Well...
- I'm trying to figure out
how to put her to rest.
I can't shove her in
my closet anymore.
I have to deal with her.
- Well...
- And this is me... trying to evolve.
I'm trying here.
So, cubby or car?
You're asking me if I think you
should put your mom's ashes
in your cubby or your car? OK.
And you don't think
that's very, very strange?
Are those really
your mom's ashes?
It's strange,
right? It's strange.
- Are you lost?
- No. My mom works
in the cafeteria.
She said I could come up
here and look for Dr. Sloan?
Do you know him?
Um... can you take care of him?
Yeah. Can you take care of her?
Good morning.
- Don't do that. Don't smile at me.
- Don't smile at her.
- Don't smile at me either.
- We're on to you.
- We've compared notes.
- Compared notes. Really?
Mm-hmm. Compared notes,
pick-up lines, techniques.
- Techniques?
- Identical.
- Identical?
- We've formed a club.
"Nurses United
Against Mark Sloan."
Are there any,
uh... club activities?
Oh, man. You would not
believe what just happened to me.
- There's a... kid looking for you.
- What?
- Daddy?
- Nicely done.
- Thanks.
- I'll be getting
you back for that.
- Looking forward to it.
You're not my father.
But I am hoping you'll
build me some ears.
Dr. Karev? Request
for you. Curtain three.
Dr. Karev? I'm feeling a
little under the weather.
And rather than risk
spreading germs to the patients,
I thought I'd head home.
Do you want to be a surgeon
or do you want to go to bed?
One or the other.
Surgeons stand up
through ten, 12,
15-hour surgeries.
Without food. Without bathroom
breaks. Without complaints.
Surgeons do not go home because
we have a tickle in our throat.
Not a tickle in my
throat as much as...
- Make yourself busy, Norman.
- Right.
All the moms in my town,
they all dress up for Halloween.
So I was thinking,
what would I want to be?
If I had to dress
up, what would I...?
And the only thing I
could come up with,
the only thing that I
wanted to be... was Ava.
♪ But I need your
little shining light ♪
♪ You promised the world
Opened up your door ♪
♪ And the words you fed
me left me wanting more ♪
You found him.
You two know each other?
You know his parents?
His mom works in the
cafeteria. What's all this?
Letters from the
kids in my class.
Letters to me.
He has the internal
structure to hear.
He just doesn't have the
canal or the external structure.
So I thought if I came
in with my letters,
Dr. Sloan might feel sorry for
me and do the surgery for free.
Uh, look, I'd like to help.
I would if I could, but
pro bono surgery...
You should know
that on my way here
three different people
thought I was in a costume.
My head looks like a
permanent Halloween costume.
- Just thought
you should know that.
- You're good.
Pro bono surgery's not just
about me giving you my time.
A surgery like this requires
OR time, an anesthesiologist,
a general surgeon to remove
the cartilage from your ribs,
- at least two surgical nurses.
- Couldn't you
ask them for help?
I could. But I don't
have any social capital.
The nurses hate me. They've
formed a club that's all about hating me.
And the other doctors
don't owe me any favors
because I've never
done any for them.
I'm sorry. I wish I could help.
I would if I could.
I have social capital.
Or, I don't. Nobody knows me,
but they knew my mother.
So maybe I can make this happen.
Fine. Make it happen. You
manage that, I'm all yours.
These people who
knew your mother...
Do they know you brought
her to work in a baggie?
Oh. You... You...
You didn't come for me! You...
You chickened out.
When I... When I was
leaving. When I was...
When I asked you to
give me a reason to stay,
you chickened out. Which I get.
I get that. It was a lot.
It was scary. And I know
it can be kind of intense,
but I thought-I thought... Oh.
I thought after the
chickening out part, I thought...
you would come for me.
I came back for you. Which
basically makes me a beggar.
I'm a beggar for Halloween.
- And now you're mocking me.
- I'm not mocking you.
We need to talk.
We will.
Body Dysmorphic Disorder?
You can prescribe
some anti-anxiety meds,
to try to lessen the
urgency he's feeling.
The man is requesting
an amputation
and the best you can come
up with is anti-anxiety meds?
Dr. Bailey?
- Chainsaw contest time?
- Yep.
- Mr. Miller.
- Duquette Clinic.
I have to get to the ER,
but I'm going to write
you a prescription
for some medication
I think may help you.
Medication? I need...
I need a surgeon.
A surgeon can take off
the foot. Get me a surgeon!
I am a surgeon! And I
can tell you right now
that you won't persuade me or any
other surgeon to do what you're asking.
Please, try this medication.
I have an earless boy.
I'm sorry?
Sloan has agreed to
build him ears pro bono.
If you will donate the
OR and all the equipment.
I'm sorry, my pro bono slate is full,
there are protocols to be followed,
- all sorts of red tape...
- Trick or treat.
Get it? He's trick
or treating. For ears.
- Grey...
- You know, my mother...
She was big on
pro bono surgeries.
OR two is free at 6:00pm.
Thank you.
If you two need to talk
I could wait over there.
Why? It's not like we
have any secrets anymore.
Callie told everyone. Everyone.
Yeah. It's going
to be a long day.
Erin Shanley, 34, massive head trauma,
a brick came through her windshield.
- GCS of three.
- Brick through her windshield?
Kids screwing around on
a bridge. Halloween crap.
- I'm looking at brain matter.
- - I checked, she's a donor.
- Oh, God.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
- Her father's on three.
He's waiting for a new heart.
It was awesome.
It was the sickest pumpkin
head you ever saw.
Mm-hmm.
The next thing you know
it's like, blood gushing
and it totally stained
my pumpkin head.
- You don't say.
- Made it even sicker, though.
- I brought it in. The digit.
- Oh, you have the finger?
Yeah, but it's like,
lodged in the chainsaw.
Wait. It was right here.
Who took my saw?
Sir, the cut isn't clean
enough to consider...
Yo! Who took my saw?
Oh. Oh, no.
- What is that noise?
- I have no idea.
Dude, sick!
The tibial nerve is shot.
There's nothing salvageable here.
Completely mangled.
Can't believe he held that
saw to his leg long enough...
- Was he high?
- No. Gave him some
morphine for the pain,
but tox screen was
clean before that.
Unbelievable.
All right. I'll finish the job.
Yang, go ahead and prep
him for complete amputation.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
Hey, you OK?
Severed limbs
don't sit well with me.
Just a little queasy is all.
No, I'm fine. I'll help Dr.Yang.
OK.
Got to love Halloween.
When all the crazies
come out to play.
I kind of get it. I mean, I get
that you can wake up one day
and your life doesn't
feel like your own.
I heard. About your marriage.
And if there's anything
you need me to do
to cheer you up, I'm around.
Day or night.
Night in particular.
I was married.
I said "Till death do us
part." OK, in a church.
I mean, it was the Church of
Elvis, but still it was a church.
I just... I can't
believe this is my life.
I don't understand. How did this
happen? How could this happen?
Injuries like these
happen very quickly.
She probably didn't
feel any pain at all.
Mr. Shanley...
According to Erin's driver's
license, she was an organ donor.
And as next of kin,
if you agree to take
her off of life-support,
you can direct the
heart to yourself.
She is young, she was healthy.
She would be a perfect
match for you, sir.
Could you just please go away?
- Mr. Shanley, if you would...
- Please. Please go away. Please.
Dr. O'Malley will bring
you to see your daughter.
If you'd like.
- Oh, so sorry. Excuse me. Are you OK?
- No. No apology necessary.
I'm Sydney. Dr. Sydney
Heron. General surgery.
Big fan of your work. Yeah.
We were seated
together once at an M & M.
Anyway.
Now seems as good as
time as any to make it official.
- Our introduction.
- Derek Shepherd. Pleasure.
It's very, very
nice to meet you.
Nice meeting you too.
- You think she's pretty?
- Yeah. I like cheerful people.
I can be cheerful.
I think the ashes thing
makes that kind of unlikely.
Dr. Bailey? We're going to help
rebuild a little boy's
ears today, pro bono,
and I thought maybe you
could donate some time.
Thanks to the fine
upstanding citizen
who cut off his
foot on my watch,
I've got a mountain
of paperwork.
On top of that, I promised to
try and get out of here in time
to see my son in his
Halloween costume.
Is Tuck even old enough
to know what Halloween is?
He's not, but his father is,
and that's who I promised.
Trick or treat!
For ears? He's trick
or treating for ears?
Yeah. Could you also persuade
some of the surgical
nurses to help out?
They seem to really like you.
- Trick or treat.
- Stop that.
All right. I'm in.
She's warm. It
doesn't make sense.
I'm sorry.
She's breathing with
the help of machines.
Erin, the person that you
knew, isn't there anymore.
Um, would you
bring this paperwork?
Mm-hmm.
You can have her.
You can have her organs.
That's what she wanted.
And her heart?
Give it to someone else.
You could scatter
her off the roof.
She was afraid of heights.
They're ashes, Meredith.
The ashes aren't acrophobic.
I need to put my mother to
rest. I need to not become her.
I need to not die emotionally
crippled and alone.
And I need to not
attend the wedding
of Derek Shepherd
and Sydney Heron.
I need to put my mother to rest.
Sydney Heron?
Just ask.
- So, you two are together?
- Yeah.
Like, together-together?
In love together? Sexy
love, not sibling love.
Yes. Yeah. We're together.
And you two have been...
I mean, without
any of us knowing...
doing this the whole time?
- Just once.
- Iz.
I said she could ask questions.
Just once.
And now we're
waiting to be together.
- Out of respect.
- For Callie's feelings.
- She's not judging.
- Right.
I have an earless
boy waiting for me.
But... I'm happy for you guys.
- Norman.
- Do you have to go?
No. Norman can get by for a
few more minutes without me.
How are you? I mean,
how have you been?
I'm in love with my daughter.
She's perfect. She's...
She sucks on her fingers...
It's her new thing...
and she makes like this,
perfect little cartoon
suckling sound.
And your husband?
My husband's in love
with my daughter too.
- You look tired.
- I haven't been sleeping much.
I haven't been
sleeping much either.
The baby wakes up all the time.
Not as much now
that I figured out
that if I wrap her in
whatever shirt I'm wearing...
Hmm. She smells you. Yeah.
Yeah. She sleeps.
Alex, what are we doing?
I mean, what are we going to do?
Hmm.
Dr. Hahn. Thank you for
coming on such short notice.
Oh, not a problem. Are we harvesting the
heart for UNOS or is the recipient here?
I'm hoping the recipient is
here, but he hasn't agreed yet.
I've never had much trouble talking
a heart patient into taking a heart.
- It's his daughter's heart.
- OK.
- Get him to OR two
and page Torres.
- OK. Where are you going?
- Hey. What's Hahn doing here?
- She's been declared
brain dead.
Heart transplant. Don't
even think about it.
- It's my patient.
- Dr. Hahn.
You're doing a heart transplant,
I thought I'd
volunteer to scrub in.
Isobel Stevens. She's
my patient, the donor.
So if you need any
information, I have it. All of it.
She's my patient.
You've got some eager
junior residents around here.
Lucky me.
Take your pick.
Well, Yang, I appreciate
the offer, but I date men.
So I don't think
you'll impress me
the way you've impressed
your mentors in the past.
I... What?
You sleep with them, right? Preston
Burke, Colin Marlowe. That's your thing?
It's my... It's... I'm...
I'm sorry... What does that
have to do with anything?
My theory is, if you
had the chops in the OR,
you wouldn't need to try
to impress in the bedroom.
- Stevens, is it?
- It is.
Let's go, Stevens.
Well, I bust my ass here,
Burke skips town with
my cardio reputation...
So instead of a
heart transplant,
I get to participate
in the amputation
- of a crazy man's foot.
- I'm not...
Crazy. Cutting off
your foot is crazy.
Walking through your
life like you have no power,
like you have no say...
No say in your own destiny.
Like you have no control
over your own body.
Walking through life
like that is what's crazy.
I still think it's
cutting off your foot
with a chainsaw that's crazy.
Mr. Shanley, I'm Dr. Hahn.
The transplant team is in place
if you're ready to say goodbye.
- You must not have children.
- I'm sorry?
If you had children,
you'd never say that.
You'd never say, "If you're
ready to say goodbye."
Mr. Shanley, I'm very sorry.
- But I want to suggest
one last time...
- No! I'm not taking her heart.
I can't have my daughter's
heart beating in my chest.
It would haunt me
every day of my life. No!
All right. I'm very
sorry for your loss.
Page me when he's ready.
Mr. Shanley?
I don't have kids, so I don't
know what it's like to lose a child,
but I do know what
it's like to lose a parent.
Your daughter loved
you. I saw her this morning.
She was fighting for you.
She was fighting for your life.
You're her dad.
You're her dad... she
didn't want to leave you.
I know that.
I also know that she would
want you to have her heart.
I would've given my
dad my heart if I could.
If I could have saved him...
I would have given him my heart.
All right.
- It's not my fault
Hahn chose me.
- Whatever.
I can't believe that
you are judging me.
After what Hahn said to
you, that you are judging me.
- It's not the same thing.
- It is the same thing.
It's exactly the same thing.
I'm sorry that I hurt Callie.
I didn't mean to hurt her.
You slept with her husband.
I slept with my boyfriend.
It's not the same thing.
Meredith slept with
another woman's husband.
another woman's husband!
The two of you are
like this closed circle.
You can commit whatever crime you
want, in your little circle, it's all fine.
I... I know that you didn't
sleep with Burke to get ahead.
And if Hahn had asked
me, I would've defended you.
I'm not even asking
you to defend me.
I'm asking you to just
cut me an inch of slack.
And believe me when I say
that I am sorry I hurt Callie.
We are not a closed circle.
You are.
- Dr. Shepherd.
- Yes.
Were there actual
shepherds in your lineage?
I'm sorry, what?
Shepherds, ones who watch
over sheep. I'm into genealogy.
My name, for example,
not actually after the bird.
I'm sorry. Would you excuse me?
- Of course.
- OK. Thank you.
- You did this.
- Payback's a bitch.
- What the hell'd you tell her?
- I put the word out
that you're lookin'.
- That I'm looking?
- Lookin'.
- Sounds dirtier without the G.
- You wonder why
they formed a club?
- You heard about that?
- Yeah.
OK. So we have
one plastic surgeon.
A general surgeon.
An anesthesiologist.
One, two, three scrub
nurses. And an OR.
Let's call your mom, kid.
You're going to get some ears.
- He cut off his foot.
- Yeah.
- He cut off his
perfectly good foot.
- People do some strange things.
Well, I had the world's
shortest marriage.
I was left in a church.
While I was literally
wearing a wedding dress.
Hmm.
George cheated on me, right
in front of me. And I missed it.
Burke sent his mother
to say goodbye to me.
- I'm going to be a divorcee!
- Now Erica Hahn
thinks I'm a fraud.
I... I'm not feeling very...
- Norman!
- Norman?
- Oh, crap.
- Hmm? What?
My intern... something
happened. I don't know what.
- We need to talk.
- We will. I'll come back, OK?
OK.
Don't chicken out.
You know, I'm impressed.
I didn't think
you'd pull this off.
I'm actually pretty
surprised myself.
Considering this was my
first time trick or treating.
- Your first time?
- Yeah.
My mom never made
it home to take me.
Never got it together
to make me a costume.
Plus she said it was rude
to knock on people's
doors and beg for food.
Huh.
- What?
- Just...
The apple fell pretty
far from the tree, huh?
- Dr. Karev? You want to slow down?
- Yeah. I just heard.
- Did he have a stroke?
- He did.
Three inches to the
left, he'd never talk again.
Yeah, but he's
going to be OK, right?
No way to know until we get
the clot out and he wakes up.
- But he's going to be OK?
- Karev, stop talking.
Is your marriage really over?
Yeah.
- I'm sorry.
- Thanks.
Did Meredith really bring
her mom's ashes to work?
♪ From here on
in it's up to you ♪
♪ I wish it wouldn't
but you know ♪
♪ The show goes
on I have to go ♪
♪ Promise to get well soon ♪
Look at that.
Not a bad day's work.
Paddles.
Let's see what we've got.
There it is.
Come on, Norman. Come on, man.
Come on, come on, come on.
What happened?
I just saw a heart transplant.
I just helped build a
little boy some ears.
- That's cool.
- Yeah.
I dug up my mom's cat.
What?
My mom didn't
leave any instructions
because it was so unexpected.
So we had to figure out on our
own what she would have wanted.
And my mom loved that cat.
So I dug her up. The cat.
From her little grave
in our back yard.
And I snuck into the cemetery
in the middle of the night
and reburied her
right beside my mom.
And it was creepy and morbid
carrying around a
dead, decaying cat
through the cemetery
in the middle of
the night. But...
it made my mom really happy.
At least, I like
to think it did.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
Look, Tucker, I said
I'm sorry. No, I didn't...
No, I...
Tucker.
Perfect.
Hi.
We just put a man's
daughter's heart in his chest.
- His daughter's heart?
- Mm-hmm.
Well, that just makes you
want to throw up, now doesn't it?
You all right?
You're Dr. Bailey.
You hear everything.
And even if you haven't heard
everything, I'm sure you've heard...
About your marriage?
Yeah, I probably would've.
I'm sorry.
If I... disappointed you.
I'm not your mother, O'Malley.
Oh... Oh.
Oh, I have to apologize
to her now too.
O'Malley.
Look, you're not a bad guy.
I don't mean to let you off the hook
entirely because what you did was unkind
and hurtful and wrong.
But you're not a bad guy.
I'm just saying it takes two.
To reach the point you reached
in your marriage, it takes two.
I mean... I mean, I'm here,
late at night, Halloween,
helping an earless boy get ears
and my husband wants to act
like that isn't an important thing.
He wants to act like it isn't
a good thing that I did today.
Now that isn't just on me.
That's him wanting things
to be the way he wants.
to be purely black and white.
I mean, I missed my
son's first Halloween.
And my heart is aching
inside of my chest but,
you know, that
doesn't mean anything.
That doesn't count. Because
in a black and white world,
I simply didn't make it home.
And that makes me
the bad guy. Always.
I'm always the bad guy.
You hear what I'm saying...
I'm sorry you missed
your son's first Halloween.
Look, what I'm
saying to you is...
OK, I was there. OK, I was
there the day your father died,
I was there when you came back
from Vegas married after a week and...
All I'm saying is, it's
not black and white.
And you're not a bad guy.
Nurse Kruger to the OR.
I did not sleep
my way to the top.
I'm attracted to talent
that resembles my own.
Not that it's any
of your business.
Your comments were
unprofessional and inappropriate.
You know what? You're
inappropriate and unprofessional.
This is going to be so much fun.
Dr. Yang. Did you hear?
Dr. Hahn has agreed to become our
new head of cardiothoracic surgery.
Looking forward to it, Dr. Yang.
You can't have my apartment.
I'm sorry I didn't listen when
you said you weren't feeling well.
I'm sorry I didn't
answer your page.
- Do you know why
I chose surgery?
- No.
I'm a little south of sixty. And
blood makes me squeamish.
See, I wanted to go into
psych because I like to talk.
- I've noticed that.
- But I had this voice
in my head,
telling me to choose surgery.
It was as if my Mary Beth
was whispering in my ear.
And so I listened. And do
you know what I think now?
No.
I think I was about to
have a massive stroke.
And my Mary Beth wanted
me to be surrounded by...
world-class surgeons
when it happened.
Mmm.
So what are you going to do now?
Well, I'm going
to go into psych.
Because you
people... you surgeons?
My... You're all just a
bunch of little children
running around with your scalpels
and your severed feet and your...
inappropriate sex in
inappropriate places.
You all need a good shrink.
- Dr. Grey?
- Hi.
Hey.
I had a goldfish and when he
died we flushed him down the toilet.
Back to the sea.
OK.
Back to the sea is
better than your cubby.
You OK?
I don't know if I can handle
one more night in that hotel.
♪ I will show you love ♪
♪ Like you've
never loved before ♪
What's the matter with you?
I have to start dating.
It isn't just surgeons.
The truth is I don't know anyone
who isn't haunted by something.
Or someone.
♪ You will hope
in something real ♪
♪ Won't depend on how you feel ♪
♪ When you call my
name then I answer ♪
And whether we try to slice
the pain away with a scalpel,
or shove it in the
back of a closet,
our efforts usually fail.
We made it through this day.
That we did.
So the only way we can
clear out the cobwebs
is to turn a new page.
So, it's the kitchen.
Bedroom. Bathroom.
It's a sofa... you
can sleep here.
Great. So, do you
mind if I clean up a little?
Yes. I mind a lot.
Or put an old story to rest.
♪ 'Cause you have
climbed an uphill road ♪
♪ You have worn a heavy load ♪
♪ You have cried
through endless nights ♪
♪ Nearly given up the fight ♪
♪ Watch your dreams
like falling stars ♪
♪ Heartache made
you who you are ♪
Grey.
Chief.
What are you doing, Grey?
This is a sterile environment.
It's my mother.
And I think this is
where she'd want to be.
♪ When the world was made ♪
♪ Trust in me, my child
Trust in me, my child ♪
♪ Where you gonna hide? ♪
♪ Where you gonna hide from me ♪
Should we say a prayer?
She didn't believe in anything.
Finally, finally to rest.
Ashes to ashes.
Dust to dust.
♪ I would never lie ♪
♪ This is not the end ♪
♪ There is still a hope ♪
♪ And I am on your side ♪