Previously on Grey's Anatomy:
Her or me?
I need him to stop talking to Meredith.
- You're staying with her?
- She's my wife.
I broke up with Derek.
- So where are we?
- We are a couple.
I know the rules, but I don't want
to have a relationship in secret.
Boys are stupid.
- What, you got a date?
- Yes, yes I do.
- You're married?
- Ten years today.
- How come I didn't know?
- You never asked.
In the eighth grade,
my English class
had to read Romeo and Juliet.
Then, for extra credit, Mrs. Snyder
made us act out all the parts.
Sal Scafarillo was Romeo.
As fate would have it, I was Juliet.
All the other girls were jealous.
But I had a slightly different take.
I told Mrs. Snyder
that Juliet was an idiot.
For starters, she falls for the one guy
she knows she can't have.
Then she blames fate
for her own bad decision.
- You kissed me.
- I did.
Should we... There's a discussion we
could have if you wanted to have one.
Izzie. I kissed you. With tongue.
And I plan to do it again and again.
Get used to it. End of discussion.
OK.
Mrs. Snyder explained to me
that when fate comes into play,
choice sometimes goes out the window.
God.
Congratulations.
- What?
- Fellowships.
Five applications, five offers.
Do you know how rare that is?
This is your year.
Everybody wants to dance with you.
Of course, Seattle Grace's
fellowship program is the best.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
You are taking my fellowship,
aren't you?
I don't know.
I haven't made a decision yet.
At the ripe old age of 13,
I was very clear
that love, like life,
is about making choices.
I would not wish this on anyone.
It's like someone ripped my guts out.
- Baby, you had food poisoning.
- I had one, lousy restaurant clam.
- Wait a minute. Where's Billing again?
- The basement.
And fate has nothing to do with it.
We're going the wrong way.
- Coffee?
- Oh, thank you. It's date night.
Yeah, it's a night, with a date.
- You forgot.
- No.
Yes.
You want to cancel?
No.
Everyone thinks it's so romantic.
Romeo and Juliet. True love. How sad.
Oh, crap!
If Juliet was stupid enough to fall for
the enemy, drink a bottle of poison,
and go to sleep in a mausoleum...
What the...
... she deserved whatever she got.
Window washer,
fell from fifth-floor scaffolding.
Obvious open tiblfib fracture,
but otherwise OK.
After a five-story fall
he's got equal breath sounds.
This is unbelievable!
Do you want to hear?
Somehow I believe you. Yang,
get in there and palpate his abdomen.
- Does this hurt anywhere?
- No.
You fell from the sky. Five stories.
You only injured your leg.
- George.
- No. Don't "George" me.
A few seconds earlier,
he'd have landed on me.
OK, rolling on three, please.
One, two, three.
- Are these feathers?
- My life was saved by that pigeon.
Let's get some X-rays.
And after that you might want to get in
there and look for the rest of Tweety.
Thank you.
Esme wanted to wait until tomorrow
to see her doctor.
But she hasn't been able
to keep anything down since yesterday.
So I brought her in.
Mrs. Sorrento,
you have acute cholecystitis.
Which means that your gallbladder
may have to come out.
She has gallstones?
He watches cable.
He thinks he's a doctor.
I'm giving you antibiotics and IV fluids
to cool the gallbladder down.
Then I'm going to call Dr. Bailey
and I'm going to see if surgery
is the best way for us to go.
- Do you have any questions?
- What happened to your forehead?
Nothing.
I've told you.
I don't need an appointment.
I am not a patient.
I am a friend from New York.
Weiss?
Derek! I've been looking for you!
Sav, why didn't you tell me
you were coming?
If I knew you were coming
I would have taken a day off.
- It was kind of last minute.
- Are you all right?
A month ago, her mother died.
Ovarian cancer.
Catherine died?
I'm sorry.
And Savvy, she's...
I mean, you know how close they were.
I mean, all she can think about is this
breast and ovarian cancer gene.
BRACA.
A positive test result
isn't the end of the world, Sav.
It just means you have
a gene mutation that could...
I know what it is.
I've talked to the genetic counselor.
I've been to my gynecologist.
And now I'm here.
Addy, you're the best surgeon there is.
True.
- But this isn't surgical.
- Yes, it is.
No. Sav, you understand
you don't have cancer?
And I have no intention of getting it.
So you want me...
I want you to take out my ovaries
and the uterus,
and when that's done,
you're going to find me the best person
out there to cut off my breasts.
- Beak?
- Claw.
We need to widen this incision
to take a better look.
- Does your leg hurt a lot?
- I'm fine, man. Just do your thing.
Is there anyone you'd like me to call?
What for?
You fell five stories
and lived to tell about it.
I'd kind of want to shout it
from the rooftops.
So to speak.
It's a miracle. You may not understand
the medicine of it.
A five-story fall, your lungs should be
collapsed, your back should be broken.
- Your aorta should be totally severed.
- George, enough.
I'm just saying, you know,
there's a reason for this.
You lived. We both did.
Carpe diem, man. Seize the day.
- Any chance you can make him leave?
- I really, really wish I could.
Mr. Vargas,
your lower left leg bones are shattered.
- We'll need to get you in for surgery.
- Oh, great. Just my luck.
Beak!
Could I... Would you mind,
could I keep that?
My mother died of it, my aunt. My
cousin. She's 37, has ovarian cancer.
But you don't. You don't have cancer.
But I have the gene.
Which gives her up to an 85%% chance
of getting cancer, Weiss.
- And a 15%% chance she won't.
- I'm not betting my life on 15%%.
- Were you invited?
- Weiss asked me.
- I thought it might help.
- Help what?
I'm sorry, Derek,
I'm really glad to see you.
But until you grow a uterus
and watch your mother die from this,
- you don't get... you don't get a vote.
- Did she say they tried for a baby?
- She did.
- Having a hysterectomy is...
- Derek!
- We've tried for months.
- Why give up now?
- Come on, we've talked about this.
There are other ways to make a family.
We can adopt.
- Savvy, I just...
- No. No! I'm not talking about this.
Let's just take a step back. All right,
take a deep breath and think about this.
I've already thought about it, Derek.
This... This is going to happen.
Dr. Stevens, get a complete history
and do her pre-op labs.
Schedule her for a double-mastectomy and
consult Dr. Quenar for a reconstruction.
- Derek?
- Addison, this conversation isn't over.
She is my patient, Derek.
We're doing a bilateral prophylactic
oophorectomy and hysterectomy tomorrow.
Get moving.
Prophylactic surgery is extreme.
This has nothing to do with you.
She came to me for a medical
consultation, Derek. I'm her doctor.
Those are some of our closest friends.
This is personal.
Fine. If it's personal,
we should deal with them as a couple.
- Acting like a couple.
- What? What does that mean?
- See the ring?
- Don't go to the ring.
The ring, Derek. Remember?
When we're here at work,
you won't talk to me.
Or on the ferry,
you pretend not to see me.
Or in couple's therapy, where we argue
about whether we should be in therapy.
- What are we doing?
- It's not about us.
It is! Medicine aside, our friends
are going through hell in there,
and we can't even act like we like
each other long enough to help them.
What's that other animal
that's monogamous?
I think it's voles.
I know it's hard. I'm a pincushion.
It's OK, don't worry.
I won't stick until I find a good one.
- Otters mate for life, you know.
- Excuse me?
As do voles, I suppose.
OK, I got it. Hold still, it's going
to take a second for the tube to fill.
I've always liked otters.
I've always been
more of a dog person myself.
Shouldn't he be more excited?
Maybe he's in shock. I don't know.
I mean, he survived. That's huge.
He's got to realize,
things happen for a reason.
Oh, yeah. My ex-boyfriend moved his wife
to Seattle. Reason? To torture me.
- I'm serious.
- So am I.
- What's with the Hello Kitty?
- I don't want to talk about it.
- Can I sign out to you early?
- You don't want in on Stu's surgery?
Can't. I have a test date.
Burke is testing me.
I've already spent an hour picking
bird parts out of the guy. I'm over it.
Carpe diem.
I have a zit on my forehead
and I am beginning to look how I feel.
- Carpe that.
- This is the luckiest day in the world.
Tell that to the bird.
Thank you.
Is it the kid thing?
I saw your face upstairs.
It's the kid thing for most people.
And the breasts.
Oh, and the total menopause,
like, overnight.
- It's a big step.
- I think it's brave.
Thank you.
And, yes, I'd love to be pregnant.
I want a lot of things. I want
to skydive. I'd like to learn Italian.
I want to go to St. Tropez with my
husband and lie topless on the beach.
They do excellent implants these days.
Won't even know the difference. Plus,
you'll never have to wear a bra again.
- That's something, right?
- Alex.
Didn't I see your service on the
OR board for a biopsy right about now?
Yeah.
- It's not the kid thing.
- OK, what?
It's not like I have a lot of options.
One, take my chances
and never get cancer.
- Two, take my chances and die young.
- There's a third option.
OK, I'm listening.
Take your chances, get cancer,
and fight like hell to survive.
Uh... They're both really nice.
I know. I bought them.
But which one is right?
For what?
You're going to look hot in either one.
Well, clearly. That's not the point.
You look hot.
Yeah. Burke and I are going to talk
about how hot I am over dinner.
- This date is such a mistake.
- It's easy to get nervous on dates.
It's especially hard
if you're out of practice.
- So, you just got to be mellow...
- I know how to date. I'm not you.
I have her scheduled for the mastectomy,
and I stay while Plastics
does a TRAM flap reconstruction.
- I couldn't do it.
- Do what?
Make yourself all hot and sexy
for your boyfriend like Yang?
Go wrestle something.
Cut off my ovaries and breasts
just 'cause I might have cancer.
Think of it like a hand.
If you knew you'd die if you didn't
chop off your hand, you'd do it.
Except when you chop off a hand,
you don't kill your sex drive,
have silicone breasts, get hot flashes,
and lose your ability to bear children.
I wouldn't have the test.
What's the point?
We're all going to die anyway, right?
It's the Hello Kitty Band-Aid
on my head. It's freaking me out.
I say slice 'em and dice 'em.
They're body parts.
- So you'd cut off your penis?
- If it kept me from dying.
Besides, I've got plenty to spare.
I can do hot in my sleep.
I look hot in scrubs. I'm a hot person.
- He's seen me naked 1,000 times.
- Bad, bad images in my head.
But he's never seen you
outside the hospital.
Thank you.
You look lovely.
Thanks.
Oh.
Very polite. Thank you.
OK, Grey. Adhesions are down.
What next?
Put in graspers to lift the gallbladder
so we can dissect it out.
Good. And what are we
looking for in Calot's triangle?
The cystic artery.
That's right. Wait a minute.
What do you see?
Porcelain gallbladder.
That's not good.
Mr. Sorrento,
when we removed your wife's gallbladder,
we found that there were calcifications.
What does that mean?
It's often a sign of gallbladder cancer.
We sent it off to Pathology.
- She has cancer?
- I'm afraid so.
We can keep her comfortable,
but she's going to need more tests
to see what our next steps are.
This might include more surgery.
But this surgery will save her, right?
The cancer appears to be advanced.
There are palliative surgeries
we can do.
That is, surgeries to help with
the pain, but it won't cure it.
How long has she got?
From what we can tell so far,
she has about four to six months.
I'm so sorry.
I don't want Esme to know.
- What?
- Esme.
- I don't want her to know she's dying.
- You don't want to tell her?
Please. You saw her. She's happy.
Let me take her home.
I don't want her to be afraid before
she dies. She doesn't need to know.
No, please don't.
No more carpe diem, man.
I don't want to seize the day.
That's what I don't get.
I'm standing here, and I'm just
incredibly happy to be alive.
I'm looking at the sky, it's bluer,
food tastes better,
and I didn't survive a five-story fall.
You jumped, didn't you?
The whole way down,
all I could think about was Daisy.
She's my ex-girl.
She works in this hospital.
What kind of joke is that?
Maybe... Maybe you got a second chance.
Daisy.
You got to go and find her for me.
I wanna talk to her.
Tell her she's the reason I'm alive.
We had a future.
You know, we had plans.
We picked out baby names together.
She betrayed that
without even asking my opinion.
Without even giving me time
to process it.
It's a difficult time for both of you.
- She's emotional.
- And hormone changes, mood swings.
They say she could lose her sex drive.
You'll get through this. All right?
You can do this.
You guys love each other.
Is that what you said
about you and Addy?
What?
- You left her.
- That was different.
Was it, Derek? Really?
You know, I got to check on a patient,
then get ready for dinner.
See you later.
Sure.
Where's the butter?
Oh, no, that's olive oil. I want butter.
Should I send the sommelier over?
That won't be necessary.
What is a nice, oaky Chardonnay?
I want Bordeaux.
The Chardonnay is better with lobster.
I'm having steak.
You... You eat red meat?
You don't?
You're seriously going to try
to find this girl?
Hunt her down
while she's working?
Look... OK, I know it's crazy, but
someone's got to tell her how he feels.
I mean, he's alive, right? Something
good has got to come out of this.
I mean, this could change everything.
See, I thought you were a romantic.
Was. Past tense.
Well, this is fun. Again.
I like the Hello Kitty, by the way.
Very pink. Very cheerful.
Daisy works in Billing. Which is where?
In the basement.
You need something, Chief? I have
one more surgery and then I'm free.
- No, no, no.
- OK.
- Have you made a decision yet?
- Sir?
The fellowship.
The Seattle Grace fellowship.
- I thought you'd have accepted.
- I haven't had a chance...
We're a private hospital
with extensive resources.
You'll get more
surgical experience here.
Write your own ticket.
Why aren't you excited?
No! I'm excited. I... Excuse me, sir,
I just need to scrub in. Thanks.
Dr. Hines to the OR.
- What?
- Oh, nothing.
You know, we should probably
skip dessert. I have an early morning.
Oh. Right. Not a problem.
Help! Is there a doctor in here?
Yes!
Call 911.
- He said he had heartburn.
- Is there a pulse?
Yes. It's rapid and unequal.
- Look. The length of his fingers.
- He's got to be at least six-foot-four.
- Marfan's.
- What does that have to do with it?
He's showing classic markers
for Marfan's syndrome.
- His blood vessel walls are weak.
- We need that ambulance.
- Fast. We need to get him to the OR.
- Before his aorta ruptures.
What are you talking about?
Who are you people?
We have a dissecting thoracic aorta.
We need a CT cleared and an OR ready.
Start another large-bore IV.
Continue high flow O2. Transport
sirens and lights to Seattle Grace.
- Who the hell are you?
- Hey!
He's the cardio-thoracic surgeon
who'll operate on him.
And she's with me.
Oh, I didn't...
Have you been discharged?
No. I'm going out to dinner
with my surgeon and our husbands.
Sort of a last supper, I guess.
I know, I know. Nothing after midnight.
You're disappointed, aren't you?
How do I look?
- You're a beautiful woman.
- And so are you.
Is that why this is
so hard to understand?
Ugh. Menopause. I know.
The boobs.
But they have hormone replacement,
reconstructions.
But the sexy Savvy,
the Savvy that gets noticed
when she walks into the room...
The Savvy that wakes her husband up
in the middle of the night to make love.
Yeah, I wonder if that Savvy
is still going to be there.
Honestly, I haven't a clue.
But then I think,
is that why Weiss married me?
God, I hope not.
Could this place be any further away?
It's like Siberia down here.
That's 'cause we don't like sick people.
Oh.
You know, you're in a hospital.
Uh, are you Daisy?
I don't deal with billing questions
after 7:00p. m.
- I'm just data entry at night.
- No, actually, Stu sent me.
- Is this some kind of joke?
- No. He's in this hospital.
He's had an accident.
I'm his doctor. He's fine.
We're taking him into surgery.
But he wanted me to find you.
You just tell that bastard that he could
have come looking for me ten years ago.
- OK, hold it here. Is this good?
- Yeah.
Lock it.
- What are you pissed about?
- You look at everything in a skirt.
I'd look at you in a skirt. Short.
Maybe something schoolgirl? Pleated.
If that skirt didn't have a pair of big
boobs attached, you'd stop looking.
When you cut 'em off,
you build 'em back up.
Maybe you get to upgrade.
Life goes on.
If there was a test
for testicular cancer,
you think men who
tested positive would have surgery?
No. You know why? It's castration.
What man would willingly
get rid of the part of his anatomy
that makes him a man?
This woman is having herself castrated.
And we book an OR and act like
it means nothing. It's not nothing.
God, how can you possibly act like it's
no big deal? I mean, what if it was me?
Izzie. You're making... Freaking out...
You know that, right?
If I was the one with the cancer gene,
if tomorrow my boobs
were made of plastic
and my skin had aged ten years
and my sex drive had dried up,
if it was me, Alex,
would you be so fine with it then?
Yeah, you'd be really hot to kiss me
with tongue then, wouldn't you?
Dr. Bailey's scrubbing in,
so we're going to get started.
OK. Hey, George, listen,
did you find her?
I'm very sorry, Stu.
They said she was on vacation.
Oh, yeah?
Maybe her parents.
I bet you she went up to New Hampshire.
That's where she's from.
- I'm going to push the joy juice.
- Up, up and away.
Maybe you can see her after
your surgery. When you recover.
It's all good, man.
Thanks for trying.
It really meant a lot to...
- Hold on, we have a problem.
- He's crashing? Dr. Bailey?
O'Malley, start CPR.
Push epi.
- You'll need to notify the family.
- What happened?
There'll be an autopsy. Sometimes people
get on the table and they just die.
There's no way of knowing beforehand,
or of controlling it.
But he fell five stories and lived.
It doesn't make any sense.
He survived,
so I could go and find Daisy
and then she didn't even want
to see him. So what's the point?
We're all part of the cosmic joke,
O'Malley. Now leave me alone.
- Oh, Dr. Bailey...
- What?
Mr. Sorrento doesn't want me
to tell his wife that she's dying.
- You haven't told her yet?
- No.
OK, I didn't hear you say that.
You're her doctor.
It's your responsibility to give
patients the information necessary
to make an informed decision. Now,
I'm hungry. I'm tired. You're in my way.
- Can you see the echo?
- A dissection isn't subtle.
Did you see that wing span?
And the pectus carinatum?
- What about his palate?
- The definition of high arched.
- You're being wooed, aren't you?
- Excuse me?
The fellowship. LA Med,
Chicago Central, they're wooing you.
You're fielding offers, looking at
bonuses, letting yourself be wooed.
- No, Chief...
- No, it's fine, it's fine.
Go be a hotshot somewhere else.
But tell me...
how could you do this to me?
You know, I'm hurt.
Really hurt.
After all I've done for you.
You're gifted, and you're ungrateful.
And that's all I'm saying.
I'm pregnant, you blind moron.
You're what?
My heart rate is 110.
I'm burning 3,000 calories a day.
My legs are swollen.
I've got indigestion and gas.
Did you know that carrying a boy in your
uterus means you burn 10%% more calories
than if you had a girl?
Guess what I'm carrying.
I try for seven damn years, and a month
before my fellowship notifications,
the stick turns blue. Men.
From the very beginning they just
suck the life right out of you.
I'm not leaving. I'm pregnant.
Um...
Congratulations.
Dr. Yang, you're handling the saw.
Thank you, Dr. Burke.
You won't let me pick the wine,
but this you'll let me do?
- Are we all set for bypass?
- Almost there.
So, apparently we both live
in this elevator.
Meredith.
You could at least acknowledge I exist.
Hello, Dr. Grey.
Hello.
- You ready to go?
- I was on my way.
Well, it took three hours,
but the surgery went perfectly.
All we have to do now is wait and see
how he's doing when he wakes up.
- Why did this happen?
- Almost every patient with Marfan's
has an aorta that fails.
It's just a matter of when.
I guess it's lucky you two were
having dinner at the next table.
It was.
Take care.
And we can treat it with surgery
and chemo, but...
We're supposed to go to Venice
at the end of the month.
- Do you know the story?
- No.
They say if you ride a gondola
under the Bridge of Sighs,
you're together for eternity.
- You didn't tell Jed, did you?
- Excuse me?
He's always been so worried
that I'd go first.
You don't want him to know?
You're young. I don't expect you
to understand an old broad like me.
You can't have a relationship
built on a lie. Can you?
Honey, it's not a lie.
It's our future.
I've been with the love of my life
for 60 years, and now I'm dying.
We're going to Venice.
We're getting in that gondola.
When Addy told me she was
coming here, I had such a good feeling.
You guys are going to make it.
You were always meant to be.
A couple of clams on the half shell.
Couple of peas in the pod.
- We're working on the pod part.
- It's about choices.
Well, here's to taking life
in your own hands.
Cheers. Cheers.
Yeah. And here's to bull.
And here's to crap.
And here's to oophorectomy,
hysterectomy,
double bilateral mastectomy.
Please. Stop.
- How smart am I to know those words?
- Stop.
Here's to breast reconstruction,
nipple reconstruction.
Here's to losing your wife.
Here's to being the ass
who can't be supportive.
Here's to that.
Weiss?
Don't talk to me. Keep walking.
You should get some sleep, sober up
so you're ready for Savvy's surgery.
Come on, I'll drive you.
Oh.
I'm supposed to hold her hand
while they rip her apart?
That's the definition of love?
- You can do this.
- Maybe I can't.
- Maybe I just like to screw my wife.
- Weiss.
And that's what she'll think
if I'm not there.
You're going to be there.
This from a guy who packed his bags
in the middle of the night
and drove 3,000 miles
to live in a trailer.
Yeah, well, what am I doing
with Addison now?
Hm? I'm trying to work it out.
I don't know, am I out of my mind?
I don't know, you tell me.
It's about the ring.
It's about the vows.
Savvy didn't screw around with you
with your best friend.
She's looking for support.
If you don't give that to her now,
if you don't give her that support,
then what the hell am I doing?
You didn't tell her, did you?
No. I didn't tell her.
- I thought he cheated fate.
- Maybe he did cheat fate.
He died.
I think you can't wait for someone to
fly underneath you and save your life.
I think you have to save yourself.
You mean the pigeons
aren't going to come?
The pigeons aren't going to come.
Hold still.
Come on, make sure you get both sides.
You know these are going to be
next year's holiday cards.
I want them to be immortalized
before they're gone.
And this way, Weiss gets
to look at them whenever he wants.
These are going to be great.
- We're scheduled to go in at eight?
- Yeah.
I'm taking you down to the pre-op
in just a few minutes.
Weiss will show up, Addy,
he always does.
Sav, as your doctor
you know I'm 100%% on your side.
But as your friend,
are you absolutely sure about this?
I know what I'm losing.
I get it.
But think about what I'm gaining.
My life.
This gives me a shot.
A shot at the future.
A shot at me and Weiss
becoming this crazy old wrinkled couple
that argues all the time.
I mean, wouldn't you want that?
A chance to grow old with Derek?
Yeah.
Yeah, I do.
- Oh, God.
- Oh, Sav.
Maybe Romeo and Juliet
were fated to be together,
but just for a while.
And then their time passed.
If they could have
known that beforehand,
maybe it all would have been OK.
Here's the thing. I like your rack.
What is wrong with you? Why do you have
to be so... What is wrong with you?
I like your rack. I'd want them around
if I could have them. Trust me, I would.
But it wouldn't be the end of the world
if you got rid of them.
Because really, I'd want you.
Ow! What was that for?
I told Mrs. Snyder
that when I was grown up,
I'd take my fate into my own hands.
I wouldn't let some guy drag me down.
Mrs. Snyder said I'd be lucky if I ever
had that kind of passion with someone.
And that if I did,
we'd be together forever.
We never really got our date.
Are you kidding? That was the best date
I've ever been on.
Even now, I believe that for
the most part, love is about choices.
He's not coming, is he?
You're shaking.
You're here.
It's about putting down
the poison and dagger
and making your own happy ending,
most of the time.
I'm going to get started now.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
Ready.
And that sometimes,
despite all your best choices
and all your best intensions,
fate wins anyway.
I miss you.
I can't.
www.tvsubtitles.net