Previously on Grey's Anatomy:
Surgical training protocol
is officially changing, people.
Thought you'd defend your
boyfriend to me and I'd take it?
He's not my boyfriend.
- Hi.
You and Derek will not work.
Why do you care what I think?
If I'm gonna do this with him,
I need you to cheer me on.
As surgeons, we are
trained to fix what's broken.
I'm in a hurry. I can't stay.
Chief's having a big meeting,
but I wanted to tell you
that I'm finished with therapy.
The breaking point is
our starting line at work.
Meredith, you are not finished.
You have worked incredibly
hard. Look how far you've come.
- You're scratching the surface.
- Derek's moved in
and we've taken
it to the next level.
It's not about Derek.
- I'm happy.
- You're not done.
I am happy. Isn't
that the point?
- No.
- But in our lives,
the breaking point
is a sign of weakness.
- I need you to stay. I know.
- The meeting, the Chief.
Thank you, Dr. Wyatt.
Thanks for everything.
And we'll do everything
we can to avoid it.
♪ Trying to place a
name on what it's called ♪
♪ Make you feel
like a losing streak ♪
Whoa!
- Sorry.
- What are you doing in here?
Thinking about making this
my office when you move out.
When I move out?
When am I moving out?
Oh. Soon?
♪ Louder than
they Allow, allow ♪
- ♪ Say Aha, Aha ♪
- Mmm.
You know Meredith was
planning on making us move out?
- I'm busy here.
- Join us if you want.
No!
When were you planning
on telling us we had to move?
When did you plan to tell
them they had to move?
- Why do they have to move?
- I made this for you.
It's a zoo, a frathouse. Alex
and his parade of women.
- His parade of skanks.
- Am I apartment hunting?
I don't know. I have
to think about it.
Just eat the muffin,
Mer. Taste the muffin.
Remember the muffin.
- I like my roommates.
- I like them too.
That was your
life. This is our life,
and I'm excited about
building our life together.
Come on. It's gonna be great.
So Derek wants Alex
and Izzie to move out.
Since when does he
say "jump" and you jump?
- Well, I'm happy.
- They'll be pissed off.
But do whatever you want.
Hey, you hear anything
about what the new rules are?
Last I heard you were at
hand-holding, foot rubs,
and lots of late-night
gab sessions.
- Excuse me?
- Listen up, everyone.
You're talking about
the Chief's new rules.
- Thought it was you and Torres.
- Listen up!
I've been wrong before.
We're busy people, I'm
gonna try and be brief.
I am implementing a new teaching
protocol here at Seattle Grace.
Some of these rules are new,
and some are old and are
going to be newly enforced.
Jack O'Brien, 47.
Scheduled for an abdominal
aortic aneurysm repair.
Last CT showed calcification.
So I ordered a CT angio
to determine if it had
worsened or remained stable.
Nice catch, Yang. You can
take him down after rounds.
Dr. Karev will take over. Dr. Yang,
you're done here. Thank you.
First, second and
third-year residents
will no longer be allowed
to de facto specialize.
The practice interferes
with the development
of a fully-rounded surgical
education. No more.
Barry Patmore, 63.
Has been experiencing chronic
headaches for the past seven years.
Has been treated with narcotics,
anti-seizure medications,
antidepressants, and anti-psychotic
medications with no success.
How severe is the
pain, Mr. Patmore,
- scale of one to ten?
- Eight. It's always an eight.
Which is why Mr. Patmore's last
consult suggested a bilateral cingulotomy.
A frontal lobotomy
for a headache?
Too loud. Please.
And could you do
something about the buzzing?
Do we need all these machines?
Mr. Patmore has been
experiencing pain every day
- for seven years.
- A cingulotomy could cause
seizures, cognitive defects
or behavioral changes.
Which is why we are going to
explore every possible option
before resorting to
such a radical surgery.
- More tests?
- Yes.
Dr. Yang, you'll be
assisting Dr. Shepherd today.
Personal relationships,
personal loyalties
and personal favorites
will no longer be a factor
in our training program.
Attendings, you will spread
your wealth of knowledge equally
among all of the residents.
In addition, we'll
refocus our attention
on patient communication and
bedside manner. For some of us,
this means learning the lost
art of humanity and compassion.
For others, this means
learning how to treat patients
without becoming
emotionally involved with them.
Shelley Boden, 30, stage four
colon cancer with liver mets.
Shelley has been through
extensive chemo and radiation.
According to the CT, a liver
resection could be curative.
Will be curative. Will.
Do you have any
other questions for us?
What happens if you find
more cancer than you expect?
No, Jen. A, that's
not gonna happen.
B, Izzie's already answered
all of your questions three times.
- Izzie's not the main surgeon.
- Izzie's awesome. We love Izzie.
This is Dr. Grey. She'll
prep you for surgery
and answer any
questions you have.
- Izzie's not staying?
- This is a surgical program.
Psychiatry is
on the fifth floor.
Let's not confuse the two.
In addition, residents,
your interns reflect on you.
If they fail, you fail.
If they succeed, you succeed.
Attendings, that goes
for residents as well.
Teach with enthusiasm.
Learn with enthusiasm.
We are surgeons.
We cut out malignancies.
Let's start at home.
O'Malley? This is
Dr. Bennett Epstein.
He'll be your proctor
for the exam today.
- You're about ready, O'Malley?
- Yes, sir.
You have three hours from
the moment you open the test.
Once you break this seal,
you may not leave the room
until you have completed
the entire exam.
- Good luck, O'Malley.
- Thank you, sir.
I can do this.
I'm not married and cheating
on my wife with my best friend.
Everything's just
as it should be.
Oh!
Damn chair. Hang on.
Looks like the wheel's broken.
That's how things
work around me.
My toaster broke last month.
Then my cat ran away and
my back porch collapsed.
Also, my TV only
shows the color green.
I'll get another chair.
Don't bother. I'll
walk. Probably safer.
No. Mr. O'Brien, you
need to stay in the chair.
- It's hospital policy.
- I had three car accidents...
Mr. O'Brien.
Somebody get me
a gurney over here!
- Sir, I am very sorry.
- I hit my head.
I am very, very sorry.
Get him a CT. I want hourly
updates on his condition.
- Yes, sir.
- You're gonna be OK.
Mike, my ceiling's raining here.
Looks like a pipe burst.
Gotta turn off the water...
No. This is a surgical floor.
Water's required to
scrub and clean equipment
to keep people alive.
- Fix this with the water on.
- I can try.
Keep me posted.
Chief, there is some kind of
leak in the conference room.
- You don't say.
- I was wondering
if there was anywhere
else I could take the exam.
I will find a different
room on my own.
Thank you, sir.
We have a problem.
Mark Sloan has found us out.
Mark's known from
the beginning. I told him.
He's Mark Sloan.
You don't have a person
you talk to about things?
You are the person
I talk to about things.
I like to keep my
private life private
from everyone, but most
definitely from Mark...
Sloan.
- How long'll the operation be?
- At least a couple of hours.
Think it could be longer?
If there are complications or
the mets are more extensive.
They won't be, Jen.
Please, stop. Call Mom
and Dad, tell them two hours.
Since I got cancer, my sister's
only capable of talking about cancer,
which is so much
worse than the cancer.
So I know I don't
know you, but spill.
- Spill what?
- Anything.
I'm begging you,
before she comes back
and asks you to describe
my liver cell by cell.
Please.
OK. Um... Do you
want to hear about my
stupid boss or stupid boyfriend?
Oh! Boyfriend!
Definitely the boyfriend.
Mr. Patmore, I'm gonna give
you a variety of different stimuli
so we can take a look at
the wave patterns generated.
I need you to remove your
hand from your eyes now.
OK. Are we still at an eight?
- It's still at eight.
- OK.
Starting visual stimuli.
If you were me
you'd want them out.
The roommates.
- I'm not being unreasonable.
- Pulse is coming down.
But you have to admit,
you'd want them out.
If you were me, you
would want them out.
If we have to operate,
I'll let you drill the
burr holes by yourself.
Fine. I'd want
them out. Whatever.
I knew it. OK, Mr. Patmore.
OK, we're gonna
change your position.
- I think I have an idea...
- No, don't think. Know.
Run to the lab
for his test results.
But Izzie bakes
and Alex fixes things.
OK, when I am no
longer Cancer Girl
and I can go out and meet a
hot doctor who rocks my world
and wants to move in with me,
I might forego the baked
goods and repair work.
Ooh. Heads up. Twelve o'clock.
Just so you know, Cristina thinks
you should move them out. Talk to her.
Dude, you failed
to mention the hair.
Yeah, yeah, the hair.
It's one of the many things
that makes me happy.
Dr. Sloan, I'm working with
Shepherd today on a pain patient,
and I read this article while
I helping George study...
Pathetic.
Yes. I know, I'm pathetic.
I did read this article. I do
have a photographic memory.
Chief's on his new thing
with the interns to be heard...
- Use fewer words, Grey.
- I think he needs an ENT.
You're an ENT, right?
How are you doing
in there, Mr. O'Brien?
Could be worse. Could have
brain leaking from my ears.
That's the spirit. It'll only take a
couple more minutes. Hang on.
Guess what I
found. An apartment.
A beautiful apartment.
With hardwood floors and
an honest-to-God fireplace
that you can build
honest-to-God fires in...
and I can't afford it by myself.
So... I thought if you
could get over yourself
we could live together.
No, thanks.
I mention the hardwood floors,
the honest-to-God fireplace?
I'd rather live in my
honest-to-God car.
Right.
How's he doing? Think
we're looking at a lawsuit?
No, we don't have a
picture yet, but... no.
This guy doesn't seem
like the lawsuit type.
Let's hope you're right.
Hello?
I cannot apologize enough.
Treat him like a king.
Hear that, Mr. O'Brien?
Dr. Karev is going to
take great care of you.
You are our number
one priority today.
- Are you OK?
- God hates me.
- Mr. O'Brien...
- My wife left me.
My accountant stole from me.
The store I worked
at burned down.
I was diagnosed with an aneurysm
for which I'd require surgery
in a hospital that seems
to be crumbling around me.
God hates me.
You can see the remaining
tumors easily identified here.
Her liver looks so healthy.
That's the beauty
of general surgery.
See badness
surrounded by goodness.
Cut out the badness,
all's right with the world.
It's just you and your scalpel,
one on one, mano a mano.
OK, this is me teaching
with enthusiasm.
Oh...
Oh, no.
- O'Malley.
- What?!
Um... if you're
finished with your test...
Look, the hospital's
flooding. The CT's on the fritz,
my post-op and pre-op
patients are backed up for days,
I gotta get a
handle on this thing
before the patients find out and
our ranking drops way past 12.
I found a nice, quiet room in
Psych for you to take your exam.
Oh, I see. Um...
No, you go ahead.
Chief!
I am your intern at
least for one more day.
I can help.
- Dr. Shepherd, a word.
- Excuse me. Yes?
You mind if I run a
quick test on your patient?
He's in a lot of pain. I don't
think he needs a tummy tuck.
That's funny. No, Dr. Grey came
to me with an interesting idea.
Unlike you, I'm taking the Chief's
new teaching protocol seriously
so I listened.
I read a thing about swelling
and compression
of the ethmoid nerve.
I believe if we were to stick
a cottle elevator up his nose...
I'm sorry, up his nose?
If Dr. Grey is on
the right track,
the patient'll let us know.
OK.
Mr. Patmore, I'm Dr. Sloan,
head of plastic surgery and an
ear, nose and throat specialist.
I'd like to run a test
with your permission.
I've seen 16 ENT's.
Not one could help me.
Now breathe normally.
I'm gonna angle this into here.
Let me know when you
feel any... pain or anything.
That's it. That's the pain!
That's what's causing the pain.
Oh, my God! Oh, my God.
Anterior ethmoid
neurovascular complex.
A simple middle
turbinectomy will fix it.
Unless you still want to
chop out the front of his brain.
Nicely done.
Hi.
How'd it go?
Hi, Shelley.
We found that the mets were much
more extensive than the CT detected,
and the main tumor actually
extended in and around
the major blood
vessel behind the liver.
We're gonna start a new
round of chemo, that's all.
I already have a call
in to your oncologist.
That's him. I'll be right back.
We can manage your pain.
I'm sorry we don't
have better news.
So did you decide what to
do about your roommates?
I'm so sorry, Shelley.
Come on.
So how good is the
hot boyfriend in bed?
Look, we don't even
know what we are yet.
So how does Mark Sloan know?
Why are you talking
to him instead of me?
Ladies.
Am I interrupting?
- Your timing is perfect.
- Really?
Were you about to feel her up?
- Stop. You have to stop.
- I can't.
- Seriously, she hates it.
- That's why I can't.
- Don't... You want a spanking? I...
- OK?
You told Derek you think
I should kick them out?
No. No, I...
I told him I would want
them out. Me, not you.
I only said it because
he wouldn't stop talking.
You don't think I should? I think
I'm going to. It's the adult thing to do.
- What does your shrink say?
- I quit my shrink.
- I'm happy. We're happy.
- Can I sit here?
George... George, how did it go?
There's a water problem.
I'm just trying to help the Chief.
Now the medical facts
are falling out of my ear.
Eat this, it's brain food.
My dude with the aneurysm?
Fell in the water, smacked
his head, got stuck in the CT.
My patient's dying. I hate it
when I like them and they're dying.
Our guy's been in pain at
a eight the last seven years
because of an inflamed
nerve in his nose.
I wish I had an inflamed nerve.
There is no way that guy's been
living at an eight. He's a wimp.
His eight? My
three. I can take pain.
You can't talk to my
boyfriend for ten minutes.
There's pain and then there's
torture. I can take pain. Test me.
- Nothing.
- Impressive.
Shut up! You barely touched her.
- Ow!
- Ow! No! No!
- Knock it off! Stop it!
- How did you diagnose
that nerve?
Because I've never
heard of that condition.
I remembered an article
from the British journal of ENT.
It was issue 47,
page 19, from 1964.
- A photographic memory.
- Dude. Lexipedia.
- Oh, I hate you.
- Don't hate me. I can help you.
Chief, what's going
on with the flood?
It's not a flood,
Bailey. It's a pipe that...
It's minor, OK? Not to worry.
Aren't you headed to surgery?
Yes, sir.
Chief, a few months ago
little Tuck flushed one of his
action figures down the toilet.
I thought it was
no big deal. Minor.
But then I came
home to a kitchen
filled with several
inches of poop water.
- Poop water?
- In my kitchen, sir.
Thank you, Dr. Bailey,
but I have this under control.
Yes, sir.
Poop water.
Hey. Hey. So apparently
there's some kind of leak.
Chief wants me to move the
pre-op patients to the clinic.
Who's free to help me...? Ow!
- What the hell?
- Not a high pain threshold?
You know what? Throw
him out. Not me, just him.
- She likes me more.
- I bake for everyone
and I clean.
The only thing you
bring to the house is filth.
What would you prefer,
chocolate cake or an STD?
Water!
- Get out, get out.
- Where is this coming from?
- Get the Chief.
- Let's keep going.
Post-ops to rooms 2415.
Pre-ops to rooms 2233, 4 and 5.
- Overflow goes into the clinic.
- OK.
Chief!
I got everything
under control up here.
I need you to oversee Stevens
with the pre-ops in the clinic.
Sir, maybe we need to shut down.
Just send the patients to
Mercy West, Seattle Pres.
They can repair the pipe. We'll
be up and running in no time.
I am sending our
patients to dry ground.
I closed all but two ORs.
Maintenance has isolated the
broken pipe, so thank you, Dr. Bailey.
When I say I've got it under
control that's what I mean.
Sir, they may have isolated
it, but a lot of water got out.
- I'm just saying...
- Dr. Bailey, clinic now!
Yes, sir. On my way.
Slow down!
OK, what next?
Wait. Are you sure
you have time for this?
I want you to get
to take your test.
- Thank you.
- Grey.
Despite your
unfortunate taste in men,
turns out you're
not entirely useless.
Mr. Patmore's condition
is extremely rare...
and you nailed it.
You can scrub in.
Now? You're doing the
surgery now, with the flood?
Flood's contained. Our man's
been in pain for seven years.
See you in surgery.
I can't. I'm sorry. Um...
But I'm really busy helping
the Chief... the Chief's intern.
I... Thank you, but
maybe next time?
No, Lassie, there
won't be a next time.
Pathetic.
Mr. Patmore, I'm
gonna draw some blood
and place a topical decongestant
before I take you to surgery.
Absolutely, of course.
How's your pain level now?
Eight.
It's always at eight.
Oh. It looked like
you had some relief.
I've spent seven years.
I've seen 39 doctors.
I've tried every kind of
painkiller and nothing helps.
I've had doctors tell
me it's my imagination...
that I'm crazy.
Called me a drug addict.
My wife died last year.
After spending years carting
me around to doctor after doctor,
test after test, she died.
She was my best friend.
She was my favorite
person in the...
And she died.
But I couldn't feel it.
I couldn't feel that pain
because I was so completely
occupied with this one.
Now I finally know what's
wrong and Dr. Sloan is gonna fix it
so you're right, you're right,
that I'm feeling some relief.
OK, let's get your blood drawn.
I'm not gonna do it. I'm
not gonna have surgery.
It's just gonna hurt.
She's gonna slice me in
half and probably kill me.
If she doesn't kill me,
it'll just hurt like hell.
Probably get infected and
hurt worse. I'm not gonna do it.
I get that you're scared, but if you
want to live you need the surgery.
If I want to live? Have you
been paying any attention?
My girlfriend had a hysterical
pregnancy and went nuts,
cut her wrists while I was in the
next room, had to be committed.
Now my roommate's
planning to make me move.
I have no money for a deposit.
Chances are next
week I'm homeless.
You're making stuff up
to make me feel better?
You must have
something to live for.
Or even just the
possibility of something.
This girl at the grocery store.
I keep meaning to say hello.
Instead I... just keep
asking her about the produce.
All right. So you
get the surgery.
'Cause chances are your
luck's gonna turn around.
It's science. It's
the law of averages.
It's gonna turn around.
And when it does, you say hello.
I say hello.
Chips?
Chocolate?
Thanks.
- What?
- You're not a terrible person.
- OK.
- I know we don't see
eye to eye, but...
I found this really
great apartment.
It's across the street from
the hospital, has great light.
I know you can afford
it and it's Burke-free.
It must be kind of awful
living in his old place.
Think about it.
You can open that retractor up
more if you want to get a better look.
Just make sure you keep
the small bowel inside.
I want to avoid a post-op ileus.
We better. He thinks there's a
dark cloud following him around.
That sounds overly dramatic.
What's that?
- What's...?
- What the hell?
Hey, hey. Hey, move! Move!
- Move the patient!
- What?
Move the patient!
Oh, my God!
Is everyone OK?
How's our patient?
- Vitals holding stable.
- Irrigation, please.
- How can I help?
- Find Chief,
tell him what happened.
God, we need a new OR.
Shut down the other ORs
except for this one and Dr. Sloan's.
Karev, go to Sloan. He just
got started, maybe he can close.
I need everybody's help.
Get ready to move Mr. O'Brien.
- What do I tell Sloan?
- Tell him the damn sky
is falling!
Nasal speculum and lidocaine.
Larger speculum,
another lidocaine.
- You're just watching?
- I'm a pain specialist
and I would've missed this
thing. So yes, I'm gonna watch.
Don't ever use me again
to try and influence her.
You and I are not Team Meredith.
We need the OR.
We need the OR!
On a patient?
- Yes, sir.
- Collapsed?
Your staff wasn't hurt, but the
patient's abdomen was open.
He's stable, as far as I know.
Dr. Bailey, spread the word.
We are closing
the surgical floor
and shipping
patients to Mercy West
- and Seattle Presbyterian.
- Yes, sir.
And Dr. Bailey...
- Try not to gloat
on the way out.
- No gloating, sir.
Anybody see any more
damage? Any bleeding?
No bleeding. I cleared
the lower left quadrant.
Give me the pulse irrigator.
Dr. Hahn, take a
look at this right here.
The pancreas. Is that
damage from the debris?
No, no.
That's a tumor.
Oh, son of a bitch.
You're the shrink, right?
- Yeah.
- Well, you can't let her quit.
Let me guess. Cristina.
She talks? Whatever.
Um, you can't let her
quit because I'm no longer
allowed an opinion.
I'm being supportive.
So you're my last hope.
It's your job to have
an opinion, right?
You're paid to have an opinion?
- That's right.
- OK. So, um...
She lives her life on an eight.
Her pain. On any given
day, she lives at an eight,
and he doesn't get that.
I mean, he moves in and expects
her to move her roommates out?
Which goes to show you how
completely he doesn't get her
because she needs them.
So you need to tell her
not to move them out.
It's not gonna work
out in the long run.
She thinks that she's
happy, she's not.
It is your job to tell her.
♪ 'Cause it's long gone ♪
It must be incredibly
painful for you,
the idea of losing
Meredith to Derek.
♪ It's not over till
it starts again ♪
You're a terrible shrink.
- Just talk to the oncologist.
- No.
There's a clinical trial
using chemo plus Avastin,
- and there's...
- You're not a doctor.
Please stop talking
like you're a doctor.
Hello?
- Did you have me paged?
- Yes, because I'm dying
and you can't let me die without
knowing what you decided.
No, they found mets
underneath her liver.
♪ When I saw you
stuck in a rut again ♪
♪ Oh, that drink
went down smoothly ♪
You look very serious.
Oh, my God, are you
gonna break up with him?
No fair!
I'm dying and you're casting
all that hotness in the wind.
No fair.
It's no fair.
- No fair. No fair.
- ♪ It died out long ago ♪
I...
I'm alive.
Dr. Hahn's gonna come in and
talk to you in a couple of minutes.
How'd it go?
- OK?
- Actually, not so OK.
The flood weakened
the ceiling in the OR.
The ceiling collapsed and several
fragments landed inside your incision.
'Cause of the ceiling thing we
had to explore your abdomen
more thoroughly than
we normally would have.
As a result we found a
malignant tumor on your pancreas.
Cancer?
You found cancer?
Whoa, wait. Listen. Listen,
man, 'cause here's the thing.
We took it out,
sent it to pathology.
- It was only stage one.
- Only stage one.
We never find pancreatic
tumors so early.
They're almost always a death
sentence by the time they're diagnosed.
But not for you.
We took the tumor, the
whole thing. We took it out.
You won't even need chemo.
That ceiling collapse,
it saved your life.
Your luck has turned, man.
It's turned.
I'm gonna go say hello...
to that girl.
I'm gonna say hello.
Chief.
Chief? I've downloaded all our
patients' labs and radiology onto DVDs
and attached
them to their charts.
Is there anything
else I can do to help?
♪ I see his thumbs
working overtime lately ♪
♪ Immersed in a text
you sent discretely ♪
How'd it go?
I know. I'm pathetic.
And George doesn't know
I exist, I missed my surgery.
- Could you tell me how it went?
- We didn't get to do
the surgery.
Mr. Patmore's been shipped
off to another hospital.
And he will be out of
pain by this time tomorrow.
Photographic memory, huh?
- Yeah.
- Periodic table. Go.
Hydrogen, helium, lithium, beryllium,
boron, carbon, nitrogen, oxygen,
fluorine, neon, sodium, magnesium,
aluminum, silicon, phosphorus, sulfur...
I can keep going.
- We can burn actual wood?
- That's my favorite part.
- You can't find that anymore.
- It's gorgeous.
- What do you think?
- This is a fantastic apartment.
- We love it.
- I love it.
It was really great
of you. Thank you.
You're kidding, right?
Cristina, are you kidding me?
I am getting kicked
out of my house.
Think I pulled this
off the board for you?
I was asking you
to live there with me.
I'm sorry. I'm...
That's hilarious.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm walking to the bar.
You are just...
Give me the flier.
Um... I already put a
deposit down. I'm sorry.
You should've been more clear.
Fine. You know what? It's fine.
Keep it, that's totally
fine. Enjoy it. That's fine!
Thank you.
♪ LOL, LOL, LOL ♪
♪ I'm'a kick back and
watch this go down ♪
♪ While you're standin'
waiting for her to come around ♪
I get that you're a private
person, but I am not.
I process my stuff out loud.
I gave up too much of
myself in my marriage.
I can't give up pieces
of myself again.
And Mark is my friend.
I think I just hate him
because he's seen you naked.
♪ Beat you to the punch line ♪
♪ Broke your heart
before you broke mine ♪
What was the point?
All those hours
and all that money?
What's the point? The
world is a horrible place.
Young people die of diseases.
It makes absolutely no
sense to try to be happy
in a world that's
such a horrible place.
Yes.
- What?
- Yes, horrible things
do happen.
Happiness, in the
face of all of that,
that's not the goal.
Feeling the horrible,
and knowing that you're not gonna
die from those feelings, that's the point.
And you're not done.
You've made progress
because you're feeling
and you're telling me about it.
Six months ago it would've been
just you and a bottle of tequila.
My door's always open.
Bones break.
Organs burst.
Flesh tears.
Hey. Are you OK?
♪ The love we made
we can't erase it ♪
You know, I'm happy for you.
I am. I'm really happy
for you and Derek,
and that you guys
are moving forward.
♪ Pitterpat the angel
on my shoulder ♪
I don't know how it happened
that I don't have anyone,
but... I don't have anyone.
♪ The clock is getting louder
ready for me to decide ♪
That's not true, Iz.
That's not true.
♪ I've lost my sense
of right and wrong ♪
♪ When justified
my soul to carry on ♪
Hello.
♪ I feel so damn good
to write off the rules ♪
We can sew the flesh.
Repair the damage.
Ease the pain.
I found your mom's
vintage martini set.
♪ Pain takes my heart's place ♪
They're my family.
You can't just assume I'm
gonna kick my family out,
and you don't get to announce
it to them and ambush me.
And you definitely don't get to
try to get Cristina on your side.
They're my family, they're
who I have. You and them.
♪ The angel on my shoulder
is haunting me tonight ♪
OK.
♪ Tick-tock, the clock
is getting louder ♪
♪ Ready for me to decide ♪
- OK?
- I'd like to
talk about it again,
when you're ready.
But for now, OK.
♪ The sun is coming down on me ♪
♪ Could fate be so unkind? ♪
So you still love me?
But when life breaks down...
- Meredith...
- when we break down...
yes.
There's no science,
no hard and fast rules.
We just have to
feel our way through.
And, to a surgeon,
there's nothing worse
and there's nothing better.
Are you sure about this,
sir? You've had a long day.
It's one thing to stand on
a stage and give a speech.
But if I want our teaching
program to be the best,
and I do, it starts here.
And it starts with me.
I can't do anything
about the flood.
But I can give you
your shot, O'Malley.
You earned it.
- You ready?
- Yes, sir.
OK.
You get three hours.
Go.