Previously on Grey's Anatomy:
I have a feeling.
- What kind of feeling?
- Like I might die.
Hello? Clearly not my dream.
My contractions are ten minutes apart
and my water just broke on your shoes.
- Can't we use first names?
- I don't think so.
I can't remember our last kiss?
Where... is my husband?
Got into a car accident
getting to the birth.
- Is my wife here?
- There's not going to be a baby today!
Meredith and Cristina are doers.
They're doers.
I'm horny, I'm half-naked.
You want to talk metaphors
or do you want to take off your pants?
A quiet board means trouble.
A quiet board is death.
Hannah. Hannah Davies.
Why do you have your hand
inside my patient?
My husband has to go
and stand in front of his big gun.
He shot himself with a bazooka?
- Was there an explosion?
- No.
I'm touching live unexploded ammunition?
Ten minutes ago the operating rooms
at Seattle Grace were evacuated
- except Dr. Burke's team.
- And Dr. Shepherd's team.
I can't leave Bailey's husband
with his skull flap open.
Pink mist. That's what the bomb squad
calls you when you blow up.
Dylan Young, bomb squad.
That device is homemade
which means it's unstable.
I am 22 years old.
We need to clear the room.
This is a mistake.
Calm down.
What did I do? What did I do?
In hospitals, they say you know.
You know when you're going to die.
Some doctors say
it's a look patients get in their eyes.
Some say there's a scent,
the smell of death.
Some think
there's just some kind of sixth sense.
When the great beyond
is heading for you, you feel it coming.
Whatever it is, it's creepy.
Because if you know,
what do you do about it?
Forget about the fact
that you're scared out of your mind.
If you knew
this was your last day on Earth,
how would you want to spend it?
- What's going on?
- Uh, something happened in OR Three.
- What?
- I don't know.
All I know is Hannah,
the paramedic, she's missing.
Chief? What's happened?
A quiet board.
A quiet board is what's happened.
Dr. Shepherd?
Dr. Burke.
How's it going?
He's got a second bleed
under the skull base.
If I do what the textbooks say,
he could lose the power of speech,
herniate and die.
- What's your other option?
- If I do what I want,
he could lose the power of speech,
herniate and die.
Well, good luck with that.
Thanks.
Is there something you want?
You know, it was really stupid
of you not to evacuate.
- You, too.
- Yeah, I know.
We should consider a new profession.
Yes, we should.
Now, can you operate
and remove the device from the guy?
After the bomb squad is through
assessing him, I'm going to try.
I don't want to be the guy
that kills Bailey's husband.
that kills us all.
- Dr. Shepherd.
- Dr. Burke.
You realize how stupid that was?
- It was, incredibly stupid.
- I don't need to be made fun of
when I have my hand inside
a body that's got a bomb in it
and a stranger is Velcro-ing
a flak jacket to my boobs.
You've got a sense of irony.
Only when things are really ironic.
I had a feeling.
What's that?
Nothing.
- Time for you to go.
- No, I'm staying.
There's nothing more you can do here.
We got it covered.
Cristina,
this is not another cool surgery.
This ammo can go off any time
and kill everyone.
Do you get that?
You cannot be in here.
- Do you think this is about surgery?
- I cannot do this with you here.
I cannot think.
We'll be fine.
It's OK.
You know in the movies
how there's always the hero
and then there's the other guy?
You know the guy who sees danger
and runs in the opposite direction?
Yes.
Be the other guy.
So, you have a plan, right?
You have a way to get me out of this?
I feel colors are brighter.
Does anyone feel colors are brighter?
- My head hurts.
- It's the adrenaline.
- Do you have the smell thing? I have...
- Shut up!
- Are you OK?
- Of course not.
How could she be OK?
You're insensitive.
- I am not insensitive.
- Would you shut up!
Nobody cares if the blue is bluer
or if you have super smelling powers.
Meredith could die.
Any minute she could just... die.
Actually stop living.
Dead.
Corpse.
Look, I'm sorry.
God, I have really inappropriate
reactions to this kind of stress.
I'm sorry. Hold on.
- OK?
- Yeah.
Should we like... do something?
- I mean, call Meredith's family?
- We are Meredith's family.
I'm sorry.
We are Meredith's family.
- This area's been evacuated, Dr. Yang.
- And somehow you're still here.
- I have to be here. You don't.
- Yes I do.
- Dr. Yang.
- Yes I do!
Besides, I...
I'm guessing you need a little company.
- How's he doing?
- He's hanging in there.
- How's the paramedic Hannah doing?
- Hannah?
The girl with the bomb.
Oh, uh, she's hanging in there, too.
- Calm down.
- Calm down?
I have an evacuated OR,
a bomb in a body cavity,
a missing paramedic, an intern
with her hand on the explosive,
two world-class surgeons in harm's way,
a man on a table
who may bleed out any moment
unless we remove the bomb from his chest
and my favorite resident in labor who
you are now telling me refuses to push.
Really? Calm down?
- You really want me to calm down?
- OK, don't calm down.
Dr. Bailey is scared, sir.
It's a day to be scared.
She won't let me examine her but
her contractions are 40 seconds apart
and she is refusing to push.
The baby could go into distress
and if she doesn't come out of this,
I'll need an OR
to do an emergency C-section.
I can't give you an OR, Addie.
I don't have an OR to give.
Convince her. Bailey's rational.
She's not Bailey,
she's a woman in labor
whose husband is
in surgery next to a bomb.
- So is yours.
- This is about Bailey. I need an OR.
- I don't know what to tell you.
- Look, Richard, we have about an hour.
And then I'm going to need you
to get me an OR, build me an OR,
find me a helicopter to fly me
to any OR in the city.
Otherwise, instead of having a baby,
she'll be losing one.
- Here are the blueprints you asked for.
- Thank you.
I laugh at funerals.
I don't go to funerals.
Izzie. Iz.
I was jealous.
I was jealous of Meredith
and the surgery and I...
I... I was...
jealous, and now...
I was jealous, Alex.
Is this the strangest thing
to happen in your OR?
- I'd have to say that it is.
- Good, because I'm very competitive.
All the best surgeons are.
Dr. Montgomery-Shepherd
talked to the chief.
She's on the phone with Mercy West now
- to see if they have any ORs.
- I need someone to drive me home.
They're talking about doing a C-section.
Let them talk.
I'm not going to Mercy West.
This baby is not coming out.
I need a ride.
I can't focus enough to drive myself
and Tucker...
- I need a ride.
- You could lose it.
I told you, I'm not having this baby
until tomorrow.
- It could die before it's even born!
- Can you give me a ride home?
- Dr. Bailey...
- Then get out!
Is there any news?
What? Oh, I'm sorry, Mrs. Carlson.
My husband. I was wondering
if there was any news.
Because you look so worried.
And I heard this doctor saying
even though that girl has
her finger on the tear in his heart...
that my husband's losing... blood.
Every second he's losing blood.
Which means he could die.
He could die?
I ask because
I know you'll tell me the truth.
Because you look so worried.
Mrs. Carlson...
Yes, it's possible that he could bleed
out and die if we don't operate soon.
OK.
Thank you for telling me the truth.
I'll just...
I'll just go wait... over here.
Will somebody get me an update?
And where's the head of the bomb squad?
I'm right here.
And we're good to go.
My team's in place, Dr. Burke is ready.
The patient is stable.
We can have the bomb out
in ten minutes if I'm not interrupted.
In the OR we put our patients
under general anesthesia.
- Yeah.
- That involves a steady flow of oxygen.
Well, can't you turn off
the oxygen to my OR?
I can and I have.
But... this is your OR.
This is the OR floor's main oxygen line.
It's going to be OK.
- You don't know that.
- It's just what you say.
I know.
- Where you going?
- I can't just...
I got to do something to help.
Thank you...
for saying that it's going to be OK.
Even if it is just what you say.
Stop it.
- I'm not a patient.
- What?
You two are looking at me
the way we look at patients.
Like I'm going to freak out any minute.
I'm not going to freak out so,
whatever it is, just tell me.
The main oxygen line
runs directly under this room.
OK.
Not OK?
Well?
I need one of you to tell me
what this means exactly.
Because I think I know what it means,
but I tend to be
"glass half empty" these days,
so I won't trust what I think it means.
Because I think it means
that if the bomb were to explode
over the oxygen line,
the whole hospital could blow up.
And that's just crazy, right?
I need an answer
on when they're going to start moving.
- Look, I'm busy.
- I know.
I know you are,
but if there was something,
anything we could do to help,
it would be very helpful.
We need an assignment, sir.
- Look, I need...
- Chief?
- He's full-on diaphoretic.
- Check his pulse.
- We need help.
- Let's move!
- I'll get a wheelchair.
- I think it's a heart attack.
Meredith, all it means...
- is that we have to move.
- Move?
That's right. We have to move.
I don't want to spend
another second here.
Wait. I can't wiggle my fingers
because we can't shift the ammo,
and now you want to roll out
the entire gurney?
Well, that's our safest, safest option.
So we move. Not a problem.
We can do this.
- You handling this, Grey?
- I'm handling this.
- So how's it look?
- Hard to say. EKG is normal.
- That's good news.
- I'm getting up.
Sir, you should wait
until we get the blood work back.
- I'm not listening.
- You can talk to me, Dr. Stevens.
Um...
OK.
Your husband should really wait
until we get the blood work back
for confirmation.
OK, out! Both of you!
- I'm getting up.
- You have to body-check me to do so.
Adele, there is a bomb!
I heard.
Dr. Montgomery-Shepherd?
What are we going to do?
I mean, about Dr. Bailey.
Can we drug her?
- Against her will?
- No. Well... yes.
I mean, can't we force her to push?
lf... Declare her temporarily insane?
You want me to declare Miranda Bailey,
Miranda... Bailey, incompetent?
Do you think that will help?
Do you think it will make her more
inclined, comfortable giving birth?
- I don't know.
- Do you think I'm not doing
everything I can to help her?
Do you think I'm just out here
because I needed a little me-time?
- I'm just asking.
- Stop asking!
No matter what you ask,
I don't know.
I am doing everything I can.
Everything I can.
Miranda Bailey's husband is
in mortal danger, actual mortal danger.
There's not a lot I can say
to comfort her
because there's not a lot
anybody can say to comfort me.
I'm doing my best.
Dr. Bailey is doing her best.
And I need you to do your best
and I need it to be better
than standing here asking me
the world's stupidest questions!
I don't know, O'Malley!
Hey.
You OK?
Wait, are you bleeding?
I... I think I fell.
I was... I was running and, um...
and I fell.
It... It's OK.
Are you Hannah?
Yeah.
Microscissors, Dr. Yang.
What is so interesting out there?
I, um, I'II...
You're doing great.
Let's go over it again.
The device is shaped like a rocket
about eight inches long.
We'll have everything ready,
Dr. Burke's team will be in place,
my team will be in place.
Then I'm going to ask you to take
the hand that you have in Mr. Carlson
and wrap it around the device.
- And pull it out.
- Level.
Pull it out while keeping it level.
You know, I don't like you very much.
I don't like you, either.
- What are you doing?
- Stop where you are.
- Dr. Burke told you to leave.
We're moving to an OR further away from
the oxygen line. In case we blow up.
I remember him telling you to leave.
- Where is he?
- He's prepping the OR.
Then he'll never know, will he?
You stay over there.
You ready?
- Tell me something.
- What?
Cristina, I have my hand on a bomb,
I'm freaking out.
And most importantly,
I really have to pee. Tell me anything.
He told me he loved me. Last night.
He thought I was sleeping, but I heard.
Burke loves you.
Yeah. Mind your own business.
- Burke loves you.
- Yeah, everybody has problems.
- Well, are you going to say it back?
- Of course not.
He didn't say it to me,
only to the sleeping me.
Reciprocity is not required.
- Besides, he might blow up.
- Excellent point.
All right, everybody.
Let's just keep placing
one foot in front of the other.
Nice and slow.
- Meredith, we're almost there.
- OK.
We're almost there.
Nice and easy. Ready?
- Yep.
- All right, let's go.
Nice and slow.
You had to say
you were going to die today?
I told you.
It's not too deep, but you are
going to need a couple of stitches.
Hannah, is there someone
you would like me to call?
Family? Or maybe... a friend?
That doctor...
Dr. Grey? Meredith.
- Is she...?
- She's still there.
- So she's still alive?
- She's alive.
She's still alive.
Dr. Milton shouldn't have left you.
- He's a coward.
- I'm a coward.
- No.
- I ran away.
You think you're going to be different.
You think you're going to be the kind
of person who stays and does something.
You know, a good man in the storm.
I'm a paramedic.
I'm supposed to stay and do something.
I'm not supposed to run away.
I'm not supposed to hide
under the stairs
because I left two people to die.
I'm supposed to stay and do something.
I ran away.
Well, blood work's back.
The chief had an anxiety attack.
Who's going to tell him?
Um... I gave you sex
in the linen closet. You tell him.
Fair enough.
OK, Dr. Bailey. Let's go.
Dr. Bailey, I need you to turn
on your back. I need you to push.
Leave me alone.
Miranda...
I can't let her go any longer.
I'll go tell Richard
that he has to give us an OR, OK?
Dr. Bailey, I'm surprised at you. This
is not how I thought you would do this.
Dr. O'Malley, I don't think...
I truly...
- I expected more.
- George.
You're Dr. Bailey.
You don't hide from a fight.
You don't give up.
You strive for greatness.
You...
Dr. Bailey... you are a doer.
I know your husband's not here
and I know there are
a lot of things going on here
that we have no control over.
But this...
This...
we can do.
OK?
OK.
Let's have this baby.
We're ready when you are.
We're good. Meredith?
Yeah.
I'm going to extend the wound.
When I cut,
the bleeding is going to intensify.
If we're going to save Mr. Carlson,
you must pull the ammo out immediately.
But remember: Remove it
while keeping it as level as possible.
Nice and easy.
No quick movements.
Level.
Right. Level.
You ready?
I, uh...
- Do I have a choice?
- You have to be ready.
Yeah. I guess...
Scalpel.
I guess I'm ready.
- How's it going, Yang?
- Everything's fine.
- How's the girl with the bomb?
- How's he doing?
He's almost there. Can you suction?
Irrigate. Great.
- You didn't answer my question.
- Sir?
How is the girl with the bomb?
It's Meredith.
The girl with the bomb is Meredith.
I'm good. She can go.
All right, now, Meredith...
wrap your hand around the nose cone.
Meredith.
Grey?
We're losing him. Push one of epi.
- Thready pulse.
- Epi in.
- Get me a wet lap.
- Here.
Roll him on three. Everybody ready?
Ready? We got to go!
Come on, let's go!
Meredith?
George and Izzie
shouldn't have to move out.
No. You hear me...
You should make sure...
make sure that they...
they get to stay in the house.
- Good.
- Push.
- Just a little bit more.
- I can see the top of the head.
- I got to stop.
- And stop.
- OK, that was good.
That was very good. That was...
OK, are you ready?
- Ready?
- OK.
Push.
Come on, come on.
- Wide complex bradycardia.
- One of epi and of atropine.
Come on, come on.
You can't do this, Tucker!
You cannot quit on me. Come on.
- In.
- Grey?
His pressure's dropping.
Grey?
Look, I can't. No.
I can't. This is crazy.
Burke, you're gonna go. You go.
- Both of you.
- Nobody's dying today, Grey.
I want you to look at me.
Look at me.
I know this is bad.
I know that I'm this ass
who's been yelling at you all day.
So you pretend that I'm not.
You pretend that I'm someone you like.
Whatever you need.
But you need to listen to me.
- I'm scared.
- I know.
You can do this.
It'll be over in a second.
You can do this, Meredith.
OK.
Gently.
Good. A little bit more.
Good. Stop.
Stop?
Oh, Dr. Bailey,
I can see the top of his head.
He's got a lot of hair.
- Oh, he's cute.
- O'Malley.
Stop looking at my vah-jay-jay!
Yes, ma'am.
Out of the way!
You did good.
What the hell is happening?
Who's coming up?
OK.
Come on, sweetheart.
All right, people! They're coming up!
Mrs. Carlson...
- Derek.
- Preston.
Dr. Burke.
Is my husband, um...
...alive?
- Yes.
Is he going to stay alive?
Thanks to that young lady over there,
he is.
Thank you.
- Where is she?
- You had to be a cowboy.
Where is she?
She's right here.
Derek!
You're OK.
That is not the "she" he was asking for.
Burke?
You awake? Burke.
I love you, too.
This is our son.
William George Bailey Jones.
Hello, my little man.
Hello.
He's beautiful.
There's someone at the door for you.
Hey.
You almost died today.
Yeah. I almost died today.
I can't...
I can't remember our last kiss.
All I could think about was,
"I can't remember our last kiss,"
which is pathetic, but...
the last time
we were together and happy, I...
want to be able to remember that.
And I can't, Derek.
I can't remember it.
I'm glad you didn't die today.
It was a Thursday morning.
You were wearing that ratty little
Dartmouth t-shirt you look so good in.
The one with the hole
in the back of the neck.
You'd just washed your hair
and you smelled like some kind of...
flower.
I was running late for surgery.
You said you were going to see me later.
Then you leaned to me.
You put your hand on my chest...
and you kissed me.
Soft.
It was quick.
Kind of like a habit.
You know, like we'd do it every day
for the rest of our lives.
You went back to reading the newspaper
and I went to work.
That was the last time we kissed.
Lavender.
My hair smelled like lavender.
From my conditioner.
Lavender.
Huh.
If you knew
this was your last day on Earth...
how would you want to spend it?
www.tvsubtitles.net