My mother used to
say that for a surgeon,
a day without
death is a rare gift.
Time of death, 11:53.
Every day we face death.
Every day we lose life.
Time of death, 18:36.
Time of death, 15:52.
And every day, we're
hoping for a stay of execution.
What do you remember about it?
We were at home.
- You were there?
- Yes, I was there.
It's OK to talk about it.
Dr. Wyatt, my mother took a scalpel
and sliced her wrists in front of me.
I sat on the kitchen floor
in a pool of her blood,
waiting until she passed
out so I could call 911.
It's not OK to talk about it.
Why did you wait
until she passed out?
She asked me not to
before she slit her wrists,
so I knew I would get in
trouble if I tried to save her life.
But you did save her life.
She didn't want it saved.
You must be very angry at her.
No.
- Not at her.
- Who are you angry at?
We're attached to death.
Chained, like prisoners.
Captives.
- Do you want to dance it out?
- No.
- Do you want to drink tequila?
Do you want to call me
names, mock me endlessly?
- No.
- I'm trying to cheer you up.
Yeah? Well, stop it. It's
annoying. And it's not working.
I'm deep in the wilderness here.
Do you want the sparkle pager?
- That's not funny.
- You're sad. Actually sad.
I know it's the right thing
to do to give you the pager.
You're so sad,
you're not asking me.
I'm giving it to you. Shiny, shiny
pager with lots of shiny, shiny surgeries.
If I were the kind of person who
kissed people, I would kiss you.
I tried to change.
Turn over a new leaf.
- But the leaf isn't turning.
- You weren't ready to change.
And that's OK. Adele
wanted me to change, to retire.
Well, I'm still the chief, and this
weekend, I'm moving back home.
- Does Adele know that?
- She'll be fine. She was wrong.
- I was right. And now we're...
- Doing it like bunnies. I can't change.
I can't change. I can't change.
Be who you are. I am who I am.
- A man.
I have a way about me.
I'm a man who is who he is.
I have a right to be that man.
I'm not gonna say
anything. No judgment.
The man you are
slept with my wife.
And you, you've been
on my land for six months.
But I got no judgment.
- I'm gonna miss
living on the land.
- It is beautiful.
- Wanna buy it?
- You can't sell this land.
You have blueprints. This
is your living room window.
- The house that Derek built.
- Well, that's over.
- I'm getting a place in town.
- But you love this land.
This land and ferry
boats are who you are.
A man can change.
I'm selling the land.
Ferry boats... crash.
- Morning.
- Hey. All right.
Come on.
Can you take my cases this
morning? Check in on my post-ops?
- Not coming to work?
- I'm gonna hang with Rebecca.
So if you could cover
for me... Hey, take a bite.
Yeah, I'll cover for you.
- Alex, she's
not looking very good.
- She's fine.
Come on. Take a bite.
Dr. Bailey, I got an answer for you
from the chief about your schedule.
You're not spending
enough hours in the OR,
between clinic and
chief resident work.
I checked with the attendings and
nailed the chief down to a hard count.
You need to spend at least 15 to
20 more hours per week in surgery
in order to sit for your boards.
Should I tell the chief that's possible?
Just trying to use my power as
the chief's intern for good, so...
- Dr. Bailey?
- Hush. I'm trying
to see something.
When I'm trying to see something,
I can't do it if you ask me questions.
- What are you trying to see?
- Dr. Bailey, listen.
I am really worried about Ava.
I mean Rebecca. I mean Alex.
Well, Alex and Rebecca.
Who used to be called Ava...
Anyway, listen, she's crazy,
and I don't mean funny crazy. OK?
Bad crazy, OK?
Alex is home with her,
and he's all, "Take a bite."
It's weird and sad and...
I want to help, I
don't know what to do.
I need you to tell
me what to do.
- What do I do?
- She's trying to see something.
She doesn't need
you asking questions.
What are you trying to see?
The bigger picture.
♪ Hit the beat and take
it to the verse now ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
It's just you and me and Erica.
And we're grabbing you,
ripping off your clothes.
And then you're
naked. You're so hot.
And naked.
- And then Erica
starts kissing you.
- Hold on a minute.
Erica's kissing you like
you need to be kissed.
And then I pin your hands.
- Hold on.
- Above your head.
And then I watch as
she uses one finger...
Hold on a minute!
Oh. Oh.
OK, I'm sorry, 'cause
that was good for me.
That was really, really
good for me. Good boy.
But I have a big trauma
coming in downstairs,
so we have to do
this the fast way.
Every page goes in every set of
documents. Miss one, you're on scut.
These are the most
promising trial patients.
I don't want any mistakes.
- Hard-ass.
- Where were you?
- I had to stay with Cristina.
- That's so nice.
- Rebecca's at the house. I needed you.
- She's crazy.
We've had this discussion,
and decided it's not appropriate
- to call Izzie crazy. She's spirited.
- Spirited.
Yeah. Not me! I'm not
crazy. Rebecca's crazy.
Alex is pretending
she's not. It's...
- Hello.
- I was just helping
Meredith collate.
- I'm on my way
to check your patients.
- That's fine. Take your time.
- You seem cheerful.
- I'm gettin' my groove back.
I'm gettin' jiggy with it. I'm
gettin' down with the get down.
- Meredith gave me
the sparkle pager.
- What?
She needed it for her mojo.
- Ever think I needed it?
- You'd waste it.
I need it to get out
from under Hahn.
I won't have to
beg her for OR time
if I have the pager. She's not
gonna teach, I'll teach myself.
She's just gonna use it for
evil. I... I would use it to do good.
And besides, the pager
is sacred. Sacred sparkle.
You can't just give it
away. She can't do that.
- I think it's nontransferable.
- You don't make rules.
- But I am the chief's intern.
- You're the chief's bitch.
And you have no power.
Because the power... is in the pager.
That's the chief with something
important and powerful.
No need for pagers covered with glue
and glitter when you work for the chief.
- Rebecca.
- Me and my world-class
neurosurgeon
are gonna use a cutting-edge
technique to save a life.
So I don't have time
for crazy. Work it out.
Ooh, a trauma.
- What do we got?
- Not, "What do we got?"
- What do I got, I don't know.
- Sparkle pager rules.
- Whatever it is, it's mine now.
- What do we have?
- I don't know. Sparkle pager.
- No.
You can't sparkle pager
it. It's not her pager.
Yang, it's yours.
Stevens, cover the pit.
You volunteer to
oversee Karev's post-ops?
- Yes...
- Don't have time
for pettiness. Go.
- Hey, Callie.
- Hi. Hello, Erica.
- What's the matter?
- Nothing. Nothing.
- You look all hot and bothered.
- No. It's just,
there's a trauma, and it's
really big. That's all. It's big.
- It's a big trauma.
- You're acting weird.
- She uses one finger...
- Really big trauma.
Torres, it's like you never
seen a really big trauma before.
Oh, my.
Really big trauma.
So how you want to handle this?
I...
Uh...
Help me.
Really big trauma.
Please.
Help me.
- Look, we were
just joking around.
- Yeah, it was a dare.
You dared... him to lay in a vat
of cement at a construction site.
Hey, we never thought
he'd do it. It's Andy.
He never does anything.
- He doesn't have the guts.
- In the middle of the night,
you snuck into a
construction site
- and dared your friend...
- He's not our friend.
The four of us, we're friends.
But he's not really our friend.
OK, you dared him
to lie down in concrete.
Nobody made him do it. You're making
it sound like we did something wrong.
- How long?
- What?
How long did your not friend
lay in that vat of
cement unable to move
before you four geniuses,
you band of brothers,
future Mother Teresas, how
long did he lay in that cement
yelling that he couldn't move
before you called the police?
Yeah. That's what I thought.
The cytoplasmic viral
particles in the malignant cells
but not in the normal tissue.
No idea what you're
saying, but it sounds brilliant.
Boring but brilliant.
You wanted to spend
more time together.
I meant the movies
or ball games.
But a clinical trial
is just as good.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Combining the
Fr1904 and trichostatin
increases the expression
of the virus in the tumor.
Introduce them during the
M phase of the cell cycle?
- Exactly.
- Champagne with our name
written on it.
She understands
how brilliant you are.
OK, so Jeremy West
is patient number 12,
and patient 13 is Beth Monroe. Jeremy
is suffering from grand mal seizures,
Beth is paralyzed on the right
side. Who do you want to meet first?
Jeremy's surgery's today,
Beth's isn't until tomorrow.
- They're young.
- Yeah, which makes
them resilient.
- OK.
- OK. Bye.
Clinical trial, fun.
- So, what do you
want to do first?
- I don't know.
OK. Well, what do
you want us to do first?
- I don't know.
- All right, look,
we blasted him
out of the job site, but we
figured, don't blast too close.
This is a lot of concrete. Planning
on treating him, we need to start.
- So, what do you want to do?
- I don't know!
I'm sorry. Uh...
OK, I know I'm not doing my best
to instill a sense of
confidence in my abilities.
It's just that you are trapped
in what I'm guessing is
several tons of cement,
and I've never seen a
boy... How old are you?
- Nineteen.
- Then you're a man.
I've never seen a man trapped
in several tons of cement before.
But now that I have,
I'm gonna figure this out.
I'm gonna work with other
surgeons, we'll figure out a plan
and we're going to save you.
OK, I never, ever promise life,
but I'm promising this to
you. Do you understand?
- I do.
- OK.
I don't know much yet,
but the one thing I do know
is that the cement you're encased
in is slowly leeching the water
from your body, and you're gonna need
all the water you can get, so no crying.
You're a strong young
man. I know you can do this.
Good. Good.
OK, you're gonna live.
I'll make sure that you live.
Here you go.
- Hello.
- Dr. Grey, is this him?
- Him?
- She has a pet name for you.
- The Seattle Grace
Brain Butcher.
- Beth. I'm sorry.
- Oh, no,
that's fine. That's me.
- How do you do?
- Nice to meet you.
Pleasure.
Um, that hand's just
for show. So come on.
Tell me, how does this work?
You're going to inject a
live virus into her tumor?
Mm-hmm.
And that's safe?
The virus is still
in testing stages.
I've made adjustments
that destroy the tumor.
- Hey, tumor destroyers. I like that.
- Has this ever worked before?
- No.
- So I'm your lab rat.
- Beth.
- I'm just saying if this works,
my name will go down in the annals
of some book. That's kinda cool.
- Not if I beat you to it.
- Beth. This is
our other patient.
- Jeremy.
- You didn't call.
- Know each other?
- I thought you backed out.
As if I'd break our
pact? Come here.
They know each other.
- What is he doing here?
- His surgery is this afternoon.
I knew she didn't find this
clinical trial on her own.
Bizarre experimental
surgery, it had to be Jeremy.
They met when they were both
being treated at Mayo last year.
They went through chemo,
radiation, a support group.
- You don't want them
to be together?
- Look, we like Jeremy.
He's a good kid. I feel for him
that he's going
through this alone,
but we worry about Beth. She
thinks that she's in love with him.
We just don't want her getting so
attached to someone that might...
- Die.
- If something happens,
if he doesn't survive,
Beth won't want to live.
She's my only
child. She has to...
She has to want
to fight to stay alive.
- You paged?
- Oh, O'Malley.
There's a binder on occupational
medicine articles in my office.
Should be a toxicology section. See
if you can find anything on cement.
- Yes, sir.
- Let Shepherd or Grey know
- I need to see them.
- Will do.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
My God.
Why...? Wh...?
What is everybody doing
standing around here?
This is what your
guys told us to do.
And exactly where are my guys?
Work from the outside in! No more
time. This is what we have to do.
- I am right.
- Why is the patient in there
and all of you are in here?
Torres is worried about limbs.
Bailey about abdominal crush.
Dr. Sloan feels the burns
should take the first look,
Hahn feels the heart and
lung issues are gonna kill him
- before we get to any of this.
- In other words...
- No one can agree
on where to start.
- I know where to start.
Cement's contracting. I don't get
in, he could lose legs and right arm.
I'd like to see
him without a liver.
We'd prefer him to
suffer a painful death
as the alkaline continues
to burn through his skin?
You can't chip away. Once
his circulation opens up,
the built-up toxins will stop his
heart, not to mention rhabdomyolosis.
- Treat with dialysis.
- Let us work.
- I found an article,
doesn't say a lot.
- Put in a Swan-Ganz.
- Usually at the bottom of a river.
- - You are so wrong.
- I'm so wrong?
- You are. Wrong.
- You two working
together on this?
- Everybody stand down!
We are fighting the clock. It took
one hour for the kids to call 911.
Three hours for search and rescue
to get this guy cut out of the cement.
Less than four to six hours
to get him out of cement
and into the OR before he is dead.
We are fighting one hell of a clock.
Every minute counts. We
work as a team, or that man dies.
- Do you understand?
- Yes, sir. Of course.
Where do you want me, chief?
Find Grey and be
her intern for the day.
I have too many
bodies in the room.
Patient's name?
Andrew Langston.
OK, let's go save his life.
Hey.
You intimidate me a little. I mean,
you're not an intimidating person,
but the legend of
Meredith and Derek.
It's... intimidating.
- No legend.
- He's selling his land
because of you.
- There's a legend.
- Derek's selling his land?
He doesn't say
it's because of you.
He was making plans to build a house
when you were together, and now...
I'm... I'm not trying to...
I just really like him.
And you intimidate me.
There's no legend.
OK.
Izzie had a question
about some post-ops.
- What'd I miss?
- What?
The movie. What'd I miss?
- Hey. Hey.
- I'm sorry.
Don't be sorry.
I think...
I wet my pants.
Oh.
Oh, that's, uh... that's OK.
That's... that's OK.
I'll do better. I promise.
Don't worry about
it. You're doing fine.
Come on.
I forgot to tell you.
Guess who called me.
Carrie from our support
group. She didn't sound so good.
Have you talked to her lately?
- No, she...
- Oh, God.
Her husband said they
tried radiation one last time.
He said it was bad.
The last day, she didn't even
recognize him. And the pain.
She was screaming
and begging them to...
He said it was bad.
Yeah.
Hey.
At least we don't have to
worry about that. You know?
This surgery will work. OK?
And if it doesn't, at
least we'll die quick.
Yeah, we'll die super-fast
and without pain.
Yes.
Dr. Grey, I thought we talked
about changing Beth's room.
It isn't sunny enough in here.
The room is fine, and it's
right down the hall from Jeremy.
I'd like to move her
as soon as possible.
Mrs. Monroe, I checked.
There aren't any beds available.
Not in a private room.
Mom, why don't you go find Dad?
I can wait for him here.
Mom, why don't you go find Dad so I
can kiss Jeremy without you watching?
- It's time Jeremy went back...
- I don't understand wh...
Nurse!
I need a nurse. He's seizing!
All right.
Let's run a second set
of labs before surgery.
How's Beth? Was she...
was she scared? Or...
She's fine.
Chief wants you or Shepherd.
He says it's important.
- I'll go.
- He put me on you.
- What can I do? How can I help?
- You can run labs for me.
- Labs, that's it?
- Yeah. Thanks.
Hi.
- What's that?
- - Pouring vinegar on your flesh
to minimize burns inside your
skin caused by the cement.
I'm burning from the inside out?
I'm dying. I'm dying, aren't I?
Andrew, that word's
not allowed anymore.
I'm banning that word
from your vocabulary.
Can you move your fingers?
That's very good.
I'm not usually this dumb.
Most people think
I'm pretty smart.
I make the dean's list. I tutor.
I'm not... I'm not usually
the guy who's dumb enough
to jump into a tub
of cement for a girl.
Wait, not the girl
you came in with?
- You did this for her?
- Lola.
The guys dared me.
She was watching.
And I...
And now not only is
she totally unimpressed,
but after I'm gone,
she'll remember me as the
idiot who was dumb enough
to jump into a tub of cement.
People will write
stories about my idiocy
and forward them
to their friends.
I'm gonna die as a
bad e-mail forward.
Hey. We all mess up.
I'm the guy who died in a block
of cement trying to impress a girl.
I'm like Han Solo.
In Star Wars?
He was encased in carbonite?
You wanted to see me?
I got a call from the IRB.
The national board that
oversees and reviews clinical trials.
Your clinical trial.
You've had 11 deaths. They're
giving you one last patient.
You get it today under the
wire and hope for the best.
At midnight, if you lose him,
they're gonna shut you down, period.
One last patient.
- You're angry at him. The chief.
- But why?
- Why am I angry at him?
- Because you have
opened up your past.
It's like you're reliving it all
now. You're angry with him.
You're angry with your mother.
You're angry with yourself.
Chief went back to his wife.
My mother didn't want to live.
He did what he had to do.
She did what she had to do.
- Your mother
didn't wanna kill herself.
- No, she did.
- How can you be sure?
- How can you be? You weren't there.
The answer is
right in front of you.
Think about it.
- The IRB is saying I failed?
- You haven't.
I failed. I'll sign the
discharge order for Beth.
You can't. This is her last
shot. You have until midnight.
- Jeremy's today.
- Move Jeremy's surgery up.
Beth's this afternoon. Fit
them in before midnight.
- If I get the dosage right.
- You're so close. You haven't failed.
But are we going too far
here? These are people's lives.
- Is my ego too big here?
- Your ego is just
the right size.
We can do this.
Two patients.
Bends the rules
without breaking 'em.
- You'll clear it
with the chief?
- Yeah.
- Jeremy's going
into surgery soon?
- In a couple of hours.
- How is he?
- Oh, he's stable.
Yeah, he's actually
better than stable.
He called me the angel of death.
He's good then.
- Can I see him?
- Honey, no.
I'll just be gone a few minutes.
Can you get me a wheelchair?
If you're having surgery today,
you need to rest. You don't...
We just want to spend
some time with you. That's all.
Please.
- We're the last two.
- What?
From our support group.
Jeremy and I are
the last two still alive.
Hey. Have you seen Cristina?
I've done everything I'm supposed
to. She sees me doing nothing,
- not in the mood
to get yelled at.
- With cement boy.
- Cement boy?
- Don't bother. Don't need interns.
They don't want interns there.
Interns are in the way!
I'm not complaining.
Two minutes of complaining between
me and you. No one has to know.
I have all this
power! Supposedly.
I supposedly am imbued with
power of being the chief's intern.
But there's a cement
boy, and I'm stuck in here,
running labs, researching
effects of cement on the body
in the vain hopes somebody
asks me a question.
I'm not in with the cement boy because,
even though I have all this power,
I can't use it because
it's not real power.
- It's fake power?
- Fake power.
I can go into the chief's
office whenever I want.
You know what he
has in there? Files.
Confidential on every
resident in this hospital.
And I'm just allowed
in, and he's not worried
because he knows and I know
that I don't have
any real power.
I don't have the
power to look at them!
Make you feel
better if you could?
You know what would
make me feel better?
If I feel like there was a reason
for this, that there was a point.
Oh, God. My poor, poor parents.
How would they face
anyone at the funeral?
OK, Andrew, you're gonna
make a lot of mistakes in your life,
but mistakes are...
They're pieces.
Like this is a foolish piece,
but, you know,
it's just a piece.
Be proud of the whole picture.
The whole picture defines
you, not just this one piece.
I'm a loser. I'm a loser.
- Come on. Andrew.
- I'm a loser.
Andrew. Hey, listen to
me. Han Solo is not a loser.
Han Solo got encased in carbonite,
and... and that was a big mess.
Not what he's remembered
for. He's remembered as the guy
who made the Kessel
run in less than 12 parsecs,
and who braved temperatures
of the ice planet Hoth
in order to save someone he cared
about from the big, ugly wampa.
He is remembered as the
guy who swooped down,
blasted Darth Vader out of the
sky so that Luke could use the Force
and destroy the damn Death Star, OK?
Princess Leia saved him from the carbonite.
And they fell in love and
they saved the universe
and had twin Jedi babies that
went on to save the universe again.
Now, that's the whole picture.
The carbonite, it
was just a piece, OK?
So I like science-fiction.
Got a problem?
- No.
- It's great.
Do what you doing.
I got Jeremy's labs back.
Good to go for surgery.
- Chief sign off on that?
- Yeah.
Where are you going?
Get a wheelchair.
What are you doing?
M-My mom went to
go call my grandma,
and my dad went
to the cafeteria.
There wasn't a
wheelchair in my room.
I just want to see
Jeremy. Please.
I don't want the seizure to be
the last time I see him. Please.
- I just need to see him.
- OK, let's go.
Am I going to get to
be alone with Jeremy?
I mean, "alone" alone?
- Alone?
- We've never done it,
either of us.
We've been waiting until we
both were tumor free, but surgery...
Anything could happen.
We can do it, right?
It won't kill us or anything?
No, no.
- No, it won't kill you.
- I mean, you've done it, right?
- With each other?
- I've... He's done...
He's done it, and
I've done it, yeah.
What's it like? Is it magical?
- Yes.
- It can be.
With the right person.
I'm gonna go get you some
clothes. You got shampoo in there?
I don't understand.
I was pregnant.
I know I was.
- It's OK.
- I don't...
It's OK. You just got
confused. That's all.
You just got confused, OK?
OK.
♪ I was a little girl
alone in my little world ♪
♪ Who dreamed of
a little home for me ♪
♪ I played pretend
between the trees ♪
♪ And fed my houseguests
bark and leaves ♪
♪ And laughed in my
pretty bed of green ♪
♪ I had a dream ♪
♪ That I could fly ♪
♪ From the highest swing ♪
♪ I had a dream ♪
I have never in my life gotten a
patient laid, much less two patients.
- It's really sweet.
- We're pimps.
Yentas.
- They're so in love.
- Oh, yeah.
It's all new and
fresh and exciting.
I've never been a fan of new.
I like to know the person, their
bodies, what makes them moan.
Something happen?
Beth isn't in her room.
Oh, well, that's because I
had my intern take her down
- for a pre-op MRI.
- Thank God.
I was afraid she was
lying somewhere in pain.
No, she's not in any pain.
We should go to the conference
room. There's paperwork
- you haven't filled out.
- Thank you.
You bet.
I'll be here, doing my thing.
It's at 20 centimeters.
Inflate the balloon.
- I am.
- So then inflate it more.
- Yes, Dr. Hahn.
- They loosen another piece,
this leg swells even
more. His pressure is 18.
Does he have a pulse with that?
I always did enjoy a
good game of Twister.
- It's finished. I'm in.
- Yang, do not sew
that in. Hold it.
I will check your
work when I'm done.
- Chief, I've gotta
do a fasciotomy.
- What? A what?
Relieve the pressure in your
leg or you could lose the limb.
Don't worry. You
probably won't feel a thing.
Oh, God.
Hey, Dr. Stevens.
What's going down?
Cristina sparkle paging
me out of cement boy.
Alex not answering the phone.
Alex and his insane girlfriend.
Alex! Alex! I'm checking
in. Call me back.
- God! The things we do
for the people we love.
- Exactly. It's...
How'd it go?
- Derek.
- What?
How'd it go?
It was, um...
It was amazing. Thank you.
We have to take Jeremy
down to the OR now.
OK.
- OK.
- So I... I'll see you after?
- Definitely.
I don't think, um...
I'm not sure you'll be conscious,
uh, before we take Beth, so...
So... so I'll see you
after your surgery.
All right. See you after.
- Wait, Jer. Wait.
- Yeah.
- What if you die?
- I won't.
- What if I die?
- You won't.
OK, but...
You changed my
life, Jeremy West.
You made it better, you
made it brighter, full of joy.
- And if I die...
- Don't you dare die.
OK?
We're not finished yet.
I'm not finished loving you.
OK, go ahead. Go ahead.
Get your head chopped open.
I'm right behind you.
Do not kill him.
- You nervous?
- I have my ego to keep me warm.
- Can't you feel it?
- What?
The majesty of lifesaving.
When did you become an optimist?
Selling your land.
Trying to move forward.
So am I.
- Who's there?
- George O'Malley.
- I was paged to the supply closet.
- - Are you alone?
Lexie?
Remember how I
said I wasn't a thief?
- I think maybe I am.
- Alexandra Caroline Grey!
I couldn't help it. I had to know.
And then once I knew, I knew.
Get these back to the
chief's office right now.
I tried to stop reading, but I
couldn't. I have photographic memory,
which is how I got
through Harvard Med.
I read all files. Information is
burned into my brain. I read yours.
- No, I don't wanna know.
- You failed the intern exam
by one point. One point.
The OR is booked
and standing by.
Dr. Bailey, what is it?
Something...
Something... we're missing.
We're forgetting something.
Gangrene, compartment
syndrome, compression,
fluid balance,
electrolytes. What is it?
What is it? Gangrene,
compartment syndrome, compression,
fluids, electrolytes. Gangrene,
compartment syndrome,
compression,
fluids, electrolytes.
Gangrene, compartment
syndrome, compression, fluids, elec...
Bladder. His bladder.
We've been hydrating
him for over four hours now.
If we don't get a
catheter in him quick...
His bladder's gonna explode.
Can I have mayo?
See? You have an
appetite. That's a good sign.
- Hey.
- Hey, Iz. I'll be right back.
- What's going on?
- How's Rebecca?
She's fine. What do you need?
- Did she eat? Call her husband?
- Iz.
Don't get mad because I care.
Not caring. Butting in.
- I'm butting in because I care.
- Know how you care?
By covering me at work, not
calling me every hour and asking...
- Hang on. Rebecca?
- Alex?
Rebecca?
Alex?
Time of death, 11:47.
♪ What if we stop
having a ball? ♪
Rebecca!
♪ What if the paint
chips from the wall? ♪
♪ What if there's always
cups in the sink? ♪
You don't have to say
any... thing. Don't say it.
Alex? Are you still there? Alex?
- I'm so sorry.
- Don't...
Don't say anything.
OK? Don't say anything.
Don't say anything!
Don't you say anything
to me! Don't say anything!
Don't say anything! Don't say
anything! Don't say anything!
♪ Oh, oh, I am giving up ♪