Previously on Grey's Anatomy:
I had a bad night, I cried. I'm
over it. You need to get over it.
I'm retaking my intern test.
You and I are more
than just roommates.
We're friends. You're
probably one of my best friends.
Best friend.
You're the only
woman I've ever kissed.
- You're freaking out, too?
- A lot of therapy time.
Derek's moved in. We've taken
it to the next level. I am happy.
In 6500 BC, some guy
looked at his sick friend
and said, "I have an idea.
Why don't I drill a hole in your
skull? It'll make you feel better."
Thus surgery was born.
- Hey.
- Uh...
- Where's Mer?
- She's not here.
Oh!
So you're just in
there by yourself?
I'm not... I'm waiting for her.
- Love the outfit.
- What do you want?
I need cash. I ordered a pizza
and Alex owes me 20 bucks,
but he's not speaking to
me because I saw him crying
over his crazy girlfriend,
and there was a minute, a week
ago, I thought he'd be a human being,
- and now he won't
open the door.
- Run into the bathroom.
Just go. Go!
Karev! Give me a 20.
Thank you.
That was so awesome. Very cool.
Not that I didn't think you
were cool before, but I did not.
I just thought you were
all hair and, you know...
Now cool. You want
to share some pizza?
It takes a certain
brand of crazy
to come up with an idea like
drilling into somebody's skull,
but surgeons have always
been a confident bunch.
Your clothes, your room.
The living room will not be a
dumping ground like the old place.
Did you not hear her?
OK. She kind of scares me.
'Cause she's scary. Callie
needs a new best friend.
- Not bad, right?
- It's great.
We usually know what we're doing.
When we don't, we act like we do.
We walk boldly into
undiscovered country, plant a flag,
start ordering people around.
- Want to go on a date with me?
- It's invigorating
and terrifying.
Like a date date?
Yeah, restaurant,
candlelight, bottle of wine.
At the end of the night I
try to take your clothes off.
OK. That would be a date.
- Hey.
- You're...
- Naked and waiting
for you.
You keep a diary? Have I not known,
all this time, that you keep a diary?
- No. I... I don't...
- Aw!
Don't be shy. I think it's cute.
- It's not mine.
- I won't read it.
- Whose is it?
- Your mother's.
It was in a big box full of old issues of
The New England Journal of Medicine.
- Did you read it?
- No.
I brought it up here for you.
Why were you going
through her things?
Trying to find
space for my clothes.
Your closet is full.
I have to shower. I've been
hauling Cristina's boxes.
- You haven't read any?
- No. What if I'm in it?
I don't want to hear
what she thought of me.
- What's worse,
if you're in it or not?
- I don't know!
I mean, see, why is he in the
study rooting around in closets
trying to dig up
my mother's ghost?
I think 'cause you invited him.
Apparently some people
thought I was kidding last week
when I announced nobody was going
to hang out on their favorite specialty.
I wasn't. Junior
residents don't specialize,
so all the requests to
send you back to that place
where your true heart
lives can end now.
Dr. Bailey makes
the assignments.
Do not, and I repeat,
do not harangue her.
O'Malley, I made a call.
They don't have your score
yet. If I knew, I would tell you.
Hey.
You passed. We're gonna go to Joe's
tonight, and we're gonna celebrate.
I'm gonna buy you a beer
and all the peanuts you can eat.
What if I didn't pass?
Well, then I'm still
buying you a beer.
Beer for losers.
Grey, you're on
cardio with Hahn today.
- But...
- Stevens and Karev, pit.
- Come on!
- Chief wants us
to have a change.
That's not a change. I'm
always stuck in the pit with Alex.
When the Chief said, "Don't harangue
Dr. Bailey," what do you think he meant?
- Yang, clinic.
- What? No. No!
No, wait. The clinic is
mine. I say how it's staffed.
- She'll ruin it.
- I'll ruin it.
- Just let me do it.
- You will not. You will do what I say.
Since Yang couldn't be bothered to
show up at the clinic since it opened,
think of it as a new
frontier in her training.
Sorry.
You're not sorry. You're
psyched you got Hahn.
- If not, you should be.
- She's terrifying.
You give her unrealistic expectations
as to what a resident should be.
Stay on top of the material. Don't
get warm and fuzzy. She hates that.
Any questions, come and ask me.
I'll be in the clinic putting
Band-Aids on whiners
who don't have the balls to get
real injuries. Let's go. Come on.
Here you go.
I didn't read the diary. I just
found it and put it on the table.
I would've read it.
Every time I
actually do something
to move into the
house, she freaks out.
What are you gonna
do with the trailer?
- No.
- Come on.
Plus, there's a real possibility,
she kicks me out in a week.
I'm not letting
go of the trailer.
Sutures, fecal impaction
and more sutures.
- She'll do it.
- What do you mean
"She'll do it?"
You're good at boring, stupid
crap. You're like a specialist.
Hi, I'm Dr. Stevens. Looks
like you need some stitches.
- What happened?
- I have a cut.
- How'd you get it?
- I threw a remote
at him, OK?
All he can do is watch television
or fall asleep like a dead person.
- Honey.
- Don't "honey" me. I'm divorcing you.
Soon as you stop bleeding from
your head we're going to a lawyer.
- Ever been to Europe?
- Nope. Someday.
Don't wait until you're retired. Can't
be bothered to look out the window.
Six-month trip across the world.
I've been waiting for it for 15 years.
He slept through the whole thing.
- Marianne.
- Six continents.
I worked for 30
years. I was very tired.
Well, I'm tired, too, of
being married to somebody
with no interest in the
world, so everybody's tired.
I'm going to get coffee. I
assume this'll take forever?
Probably.
Your mouth always do that,
move to the side like that?
Like what?
- Mind if I run some tests?
- Whatever you want.
Great.
I may be wrong, but I think
Mr. Grandy has a neuro thing going on.
Get him stitched
up then up for a CT.
OK.
Give me that. Give it!
Mr. Grandy. I'm Dr. Karev, and I
will be taking you up for your CT today.
Duncan Paley, eight, recently
diagnosed with aortic valve disease
from infectious endocarditis,
scheduled for a Ross procedure.
- There's a note from his pediatrician.
- - Duncan!
- Duncan, get back here!
- Duncan!
- Go!
- Sure.
- Sorry. Duncan.
- Duncan! Duncan,
come back here.
- Duncan, you get down
from there.
- Don't touch the fire alarm.
I'm not having the surgery. No!
- Come on, get down.
- I'm not doing it!
- One, two, three...
- No!
I think this is all going
to be OK if we just...
Will you promise me no surgery?
Promise me no surgery.
I... We... We
can't really do that.
Evacuate. Evacuate.
Evacuate. This is an emergency.
Do we have this kid under control,
or do I have to call Social Services?
- He won't do anything
like that again.
- He better not.
The ceiling fell last week. I don't
need a series of false alarms.
This place looks
ridiculous enough.
- Keep the ankle-biter
under control.
- I'll sedate him if I have to.
Good. Bone up on your
pulmonary autografts.
I don't want to spend the day bathed
in your ignorance and incompetence.
- She hates me.
- What do you mean
"we'll sedate him?"
I was trying not to
be warm and fuzzy.
I don't mean sedate
him, I mean baby-sit him.
It's your last day as an intern. Think
of how happy you'll be to move on.
Hey.
I'm gonna be in
the OR until 7:00.
Is 8:00 too late for dinner?
No, but if you need to
reschedule or cancel.
Come on, are you kidding? I
made a reservation at Canto.
I even gamed out an outfit.
We are doing this.
So Hahn is doing a Ross
procedure, and she thinks I'm a moron.
It's called a pulmonary autograft.
She likes the technical names, OK?
Tell her you're excited to watch
her harvest a pulmonary valve
using her septal
sparing technique.
Cut too much of the septal muscle, the
patient won't be able to come off pump.
- None of that is in the book.
- The key to the case.
You'll sound like you've
been around the block.
I can't believe I'm
giving you my best stuff.
- Mwah!
- You don't deserve it.
Dr. Yang, Mrs. Borsokowski
needs your loving attention.
Redness, itching, inflammation:
A rash. You're giving me a rash.
No! She's the mean
one! I don't want her.
OK.
- All right, what do we got?
- Take a look.
Thing's bigger than a baseball.
Oh, wow, it's right
behind his eyes.
This'll be fun. Page Stevens.
She left the guy with me.
- She gave you the case?
- Yeah, well, Izzie
felt bad for me.
Figured this would cheer me up.
In that case you'll help
me pull this thing out.
Hey, Duncan.
We're gonna put an IV in your arm
real quick, then you can go on playing.
- What is it?
- A little tube
we put in your arm.
No. No, it's gonna hurt.
- Come on,
it's not gonna hurt.
- It's gonna hurt.
It's a needle, it's gonna hurt. But
it's only for, what, three seconds?
- I don't believe you.
- You don't believe me?
Do you want me to
prove it to you? I'll prove it.
I'll have Dr. Grey
put one in me.
This is a tourniquet.
And you wrap it around your
arm so that your vein pops out.
See? Like that.
So now, the needle.
That's the part
that's gonna hurt.
That goes in, and that's in...
Hurting. That
hurts, it hurts, and...
It doesn't hurt anymore.
Now that stuff, it goes
into here. Doesn't hurt at all.
OK, I'll do it.
- OK. I'll go get
another IV kit.
- OK.
Wow. You're really good at this.
Oh, I was an airplane
guy too when I was his age.
Us airplane guys, we like
to know how things work.
I'm sorry about the alarm.
I know.
Move!
They have the
nerve to be indignant
about how they're not allowed
to be on their specialties.
They don't have specialties. They should
be grateful they're allowed in the...
Are you listening to me?
I'm going on a date with Erica
Hahn and, uh... that's awkward
'cause, uh... she's a colleague
and because she's an attending,
and because she's a she.
And, uh, there's been
kissing, but, uh... no touching,
and what if I'm not into
it? What if I'm horrible
at all that stuff
south... of the border?
'Cause I've never been
south of the border...
with a female.
I mean, I've never even been
over the northern mountains,
you know what I'm sayin'?
We're gonna pretend
this didn't happen.
Mr. Grandy?
- What are you doing in here?
- They admitted me.
My new doctor, Dr. Karev, said
I have a huge tumor in my head.
Have you seen my wife?
Your new doctor?
Somebody page me?
I have a patient with
tenderness and erythema
from her upper
chest to her left arm.
She needs irrigation
and debridement.
She said you may have
to amputate my arm.
It's a simple rash. It's
probably dermatitis.
But look how the skin is
denuded. Could be surgical, right?
It's a rash. Go to Derm,
get a tube of CeraVe cream.
Don't ever page me to
hustle a surgery again.
It was supposed to be
done yesterday. Done!
So exactly why did
I walk into my OR
and still see a massive, gaping hole
where the ceiling was supposed to be?
You see Karev, get an 18-gauge
needle and shove it in his throat.
I have cultivated a look that says I'm
not interested in personal problems.
Can you morons
not read that look,
or have I lost the hang of it?
People are telling me problems!
I don't give a crap about your
crushing workload or love life
or your carpal tunnel syndrome.
I care about is Mrs. Caruchi, a
92-year-old woman no one can find!
Hi.
I'm Dr. Pepman. Can I help you?
Uh, yeah, um...
Where can I get
some CeraVe cream?
Um, our nurses look
like they're tied up.
If you don't mind waiting
I can get it for you myself.
- Water with raspberries
while you wait?
- Uh, sure.
Hi, Chris.
Oh. Don't mind Chris.
He's our massage therapist.
You're... a what?
Our hands do such delicate work.
It's important they stay healthy.
We have Chris on staff to work on
us when we have a spare moment.
Every attending gets their
hands massaged at work?
Oh, no. The dermatology
attendings have another therapist.
Chris just works
on the residents.
- You're a resident?
- First year, and loving it.
So I'll make an incision ear
to ear and peel down the face.
I'll crack open his forehead,
pull the tumor right out.
Keep an eye on the optic nerve.
Somebody twitches and this guy's blind.
Which one of your
roommates will be assisting?
- Karev.
- Oh, great.
Dr. Shepherd, I want back
on this case. This is my patient.
- Alex stole him from me...
- Dr. Stevens, in this hospital
I'm not your roommate. I don't
give a crap about your problems.
I have a resident. I
don't need another.
The patient's in his room, if
you want to go over procedure.
- Son of a bitch.
- Go cry to somebody
who cares.
This is my case. It isn't fair.
Surgery's like the Wild West.
You didn't get your claim
in Montana from the bank,
you got it 'cause you put a fence and
shot the ass off anyone who walked by.
Karev's a cowboy. You're not.
We're gonna transect the great
arteries at the sinotubular ridge,
use the autograft to replace the aortic
root, then attach a pulmonary homograft.
You going to use septal sparing
technique for the pulmonary autograft?
Yes. Why do you ask?
If we cut too much of the septal muscle
we can't take the patient off the pump?
Right.
Always wanted to see a
septal sparing technique.
Know how to reanastomose the
coronary arteries back to the aorta?
I do.
I'll let you sew part of it in.
You'll be in there, might
as well get your hands dirty.
Great. Thanks, Dr. Hahn.
You're going to hell
'cause you're a liar.
- Was it obvious?
- Unfortunately, no.
♪ My love, let me go again ♪
♪ Right back, back
to the top of the slide ♪
♪ Down, sad clown ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ My clown, let me love you... ♪
What?
- What happened?
- Look.
You paged me 911.
I'm in the middle of studying
for Hahn's pulmonary autograft...
They're residents.
That one baked a seven-layer cake
for that one's birthday, from scratch.
And that one, that one's girlfriend
is taking him skiing this weekend.
Oh, this one's the best.
OK, this one gets to
leave to go get a facial.
And she told her attending.
And her attending was happy
'cause they have to have
facials. They're dermatologists.
- I mean, look... look...
- Oh, my God.
The hospital has hired
someone to rub them, full-time.
I bet their boyfriends don't go digging
around in their closets without asking.
Never.
I told Hahn I knew how to do a
coronary artery reanastomosis.
- You don't.
- I know.
I looked it up, the kid's
eight. He's got tiny arteries.
Know what? Snag me some of
those grapes there, I'll teach you.
And then find Dr. Daisy Pepman.
Ask her for a suture kit
and a 7-0 polypropylene.
- Dr. Daisy Pepman?
- She's a resident.
She pours fruity drinks.
She has time for that kind of
thing. And I like saying her name.
So was that hyphenated or
did her parents name her...?
No... No mocking.
There is no mocking in
Derm. Only warmth and light.
Are you all right, Mrs. Paley?
You want to know
what Duncan's doing?
Packing to leave,
and I can't stop him.
I suck at this.
I'm tired and I'm fried because I lie
awake at night listening to him breathe
because I'm afraid his heart's
gonna stop, and he's gonna die,
and I'll have been sleeping.
I don't know how to do this.
No one knows how to be the
mom of a kid with heart failure.
Nobody teaches that.
And you have a really
smart kid, you know that.
We just need to up
our game a little bit.
- Can I try?
- Go for it.
- A baseball?
- Which is why you were
so lethargic.
Why I slept through
most of our trip, perhaps.
Not because I am
boring and uninterested
- in the cultures of the world.
- How was I supposed to know?
You were supposed to give
me the benefit of the doubt,
not throw electronics at me.
Mr. Grandy, this is a massive tumor
in an area that's very hard to reach.
You're gonna want to talk
about this with your wife.
- I'm sure she's fine
with the risks.
- Arnie.
I'm going through with
it. I got nothing left to lose.
See you in the OR.
Dr. Shepherd,
that is my patient.
I'm sure you can
use another resident...
I am not the traffic
cop on the playground.
It's the Wild West and you're the
sheriff. Can't you be the sheriff?
I'll think of you when we
crack his forehead open.
I'm not letting you do this
to me. Do not walk away.
Give me back my surgery
or I'll shoot your ass off!
He stole a very big surgery.
I'll pick it up.
- What'd you do
with the diary?
- It's in my locker.
Do you want me
to screen it for you?
- Magic Marker out
all the scary parts.
- No. No one's reading it.
OK, no. Don't. Here...
Don't pull too hard.
You're stretching the skin.
Alex stole my patient with a
grapefruit growing behind his eyes.
Your boyfriend
couldn't give a crap.
He actually said the
words, "I don't give a crap."
See that guy there,
OK? He's a resident.
He's dragging 'cause he got too much
sleep last night. Uh-huh. Too much.
- What?
- Like watching
a living freak show.
I don't talk about sex.
Please, let's just pretend I
never said even a single word.
I don't talk about sex with
anyone ever, not any kind of sex.
- Bailey, I am begging you...
- Uh!
The vajayjay is
undiscovered country.
It is the motherland.
You've never traveled there, you
don't know its customs and ways.
Now me, I've always
wanted to go to Africa.
But, if I go, I'm gonna have
to learn a few things first.
I'm going to have to prepare.
I'll need shots.
Bring my own syringes in
case something goes wrong.
And I'll want to know how
to get to the embassy...
OK, now you've lost me.
Just talk about it.
Not with me, with the other one.
Just talk about the
rules, the expectations,
figure out how to
gracefully demur
if you find you don't
like... the local cuisine.
In Ethiopia, they eat stew
off of spongy sour bread.
That's not for everyone.
♪ Your head up high,
like you think I do ♪
♪ Doo-doo-doo
doo-doo doo-doo-doo ♪
♪ Sometimes I feel so confused ♪
♪ I'm under the illusion... ♪
- Mer, I need you!
- Shh!
- Harshing the vibe.
- What are you doing?
Cristina found this magical
world where doctors are happy
and patients are pleasant, and no
one is screaming or stealing surgeries.
Everyone just rubs
each other all day long.
You all want to be dermatologists?
They apply lotion for a living.
Yeah. That's the point.
Come here, come here.
They're empty inside,
completely devoid of blood lust.
They don't need to fight for anything.
They don't want to cut anyone open.
They just... love lotion.
Do you know how much easier our
life would be if we could just love lotion?
How do you think
they got that way?
Their mothers didn't leave
diaries around for them to read.
Sloan told me today to stake
my claim in the Wild Wild West,
so I went all cowboy on Alex's
ass and I still don't have my surgery.
These women, they do
not have to stake a claim.
OK. You all need
to snap out of it.
Izzie, in the Wild Wild West
there is always a woman in the
saloon and nobody messes with her,
- even though
they all have guns.
- She's a prostitute.
The woman in the
saloon is a whore, George.
No. She just has other skills she
uses to make her way in the world.
So just use what you got.
Mer, I'm gonna take this,
and I need you to help me sell
an idea to Hahn and the Chief.
Cristina? You're coming, too.
Cristina!
How are you doing, Mr. Grandy?
Well...
I've got a tumor that's been
compared to a baseball, a grapefruit,
and an alien living
inside my head,
and... my wife, who
was ready to divorce me
even before she knew
that I was damaged goods,
she won't even look at me.
I'm sure she's just freaked out
about the tumor. It happens a lot.
What if it isn't just the tumor?
I mean, what if she's figured
out that she just doesn't like me?
No. You're a really
likeable guy, I can tell.
You're a nice girl.
Is... Is your new doctor
as nice as me? Dr. Karev?
He's all right.
That's good. Yeah.
He was having some
personal problems, depression.
He's been a little
off his game, but...
"Off his game?"
Sounds like he's bouncing
back. You'll be fine.
Wait. I don't want someone
who's "Off his game."
Can I get you back?
Oh, gee. Um, well...
Well, you could
talk to Dr. Shepherd,
tell him you don't want Dr. Karev
on your case, then I'm all yours.
- What happened?
- She said she was
feeling faint.
I thought she was pissed
about waiting for her cream.
- Her pulse ox is 90?
- The oxygen's not helping.
Get her to the ER.
- Why didn't you
move her to the ER?
- I don't know what to do.
- You've been standing here?
- I paged you. Where've you been?
OK. Aggressive fluids,
support care, steroids...
- Give her 16 of dexamethasone.
- Right away.
Hurry! Come on!
BP's going back up.
OK, um...
Call Dr. Bailey and tell her the
patient needs plasmapheresis
and a skin biopsy, stat.
- You stole my surgery.
- It's my surgery.
Using me as a doormat is one thing,
screwing with my career is another.
I have been wiping your snot and
covering your ass for weeks now,
and all you've done is abuse me.
For a little while
you get to do that
because you're heartbroken and pathetic,
and I'm a good friend, but it ends.
Get your own surgeries,
wipe your own snot.
- Dr. Shepherd,
that's my surgery.
- The patient made the request.
Nothing I can do.
Sixty percent of her
skin sloughed off.
I'm surprised she didn't
crash when she got out of bed.
Dr. Sloan didn't catch it when
he was down for a consult?
He may have been distracted by the fact
I told him it was necrotizing fasciitis.
- That'd do it.
- Can I do the biopsy?
Sure. I didn't know you had
a big interest in dermatology.
No... I don't. Just
the surgical part.
That's all right. It's
good. Branch out.
Dr. Bailey, I'm not
interested in Derm...
atology.
We're doing a bicoronal
incision. Expect a lot of bleeding.
Once I get going it'll all
happen fast, so stay with me.
Stevens, grab a Bovie.
All right. Here we go.
You are not bringing an
8-year-old child into the OR.
He's scared, doesn't know what's gonna
happen. No way for him to imagine it.
Letting the boy see a
bloody OR isn't gonna help.
Dr. Hahn has a thorascopic
lung resection in an hour.
- Three tiny incisions,
no blood.
- What's that gonna do?
It shows him the room, the instruments,
someone under anesthesia, still alive.
Pinning him down
and doping him up is...
It's gonna be
traumatic for him, and...
Showing him how it
works is such an easy fix.
- You can't see, can you?
- Nope.
I don't want to go in there.
Scared?
Well, there's not gonna be any
blood, nothing gross, nothing scary.
Just three tiny cuts that are so
small you can barely see 'em.
♪ And so right here I stay ♪
The first time that I went in
there, that room, I was scared.
But that room is the most
magical room in the world.
Only the finest doctors
get to go in there.
A lot of the great ones are not even
allowed to touch anything, just watch.
I'm pretty good, so
I'm still a watcher.
The people that work
in there, they're the best.
The very best.
It's the safest place you'll
ever be in in your entire life.
♪ So I crawl
underneath my blanket ♪
♪ Where I can hide away ♪
♪ I know I can't take it ♪
Where'd that guy's face go?
- You lost, O'Malley?
- Sorry!
No, wait! I want to see! I want to
see the guy with no face! Stop! Stop!
Promise not to mention this to anyone,
I'll give you what you want for life.
- OK?
- OK.
Good afternoon, Duncan.
Come on in and take a look.
♪ 'Cause I see now ♪
♪ It's just one of those days ♪
I want to go back
to the other one.
We're not talking
about the other one.
- This one's boring.
- Well, yours will be
boring too.
- Do I get the big lights?
- Yeah. You get
all the big lights.
- Where's the suctioner?
- Right over there.
Can I feel it? I just
want to feel it once.
Move over first.
Can I touch the scalpel?
- You just need to lie down.
- I just want to see everything.
- Look here. See this?
- Yeah.
It's a video camera. You'll be able to
watch the whole thing when it's over.
- Start shooting right now.
- Lie down.
See you after surgery.
OK, don't squeeze too hard.
The teeth on the
forceps can leave holes.
That's good.
Very good. Keep
going on that plane.
Great. OK, let me take over.
Cowboys don't have friends.
Dr. Grey, you ready?
Have good visualization
and start suturing right here.
All right. Keep going.
Very nice.
All right. Give her a
little room, O'Malley.
OK.
Beautiful.
You can tell Dr. Yang
she's a better teacher
than I would've thought.
- Sorry.
- Save it.
Your colleagues know more than
you do, milk them for all they're worth.
Lie to me again about your experience,
the next heart you see will be your own
as I cut it out of your
chest with a steak knife.
Mrs. Grandy, your
husband is in recovery.
It was a tough procedure,
but overall it went really well.
He's gonna be OK, Mrs. Grandy.
He is never gonna forgive me.
He was sick, and I told
him he was lazy and boring.
He was sick. You didn't know.
Well, I'm his wife.
I should've known.
People are terrible to the
people they love sometimes.
They're mean.
You were both going
through a really hard time
and took it out on one another. It
isn't fun, but it is what people do.
It doesn't make you the
worst wife in the world.
It just makes you a person
who made a mistake.
♪ You could put a
stick in my spokes ♪
♪ I can be the
butt of your jokes ♪
♪ I can be the laughingstock ♪
♪ I can be the hoax ♪
♪ But I ain't
gonna lose you... ♪
I miss anything good?
You're gonna love this. The
redhead just gave the short one a case
because she thought he'd find it
interesting. A pyogenic granuloma.
Gave it away.
We could transfer.
- Maybe we'd be happier.
- We'd die of boredom.
Die with great skin.
I had the biggest derm
emergency that exists today,
and it was fun for about a minute,
'cause the woman almost died,
then we saved her, and all
she needed was a stupid biopsy.
- I tore a guy's face off.
- I reattached
a coronary artery.
I hate you both.
We are not happy, glowy, people.
- Yeah.
We gotta get out of here.
Still no word on the test?
- George, I'm sure you passed.
- It'll be OK.
I mean, you're gonna buy me a
beer tonight, and then it'll be OK.
O'Malley?
Test results.
♪ But I ain't gonna lose you ♪
♪ No, I ain't gonna lose ♪
♪ Ain't gonna lose you ♪
You passed.
- I passed?
- George, you're not
an intern anymore.
- I passed.
- We are so gonna
celebrate.
I passed. I passed.
I passed. I'm gonna... I
gotta go tell Izzie and Mer.
- No. Go tell them,
and then we'll...
- OK.
Huzzah!
To George O'Malley,
repeater no more.
- You're gonna be
impossible now.
- Lexie!
- Come on and join us.
- I'm gonna get a drink first.
- Hey, Joe,
could I have a beer?
- Sure.
Want me to bring
it to the table?
No. I'm just gonna
sit over there.
Hey, Joe, can I get
another vodka tonic?
George passed his exam.
Tool.
Just the people I was looking
for. I want to buy these two a drink.
- You're the best roommate ever.
- I am.
Just to be clear, you two pull
that crap on one of my cases again,
I will have you thrown
out of the program.
You know what? I'll take
my drink at the table...
I know, OK? I know
I'm being an ass.
I can't help it. I'm
pissed off all the time,
so much I can't even breathe.
You can't be pissed at a
crazy chick for losing her mind.
There's nobody else to
be pissed at except you.
Nobody else.
We need to have rules.
- What?
- Rules.
We need rules about how we're
gonna deal with the motherland,
because it's undiscovered
country, and...
maybe it'll be the best vacation
either of us has ever had,
but... it's mysterious
and dark, and there
should be rules.
Oh, and an embassy.
And a safe word.
I'm sorry. What the hell
are you talking about?
Below the...
Below the Mason-Dixon
line. Of your pants.
I'm not sure I'm
ready to go there.
Me neither.
There's lots of undiscovered
territory above the belt. Uh...
We can take it slow.
Maybe... just first base.
OK.
Whoo! OK. Thank you.
Sorry.
Finish my wine.
I'm gonna look at the menu
while you let your blood
pressure drop back down to normal.
Erica.
Maybe second base, too.
♪ If only to be near you ♪
♪ To have you and to hear you ♪
♪ Isn't that what time is for? ♪
I could always move
back to the trailer.
No, I want you here.
I mean, I may not always
be so graceful about it, but...
I want you here.
You need a place
for your things.
It's not an
unreasonable request.
You can use this as your
den or your office or whatever.
It's your mom's den.
But she isn't here. You are.
♪ The reason I survive ♪
♪ Trust we'll be together soon ♪
What about you?
You need someplace.
Someplace you can get away to.
Well, I can always go
to Cristina's or whatever.
I think I have a better idea.
We like to think we're fearless,
eager to explore unknown lands
and soak up new experiences.
But, the fact is,
we're always terrified.
Maybe the terror's
part of the attraction.
Some people go to horror
movies, we cut things open,
dive into dark water.
"October 13, 1977.
I haven't slept
in three days..."
And, at the end of the day, isn't
that what you'd rather hear about,
if you've got one drink and
one friend and 45 minutes?
Smooth rides make
for boring stories.
A little calamity, that's
worth talking about.
♪ Take my heart ♪
♪ With you ♪