Previously on Grey's Anatomy:
- You're an intern. Again.
- Yeah.
- I won't tell anybody.
- Izzie, meet Really Old Guy.
This is the best breakup.
Don't know why we
didn't break up long ago.
He's gone.
You're my sister. You're
my family. You're all I've got.
- We have the same dad.
- We don't have the same dad.
I think my husband's
having an affair.
I'm going to tell her.
Doctors give patients
a number of things.
We give them medicine.
We give them advice.
And, most of the time,
we give them our
undivided attention.
I heard he saved a guy who
coded yesterday. By himself.
He just knows things. He
never messes up in rounds,
- always has the answer.
- And he's so calm.
I'm always terrified,
but he's, like, steady.
- Best intern ever.
- Who are they talking about?
- George O'Malley.
- Seriously?
- Don't they know that he...?
- Shh!
But, by far, the hardest thing
you can give a
patient is the truth.
Do you know O'Malley's
got these morons snowed?
- They don't know
he's a repeater.
- Yeah, whatever.
♪ Take it slow
Take it easy on me ♪
- Hey.
♪ Shed some light Shed
some light on me, please ♪
- How are you today?
- Good.
Great.
The truth is hard.
The truth is awkward.
And very often...
the truth hurts.
- Damn it!
- Bye.
She's doing McDreamy. She's
doing McDreamy and lying about it.
She thinks I'm weak? Fragile?
Like I can't handle
it because of Burke.
- Poor Cristina. All alone.
- Damn right, poor Cristina.
George, what happened?
I mean, people say
they want the truth.
But do they really?
- Do I have sex hair?
- If I did my job right.
- Go ahead.
- What?
You go ahead.
I'll wait a minute.
So this isn't just breakup
sex, this is secret breakup sex.
- Is this about Cristina?
- I don't know what to do.
We don't talk about it,
the whole Burke thing.
I want to be a good friend,
I want to take care of her,
but you don't take
care of Cristina.
OK, so by being with me,
you're cheating on Cristina?
- If she knew about
you and me...
- You'd have to talk about it.
You'd talk about you and
me. It'd be a long conversation.
There'd be no time
to talk about her.
- I told you,
we don't talk about it.
- Mm-hmm.
Pierce, you're in the pit.
James, need you in peds.
- Laura, you're on scut.
- I was on scut yesterday.
Oh, and just for that, you're
on scut tomorrow. Get lost!
Dr. Karev, this is
Dr. Norman Shales.
- Hey.
- Strong handshake. That's a good sign.
Norman's transferring
in from UCLA.
I want him to work with you.
- Are you the new ob/gyn guy?
- I don't have a specialty yet.
Norman is an intern.
- You'll be his resident.
- He's my intern?
Don't you worry. This tugboat's
ready to pull his own weight.
- Age is just a number, right?
- Absolutely.
A pretty important number.
- Hey.
- You OK?
- I don't know.
I think it's all just
hitting me, you know.
Stupid Burke, dumping me.
Then stupid Mama coming
to reclaim her magic necklace.
- You want to talk about it?
- No. Not really. Not yet.
If there's anything I can do...
You know, I just wish I
had a good bloody surgery.
You know, bloody surgeries
make me feel better.
One, Two, Three,
Four. Follow me.
Joanne, this is why you and I
need to get sick. These doctors.
One's more handsome
than the next.
And here comes the
handsomest one of them all.
- Hi, Dr. Webber.
- Connie.
He took my appendix
out three years ago.
Barely left a scar. How's Adele?
Um... She's good.
Good. Marriage is hard.
But we're dating again... and
she agreed to date me tonight.
But... more importantly,
how are you doing?
I just had a little bump on
my tongue removed, is all.
Couple of taste buds.
It was a touch of cancer,
so I'm here to
have the rest out.
I mean, you know, the
cancer. Not the taste buds.
I don't know
exactly how bad it is
because Dr. Sloan's been quiet.
Because you don't let him
get a word in edgewise, is why.
Uh, how is she, Dr. Sloan?
We just got back the
pathology report, Connie.
Unfortunately, the cancer is a bit
more widespread than we'd hoped.
It's over 60 percent
of your tongue.
Well, what does she do? Chemo?
I think the best bet is a
microvascular free flap.
Dr. Grey?
He'll remove the
cancerous part of the tongue
and then reconstruct it with
a strip of flesh from your legs.
- George?
- Uh, the extra flesh would
provide the bulk
your tongue needs
to breathe properly,
chew, swallow.
And talk?
Dr. Sloan? I'll be
able to talk, won't I?
You will be able
to talk, Connie.
I just don't know how
well you'll be understood.
- It'll be OK.
Nurse Hollister, Peds ICU.
What are you doing in my clinic?
I thought you didn't
work in the clinic.
I don't. But I thought I'd get my new
intern, Norman, settled in with you.
Bailey's the best.
You'll really learn.
Oh. Pleased to meet you.
You want to leave Norman with
me while you troll for surgeries.
The dude's got a bum hip and
he smells like arthritis cream.
He can't keep up.
Come on. Do me a favor
and I'll do you a favor.
I'm calling in my favor
now. Curtain Five.
You can take your intern and
show him how we do an H & P.
- Nice to meet you, Norman.
- Thank you.
Hunter, I'm Dr. Karev.
This is Dr. Shales.
- What's going on?
- My son is on drugs.
- I'm not on drugs, Mom.
- I wasn't born yesterday.
I know the signs.
He's lethargic, irritable,
school work's gone
down the drain.
- I'm not on drugs.
- There are a host of reasons
why your son could be
exhibiting those symptoms.
I think we should
run some tests.
But first a drug
test, Dr. Shales?
- I'm right to want a drug test?
- Yeah, I just said that.
Mrs. Chapman, you are not wrong.
My Mary Beth, God rest
her soul, was just like you.
When one of our kids
started heading down
that slippery slope,
she just knew it.
You have a mother's
instinct. Right, Dr. Karev?
Yeah. Right.
OK. What happened?
George. It's Really Old Guy.
We could bring a
marching band in here.
- What happened with Callie?
- What happened?
You were gonna
tell her last night.
I tried, but she would not
let me. She wouldn't let me.
And I wanted to kill her,
but then I couldn't kill her
because she did help
me through a lot of stuff,
and it was a lot of stuff.
Then I wanted to kill her again
because who marries someone
who just buried their father?
And then I went to bed.
So what does this mean?
I told you I needed a
minute before rounds.
- We heard you saved
a guy yesterday.
- What?
- Rounds!
- Excuse me.
We'll start in here.
Graziella, what can you
tell us about Really Old Guy?
- He has a name.
- I know he has a name.
We call him Really Old Guy.
Eighty-two year old
semi-comatose male.
Came in a year ago status
post fall and is post-op day 352...
Which means he hasn't
woken up for a year.
So what's the treatment plan?
Um... um...
It's really very simple.
Daily labs and dialysis
three times a week.
Don't bother with
any more dialysis.
I plan to die today, so
it won't be necessary.
Nice to meet you.
And while I think Really
Old Guy is charming
in a neglected patient kind
of way, my name is Charlie.
Charlie Yost.
Hey, I just heard. Welcome back.
Is it true? Really
Old Guy woke up?
He has a name.
This time tomorrow you
can call me Really Dead Guy.
I don't think Mr. Yost
knows who you are.
Sure I do. That's Meredith.
She and the brain doctor are
always running hot and cold.
And you're Alex.
You still got a thing for
that old patient of yours?
I was semi-comatose, Blondie.
I could still hear you guys.
Get a CT, a CBC and chemistries.
Your kidneys may be working,
which may be why you
woke up. It's good news.
Oh, it just means now I
got two things to do today.
- Take a pee and die.
- Nobody's dying. "Aah."
- Functional muscle transfer.
- What?
For Connie. I was reading
up on glossectomies
and saw the procedure.
We could microsurgically
reinnervate her
hypoglossal nerve.
A nerve graft? It's too risky.
The free flap's
still your best bet.
Even if that goes well, you and I
know she'll never speak the same.
- That woman loves to talk.
- What's a functional
muscle transfer?
You won't find it in the
books. It's cutting edge.
Connect the nerves from the leg
with the nerves from the tongue.
- Gives her a shot
at really speaking.
- If it works.
They've only done a
half a dozen of them.
Better than none. Sometimes
you got to push the envelope.
Better to do a surgery that
neither of you have done
than do a surgery that you
know at least gives her a chance
to have a normal life? Do
you know how to do this?
Are you saying that we're too
old to learn new ways, O'Malley?
No.
Saying we're old dogs,
can't learn new tricks?
- No. I was just asking...
- We're not old dogs.
- We still got it.
- OK.
I did do a functional
muscle transfer
to restore elbow function once.
Elbow, tongue. That's pretty
close. Come on. What do you say?
- Let's light this candle.
- Yes, sir.
- Age is just a number.
Excuse me.
I got Karev down
in the clinic all day.
- I hope that's not a problem.
- Nope.
I know how you like
to be told these things,
- so I'm telling you.
- Thank you.
You know, he tried to dump
a new intern on me, Karev.
Not interested in teaching.
Thank you for letting me know.
- You ever feel old?
- I'm young. I'm a fetus.
You ever feel like
there's going to be a time
when new techniques pass you by?
- I'm a genius and a scholar.
- Shut up.
Meredith isn't telling
Cristina about us.
And, well, she tells
Cristina everything.
- I thought you broke that off.
- I meant to.
You think she's gonna
want to get back together.
No.
You think she's going to grow up
and get all whole and
want a relationship.
- I do not.
- You're a bad liar.
- You're old.
- I'm just getting started,
my friend.
Hey. You feeling any better?
Heard you're on that
hemiglossectomy.
Tongue surgery? Yeah.
Here I am stuck in the pit
with those know-nothing interns.
You'd think, eventually,
I'd catch a break.
Are we ever going to talk
about this, the Burke thing?
I'm not Izzie. Not going to lie
on the bathroom floor all day.
I'm going to lie
here, on the counter.
I'll trade you the
hemiglossectomy.
What?
You take the hemiglossectomy,
and I will take the
ER and your interns.
- Are you sure?
- Take the surgery
if it makes you feel better.
You're starting to freak me out.
I saw the whole thing, Yang.
You can stop pretending.
I'm not pretending. I'm
sad. I'm very sad. Me so sad.
I should try it. See if I can
get Grey to take my new intern.
No. Hey. Forget it. Sad is mine.
Go find your own
pretend emotion.
Blondie!
Hey, Blondie!
Charlie, I have a million
charts to update. I'm busy.
- I want lobster.
- What?
For my last meal.
It's traditional.
The dying man gets to
choose what he wants to eat.
- I want lobster.
- I'm not getting you lobster.
You're not dying.
I won't allow it.
A man can only hang
on for so long, Blondie.
After a while it's
just not worth it.
Don't you have any
friends? Family? Anyone?
They're all dead or
on their way to dead.
You'll understand someday.
When you're older. Less naive.
- I'm not naive.
- You and what's his face.
That's not naive?
I don't know what you're...
You know about what's his face?
I know you're crazy if you
think he's leaving his wife.
Guys always say that.
Not that it's your business,
but this is different.
I'm sure it's true love.
I'm sure he's told his wife.
I'm sure he's moved out.
And I'm sure all your
friends know. Right?
Yeah. By the way,
I want real lobster.
Not that fake whitefish crap.
Dr. Pierce, ER stat.
Hey, I'm filling in for
Cristina. So how's it going?
Pulled a splinter out of a guy's
toe, now I'm writing about it.
OK. Well, if you
have any questions...
I have a lot of questions.
Just not about a splinter.
- OK.
Coming through! Forty year old
unrestrained driver
in a rollover MVC.
- Lost vitals,
unable to intubate.
- Lexie, let's go!
Open the intubation tray.
How long's he been down?
Took ten minutes to load
him, 14 to get here, so 24.
Do you know how to intubate?
- Uh, I've never done it.
- You've seen it done?
- A couple times.
- Come do one now.
Are you sure?
Visualize the cords, pull
straight up, watch the tube,
go through the cords.
I can't see the cords.
You should do this.
You can do it. Just don't
rock up against the teeth.
- Just pull straight up.
- Pulse ox's down to 86.
That wasn't bad.
What?
That wasn't bad for
your first intubation.
Is that some kind of a joke?
The guy is dead. He died.
He was dead when he came in
here. He was dead on the scene.
He was dead for 15
minutes in the ambulance.
He was dead before I
asked you to intubate.
You're pretty cavalier,
don't you think? I mean,
they brought him here for help.
They brought him here because
they're legally required to.
And I had you intubate
because I'm required to teach you,
- and that is how you learn.
- No. No.
You should have done
everything that you could.
That was everything I could.
- What kind of doctor are you?
- What is this about?
If you don't want to
learn from me, that's fine.
But I have to
cover the pit today,
Why don't you do
both of us a favor
and go help
Bailey in the clinic.
- Fine.
Pretend I'm not here.
Pretend I'm not
busting in on you
and your pictures of tongues.
Really Old Guy is
giving me a hard time.
I liked him better
when he was sleeping.
Which he's not. He's awake.
You've probably heard.
But my point is, is
that he's stubborn.
He's stubborn and really old
and he's telling me I'm an idiot
for thinking you're gonna
leave Callie. Seriously?
We're in this together.
You're going to tell
her tonight. Right?
- George?
- I have to
get this research done.
You're not gonna tell her.
Just yesterday you said
you didn't want me to tell her.
Fine! Forget it!
Just play with your
stupid pictures of tongues!
We got back the tox
screen back, Mrs. Chapman.
Your son's not on drugs.
You're sure? There's
no drugs in his system?
No, it came back
clean. Your son is fine.
This is not my son,
Dr. Shales. It's not.
Maybe we should
order more tests.
You know, he's a teenager.
I raised four of them myself.
Teenagers don't
like to do homework,
they talk back to parents and
never come out of their rooms.
You have apple hair. I threw a
pancake in the river. A pancake!
Hunter?
- Do you know what you said?
- I'm... I'm not sure.
- Did you mean to say it?
- No.
I was trying to say that
I wanted to go home.
- Oh, my God.
- We need to do
a full neuro exam.
Order a head CT and labs. Now.
It's going to be OK, you know?
- It is. It's going to be OK.
- Do you think so?
Dr. Sloan's going to do
this fancy new surgery.
You'll make it into
medical journals.
Maybe you'll be famous.
- What if the surgery doesn't work?
- - Oh.
What if this is my
last chance to talk?
I still have so much to say.
- Say it now, Connie.
- Don't be so morbid.
The surgery will
work. You'll be fine.
She should say it
all now, just in case.
She shouldn't have
any more regrets.
You can tell us anything,
Connie. We're your best friends.
You should tell them.
I'm sorry, I don't mean to pry,
but if you have something you
want to say you should say it.
I've been here
long enough to know
that things don't always go
the way that you want them to,
and if there's something you
want to say, you should say it.
Joanne, stop
wearing those pants.
Make your ass look like
two puppies are
struggling to get out.
As a matter of fact, all
of your pants are too tight.
You have to buy some new pants.
Elaine, your
breath is god-awful.
- My breath?
- You need to see a doctor,
because I know you have good
hygiene, but sweet God, your breath is bad.
And you've got to get a new
hairdo. The 80s are over, honey.
- What now?
- He's pulling off
his monitor leads.
I told him he could pull
them off, he's not gonna die.
I'm sick and tired of waiting.
I'm tired of coming
to your room.
Sorry, Blondie. It's time I
took things into my own hands.
Know what? You want to die?
Fine. Here. Let me help you.
You missed this one.
Damn. You're still with us.
Oh, wait, this looks promising.
A nice, thick wire. How's that?
Any luck? No? Well,
no wonder that's why.
It's attached to this lamp.
OK. Let's see what else we got.
- Dr. Stevens.
- What?
- He's not breathing!
He doesn't have a pulse.
He's in cardiac arrest.
I swear, I didn't do anything!
Code blue, fourth floor.
- The epi and atropine in?
- Epi's in. Pushing atropine.
Hold CPR, let's
see what happens.
- Looks like v-fib.
- Charge paddles. Three hundred.
Clear!
- No change.
- Charge again. Clear.
We got a pulse.
Charlie?
Stop saving my life!
I can't believe I said all that.
Do you believe I said all that?
- Not really, no.
- Think I hurt their feelings?
I mean, real bad
hurt their feelings?
You think they'll forgive me?
You told me. You
told me to tell them.
You told me to say everything.
You said it would be OK.
I'm really sorry.
Dr. Bailey? Dr. Grey sent
me down here to work with you.
She did, did she?
And why is that?
Truthfully? Uh...
She didn't want to work with
me anymore. She kicked me out.
You can go and tell Dr. Grey
that the clinic is not a
dumping ground for strays.
We are not the Island
of Broken Interns.
Please go tell her that.
Please don't make me do that.
I can't work with Meredith Grey.
I can't work with her
because I can't look at her.
Because she hates
me, she hates my dad.
She obviously hated
my mother. I am...
Please just let me work down
here today. Please, Dr. Bailey.
Kid in Curtain Three
needs stitches. Go.
- What do you got?
- A teenager came in
this morning.
He was lethargic,
irritable, dysphasic.
Sorry, I don't know you.
- Norman Shales. Up from UCLA.
- Are you neuro?
I thought I knew
all the neuro guys.
Norman's an
intern, Dr. Shepherd.
- My intern.
- Welcome.
Thank you.
OK. What do we got?
Hmm... Look at this.
The kid's got hydrocephalus.
Pushing against
his Broca's area.
Which explains the
screwed up speech.
I was sure it was drugs.
That's what happens when
you're a pharmacist for 30 years.
You're sure everybody's
hooked on pills.
I won't make that mistake again.
Right. OK. Um, we
need to put in a shunt.
Schedule an OR and
we'll talk to Hunter.
Will do, captain.
The guy doesn't
know when to shut up.
He does it with patients, too.
- You're his resident.
- I know.
But it'd be like yelling
at my grandfather.
Hey. I heard about
Really Old Guy.
What's the matter,
couldn't find his LVAD wire?
It was a coincidence.
And he's still alive.
Well, have fun
with Really Old Guy.
I'm off to do Meredith's
hemiglossectomy.
Has George said anything to you?
She's faking! She's
faking sadness.
Pretending to be sad
to steal my surgeries.
OK. I have a really old guy
trying to kill himself
and problems of my own!
So I don't have time for the
two of you and your fake drama.
A person wants to die,
you let them. It's polite.
Not in a hospital, it's not.
In a hospital, it's a lawsuit.
- I don't like you.
- Really? I thought
we were BFFs.
You know what? Just for
that? I'm dying right now.
That might make
you poop your pants,
but it's not gonna make you die.
Damn it!
You really think he's not
going to leave his wife?
I think if a person wants to do
something, like die, they do it.
Oh.
Maybe I'm wrong.
Maybe there's hope.
Maybe he'll tell her
and you two will get
together and end up happy.
- You think?
- Not that I'll be alive
to see it.
You're not dying,
Charlie. Not on my watch.
- Dead Man Walking!
- I don't see much walking.
You know Yang and Grey are
playing musical chairs with the interns?
Oh?
I thought that might interest
you, seeing as how one of
Yang's interns is actually
one of Grey's relatives.
The two Greys are having
some kind of family feud.
I'm just saying it
would probably be best
if the residents stuck with
their own interns in the future.
Yeah, I got it. Thanks.
You plan to hide
out here all day long,
or you plan to emerge at
some point and do your job?
Why would I come
out there to do my job
when you clearly
do it so much better?
I'm doing paperwork because
I don't have more fight in me.
I don't want to fight you,
I don't want to fight my...
I don't. I don't
want to fight today.
So I'm doing paperwork, OK?
- Graft's a perfect fit.
- Yeah.
It's got good vascularization.
You may actually get to
go on that date with Adele.
Yeah, I better. Can't very
well have her take me back
- if I cancel our first date.
- Where are you taking her?
There's a nice little Chinese
restaurant we like to go to.
Hmm.
- What happens next?
- Um...
- Dr. Sloan, I...
- I know.
Is everything OK?
Um...
- We're not sure.
- What does that mean?
It means we've
never done this before.
What about if we coapt the
lingual nerve underneath here?
We'd end up losing
the vascular supply.
The graft might not work at all.
She likes to talk, Sloan.
She likes to talk a lot.
We need an extra set of hands.
Someone who knows nerves.
- O'Malley, get Dr. Shepherd.
- Yes, sir.
A functional muscle
transfer of the tongue?
Yeah, it was looking
good for a while, but, um...
- I'll be right there.
- Yeah.
- Izzie.
- What?
What is there to say, George?
I'm a "Blondie." I'm
the other woman.
- I'm a bad '50s cliché.
- No, no, no.
We're not in this together.
Wow. Great. Well, thank
you for letting me know.
Hey. No. No, you don't
get to be mad here.
- Seriously? We said...
- No, no! There is no "we!"
It's just me. I'm the one
who has to tell Callie.
I'm the one who
has to destroy her.
This is not about you and
me. This is about her and me.
I'm ending a marriage
to a wonderful woman.
Me. I'm the one. It's not you.
You...
It's not something you
just blurt out. It's not.
I'll do it.
I will do it.
You have to back
off and let me do it.
I'm sorry.
You traded? A
hemiglossectomy for the pit?
It's a long story.
A story that ends with you
pawning off Lexie Grey on me?
I had her do an
intubation on a dead guy.
It's something you
used to have us do.
I was trying to teach her.
Whatever she told you...
- She told me you hate her.
- I don't...
- And you hated her mother.
- I didn't say that.
Her mother who came to
you with a case of hiccups
and died in our hospital.
Do you see where
I'm going with this?
- She's not my intern.
- No, she's your sister.
You haven't said a kind word
to say to her since she got here.
You were her mother's doctor.
What is she supposed to think?
Whether you like it or not,
your job is to help that
girl be a better doctor.
So help her.
- You paged me?
- Really Old Guy?
- Yeah.
- He's checked out AMA.
- He's leaving the hospital.
- He can't leave. He's sick.
He can barely walk.
And I got him lobster.
- I got a 911. What happened?
- He collapsed.
- He started talking nonsense...
- Pupil's blown.
Brain's starting to herniate.
We got to get him up on a bed.
- What's happening?
- Count of three. One, two, three.
- His spinal fluid's backing up.
- Shepherd's not answering.
- Try it again!
What do I do?
Hyperventilation. Mannitol.
I don't know everything.
Go get Shepherd. Go.
♪ And torn at the edge ♪
♪ And I've look upon
it for so many years ♪
- Dr. Shepherd.
- I'm busy right now.
Hunter Chapman's brain is
herniating. Right pupil blew.
Do what I say or that kid's gonna be
dead in ten minutes. Can you do that?
- Yes, sir.
- Get the biggest needle
you can find.
♪ Oh, the ocean rows us away ♪
- Dr. Karev. What's going on?
- Where's Shepherd?
Dr. Karev.
It might help Mrs. Chapman
if she knows exactly...
- What are you doing?
- Get her out!
- She is the boy's mom.
- Get her out of here, Norman!
- Mrs. Chapman, it's time to go.
- What are you doing?
- Hold his head.
Shepherd told me what to do.
♪ You're caught on my
head like a thorn on a vine ♪
♪ To forever torment
me And I wonder why ♪
♪ Do I wish I've never
known you at all ♪
♪ Oh, the ocean rows us away ♪
Charlie, you can't go.
I know that you
think your life is over.
I know you feel you
don't have anybody,
but your life's not over.
And... And you have me.
You have me. I need you.
I need somebody to talk to.
I think you may have
been right before.
I don't think George
is gonna leave his wife,
and I need you to
tell me what to do.
I need some...
You can't go, Charlie.
Charlie?
♪ The sun and the moon ♪
♪ An ocean of air ♪
Charlie?
♪ So many voices
but nothing is there ♪
♪ But the ghost of you
asking me, "Why?" ♪
♪ Why did I leave? ♪
Crap.
♪ Oh ♪
♪ The ocean rows us away ♪
♪ Away ♪
All this time, he was
telling me the truth.
Once we get the shunt in, any excess
spinal fluid will drain to his abdomen.
He's going to be OK.
Excuse me.
Sorry I unloaded on you, Norman.
You know how it is,
heat of the moment.
- Don't apologize to him.
- What?
- Dr. Bailey's right.
- Shut up. I'm not
talking to you.
He got in your way.
He's been doing it all day.
When that happens, when an
intern gets in the way of a resident,
you're not doing what's
best for your patient.
You almost missed
diagnosing that kid today
because Norman thought it
was drugs. So don't apologize.
He should be yelled at.
Dr. Bailey, he's
as old as the hills.
I don't care how old he is,
Dr. Karev. He's still an intern.
And interns are
basically teenagers.
We are not hard on
them because it's fun.
We're hard on them because
this is a life and death job.
They need to learn that.
There's a reason why we have
a pecking order in a hospital.
It saves lives.
That woman's gonna be able to talk
for the rest of her life, thanks to us.
- I think I still got it.
- I think you do, too.
We've got to figure out what
you're going to tell Adele.
I forgot about that.
First off, don't tell her
you want to move back in.
- No?
- Reeks of desperation.
It's a deal breaker. Trust me.
I can't take this anymore. You
guys are kidding yourselves.
You know how close you came
to that woman losing her tongue?
To her never speaking again?
Oh, yeah. You were a
couple of cowboys in there.
Telling yourselves you can
do this. Acting like the big boys.
You had no business
doing that surgery.
No business. Lucky
I came in when I did.
Shame on you. And shame on you.
As for Adele, tell her you can't
imagine your life without her.
Tell her for the last month you've
been walking around this hospital
just thinking about
her. Tell her the truth.
I'm sorry I called you an idiot.
Hey. So I've been thinking
about how you're sad.
- And what I can do to help.
- You have another surgery?
- No, that's not what you need.
- It kind of is.
No. What you need
is me. And my time.
So I thought we could
go back to my house
and get into our pajamas.
Just sit and talk
about this Burke thing
and get to the root
of your feelings.
Just talk all night
long if we have to.
- Talk.
And cry.
Cry.
You know.
You're damn right I
know! Surgery-stealer!
So? Person who's
sleeping with Derek.
How'd you know that?
What, think I'm too fragile
to handle your sex life?
Well, he did leave you at
the altar and I'm your person.
How? By protecting me?
That's not how to be my person.
That's not what we
do. You know that.
I'm dealing, OK? The best I can.
If you need to take
care of someone,
you're gonna need to
take care of someone else.
Fine. But you owe me a surgery.
Yeah, well, you
owe me sex details.
Are we doing this or not?
What are we supposed to say?
- We didn't even know the guy.
- We ate lunch here for a year.
The least we can do is say
a few kind words about him.
He...
didn't snore too loudly.
He, um... never complained.
And he always took his meds.
- Hardly ever farted.
- Alex.
Fine.
He had 12 surgeries this
year and he lived through them.
- That's... That's impressive.
- Thank you, Alex.
Cristina?
I got to practice stuff on him.
Central lines and IV,
it was good practice.
Um...
Charlie, the truth is, you
were a bastard. You were.
You were mean and
stubborn and just a bastard.
But you were a bastard
who knew what you wanted.
And you stuck to your guns
and proved that if you want
something badly enough,
if you're determined
enough and patient enough,
eventually it will
happen. It will.
And that gives me
hope, so thanks for that.
Bye-bye, Charlie.
The truth is painful.
It went really well.
♪ I remember it most ♪
♪ What it said ♪
Your friends, um... I'm so
sorry. I haven't seen them.
- How'd she do?
- Great. She did great.
- She's going to talk again?
- Yeah, the chances are good.
In that case, we have a
few things we'd like to say.
Your first husband?
He put his hand on my
ass every chance he got.
And your second husband?
He spat when he talked
and plus he was ugly.
We know that you
thought he was handsome,
but the man was a troll.
- That guy you dated last year?
- Comb-over guy.
- My God.
- Deep down, nobody
wants to hear it.
Especially when it
hits close to home.
What?
I have your mother's
death note here.
Everything that happened
on the day she died is in here.
And I know because I wrote it.
So, I'd like to go over
it with you, if that's OK.
Yeah.
First of all, let me say that
everything that happened
that day... every setback,
there was a one percent chance
of each of those things
happening. One percent.
And your mother
was the one percent.
She came in complaining
of a persistent hiccups.
We did an endoscopic
fundoplication.
You did it endoscopically?
So it would be an
outpatient procedure.
We wanted to
avoid major surgery.
For what it's worth, I was very
fond of your mother. She was...
I was very fond of her.
♪ And how that made me feel
so sick and bored with myself ♪
She got bacterial endocarditis
from the procedure.
Sometimes we tell the truth
because the truth
is all we have to give.
♪ Friends Let's
do it all again ♪
I've been having trouble with
this whole pecking order of things.
I've been having trouble.
Because I'm used
to being number one.
But I'm not number
one. Not anymore.
So the best that I can come
up with is to be number two.
The best damned number
two this hospital has ever seen,
but your number two.
I will... I will...
I will help you.
We'll be like a team.
Because, look, girl, you just
seem to be having a hard time.
And, uh, I know I'm
having a hard time,
but together we could do this.
I just think we can
do this together.
Sometimes we tell the truth
because we need
to say it out loud
to really hear it for ourselves.
You got to reattach
a woman's tongue?
I was there. I didn't
do the reattaching.
Yeah, but still, you're the
intern they wanted on that case.
- He's a repeater.
- What?
Your big hero here, he
was an intern last year.
That's why he knows
some of this stuff.
He's already been through it.
But if you want to learn from
someone, really, really learn,
go to a resident. Not this dude.
Well, he's right.
If you want to emulate
someone, it's definitely not me.
I'm not that guy.
And sometimes we tell the truth
because we just
can't help ourselves.
What the hell are
you looking at?
♪ Let's do it all again ♪
Interns.
And sometimes...
we tell them...
because we owe
them at least that much.
Just say it.
I slept with Izzie.