You never know the biggest day of
your life is going to be the biggest.
The days you think are
going to be big ones...
They're never as big as you
make them out to be in your head.
It's the regular days.
The ones that start out normal.
Those are the days that
end up being the biggest.
And today was the wedding.
It was beautiful.
Perfect.
- Just a normal day.
- Normal day.
Going to work.
Just a normal day that ends in
a ceremony in a churchy church.
This has nothing to do with us.
We're just the bride and groom.
- We're getting married tonight.
You slept here?
- I'm awake. What?
- You slept here? I slept here.
- How? Wait... Who... What?
- I slept in the on-call room.
I could have been at
home in my own bed.
- Sorry.
- I have to work all day.
Then I have to be happy maid of
honor and get Meredith down the aisle.
I'm so tired.
Because I slept here.
'Cause you wanted to get your
freak on with roller skate girl.
I'm sorry. I was gonna, but...
We went to dinner
and... things didn't...
I wasn't in the mood. Had to
be here early, anyway, to run ER.
You're picking up
extra shifts in ER?
- So is Owen not here today?
- He's here. Crap, I'm late.
- Hey.
Big day! Biggest
day of your life!
Don't do that, the peppy
maid of honor thing. It's creepy.
Really? Good. Wait. Is this
the calm before the storm?
Need me to drug you?
Or shave your eyebrows
- to numb you into submission?
- I'm fine.
Not the biggest day of my life.
Biggest day of Izzie's life.
I'm excited about the marriage,
not some wedding. She's
the one who's gone Bridezilla.
Bridezilla!
You should see the
bridesmaids' dresses.
Oh! And the flowers! They're
being delivered at 5:00.
I had to pay extra to have them
decorate but Derek gave me his credit card,
told me to do what I had to
do so... It's gonna be perfect.
- How's her pressure?
- Within normal.
And her incision site?
As expected, two
weeks after surgery.
She got off the IL-2 hours
ago. She could still have...
Her mets are gone. Her blood
pressure's fine. Her incision doesn't hurt.
She's doing well.
It's wedding day! And I'm going.
I'm a bridesmaid. I'm
going. Right, Bailey?
- I said you could go.
- Wedding day!
Up top, Alex!
I'll check on you later.
Don't leave me hanging,
Bailey. Wedding day!
Wedding day...
You did that 'cause
I have cancer.
- You didn't mean it.
- True.
My hair is starting to fall out.
You still look good.
I know what this means.
- You being here.
- I'm sorry.
I'm still going to the wedding.
- How's Izzie?
- Good.
BP stable? If she's hypotensive
she shouldn't go to the wedding.
- Let me worry about Izzie.
- All right.
Anything for us? Anything good?
Nope. It's slow.
You don't say it's a
slow day in the pit.
Never say it's sl...
- You just jinxed us.
- It's a day and it's slow.
That phone starts
ringing, you're gonna
- wish you hadn't said that.
- Not gonna ring. It's a slow day.
Go for Seattle Grace Emergency.
- I'll get the trauma gowns.
- Crap, crap, crap... Incoming!
How's it going with your shrink?
Uh... I'm doing
better. Inch by inch.
Progress is slow.
It was your ceiling
fan. Above your bed?
Blades spinning like
blades of a chopper.
My shrink says
that was the trigger.
To me...
choking you.
Oh.
We should probably get going.
David Simons, 22, in the driver's
seat when his car got crushed by a semi.
Truck blew a tire and
jack-knifed across traffic.
- Bay One until
we get a trauma room.
- Injuries?
Chest contusions. Otherwise
vital signs were stable.
- We can't be late.
- Ready? One, two, three...
- Late for what?
- Graduation.
Becca Wells, 21-year-old,
back seat. Vitals stable.
- Some shortness of breath.
- Bay Two for now.
- Gonna be so late.
- David, that you?
Becca? Are you OK?
- I think so. I don't know.
- One, two, three.
I'm talking. Can't be
too bad if I'm talking.
22 year-old passenger, tenderness
above pelvis and unstable BP...
Bay Five.
Is my girlfriend here?
She was in the back seat.
- Jordan?
- Becca?
Have you seen Dana?
You were sitting next to her.
Can you check our friends?
Dana, Michelle, Pete?
Eight piled into the SUV?
- Are they all this bad?
- These are the healthy ones.
OK. I need beds. And blood and
interns. And Owen Hunt. Where's Hunt?
V-tach! BP's dropped out! Need
crash cart. I'm gonna cardiovert!
David! What's wrong with him?
- Charge to 100! Clear.
- David!
- What's wrong with David?
- Have to save him.
You can't let him die! We're
supposed to be graduating.
- Charge to 200! Clear!
- This is the biggest day
of our lives.
Where in the hell is Hunt?
Hunt, thank God. Trauma
One through Three.
What do we got?
Becca Wells. Respiratory
rate up 20, but vital signs stable.
Is David OK? He has to graduate.
He's the first in his
family to go to college.
Don't worry about
your friends right now.
No hemothorax or
pneumothorax. In line for CT.
Gonna get a few
X-rays, get a better idea.
You should rest. Your
body's in serious shock.
I have a speech to give.
I'm supposed to...
I'm the valedictorian.
All I've ever done is
school. It's all I've ever done.
I haven't done anything else.
Until today. Today's the day
that my life is supposed to start.
Which is why I'd
really like to live. OK?
- Let me know
the results of the CT.
- OK.
I haven't seen Dana
yet, my girlfriend.
- She was in the backseat...
- Hang blood and push fluids.
She was singing to the radio.
She never knows the words.
I turned around to tell her
and then... she wasn't there.
Calm down so we can treat
you. Very serious injuries.
She was not in the car anymore!
I promise I will check for you.
You need to stay still for me.
- She's wearing a pink sweater.
- OK.
Keep working. Try to get his
pressure up before you move him.
Systolic's stabilizing, but
still multiple arrhythmias.
Thinking cardiac contusions.
- I'm about to use a chest tube.
- You got this, O'Malley.
- I've got blood.
- Put it in the rapid infuser.
Are my friends here?
Did you see Pete?
- Which one's Pete?
- He's wearing red sneakers.
And Michelle, she dyed
her hair blue for graduation.
- Did you see her? Is she OK?
- I'll find them.
- My whole family is coming.
- I know. It's a big day.
For them. Today is for them.
V-fib! He's coding!
Get the paddles!
Page me?
Yes. You get the
check for the caterers?
- And cash tips for the waiters?
- Yes.
- Did you write your vows?
- Not yet. I will.
You have to write your vows.
What you say this day, it's
important. She'll remember it for life.
If you paged me to
talk about the wedding...
That's not why I paged you.
I have a craniotomy to get to.
He's back. Denny. He's back.
I'll page Dr. Bailey
and we'll...
Order an MRI. I know the drill.
You wanted to see me, chief?
Derek was supposed to do this,
but he got pulled into something.
- I said I'd give it to you.
- What?
Your wedding present. Not from
me, from Derek. I have to oversee it.
I was supposed to
get him a present?
This is why weddings are stupid.
Our life together should be the present.
Not some stupid...
Whatever it is, I don't want it.
Tell Derek to take
it back. I'll tell him.
- He got you a colon.
- What?
A colon.
It's non-refundable, inflamed,
it's about to go under
anesthesia in OR 2.
You really wanna
say you don't want it?
A solo surgery?
Happy Wedding Day.
- Yes or no?
- Hey.
I don't need a maybe.
I need a yes or no.
OK. I'll be right here, waiting.
You think Shepherd and Grey
are gonna last? Like 50 years last?
A semi crashed into a
bunch of college kids.
On the day I decided to
take an extra shift in the ER.
Great, thank you.
There's burns, digit amputations,
nasty facial lacerations.
- Don't go anywhere. OK?
- Relax.
- Promise?
- You're handling this.
I am handling it.
You can't put him here.
Doctors need access!
What went wrong last night?
Kinda busy here, Arizona.
I have four surgeries and a
kid on life support. I'm busy too.
- What went wrong?
- Not any better. In the hall!
We went out. To a
four star restaurant.
Best in Seattle. Supposed
to be fun. Romantic.
But you order a salad when
they make delicious French food.
You picked at it, barely
spoke and then bolted.
What went wrong?
Did I do something?
I wasn't feeling it. I
was exhausted. Sorry.
Hey! I said the hall! The hall!
Fill me in, O'Malley.
Put in the chest tube,
but there was no blood.
Tried another, but
there's no pulse.
- How long's he been down?
- Twenty minutes.
- Open his chest...
- He's gone.
- He's supposed to graduate...
- O'Malley, let it go. He's gone.
You can't save him. Move
on to save the people you can.
There's more trauma coming in.
- O'Malley. Now! Move!
- Call it, Grey.
Time of death, 9:24.
It could be anything. Could
be scar tissue. Wait and see.
- It's a tumor.
- You don't know that.
Denny Duquette is
standing behind you.
It's a tumor. Right, Denny?
Yeah. It's good to
see you, Dr. Bailey.
You can't see him. Because you
don't have a tumor. But he says hi.
Tell Denny Duquette
I said, "Go home."
- It's a tumor.
- Wait and see.
I'm sorry, I'm crying
more than usual.
You said it's shock, is that it?
Yeah. Also the morphine.
I should've slept with David.
I thought about it,
but he was sweet and funny...
I would've fallen
in love with him.
And I didn't want a
relationship till after school.
I don't like to do
things halfway.
I was doing school. And
then I was gonna do life.
And now... David's dead.
- David's dead.
- How's the CT, Karev?
Stomach herniating into her hemithorax
from a huge lac in her diaphragm.
OK. Becca, we're taking
you to surgery soon.
I should have had sex with
David when I had the chance.
Dana... Is she OK?
The paramedics
haven't brought her in yet,
but as soon they do, I'll let you know.
Do you have family we can contact?
They're in Argentina.
Supposed to fly there tomorrow.
It's D-Day.
- It's what?
- That's what Dana calls it.
Parents don't have the money
to let me stay. I have to go back.
Both knew D-Day was coming.
Tried to break up with
her to make it easier.
I'd switch classes every semester
so we didn't have any together...
but it didn't matter.
I couldn't stay away.
When you love
someone... Love is love.
Doesn't matter that you're
not supposed to be together.
How's he doing?
He's starting to stabilize.
Good. Looks like
he's ready for CT.
I think...
maybe she got out in time.
Maybe she's not hurt that bad.
Because when I turned around...
she wasn't there.
She was not there anymore.
OK, X-ray's really
backed up, but...
- That's Pete.
- What?
David's friend. Pete.
The red sneakers.
Help me. He's bleeding through
the dressing on the chest wound.
Pulse is 220!
Pericardial effusion. Get me
a syringe and a spinal needle.
I'm going in through the wound.
I need another syringe. Now.
- There's too much blood.
- Keep syringes coming.
Give me a 60cc this time.
- Asystole. He's flat-lining.
- Get the cardio board.
Just keep holding pressure.
Starting compressions on
my count. One, two, three.
- George...
- Keep putting pressure.
I'm not losing another one.
Thank you.
You're scrubbing in? I
thought I was doing this solo.
You are.
Why aren't you sitting
in a corner, reading?
It's a big day, Meredith.
Taking precautions.
Afraid I'm gonna kill the
patient on my wedding day?
It's a routine colectomy.
I'm not gonna kill him.
I know. You're gonna do
great. Pretend I'm not even here.
OK. OK. Scalpel.
Great. Very nice.
What?
The way you asked for the scalpel.
You didn't mumble. You took charge.
Right off the bat. Loud
and clear. "Scalpel."
It was good. Very impressive.
Great.
I'm gonna get started now, so...
Of course. You won't
even know I'm here.
- There we go.
- Thanks.
I'll toast to the fact
they found each other.
Doesn't bring up the future,
about whether they'll make it.
- It's good, right?
- Mm-hm.
You said you were tired.
You can't be that exhausted if
you're working on your day off.
- I rallied.
- You rallied?
- Yeah.
- You're lying.
No, I love the ER. Can
you hold, please? Thanks.
- You love the ER?
- Can't get enough of it. It's fun.
- You should tell her.
- Yeah... Suck it, Mark.
Hey! We need more
blood in Trauma Two. Go!
Dr. Hunt, I just lost another one.
My patients are dying. Pull me.
That's for me to decide.
There's an ambulance coming.
- I'm in over my head.
- Walk away, O'Malley!
That's Michelle. She dyed
her hair for graduation.
Look.
I'm looking, I
don't see anything.
Because there's nothing
there. Scan's clean.
I told you.
Then why is Denny back?
The man's a hallucination.
- There has to be
something there.
- Izzie, if it's clear, then...
I want to go to this wedding.
I want to watch the bride walk down
the aisle. I want to hear the vows.
I want to catch the bouquet.
I planned this wedding
down to the last detail,
it's the perfect wedding.
This wedding is perfect.
You know how much
I wanna be there.
So why would I tell
you about Denny?
Today of all days?
Why wouldn't I just wait?
Denny is back. That
means something is there.
It's not like we can
just map the brain
for hallucinations the
way we do with seizures.
What are hallucinations?
Hallucinations are
neurons firing in the brain.
- Exactly.
- Why?
It's never been done
before, but if we can somehow
induce your hallucination,
there's a chance we
could pick it up on an EEG.
We could pinpoint the part of
the brain that's hallucinating.
- Trauma One's open.
- What do we have?
Had a pulse, but we haven't been
able to get one for over 30 minutes.
I'm pretty sure we left half
her blood on the side of road.
She's DOA. I just
need you to call it.
Oh, God. Oh, my God.
Crap. Pink sweater.
That's Jordan's girlfriend.
- Move her out.
- Need you to call it.
Dana! Dana, no!
Dana! No, I need to see her!
- Time of death, 10:45.
- Coding. Get a crash cart.
No. No, we are closed to trauma.
Because we have trauma
coming out of our butts!
You have a nice day,
too! Oh, for the love of...
So the ER is fun, but I'm not?
- Arizona...
- You can get enough of me?
Is that what you're saying?
Do you just want to end this?
There are women
lining up. I'm hot.
If you want out, you should
just say so. I can take it.
Maybe this was just
a fling. Maybe it's over.
Maybe it is.
Got some adhesions. Need to
dissect down to mobilize the sigmoid.
Bovie, please.
Mm... Mm-mm. Mm-mm.
Do you have something
you'd like to say?
No, no. You're doing fine.
How's the solo surgery
coming along, Grey?
I think it's going OK, but you
should probably ask the chief.
She's doing great.
Chose a cautery at one point
when I might have gone with scissors,
but she made it work.
We'll be out of here in
plenty of time for the wedding.
- Good. Then she won't
have any excuses.
- Excuse me?
This is the second time
I've been Derek's best man.
I have to come up with a toast,
offer words of wisdom. A lot of work.
I don't want to be his best man a
third time, if you know what I mean.
You came in here to threaten me?
I'm his best man. That's my job.
Mm.
What now?
No, it's OK. It's fine.
Everything's fine, right? I
don't need to say anything.
Hmm.
So now what? I just...
try to have a hallucination?
- Yeah.
- OK.
Stevens, is it always
Denny? No one else?
- Yeah.
- Hm...
- What?
- Nothing. Um...
Makes sense. It's
the man you love...
- He's not the man I love.
- He's not?
I mean, I love Denny, I
will always love Denny.
He means a lot to me.
But I think I hallucinate Denny because
I associate him with death and dying.
When I think about my future,
who I am and who I wanna be,
how I want to spend my life...
When you get that flutter in your chest.
Alex. Alex is the man I love.
Karev.
I love Alex Karev.
So let's find this tumor
and get it out of me
so we can have
our perfect wedding,
a wedding not wasted on two
people who don't appreciate weddings.
- I can hear you.
- I mean for you to hear me.
What if I can't make him appear?
We'll wait until he appears.
You have to be at the church
in two hours. It could be more.
- I'll be late.
- No! No being late.
I'll make him
appear. I can do this.
Come on, Denny...
How are my friends doing?
Just tell me. I can take it.
I mean, I can't but I can.
Did someone else die?
Why don't you tell me your
speech? Your graduation speech.
I can take it.
Becca. Just... Just
give me your speech.
You worked hard on it. So
you should do it. Right now.
Come on.
Today's the day my life begins.
Today, I become a
citizen of the world.
Today, I become a grown-up.
Today, I become accountable to
someone other than myself and my parents,
accountable for
more than my grades.
Today I become
accountable to the world.
To the future.
To all the possibilities
that life has to offer.
Starting today...
- Come on, Denny. Come on.
- My job is to show up,
wide-eyed and willing and ready.
For what, I don't know.
For anything. For everything.
Come on, Denny. Come on.
- Charge to 360.
- To take on life.
- Nice job, Meredith.
- To take on love.
All the times I didn't ask for you,
you were here. Now I'm asking. Please.
Please come to me
now. Please help me now.
Come on, Denny.
You come to me now.
Denny...
To take on the
responsibility and possibility.
Today, my friends,
our lives begin.
Time of death, 13:02.
And I, for one...
Denny.
- Denny!
- There.
- Can't wait.
- I'm here for you, Izzie.
It's right there.
These the results
from the tesla 7 MRI?
Yeah. The part of the brain that
reacted during the hallucination?
It was the other temporal lobe.
And that... That's the tumor?
Yeah. Tiny.
Too small to pick
up on a normal MRI.
If it's that small, how
are you going to get to it?
I wish there was
something I could do for her.
I wish I could.
I like Stevens. She's
one of the good ones.
I wish there was
something I could do for her.
I...
I know something you can do.
I just want you to
know that I'm hurt.
I am hurt and I am angry.
I thought we had something,
we were going somewhere.
If you're just making the rounds of
girl surgeons then you ought to know...
- We went to a fancy restaurant!
- What?
We went to a fancy restaurant.
The nicest restaurant in Seattle.
The salad I ordered...
The salad cost $26.95.
The wine you ordered
cost $125 a bottle.
I didn't even look at the entrees
because I was already out 75 bucks,
and I don't even like salad.
- Then the bill came and you...
- I paid.
You know what I was doing
before they brought the check?
I was counting in my head,
trying to figure out how I was
going to buy food the rest of the week
if my half was $75, because I
don't have seventy-five dollars.
Because my father disowned me and
cleared out my bank account. I'm broke!
And I am exhausted, Arizona.
I'm working in the ER
because I need the money.
Six people died on my
watch today and I'm fried.
I wanted to stay in last night.
I thought... I thought last
night would be the night. For us.
You know, our night.
But you wanted to go to a fancy
restaurant, and I can't do that.
- I can't.
- It's OK. It's OK. Hey.
So we stay in.
And we'll eat... sandwiches.
You don't even like sandwiches.
But I like the girl who
has the sandwiches.
- OK?
- OK.
I don't like sandwiches
either. I like pizza.
I like pizza, too.
Meredith?
Yes, sir?
I've been reading
your mother's journals.
I wish she was here today.
I don't know how she would've
felt about me getting married.
No. Not for that. For this.
Your first solo surgery.
She probably would've said, with all the
mistakes, I'm lucky the patient's alive.
That's right. But I also know
she would have been thrilled.
She wouldn't have been able to
tell you, but she would've been.
Thank you, sir.
- Hey!
- Hey.
You. Best wedding present ever.
- And you know why?
- No.
Because I have to go home
and put on a corset and
pantyhose and petticoat.
And look like one of those
idiots on top of a wedding cake,
then I have to
walk down the aisle
and have everyone
staring at me, but it's OK.
Because I got to cut someone
open from start to finish.
I saved a life.
- Um...
- What?
What do you say we
make this day even better?
Good work today, O'Malley.
Good work? They're
dead. All those kids.
- Not all of them.
- The one I didn't
touch was fine.
I was able to get to her.
And the reason I was, was
because I had you on my team.
You saved that girl
today as much as I did.
Trauma's a team sport, O'Malley.
You don't have to
be the hero, you just...
You just have to go
where you're needed.
Alex...
Bailey says Shepherd
found another tumor.
In Izzie's brain. Did you hear?
I heard. Alex...
He doesn't think he's
gonna get it out this time.
I think...
I think she's gonna die on me.
I think she's really gonna die.
Aren't you supposed to be
getting ready for a wedding?
That's what I came
to talk to you about.
Hi, I'm Dr. Grey. I'm gonna
take care of your central line.
OK.
You're crying.
You're breathing.
My shoes are, uh,
in the closet. Bailey?
Shoes. Right.
You're supposed to be
helping me get ready.
I can still go, right? I mean,
the tumor's not going anywhere.
Yeah, you can go.
OK, well, we don't
wanna be late.
- Bailey?
- Uh... Here she comes.
Mer! You're supposed
to be at the church!
I'm going. I just came
to say, this isn't my dress.
Of course it's your
dress. It's perfect.
- What are you talking about?
- This dress is not for me.
I don't... What?
Oh, God, I knew you were gonna
freak out before the wedding.
Mer, Derek loves
you. Marriage is good.
Tell her, it's good.
She's saying it's not
her wedding dress.
She's right.
The dress, it
isn't for Meredith.
Oh, Mer...
I don't...
I don't even know how to...
I...
Thank you.
OK, so who's the maid
of honor? Me or Cristina?
Cristina.
Alex... He needs a best man,
and he was asking for you.
- So what, I'm leftovers?
- You tried to save my life.
That makes you honorable.
♪ Let's take a better look ♪
♪ Beyond a story book ♪
♪ And learn our souls ♪
♪ Are all we own ♪
♪ Before we turn to stone ♪
Take my hand.
♪ With clearer heads ♪
Dearly beloved, we
are gathered here today
to celebrate the wedding
of Alexander Michael Karev
and Isobel Catherine Stevens.
This is a sacred rite...
an ancient rite.
As Isobel and Alex
prepare to join their lives,
it is important to understand
that everyone present
has played a part
in shaping their lives,
and will continue to play a vital
role in their continuing future.
And thus, we are here not only to
witness their vows to each other,
but to bestow upon
them our blessing.
And now, the couple
will read their vows.
We didn't write anything.
No. Wait, I have
something I want to say.
Today's the day my life begins.
All my life I've been just
me. Just a smart mouth kid.
Today, I become a man.
Today, I become a husband.
Today, I become accountable
to someone other than myself.
Today I become accountable
to you. To our future.
To all the possibilities that
our marriage has to offer.
Together, no matter
what happens, I'll be ready.
For anything. For everything.
To take on life.
To take on love.
To take on possibility
and responsibility.
Today, Izzie Stevens,
our life together begins.
And I, for one, can't wait.
I love you.
- Not yet.
- Hurry up.
By the power vested in me by
God and the state of Washington,
I now pronounce
you husband and wife.
- Now?
- Now.
♪ But brother how
we must atone ♪
You never know the biggest
day of your life is the biggest day.
Not until it's happening.
♪ Before we turn to stone ♪
Hey, hey... It's OK. It's
just hair. You don't need it.
It's just gonna
keep falling out.
We'll shave it off. I bet
you look good bald. OK?
Hey.
Stop. You're beautiful.
You don't recognize the
biggest day of your life.
Not until you're right
in the middle of it.
The day you commit to
something or someone...
The day you get
your heart broken...
Best non-wedding day ever.
Wanna go again?
The day you meet your soul mate.
The day you realize
there's not enough time...
because you
want to live forever.
Those are the biggest days.
The perfect days.
You know?
I'll bet you made
a beautiful bride.
It was a beautiful day.
You put the scarf on.
I told you, you don't need it.
You look gorgeous without it.
He's right.
Go away now.
Go away, I want to be alone...
with my husband.
My wife is hot.