Every patient's story
starts the same way.
It starts with them being fine.
It starts in the "before."
They cling to this moment,
this memory of being fine,
this before, as
though talking about it
may somehow bring it back.
- Long time.
- Naomi.
We got an ICU bed
all ready for him.
But what they
don't realize is that
the fact that they're
talking about it to us,
their doctors...
He was fine. We went to lunch...
means there's no going back.
By the time they see us,
they're already in the "after."
♪ She's letting everything in ♪
♪ Trouble is that
it's gotta come out ♪
What the hell are you doing?
The interns are broken.
They've been punished for
taking out their own appendixes
and it's making them
hate medicine. They're lost,
and they've forgotten
this thing they hate
is actually a thing they love,
so I'm gonna remind them.
Is this about Denny?
Is this some kind of dead
boyfriend art therapy?
This is not about Denny.
It's about the interns.
- Who cares? They're losers...
- They're not!
They're not. They're just...
They need to have a
little fun. And so do I.
Where are the damn scissors?
They're right in front of you.
Oh.
- Right.
- Iz...
Will you hand me
that large bow, please?
Great. Just put it down.
See? It's gonna be great.
Does he know how
he got the parasite?
From eating unwashed
fruit in Mexico.
- He's bradycardic.
- And hypotensive?
A reaction to the fentanyl drip.
Stop the drip, push Narcan...
Wait! Derek, he was in status.
If you take him
off and he seizes,
there could be brain damage.
Better hope that doesn't happen.
Hope?
That's what your
plan is hinging on?
Hoping the worst doesn't happen?
I'm hoping he's stopped seizing.
If we don't reverse the drip,
his heart is going to arrest.
So unless you
have a better idea.
Push the Narcan.
And while every patient's story
starts the same way,
how the story ends...
depends on us, on how
well we diagnose and treat.
We know the
story hinges on us...
He's in v-fib. Get
the crash cart.
And we all want to be the hero.
Morning, Chief. I heard
there was a guy here
with worms in his brain.
Does anyone know the medical
term for worms in the brain?
Dr. Stevens requested you
today for a special project.
OK, take an envelope,
pass the rest back.
Do not open them,
you'll need them
for the first game
we're gonna play.
That's what we're doing
today? Playing games?
Cheer up. We are
gonna have so much fun!
Don't open! Don't you know
how to play a simple game?
- I did when I was eight.
- Let's just go.
Dr. Bailey's with Addison,
so I'm gonna hand
out your assignments.
Addison's in the hospital?
Her brother was admitted
with parasites in his brain.
Addison's brother has
neurocysticercosis?
- See?
- Huh?
That's what I'm taking about!
I cleared my schedule.
You didn't have
to do that. I'm fine.
Your brother has parasites.
I cleared my schedule.
You cut your hair.
- Yeah.
- I like it. Dr. Miranda Bailey.
I'm sorry. Miranda,
Naomi. Naomi, Miranda.
Naomi's our fertility
specialist at Oceanside
and one of my oldest friends.
- Nice to meet you, Miranda.
- How is he?
- I don't know.
- He's groggy.
His eyes are open but
I don't think he's awake.
He hasn't tried to kill me.
Her brother hates me.
People pick sides
in a divorce, Derek.
He picked sides in the marriage.
He first seized during
sex with his girlfriend.
Wonder why she's not here?
Oh, she is.
Naomi?
I'm going in there.
- You and Archer?
- No.
Well, yeah. I don't know.
I don't know what we are.
How's Sam?
Sam's good. And how's...
Meredith, is that her name?
She's good.
- Good.
- Yeah.
Look at us.
We're making polite
conversation about your girlfriend.
You two are divorced,
me and Sam are divorced.
I'm with Archer, sort of...
What the hell happened?
I mean, you wrote
Addison a song, Derek.
Let's forget about the song.
- Enough about the song.
- What?
You wrote her her own love song
and sang it to her
at the wedding.
Mark wrote it or Sam.
I don't remember.
I do. I was drunk at the time,
but I remember thinking
you were going to last forever.
We were all gonna last forever.
Yeah.
You should call
Sam. He misses you.
Yeah.
- How'd you sleep?
- Not too well.
- Shoulder pain?
- No. Pain in the ass wife.
I kept him up
because I was afraid
my aneurysm was gonna explode
and I was gonna die.
- Hi, I'm Dr. Karev.
- Where's Dr. Grey?
She's supposed
to be in my surgery.
She and Dr. Shepherd got
called in on an emergency.
So he's not going to get
to your aneurysm until later.
- Wha... Later when?
- Could be a few hours.
- Could be tomorrow.
- Tomorrow?
She's waited until
tomorrow. Today is tomorrow.
- I'm sorry, who are you?
- I'm her husband.
- I look like this because...
- I ran him over with our car.
Before I knew I had this
huge time bomb in my head.
When I was just a big
old pregnant person
waiting for her baby.
So, just... please,
if he could get to me
sooner rather than later...
Um...
- What's the emergency?
- Addison's brother.
Addison's here?
We were having dinner
and he just passed out.
I am telling you, it is
probably just my hernia.
He has an inguinal hernia.
It doesn't seem to be
the source of obstruction.
It's gonna take these
doctors a long time
to figure this out. I'm fine.
You gotta go to work.
He hates it when
we try to help him.
He's a lot like my
second graders that way.
OK, Daddy. You win.
I have my cell, so
call me if you need me.
Bye.
I have colorectal cancer.
I've had five polyps removed
in the last three
years and radiation.
My daughter doesn't know
and I'd like to keep it that way.
Um... Dr. Yang's going to set
you up for a CT with contrast.
Where have you been
treated? We'll need your records.
Columbia Hospital
in Verona. Dr. Shulty.
I... I work here now.
I saw you were in and I...
You waited till she left
to come in and say hello.
Just like you to face
up to things like a man.
You should tell her about the
cancer. She deserves to know.
You lost the right to tell
me anything about her
when you broke off your
engagement in a two line email.
♪ Our eyes met
over the cadaver ♪
♪ And I knew I had to have her ♪
What was the next line?
Can we talk about
something else?
♪ Had his mitral valve
grown too thick? ♪
♪ Is that what made
our cadaver so sick? ♪
- Greatest love song
of all time.
- Hey!
You get to the part where Derek
rhymes "gross anatomy class"
with "Addison's fine ass,"
because I wrote that line.
- Oh, my bad.
- No, no, it's fine. I, uh...
I think it sounds
like a fine song.
Archie, heard you
were gonna let Derek
remove those suckers
from your brain.
- Maybe.
- He is.
I hate surgery.
Especially brain surgery.
Yeah.
Being a neurologist you probably
see a lot of patients post-op
who are scrambled
eggs up there...
You're not helping.
We're sitting here trying to
convince him that surgery is...
Is not an option.
According to these
scans, the single cyst
you had on your last CT
has now multiplied by eight,
all clogging the third ventricle.
There's no way I could
surgically navigate
through a mess like that
without rupturing one.
So, what does that mean?
You're in a room full
of doctors, Addison,
who are all being
very quiet right now.
I'm gonna die.
That's what it means.
Inside each one
of your envelopes
is the name of a surgery.
Your task is to drape
your patients accordingly.
On your marks, get set... Go!
Come on, lighten up,
this is supposed to be fun.
Don't take it so seriously.
You suck at this! My grandmother
could drape better than you!
I'm sorry. I'll
try to do better...
No, you're doing great.
I'm trash talking. I'm
having fun. It's just... fun.
What are you...? Woo!
Woo! Woo! Woo!
Looking good! Good job!
Done!
Laparoscopic cholecystectomy
- Yeah, that's good.
- Your next challenge.
- I'm done, too.
A whipple is for
pancreatic cancer.
Were you planning on
going in through the mouth?
Start over.
There's just no way, Addie.
Dr. Conroy at Cedars and
Larry at Mayo, they agree...
I've put you in a tiny box.
After the divorce I made
you petty and inconsequential
and nothing special,
so that you could fit
into this tiny, little box
that would help me get
out of bed in the morning.
But now...
now I have to take
you out of the box
because I need to
believe that you can do this,
that you can save my brother.
I need you to be a god.
Just today. Be a god.
Montgomery,
Archer. I'm a friend.
I'm Dr. Miranda Bailey.
I'm a friend of Addison's.
- Which one are you?
- I'm sorry?
Archer is Addison's brother.
Archer's girlfriend is
Addison's best friend
who married Derek's best
friend who Derek hasn't spoken to
- since the divorce.
- That would be me.
The ex-husband,
Dr. Samuel Bennett.
Sorry, I didn't think
the ex-husband
would show up at the
ex-wife's boyfriend's bedside.
Don't worry about it. Even
I don't know why I'm here.
- But... yeah.
- Third floor. Room 3420.
Thank you.
- Dr. Bennett.
- Uh... Sam.
Dr. Shepherd is still
studying the scans
looking for a way to operate
but it looks like
a difficult case.
Right.
Hey, Addison's brother
probably isn't gonna make it.
- His cysts are inoperable.
- Worms in the brain.
Not how you want to go.
I didn't know
Addison had a brother.
You'd think Derek would have
said something at some point.
Or sang something
while he played his guitar.
- Speak English.
- Derek used to play guitar.
Owen's ex-fiancée
is in the hospital.
Mm-hm. His ex-fiancée
he never told me about.
- What's wrong with her?
- She calls her dad "daddy."
No, what's wrong with her?
Why is she in the hospital?
She isn't. Daddy is.
You should ask Owen
if he plays the guitar.
"Find Dr. Sloan,
ask his symptoms,
diagnose him correctly to
receive your next challenge!"
What are your symptoms?
Right now, I'm battling
a rapid heart rate,
also feeling a little flushed.
I don't even want to mention
what's going on below the belt.
I don't do dirty, secret
flirting with you, anymore.
I told you, if you want to
go public with me, with us,
I will do dirty public flirting.
I mean, I will flirt publicly,
not dirtily...
maybe a little dirtily.
Please tell me your
symptoms so I can concentrate.
Tachycardia,
angioedema, hypotension,
severe chest and abdominal pain,
difficulty breathing,
throat closing.
Anaphylactic shock!
- Whoa! Whoa. Whoa. whoa. Foul!
- What?
- You heard her answer.
- The whole hospital heard.
You should've kept a distance.
New symptoms. Resume play.
Woo!
You must have questions, so ask.
When was his last polypectomy,
since you're familiar
with the patient?
- Not what I meant.
- I know what you meant.
- Dr. Yang, symptoms?
- Not a good time...
Heavy feeling in the abdomen,
accompanied by nausea
and an acute pulling
sensation in the scrotum.
Testicular cancer!
Woo!
- Cristina...
- I have to get
Mr. Whitman to the CT.
I wasn't doing anyone
any good at school so...
Owen?
I don't understand. What...?
I work here.
What do you mean?
- Beth.
- When did you get back?
I just saw your
mom. She didn't...
I thought you were in Iraq.
I've been praying
for you every night.
Every night, I'm on my knees,
praying that you're
gonna make it back,
that you'll make it
another 24 hours,
that you... you'll make it home.
Owen, you're back!
- What is she doing?
- It looks like she's praying.
Mm, no... Addie doesn't pray.
- What's she doing?
- Uh, she's praying.
Addison doesn't pray.
She must be hiding.
I can hear you. I'm not
hiding, I am trying to pray,
but I don't know how
because I'm a WASP.
We only go to
church on Christmas.
You guys go. I got this.
♪ It's the first time ♪
♪ That I've seen you in ages ♪
♪ Hold on my old time bomb ♪
I have no clout with God.
God doesn't even know who I am.
Which sucks, because I could...
I could use some help.
Dear God, I need your guidance.
- I kissed a peds surgeon.
- You kissed a peds surgeon?
I never thought I'd end up
with a woman. Not until lately.
That's not the problem, the
problem is the peds thing.
She's perky...
and has butterflies
on her scrub cap.
But she's... also hot.
Really hot. So...
help me get over
the butterflies.
Amen.
♪ Everyone gather
to the chapel ♪
♪ To the chapel ♪
You're an amazing
doctor, you save babies.
God knows who you are.
Do you really
believe in all this?
In God?
Sometimes.
Mm. Most of the time.
When it counts.
Your wife's in the
chapel, praying.
She's not my wife
and she doesn't pray.
- How are you?
- Hey.
You know, midlife crisis.
I got an earring, but I let the
hole close up the very next day.
That would have
been a good look.
I met, uh... Meredith.
Uh-huh.
She's not a midlife
crisis. She's the real thing.
That's great. I'm
happy for you, man.
- Happy for you.
- Yeah.
- I should have called...
- No.
Stayed in touch. It's my fault.
People move, they
change, we all did.
- Yeah.
- So... But, yeah.
She's praying.
Yeah. She's expecting a miracle.
I can't deliver one.
I've seen patients with one
cyst in the ventricle, maybe two.
He has eight.
There is no way I can
get a scope in there
without rupturing
one. There's too many.
Maybe you're just too close to
it. What if there were just one?
Explain to me how you
would remove just that one.
110 over 80.
What's the prize for winning?
- They need a prize.
- They're getting a prize.
A really big prize.
- I need a prize.
- What's going on?
Uh, my patients
needed a distraction
and Izzie needed real patients.
- How's it going?
- It's going great. We're having fun.
Dr. Grey! Am I
going to surgery now?
Could be any time now.
What?
- I can't find it.
- Wh...?
Is something wrong? Is
the baby's heart not beating?
You're on the kid's ass.
The heart's over here.
It's not what you think.
I can guarantee I'm not as
much of an ass as you think I am.
Does your mother
know you're back?
Page me when this is done.
All right, Archer. I need to
create room in the ventricle
so I can maneuver the scope.
If I deflate each cyst, the
scope can remove them.
The cysts will rupture.
I'm going to grab
each one with forceps,
pull it up, suction the fluid.
Suction would
have to be precise.
It will be.
- You can't do it.
- I think I can.
Control the way
the cyst ruptures?
No, he can't.
You want me to go
down fighting but...
- Coward.
- Excuse me?
You're a coward by trade.
You're a neurologist.
You feed off us,
refer your patients to us,
let us assume
the responsibility,
and if something
happens, well...
I can assume the responsibility.
The question is, can you?
- A peds surgery fellowship?
- Yep.
Just when I'm almost done
with general surgery residency.
- Crazy, huh?
- No. Just... surprising.
You don't seem like
a peds person to me.
- Why not?
- Because you don't smile.
- Peds people smile.
- I smile.
Well, I'm not
going to smile now.
But I do smile. I
smile frequently.
- Hey. He under yet?
- Yeah.
A peds surgery fellowship?
Huh.
I have a child. I am
familiar with children.
I am going to be an
excellent pediatric surgeon!
You're gonna want to keep that
temper in check around the kids.
Weird seeing
Archie on that table.
Yeah.
Asthma. Looks like I'm low.
Chris, refill this for
Dr. Bennett here.
OK.
- Thanks.
- It's good practice.
Asthma's big with the kids.
Say it, Derek. Come on,
say it, say it, say it, say it...
OK, everybody. It's a
beautiful day to save lives.
Scalpel.
You're gonna have to tell her...
This is Beth we're
talking about.
She worries herself sick
when one of her
students gets the sniffles.
She can't handle bad
news. She's a sunshine girl.
And you used to
know that about her.
Well, she'll find
out eventually.
- Dr. Yang!
- What's going on?
Ruth, call the Chief
and reserve an OR.
- Owen?
- It's a...
It's a complication.
He needs surgery.
A complication from what?
He's going to be OK. I'll
keep you updated. Let's go.
Entering the third ventricle.
Securing cyst number one.
Deflating cyst one.
Applying suction.
Any sign of the scolex?
There it is.
One at a time.
OK. I need to be distracted.
Someone talk about something
other than what's
going on with my brother.
Uh, Mark is good at
talking about himself.
I've been using endoscopy for
head and neck cancer resections.
If I can just focus the
criteria for patients,
I might have a
breakthrough on my hands.
- What happened to you?
- He met someone.
Dr. Grey.
Dr. Torres said I
had to eat. I'm sorry.
It's OK. How is it?
It's amazing.
I'm sorry. It's bland.
It's really bland.
I need my surgery now!
What kind of hospital is this?
How long am I
supposed to wait...
Stop it!
Look... if you don't settle down
your blood pressure's gonna rise
and you're gonna
start contracting.
Sorry, because I don't know you,
but you really need
to shut up, OK?
All right, look. There.
Look, there's your son's face.
That's what you
need to hold on to
for the next couple
of hours, OK?
Is that a tumor?
He's gonna need more
aggressive treatment.
- He'll have to tell
his daughter now.
- He won't.
Her mother died
when she was little.
He feels that's enough
sadness for anyone.
He sheltered her, she always
had a nice car, clothes, anything.
She'll find out eventually.
She used to call me in tears
when there was a
spider in her apartment.
Became a joke
between Michael and I.
Neither of us could be out
of town at the same time
in case Beth found a bug.
When he needs to
go through chemo
or gets so sick he
needs hospice care,
she'll find out when
it's already over.
She deserves more than that.
What's the number?
Seven cysts, seven scolices.
OK, one more.
Damn it!
He's getting bradycardic.
See if the flow is blocked.
Asystole. Start the code clock.
- Derek, asystole.
- Where the hell is it?
Get the crash
cart. Compressions!
No! Stop. Nobody move.
We can't. I have
to find the worm.
- But he's...
- We have two, three
minutes. Stop.
How long's he been down?
Two minutes, twenty seconds.
There.
Got it.
Damn it.
It's starting to tear apart.
Maybe if I rotate and
reverse it back. Yeah.
And that's number eight.
Heartrate's coming back up!
OK.
Thank you, everybody. You made
some friends of mine very happy.
Just got out of surgery.
What's going on?
- Any minute.
- She needs a prize.
Big prize, but not too big,
because they did take
out their own appendixes
and they're being punished
and you think they're not even
qualified to hold a clamp. So...
Do you have prizes like that?
They got their symptoms
from their final patients.
Get out the finish line,
it's gonna be close.
- Here they come!
- Come on!
Come on, bring it in!
♪ Roll roll it gal roll it gal ♪
♪ Roll control
it gal roll it gal ♪
♪ Roll roll it gal roll it gal ♪
♪ Roll control
it gal roll it gal ♪
♪ When them fly
up in ya face gal ♪
- George?
- Three-way tie.
- Ok, final diagnosis?
- Motion sickness!
- No!
- Dengue Fever!
- Neurocycticercosis!
Ladies and gentlemen, a winner!
Whoo! Ha!
Nicely done.
- Yes!
- Worms?
Wait, what's the prize?
You get to scrub in on
Shepherd's craniotomy
and hold the doomsday sucker.
- What's a doomsday sucker?
- Doomsday sucker?
It's just a really big sucker.
Dr. Leone call the blood bank.
Dr. Leone, call the blood bank.
It was a hard surgery,
some of the bowel was
dead as we suspected,
but we were able to remove
the diseased parts successfully.
He's in recovery. You can
see him in about an hour.
You don't even
look like yourself.
Excuse me?
You don't.
You look... hard.
And...
Look, I know it
wasn't easy over there,
I hear people come back and...
I know you can't just come back
and be normal right away, but...
He'll be asleep for a couple
hours. You can see him now.
Two lines in an email?
I deserve more than that.
Beth, your dad has
colorectal cancer.
He's been through radiation
treatments and polyp removals.
He didn't tell you...
because he didn't
want to burden you.
He'd like to spare you any pain.
Any more pain.
He had all these friends.
They sang and
they played guitar.
It's like he was a
totally different person.
He was.
It freaks me out a little bit.
I feel like I don't know him.
Well, I don't know Owen.
We don't. We don't know them.
♪ Is love alive? ♪
Sadie. Hey, hold up. Hold up.
I wanted to let you know,
I'm happy to help
you, if you'd like.
Reviewing the basics or putting
in supervised skills lab hours.
Excuse me?
I was a repeater
earlier this year,
I know how easy
it is to get behind.
- I don't need a tutor.
- You don't?
No.
At this point in your training,
you should be able to hear
symptoms, diagnose the problem
and decide whether or
not a patient needs surgery.
Can you do that?
Can you?
Because they think you can.
And they will put you in
situations where you have to.
Sadie, you could hurt someone!
♪ Is love alive? ♪
♪ This is my winter song ♪
I call her. I call my mother.
Once a week.
I haven't told her I'm back,
she thinks that I'm calling from...
I keep the conversations
short. I can't bear for her to know
that the son she
sent off to war is gone.
He's gone.
And if I just got in my car
and drove six miles to see her
she'd be so... sad.
And she would look at me the
same way that Beth does now.
Like I'm not there.
The only time I don't feel like
a ghost is when you look at me.
Because you look at me
and you see me. You see me.
This is me. This... is me.
Please, Cristina, see me.
See me.
♪ Is love alive? ♪
♪ Is love alive?
Is love alive? ♪
♪ Is love alive? ♪
Jen, I am so sorry.
I have you scheduled
first thing tomorrow.
Derek. I'm using
your first name now.
I like you a lot and I'm
starting to consider us friends,
so I'm using your first name
and calling you Derek. And Derek?
I'm begging you please, please
don't make me
wait another night.
- She's good.
- Try being married to her.
You'll never say "no" again.
Dr. Grey.
It would appear that
congratulations are in order.
Thank you, Dr. Sloan.
I'd also like it acknowledged
that I offer these
congratulations
professionally and respectfully,
without any innuendo or
inappropriate body language.
Acknowledged,
Dr. Sloan. Do you know...
What's a doomsday sucker?
- Addison Montgomery.
- Uh, Lexie Grey.
Mark. Addie. Little Grey.
Little Grey? Hmm.
I have to meet you at Joe's
in a bit. I have a craniotomy.
You're holding the
doomsday sucker.
Now?
- Great. Yes! Yes, sir.
- OR 2. See you there.
Doomsday sucker.
Can you believe
Little Grey and...
Did you hear?
Derek's going to propose
to Meredith. How about that?
I'm off to surgery.
What?
Hey.
- Iz, what's going on with you?
- Nothing.
I'm fine. You saw. The interns
are not a bunch of losers.
They know things. They're
gonna make good doctors.
Really, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
She knows nothing. Nothing.
She's a danger to the patients.
I told her she could
tell the Chief or I could.
I wanted to let you know,
because you're her friend.
Although for the life of me,
I don't know how you
two were ever friends.
- What happened?
- I quit.
O'Malley's a little narc.
I'd rather be deemed
a quitter than a cheater.
Did you cheat your
way into the program?
I said I'm not book
smart. You know that.
I learn on my feet.
I thought if I came to
where you were, you could...
Pull you through?
We've seen each
other through a lot.
We're not 25 sleeping our
way through Europe anymore.
We could, though.
Think about it.
We could get on
a plane and go...
No! No.
I can't. I have to work.
I can't just...
Well, you know...
They've sucked the
life right out of you.
- The Meredith I used to know...
- Is right here.
I'm here.
I don't want to sleep my
way through Europe anymore.
I want to be here.
- Sucker at the ready?
- Sucker's at the ready.
- You're mocking me.
- Only a little.
- Damn it. Damn it!
- What? What happened?
- BP's 88 over 60.
- Hang two units of blood.
All joking aside, Dr. Grey,
bring in the doomsday sucker.
- OK.
- Right in here. Go right in here.
Oh my God. Wow.
- Temporary clips.
- Wow.
Wow. Wow!
Wow.
Microsutures, please.
BP's 110 over 72.
OK, get the sucker out of there.
Is that it? Did you get it?
There's good flow.
Yes, we did it.
And that will teach
me to never mock
an eager young intern again.
- I'm an ass.
- You're such an ass.
I shouldn't have blurted.
A little warning
would've been nice.
But you're OK?
You know, it's strange. I...
I expected this
horrible feeling,
this wave of sadness or
something, to just take over.
But... people get divorced,
they meet new
people, they re-marry.
I don't know, maybe it was
seeing Archer in that OR,
it just changed my perspective.
Or something.
But you sort of wished
it had been you first.
Shut it! Are you gonna
tell Derek about the...
Wait. If we called
Meredith the 12-year-old,
What do we call
Lexie? A preschooler?
She's a woman.
- Oh, OK.
- And I'm gonna tell him.
I'm working on it.
There he is!
That's the kind of
welcome I deserve!
- Joe! Scotch for the neuro god!
- You were a god today.
You were a god in that OR.
You slew dragons, you
walked on water. You...
You were a god, but now?
Now you need to
get very tiny again.
And go back in the box.
- How was your craniotomy?
- It was fine.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, I stopped in on Archer.
Things are good.
Good.
♪ Had his mitral valve
gotten too thick? ♪
- Oh, God!
- Shut up.
♪ Is that what made
the cadaver so sick? ♪
We can't remember the chorus.
We got all the way
through the second verse,
your name starts the chorus.
♪ Addison Montgomery
he met her in the summery ♪
It wasn't "summery."
I'd never use
"summery" as a noun.
"I met her in the
summer, she..."
"Summer, she?" Really?
- Yeah.
- Come on.
Clever.
♪ She was cutting
up a very dead body ♪
This is why I
don't stay in touch.
♪ And in her eyes
I saw my life ♪
♪ I knew that she
would be my wife ♪
♪ And she would breathe
the life back into me ♪
♪ Ooo ♪
♪ For every day until eternity ♪
♪ Or until I be as
dead as that body ♪
Aw, gee.
Yeah, you got it.
Oh, hopeless. Cheers.
Wonderful. God.
- What's happening?
- Page Shepherd. Now!