Meredith Grey / Mr. Duff (PVM): You know how when you were a little kid and you believed in fairy tales?
Meredith Grey / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Jennings OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): That fantasy of what your life would be.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Duff (PVM): White dress, Prince Charming who'd carry you away to a castle on a hill.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You'd lie in bed at night and close your eyes and you had complete and utter faith.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Eight hours, 16 ounces of chocolate, and 32 cupcakes, and they still don't taste right.
Meredith Grey / Devo (PVM): No, these are good.
Cristina Yang / Devo (PVM): Martha Stewart would be proud.
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Duff (PVM): Yeah, look where I got her.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Duff (PVM): Santa Claus, the Tooth Fairy, Prince Charming.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Duff (PVM): They were so close, you could taste them.
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): There's something missing, some specific ingredient.
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Why can't I remember?
Meredith Grey / Mr. Duff (PVM): But eventually, you grow up.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Duff (PVM): One day, you open your eyes, and the fairy tale disappears.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Jennings OR Mr. Duff (PVM): Look, just call her.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff (PVM): Call your mother and ask.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Duff (PVM): Most people turn to the things and people they can trust.
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Duff (PVM): I don't want to call my mother.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff (PVM): So let's go sleep at your house tonight.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Duff (PVM): What?
Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff (PVM): I mean, why are we always sleeping at my house?
Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff (PVM): Do you even have one?
Meredith Grey / Mr. Duff (PVM): One what?
Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff OR Mr. Duff (PVM): A house with a closet, with your stuff in it, your personal stuff.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff (PVM): Do you even have one of those?
Hospital Staff Member / Patient (PVM): Good morning.
Devo / Patient (PVM): Hey.
Devo / Patient (PVM): You guys want a cupcake?
Devo / Patient (PVM): Easy made them.
Devo's Father / Patient (PVM): You know, I like it here.
Devo / Patient (PVM): Hey, you said so yourself.
Devo / Patient (PVM): You like to have your things around, sleeping in your own bed.
Devo's Father / Patient (PVM): You're like a health nut, aren't you?
Devo / Mr. Duff OR Patient (PVM): Can I eat muesli every morning?
Devo's Father / Mr. Duff (PVM): No, I don't.
Devo / Mr. Duff (PVM): Okay, the muesli thing, you do.
Devo / Mr. Duff (PVM): The last seven days at least.
Devo's Father / Mr. Duff (PVM): Oh, come on.
Devo / Mr. Duff OR Cricket (PVM): I haven't been here for a whole week.
Devo / Mr. Duff OR Mr. Duff (PVM): See?
Devo / Mr. Duff (PVM): Even they think it's weird.
Dr. Meredith Gray: But the thing is, it's hard to let go of that fairy tale entirely, because almost everyone still has that smallest bit of hope, of faith, that one day they'll open their eyes and it will all come true.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff (PVM): So I've checked the schedule.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff (PVM): I start ENT on the 9th.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff (PVM): It's a light rotation.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff (PVM): Can you get me in then?
Medical Professional (OB/GYN) / Mr. Duff (PVM): Oh, I'm afraid not.
Medical Professional (OB/GYN) / Mr. Duff (PVM): We have openings on the 16th.
Medical Professional (OB/GYN) / Mr. Duff (PVM): There are other options besides termination, you know.
Medical Professional (OB/GYN) / Mr. Duff (PVM): Adoption.
Patient (possibly Devo) / Mr. Duff (PVM): Keeping the baby.
Doctor (likely Neurology or Psychiatry) / Mr. Duff (PVM): You think it over.
Doctor / Mr. Duff (PVM): Call me back.
Doctor / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Mr. Duff (PVM): I'm here all day.
Doctor / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Mr. Duff (PVM): Put me down for the 16th.
Doctor / Mr. Duff (PVM): I'll confirm after I rearrange my schedule.
Doctor / Mr. Duff (PVM): I know this is a difficult decision.
Doctor / Mr. Duff (PVM): Okay, you know the talking part?
Patient (possibly Devo) / Mr. Duff (PVM): I'm not interested.
Doctor (Neurology team) / Patient (PVM): So, Devo, you just had a root canal, correct?
Devo: Yeah.
Devo: Couldn't stop bleeding after.
Devo: Literally.
Devo: Now I'm stuck with you guys.
Doctor (Neurology team) / Devo (PVM): Give me the bullet.
Doctor (Neurology team) / Devo (PVM): A 17-year-old female hospitalized for excessive bleeding status post-root canal.
Doctor (Neurology team) / Devo (PVM): Also had a significant new heart murmur associated with fever.
Doctor (Neurology team) / Devo (PVM): Now a fever along with antibiotics.
Devo: I'm going to die.
Devo: Can you pay for Mom and Dad?
Doctor (Neurology team) / Devo OR Dr. Karev (PVM): You're not dying.
Doctor (Neurology team) / Dr. Karev (PVM): Where are your parents?
Devo: In the cafeteria.
Devo: My freak father likes hospital food.
Doctor (Neurology team) / Dr. Karev (PVM): You're in excellent hands here.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Karev (PVM): Dr. Karev is going to run some labs.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Karev (PVM): And I'll see you with your parents in a little while.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Karev (PVM): Add a bleeding time to the coax.
Alex Karev / Devo (PVM): So what kind of name is Devo anyway?
Patient (Devo) / Devo (PVM): He's a rocker.
Devo: My parents did too much blow.
Esther: I call myself Esther.
Alex Karev / Devo (PVM): Nice skirt, Esther.
Patient (Devo) / Devo OR Devo OR Esther (PVM): What are you, Amish?
Another Patient (Esther) / Esther (PVM): Get a life.
Esther: Haven't you ever seen an Orthodox Jew?
Alex Karev / Mr. Duff (PVM): This guy belongs in psych.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff (PVM): What are you doing turfing him here?
Alex Karev / Mr. Duff (PVM): He's my gift to you.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff (PVM): Had a seizure two days ago and another one this morning.
Alex Karev / Dr. Jennings OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): What are you talking about?
Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff (PVM): It says right here he talks to dead people, his family thinks he's dangerous, and they had him committed.
Alex Karev / Mr. Duff (PVM): That's psych, not neuro.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff (PVM): Man, didn't you go to med school?
Alex Karev / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Yes, and unlike the correspondence school you attended.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Oh, yeah, the W. Stanford, right?
Alex Karev / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Correspondence.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I learned not to jump to conclusions.
Dr. Bailey / Mr. Duff (PVM): Sorry, ladies.
Dr. Bailey / Mr. Duff (PVM): We can't take him back until he's cleared.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff (PVM): So you're dumping him on us.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Duff (PVM): He thinks his seizures are visions.
Mr. Duff: Hello, they're not seizures.
Mr. Duff: I'm psychic.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff (PVM): Of course you are, and I'm a chicken.
Mr. Duff: Yay, genius!
Meredith Grey / Hospital Intercom OR Mr. Duff OR Mr. Duff (PVM): Okay, Mr. Duff, we're gonna start our work up now.
Mr. Duff: Work me up, work me down.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff (PVM): I'm telling you, it's a waste of time.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Duff (PVM): Okay, well, humor us.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff (PVM): Can you grip my fingers, please?
Meredith Grey / Mr. Duff (PVM): Christina.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff (PVM): Mr. Duff?
Meredith Grey / Mr. Duff (PVM): Mr. Duff, are you okay?
Mr. Duff: No.
Mr. Duff: Someone...
Meredith Grey / Mr. Duff OR Mr. Duff (PVM): Someone what?
Mr. Duff: Someone's going to check out.
Mr. Duff: Bye bye.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff (PVM): Man, he's nuts.
Mr. Duff: I'm dizzy, not deaf, lady.
Mr. Duff: And I'm telling you, someone on the fourth floor is going to die.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Jennings (PVM): Fourth floor, dead guide.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Jennings OR Dr. Jennings (PVM): Psychic predicted fourth floor, dead guide.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I need someone to cover me on the 16th.
Doctor (possibly Meredith or Cristina) / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): You in?
George O'Malley / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I'm thinking about letting my hair grow.
George O'Malley / Patient OR Mr. Duff (PVM): Maybe I won't shave, go for the stubble effect.
George O'Malley / Patient (PVM): What do you think?
Cristina Yang / Patient OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): 16th George, can you cover me or not?
George O'Malley / Patient OR Mr. Duff (PVM): Uh, yeah, I guess.
Cristina Yang / Patient OR Mr. Duff (PVM): Why?
Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff (PVM): It's none of your business.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff (PVM): Thank you.
George O'Malley / Patient OR Mr. Duff (PVM): You would be nice.
George O'Malley / Mr. Duff (PVM): It's just that I hardly know anything about you.
Cristina Yang / Patient (PVM): You know I'm from New York.
Cristina Yang / Patient OR Mr. Duff (PVM): You know I like ferry boats.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff (PVM): Enough with the ferry boats.
George O'Malley / Patient OR Mr. Duff (PVM): What about your friends?
Cristina Yang / Patient OR Mr. Duff (PVM): I'm a surgeon.
Cristina Yang / Patient OR Mr. Duff (PVM): I don't have friends.
George O'Malley / Mr. Duff (PVM): Everybody has friends.
George O'Malley / Mr. Duff (PVM): I mean, who do you hang out with?
George O'Malley / Mr. Duff (PVM): What do you do on your days off?
George O'Malley / Patient OR Mr. Duff OR Dr. Jennings (PVM): These are important questions.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Jennings (PVM): Ah, important.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Jennings (PVM): For who?
Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff (PVM): We're having sex every night.
Cristina Yang / Patient OR Mr. Duff (PVM): I think I deserve details.
Cristina Yang / Patient OR Mr. Duff (PVM): You have more details than most.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Duff (PVM): See, this is going somewhere weird.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Duff (PVM): I want facts.
Meredith Grey / Patient OR Mr. Duff (PVM): And until I get them, my pants are staying on.
Cristina Yang / Patient (PVM): Or you could just roll with it.
Cristina Yang / Patient (PVM): Be flexible.
Cristina Yang / Patient (PVM): See what happens.
Meredith Grey / Patient OR Mr. Duff (PVM): I'm not flexible.
Cristina Yang / Patient (PVM): I dare disagree.
Meredith Grey / Patient (PVM): I gotta go.
Cristina Yang / Patient (PVM): Well, find these things out.
Cristina Yang / Patient OR Dr. Jennings (PVM): That's the fun part, you know?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Jennings (PVM): That's the gravy.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff (PVM): That is what I'm talking about.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Duff (PVM): I don't want to be your gravy.
Attending Doctor (likely Dr. Miranda Bailey or Dr. Preston Burke) / Dr. Karev (PVM): Your daughter needs a valve replacement.
Attending Doctor (likely Dr. Miranda Bailey or Dr. Preston Burke) / Dr. Karev (PVM): Tests are indicative of von Willebrand's disease, which explains the excessive bleeding after the root canal.
Parent or Family Member / Devo OR Dr. Karev (PVM): And that means?
Attending Doctor (likely Dr. Miranda Bailey or Dr. Preston Burke) / Devo (PVM): Devo can't take the blood thinners necessary to maintain a mechanical heart valve.
Attending Doctor (likely Dr. Miranda Bailey or Dr. Preston Burke) / Dr. Karev (PVM): We're suggesting a porcine valve instead.
Parent or Family Member / Devo (PVM): Porcine?
Parent or Family Member / Devo (PVM): As in pig?
Attending Doctor (likely Dr. Miranda Bailey or Dr. Preston Burke) / Dr. Karev (PVM): It's the standard of care for someone in this situation.
Parent or Family Member / Devo OR Devo (PVM): Pig, huh?
Attending Doctor (likely Dr. Miranda Bailey or Dr. Preston Burke) / Devo OR Dr. Jennings (PVM): It's the other white meat.
Parent (likely Mrs. Glass) / Dr. Jennings (PVM): I don't care what you have to do.
Parent (likely Mrs. Glass) / Dr. Jennings (PVM): Save my daughter's life.
Hospital PA System / Hospital Intercom (PVM): Dr. Jennings to OR7.
Surgeon (possibly Dr. Jennings) / Dr. Jennings OR Hospital Intercom OR Dr. Jennings (PVM): I'm removing the lump now.
Nurse or Surgical Assistant / Dr. Jennings (PVM): Someone said you guys have a psychic running around here.
Nurse or Surgical Assistant / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Jennings (PVM): Is that true?
Surgeon (possibly Dr. Jennings) / Dr. Jennings OR Mr. Duff (PVM): I did not even hear you say that.
Mr. Duff / Mr. Duff (PVM): I predicted someone would die on the fourth floor.
Doctor (possibly Dr. Jennings) / Dr. Jennings OR Mr. Duff (PVM): ICU's on the fourth floor.
Doctor (possibly Dr. Jennings) / Dr. Jennings (PVM): People die all the time.
Doctor (possibly Dr. Jennings) / Dr. Jennings OR Mr. Duff (PVM): OK.
Surgeon (possibly Dr. Jennings) / Dr. Jennings OR Dr. Jennings (PVM): We'll be finishing up here, Mrs. Glass.
Surgeon (possibly Dr. Jennings) / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Dr. Jennings (PVM): We'll take this down the path, get the results of the frozen section biopsy, and see you in a few hours.
Doctor or Nurse / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Seriously, the guy's just playing mind games.
Doctor or Nurse / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I can see further into the future than he can.
Doctor or Nurse / Dr. Jennings (PVM): Why do you even care about this, Stevens?
Stevens / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I don't.
Doctor (Examiner) / Cricket OR Mr. Duff (PVM): OK, Mr. Walker, does that hurt?
Mr. Walker / Cricket (PVM): I can't feel anything until you get to my thigh.
Doctor (Examiner) / Cricket (PVM): Try wiggling your toes.
Doctor (Examiner) / Cricket OR Cricket (PVM): Are they moving?
Mr. Walker / Unknown (PVM): No.
Doctor (Examiner) / Patient (PVM): Damn.
Mr. Walker / Cricket (PVM): I could about 10 minutes ago.
Doctor (likely Meredith Grey or Miranda Bailey) / Patient (PVM): Well, your spine X-rays look clear.
Doctor (likely Meredith Grey or Miranda Bailey) / Patient OR Mr. Walker OR Patient (PVM): You fell rock climbing?
Patient: In Snohomish.
Patient: Just a small drop.
Patient: I was belayed.
Patient: My wife and boys are on the way.
Patient: What's wrong with me, anyway?
Doctor (likely Meredith Grey or Miranda Bailey) / Patient (PVM): Hold your legs up.
Patient: Should I be scared now?
Doctor (likely Meredith Grey or Miranda Bailey) / Patient (PVM): No, just try and relax.
Doctor (likely Miranda Bailey) / Patient OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Nurse, I need a stat MRI.
Doctor (likely Miranda Bailey) / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Send an intern with him.
Doctor (likely Miranda Bailey) / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Take it Meredith, correct?
Dr. Meredith Gray: Mm-hmm.
Doctor (likely Miranda Bailey) / Patient (PVM): Ooh, thick, short neck.
Doctor (likely Meredith Grey) / Patient (PVM): That isn't good.
Doctor (likely Miranda Bailey) / Patient (PVM): It's hard to intubate.
Meredith Grey / Patient (PVM): You want me to do that?
Doctor (likely Miranda Bailey) / Patient (PVM): He's my patient.
Patient: I'm fine.
Doctor (likely Miranda Bailey) / Patient (PVM): I just can't see anything yet.
Doctor (likely Miranda Bailey) / Patient (PVM): Suction.
Patient: Don't break any teeth on me.
Doctor (likely Meredith Grey) / Mr. Duff (PVM): I know that.
Doctor (likely Miranda Bailey) / Mr. Duff (PVM): Don't you think I know that?
Intern (possibly O'Malley) / Patient (PVM): Ball socks down 87%.
Another Intern (possibly Cristina or Meredith) / Patient (PVM): Damn.
Attending (possibly Dr. Bailey) / Patient (PVM): Bag him.
Intern (possibly O'Malley) / Patient (PVM): I'll raise him.
Resident (possibly Meredith) / Patient OR Patient (PVM): Are you sure you don't want to do that?
Intern (possibly O'Malley) / Patient (PVM): No, damn it.
Intern (possibly Alex Karev) / Mr. Duff (PVM): Dude.
Intern (possibly O'Malley) / Patient OR Mr. Duff (PVM): Got it.
Intern (possibly O'Malley) / Patient (PVM): It's in the esophagus.
Attending (possibly Dr. Bailey) / Patient OR Mr. Duff (PVM): Don't you know an esophagus from a trachea?
Intern (possibly O'Malley) / Mr. Duff (PVM): Damn it.
Intern (possibly O'Malley) / Patient OR Mr. Duff OR Dr. Karev (PVM): Anatomy is all messed up in here.
Attending (possibly Dr. Bailey) / Patient OR Dr. Karev (PVM): Are you trying to kill this patient, O'Malley?
O'Malley / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Karev (PVM): No, it's just I haven't done this much.
O'Malley / Mr. Duff (PVM): But when I have, it's been good.
O'Malley / Dr. Karev (PVM): It's just I haven't.
Attending (possibly Dr. Bailey) / Dr. Karev (PVM): Let's review the concept.
Attending (possibly Dr. Bailey) / Dr. Karev (PVM): Never take your eyes away.
Attending (possibly Dr. Bailey) / Devo OR Dr. Karev (PVM): Always, always know you can follow through.
Attending (possibly Dr. Bailey) / Devo OR Devo (PVM): I'll never follow through on one of my patients, O'Malley.
Intern (possibly Cristina Yang) / Esther OR Mr. Duff (PVM): A little Botox would do wonders on those frown lines.
Attending (possibly Dr. Bailey) / Mr. Duff (PVM): Okay.
Attending (possibly Dr. Bailey) / Mr. Duff (PVM): Shut up.
Intern (possibly Cristina Yang) / Mr. Duff (PVM): Are you allowed to talk to me like that?
Intern (possibly Alex Karev) / Mr. Duff (PVM): God, you're hot.
Unknown (Possibly Meredith Grey or another intern) / Mr. Duff (PVM): In a Mrs. Livingston kind of way.
Unknown (Possibly a doctor showing scans) / Mr. Duff (PVM): See here?
Unknown (Likely a doctor explaining results) / Mr. Duff (PVM): These are spikes in your temporal lobe.
Unknown (Likely a doctor) / Mr. Duff (PVM): It means you have epilepsy, not visions.
Unknown (Likely a doctor) / Mr. Duff (PVM): Seizures.
Unknown (Likely the patient) / Mr. Duff (PVM): You think I'm epileptic?
Unknown (Likely the patient) / Mr. Duff (PVM): That is so not right.
Unknown (Likely a doctor) / Mr. Duff (PVM): I'm gonna order an MRI so I can take a closer look at your brain.
Unknown (Likely the patient) / Mr. Duff OR Esther (PVM): Yeah, there's no way.
Unknown (Likely a doctor or nurse) / Mr. Duff (PVM): Mr. Duff?
Unknown (Likely a doctor or nurse) / Mr. Duff (PVM): Mr. Duff, can you see me?
Unknown (Likely a doctor or nurse) / Mr. Duff (PVM): Can you hear me?
Unknown (Likely a doctor or nurse) / Mr. Duff (PVM): Stay with me.
Unknown (Possibly a doctor or another nurse) / Patient (PVM): Wouldn't have picked you for the mommy track, Nurse Betty.
Unknown (Possibly Nurse Betty or another nurse) / Mr. Duff OR Mr. Duff (PVM): See?
Unknown (Possibly Nurse Betty) / Esther (PVM): Told you I know things.
Unknown (Possibly Nurse Betty or another nurse) / Esther OR Mr. Duff OR Esther (PVM): This pregnancy thing, you can't run away from it.
Unknown (Likely an intern, possibly Meredith Grey or Cristina Yang) / Mr. Duff (PVM): Dr. Bailey, I want off the psychic case.
Unknown (Likely an intern, possibly Cristina Yang) / Mr. Duff (PVM): I'll take whatever you got.
Unknown (Likely an intern) / Mr. Duff (PVM): Can I switch?
Dr. Bailey / Mr. Duff (PVM): Ask nicely.
Unknown (Likely an intern) / Mr. Duff (PVM): But this is me doing nicely.
Unknown (Likely an intern) / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Look, I know the type.
Unknown (Likely an intern) / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): These guys just want everybody to think they're a sideshow.
Unknown (Likely an intern) / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Let me take them.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Jennings OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I don't do switches.
George O'Malley / Dr. Jennings (PVM): I'll do your post-op notes for a month.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Jennings (PVM): Fine.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Jennings (PVM): I can accept that.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Jennings (PVM): Izzy, you get psych guy.
Dr. Izzie Stevens: Yay.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Jennings (PVM): This is your lucky day.
Alex Karev / Dr. Jennings (PVM): You get to be with me on the breast cancer.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Jennings (PVM): And they're spotting, so you need to do a pelvic.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Jennings (PVM): She's pregnant.
Izzie Stevens / Mr. Duff OR Mr. Duff (PVM): See?
Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff (PVM): This.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff (PVM): Your guy's films are clear.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff (PVM): There's no reason I can see for his creeping paralysis.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Duff (PVM): It's just so surprising.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I expected an intrusion into the spinal space, where bony sperm the nucleus proposes.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Duff (PVM): Well, you were wrong.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You don't always get what you expect, do you?
Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): What is your problem?
Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff (PVM): Give me something to go on.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff (PVM): Anything.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff (PVM): What are your grandparents' names?
Patient / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I don't have grandparents.
Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff (PVM): Where'd you grow up?
Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff (PVM): What's your favorite flavor of ice cream?
Doctor / Mr. Duff (PVM): Where'd you spend your summer vacations?
Doctor / Mr. Duff (PVM): Lighten up.
Doctor / Mr. Duff (PVM): It'll be good for your blood pressure.
Mrs. Glass / Mr. Duff (PVM): Oh, don't you tell me to lighten up.
Mrs. Glass / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I'll lighten up when I feel light.
Mrs. Glass / Dr. Karev (PVM): Don't we have treatment options?
Mrs. Glass / Dr. Karev (PVM): I mean, aren't there always alternatives?
Dr. Jennings: With this stage of invasive carcinoma, surgery, chemo, radiation, and drug therapy are your only options.
Mrs. Glass / Mr. Duff (PVM): Can I wait until the end of my pregnancy?
Dr. Jennings: The pregnancy hormones will likely speed the growth of the cancer.
Mrs. Glass / Dr. Karev (PVM): And the baby?
Dr. Jennings: Oh, none of these courses of treatment will allow the baby to survive.
Dr. Jennings: Mr. and Mrs. Glass, I understand how difficult this is.
Mrs. Glass / Dr. Jennings (PVM): No disrespect, but like hell you do.
Dr. Jennings: You're going to have to make a decision as to how you want to proceed.
Mrs. Glass / Dr. Jennings (PVM): You mean my baby's life or my own?
Dr. Jennings: Yes.
Dr. Jennings: We'll have to evacuate the fetus.
Doctor / Mr. Walker (PVM): Any changes, Mr. Walker?
Mr. Walker: I can't move my legs at all now.
Mrs. Walker / Mr. Duff (PVM): He said he was moving his legs when he came in.
Mrs. Walker / Mr. Duff (PVM): What's wrong with them?
Doctor / Dr. Jennings (PVM): I don't know.
Dr. Jennings: The paralysis is moving very quickly, and there was nothing in the MRI to explain it.
Doctor / Mr. Duff (PVM): Has Tommy been under any stress lately?
Mr. Walker / Cricket (PVM): You know what's making me stressed is being in here and not being able to move.
Unknown / Cricket (PVM): Dr. Gray.
Dr. Gray / Mr. Duff (PVM): Emotional trauma can be converted into something physical, right?
Dr. Gray / Mr. Duff (PVM): This is possible.
Dr. Gray / Mr. Duff (PVM): Like hysterical numbness or paralysis.
Dr. Gray / Esther OR Mr. Duff (PVM): Maybe there is no physiological reason, and he's just having a conversion reaction.
Mr. Duff / Esther OR Mr. Duff (PVM): You think it's psychosomatic?
Dr. Gray / Esther (PVM): It is not in your head, man.
Dr. Gray / Esther (PVM): I believe you.
Dr. Gray / Mr. Duff (PVM): Mr. Duff, please.
Mr. Duff / Mr. Duff (PVM): What was that?
Dr. Gray / Mr. Duff (PVM): Psych sent him down.
Dr. Gray / Mr. Duff (PVM): He has visions.
Mr. Duff / Cricket (PVM): Is that it?
Mr. Duff / Dr. Jennings OR Cricket (PVM): Am I crazy?
Dr. Gray / Dr. Jennings (PVM): No, no.
Dr. Gray / Dr. Jennings (PVM): I'm going to order a higher level MRI.
Dr. Gray / Dr. Jennings (PVM): We're going to figure this out.
Mr. Walker's wife / Esther (PVM): You know how important this is to me.
Mr. Walker's wife / Esther OR Dr. Jennings (PVM): This is about saving your life, sweetie.
Mr. Walker's wife / Esther OR Dr. Jennings (PVM): And you're not respecting it, or me.
Mr. Walker / Esther (PVM): You're letting them put a pig, a freaking non-kosher trade mammal, into my chest, into my heart, the very essence of my being.
Dr. Gray / Devo OR Esther (PVM): It's a porcine valve, actually.
Mr. Walker / Esther (PVM): I don't care what the hell it is.
Mr. Walker / Esther (PVM): If you give me a pig part, I might as well be dead.
Devo's Parent / Devo OR Cricket (PVM): I told you this whole Orthodox thing was a mistake.
Devo's Parent / Cricket (PVM): What was so wrong with being clean or reformed like everyone else we know?
Devo / Esther (PVM): You guys don't even light candles Friday nights.
Devo / Esther (PVM): You don't even know all the Passover plagues.
Devo / Devo OR Devo (PVM): Boils, vermin, pestilence, even I know that.
Attending Doctor / Dr. Karev (PVM): Miss Freeman, I appreciate your extreme religious convictions.
Devo / Dr. Karev (PVM): Fire, hail, slain, firstborn.
Attending Doctor / Dr. Karev (PVM): But simply put, without this procedure, you will die.
Esther: You're hot shot, doctors.
Esther: You'll come up with something else.
Esther: As long as it doesn't answer to Wilbur and say oink, I don't care what it is.
Devo / Esther (PVM): Your nostrils are flaring.
Doctor / Mr. Duff (PVM): They are not.
Devo / Esther (PVM): You're into me.
Devo / Esther (PVM): I can tell.
Esther: Dr. Small and Angry was a hot appetizer, but you, Doc, are a smorgasbord of lust.
Doctor / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Mr. Doff, you're pressing your luck.
Esther: Would you press it for me?
Doctor / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I hope you're not claustrophobic.
Devo / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): You're staring at me.
Doctor / Esther (PVM): Stop.
Esther: I'm looking at you, sweetheart, but it's the strangest thing.
Esther: I'm hungry for a chocolate cupcake.
Doctor / Mr. Duff (PVM): What did you say?
Esther: A chocolate cupcake?
Mr. Duff: Maybe one of those fudgy things with the white squiggle on the frosting.
Mr. Duff: Could you oblige?
Dr. Jennings: What?
Mr. Duff: Do I still have some chocolate on my face or in my hair or something?
Dr. Jennings: What are you talking about?
Mr. Duff: You.
Dr. Jennings: I know the drill, so keep it up.
Dr. Jennings: Next, you'll be reading my cards, telling me my dead uncle is in the room.
Mr. Duff: Is he?
Dr. Jennings: I don't have a dead uncle.
Mr. Duff: I'm watching you.
Mr. Duff: If that's turkey, can I have some?
Dr. Jennings: It's soggy.
Doctor / Mr. Duff (PVM): It'll kill you to solve everything.
George / Mr. Duff (PVM): I could have gotten that intubation.
George / Mr. Duff (PVM): I am good at intubations.
George / Mr. Duff (PVM): Why does everything in a hospital smell like a hospital?
Doctor / Mr. Duff (PVM): Don't be so hard on yourself, George.
Doctor / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Everybody makes mistakes.
George / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): You know, I'm good at a lot of things.
George / Mr. Duff (PVM): You know what?
George / Mr. Duff (PVM): I want to tell you something.
Doctor / Mr. Duff (PVM): Hey, George, you need to get laid.
Doctor / Mr. Duff (PVM): See that nurse over there?
Doctor / Mr. Duff (PVM): She's single.
Unknown (likely a young doctor or nurse) / Mr. Duff (PVM): She's got red hair.
Unknown (likely a colleague/friend of previous speaker) / Mr. Duff (PVM): Go ask her out.
Unknown (likely the person who intubated the esophagus, possibly a resident or intern) / Mr. Duff (PVM): In case you forgot, I intubated an esophagus.
Unknown (likely a friend or colleague) / Mr. Duff (PVM): Dude, you're tweaking.
Unknown (likely same as previous, teasing) / Mr. Duff (PVM): Maybe you should go see that psychic.
Unknown (likely the person being teased) / Mr. Duff (PVM): Mr. Duff is not a psychic!
Unknown (likely the teaser) / Mr. Duff (PVM): I am trying to help you.
Unknown (likely the teaser/friend) / Dr. Jennings OR Mr. Duff (PVM): Go buy her a latte and freshen up your gonad.
Unknown (likely the person being teased) / Mr. Duff (PVM): Please.
Unknown (likely another participant in the banter) / Mr. Duff (PVM): Please.
Unknown (likely the person being teased) / Mr. Duff (PVM): Shut up.
Unknown (likely a friend/colleague) / Mr. Duff (PVM): It's not too late to call her.
Unknown (likely same as previous) / Mr. Duff (PVM): You know, moms like that.
Unknown (likely same as previous) / Mr. Duff (PVM): Surprises on their birthdays.
Unknown (likely same as previous) / Mr. Duff (PVM): You know, it's very hallmark.
Mrs. Glass / Mrs. Glass (PVM): I'm 47, you know?
Mrs. Glass / Mrs. Glass (PVM): I'm 47 and having a baby, which is kind of a miracle, and it kind of sucks, if you see what I mean.
Mrs. Glass / Mrs. Glass (PVM): Would have actually given up on the whole kid thing about a year ago.
Mrs. Glass / Mrs. Glass (PVM): You know, fertility treatments, acupuncture needles in my eyes.
Mrs. Glass / Mrs. Glass (PVM): Well, not really, but it felt like it.
Mrs. Glass / Mrs. Glass (PVM): I was like, screw this.
Mrs. Glass / Mrs. Glass (PVM): I want my life back.
Mrs. Glass / Mr. Duff OR Mrs. Glass (PVM): Then one awesome night on the beach with a bottle of Merlot.
Doctor / Mr. Duff OR Mrs. Glass (PVM): I should have these labs back in a couple hours.
Doctor / Mrs. Glass (PVM): You get it, right?
Patient / Mrs. Glass (PVM): My hesitation.
Patient / Mrs. Glass (PVM): This isn't an easy decision.
Patient / Mrs. Glass (PVM): I mean, I'm having a baby.
Doctor / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): You have advanced stage carcinoma.
Doctor / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): You're 47 years old.
Doctor / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): So statistically, you have a good probability of survival.
Doctor / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Forgo treatment.
Doctor / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Chances are you won't see your baby go to kindergarten.
Doctor / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): So whose life are you interested in saving?
Patient / Mr. Duff (PVM): Excuse me.
Patient / Dr. Jennings (PVM): Where's my fingers?
Patient / Dr. Jennings OR Cricket (PVM): I can't.
Doctor / Dr. Jennings (PVM): Right here.
Doctor / Dr. Jennings (PVM): No?
Doctor / Dr. Jennings (PVM): Let me know if you feel this.
Doctor / Dr. Jennings (PVM): Anything here?
Doctor / Dr. Jennings (PVM): Up here?
Doctor / Dr. Jennings OR Mr. Duff (PVM): OK.
Doctor / Dr. Jennings (PVM): Nothing on this side?
Doctor / Dr. Jennings (PVM): All right, I'll be right back.
Dr. Jennings: Nurse, cancel the second MRI.
Dr. Jennings: Call down and prep OR staff.
Nurse / Mr. Duff (PVM): You're operating?
Nurse / Mr. Duff (PVM): On what?
Doctor / Mr. Duff (PVM): If there was something to fix, wouldn't we have seen it?
Attending Surgeon / Patient (PVM): I think the MRI missed a clot somewhere in his upper spine.
Attending Surgeon / Patient (PVM): I'm going to cut him open.
Attending Surgeon / Patient (PVM): I'm going in.
Meredith Grey / Mr. Duff (PVM): What if you're wrong?
Meredith Grey / Patient OR Mr. Duff (PVM): Couldn't unnecessary spinal surgery do more damage?
Attending Surgeon / Patient (PVM): If we wait any longer and this thing expands into his brain stem, we have a paralyzed man who can't breathe.
Attending Surgeon / Patient (PVM): I'm trusting my instincts.
Attending Surgeon / Patient (PVM): Sometimes you've got to take a chance to save a life.
Doctor (possibly Cristina Yang) / Dr. Jennings OR Devo (PVM): Your mitral regurg is getting worse.
Doctor (possibly Cristina Yang) / Devo (PVM): The valves are leakier than ever.
Patient (Teenager) / Devo OR Esther (PVM): Are you hitting on me?
Doctor (possibly Cristina Yang) / Devo (PVM): You want me to?
Patient (Teenager) / Esther (PVM): I hear they call you Dr. Evilsbaum.
Doctor (possibly Cristina Yang) / Devo (PVM): Only the people that like me.
Patient (Teenager) / Devo (PVM): I guess that explains the lack of faith thing.
Doctor (possibly Cristina Yang) / Devo OR Devo (PVM): Well, I kind of think of myself as a pagan, but, uh, hey, that's just me.
Patient (Teenager) / Esther (PVM): You know what it's like being a teenager these days?
Patient (Teenager) / Esther (PVM): My friends spend most of their time screwing around and getting wasted.
Patient (Teenager) / Devo OR Esther (PVM): At least I have God.
Doctor (possibly Cristina Yang) / Devo (PVM): Well, so God wants you to die, huh?
Patient (Teenager) / Esther (PVM): He wants me to be passionate about what I believe in.
Doctor (possibly Cristina Yang) / Esther (PVM): You don't believe in anything.
Doctor (possibly Cristina Yang) / Devo (PVM): No, my mother used to pray to St.
Doctor (possibly Cristina Yang) / Devo OR Esther (PVM): Jude for me.
Patient (Teenager) / Esther (PVM): How appropriate.
Cristina Yang / Esther (PVM): Patron saint of lost causes.
George O'Malley / Unknown (PVM): Oh.
Izzie Stevens / Mrs. Glass (PVM): The fate of Kurt Cobain.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I did an angio on my side case.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): The MRI came out clean, but I saw a digital.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): There's something here.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Jennings (PVM): Yep.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Jennings OR Dr. Jennings (PVM): You're right, there's an AVM on his left temporal lobe.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I'll schedule the OR for tonight, then.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Jennings (PVM): Oh, back up, girl.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Jennings (PVM): There's high risk of spontaneous hemorrhage.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Jennings (PVM): The attending has to see the films.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Jennings (PVM): We need consent forms.
Alex Karev / Dr. Jennings (PVM): Believe it or not, Stevens, we have to follow protocol.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Jennings (PVM): Take a breath.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Jennings (PVM): But if the AVM looks like it's going to blow, we fix it, right?
Alex Karev / Dr. Jennings OR Dr. Jennings (PVM): If the man needs to be fixed, we'll fix him in due time.
Alex Karev / Dr. Jennings (PVM): Why are you moving so quickly?
Alex Karev / Dr. Jennings (PVM): You get too involved with your patients, Izzy.
Alex Karev / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Dr. Jennings (PVM): Why do you make everything so personal?
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): It's not personal.
Izzie Stevens / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): It's not.
George O'Malley / Dr. Jennings OR Patient OR Mr. Duff OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I've got to save this cord.
Alex Karev / Dr. Jennings OR Patient OR Mr. Duff OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): This guy is built like the rock of Gibraltar.
George O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You want me to start?
Dr. Karev / Patient OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): No, I'm going to cut here from the base of the neck to the rib cage.
Dr. Karev / Patient (PVM): I want you to hit the bleeders.
Dr. O'Malley / Patient OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I still don't think we should be doing this.
Dr. Karev / Patient OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): This guy has a spinal hematoma.
Dr. O'Malley / Patient OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): We don't know that.
Dr. Karev / Patient OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Which left untreated are almost always fatal.
Dr. O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): You're cutting blind.
Dr. O'Malley / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Whatever happened to being practical?
Dr. Karev / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I need to see more here.
Dr. Karev / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Tractor.
Dr. O'Malley / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Wow.
Dr. Karev / Mr. Duff (PVM): Good cap refill.
Dr. Karev / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): The spine.
Dr. O'Malley / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): There is no wow in practical.
Dr. Bailey / Mr. Duff OR Mrs. Glass (PVM): We've decided to go ahead with the evacuation.
Dr. Karev / Mr. Duff OR Mr. Duff OR Mrs. Glass (PVM): What the hell, right?
Dr. Karev / Mrs. Glass (PVM): Maybe this is how it's supposed to be.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Jennings (PVM): We need to start chemo right away, then.
Dr. Stevens / Dr. Jennings (PVM): We'll get everything ready.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Jennings (PVM): You ever done a DNC before?
Dr. Stevens / Dr. Jennings (PVM): We learn at school.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Jennings (PVM): OK, go ahead.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Jennings (PVM): I'll call an OP resident down to supervise.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Jennings (PVM): If she needs anything, page me.
Dr. Karev / Patient (PVM): You're using up my oxygen, O'Malley.
Cristina Yang / Patient OR Patient (PVM): How does a pompous cocky jackass like you always have women all over him?
Alex Karev / Devo (PVM): Little blue love pills.
Alex Karev / Patient OR Devo (PVM): Lots of them.
Cristina Yang / Devo (PVM): Come on.
Alex Karev / Devo (PVM): Float like a butterfly, sting like a bee.
Meredith Grey / Devo (PVM): There it is.
Attending Surgeon / Devo (PVM): A bovine xenograft.
Alex Karev / Devo OR Patient (PVM): O'Malley, you think too much.
Alex Karev / Patient (PVM): Can't you see it?
Alex Karev / Patient (PVM): You got to dance and jab.
Alex Karev / Patient (PVM): Dance and jab.
Alex Karev / Patient (PVM): Like me.
Alex Karev / Patient (PVM): I am the Ali of this place.
George O'Malley / Devo OR Devo (PVM): Does the wall ever bow back?
Cristina Yang / Esther (PVM): It's called davening, smartass.
Cristina Yang / Esther (PVM): This is me communing with God, and you're interrupting.
Izzie Stevens / Devo OR Patient (PVM): I've found a transplant option.
Izzie Stevens / Devo OR Patient (PVM): At first, I thought maybe a cadaver, but they're really hard to find.
Izzie Stevens / Devo (PVM): And then I realized Dr. Burke can transplant a bovine mitral valve instead of the pig.
Patient's Family Member / Devo (PVM): She can get a cow valve?
Patient's Family Member / Dr. Jennings (PVM): Dr. Burke, why wasn't this mentioned before?
Dr. Burke / Devo OR Devo OR Dr. Jennings (PVM): The divine valve has only been an option the last few years.
Dr. Burke / Devo (PVM): And it's a much more complicated procedure.
Dr. Burke / Devo (PVM): But the best part is it's actually superior to the pig.
Dr. Burke / Devo (PVM): It lasts longer.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Karev (PVM): What incredibly small fraction of your brain were you using there?
Alex Karev / Mr. Duff (PVM): What?
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Karev (PVM): Correct me if I'm wrong, but did you not present an alternative procedure without consulting your attending first?
Alex Karev / Dr. Karev (PVM): I thought you'd be... What, impressed?
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Karev (PVM): That's just stupid.
Alex Karev / Dr. Karev (PVM): I'm sorry.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Karev (PVM): We're finished here, Karev.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Karev (PVM): You're off this case.
Dr. Alex Karev / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): You need to sign these consent forms so we can proceed with your surgery.
Patient (possibly a comedic or stubborn patient) / Esther (PVM): Sweetheart, I'm not signing anything unless it's got my name on it, followed by a whole bunch of zeros.
Dr. Alex Karev / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Look, the AVM is located in this crucial part of the brain.
Dr. Alex Karev / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): It's a tangle of blood vessels that could burst and affect your speech, among other things.
Dr. Alex Karev / Mr. Duff (PVM): So we know your visions are actually seizures.
Patient / Mr. Duff (PVM): Do you?
Dr. Alex Karev / Mr. Duff (PVM): Do I what?
Patient / Mr. Duff (PVM): Know they're seizures.
Patient / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): You're really good at reading people, aren't you?
Patient / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Telling them what they want to hear.
Patient / Esther (PVM): There's a really unfortunate alignment of Saturn in the house of Jupiter right now.
Dr. Alex Karev / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Okay, I know what you're doing.
Dr. Alex Karev / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): You watch people, read their body language.
Dr. Alex Karev / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): You say chocolate cupcakes, I lean towards you, so you think you're on the right track.
Dr. Alex Karev / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Not only do you know you're having seizures, but you're milking it.
Patient / Patient (PVM): Well, we'll just see about that, Cricket.
Dr. Alex Karev / Mr. Duff (PVM): What?
Mrs. Glass / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): What did you just call me?
Doctor / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I'm going to do a quick pelvic exam.
Doctor / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): The OB resident should be down soon.
Doctor / Mr. Duff (PVM): It's a short procedure.
Doctor / Mr. Duff (PVM): Your husband can stay if he likes.
Mrs. Glass / Mr. Duff (PVM): He changed our minds.
Doctor / Mr. Duff (PVM): Excuse me?
Mrs. Glass / Dr. Jennings (PVM): We've decided to keep the baby.
Dr. Jennings: You have cancer.
Mrs. Glass: Can you tell me I'll survive if I go through with this?
Dr. Jennings: Having the procedure does not necessarily improve the treatment outcome.
Mrs. Glass: You have quite the bedside manner.
Mrs. Glass: You know that, right?
Mrs. Glass: My mom died of breast cancer when she was in her 40s.
Mrs. Glass: I have that cancer gene.
Mrs. Glass: My chances are pretty much lose-lose, whichever way you look at it, except for the baby.
Mrs. Glass / Mrs. Glass (PVM): We're keeping it.
Dr. Jennings: I'll call down a psych consult.
Mrs. Glass: Don't bother.
Mrs. Glass: I am going to get fat and happy instead of skinny and bald.
Mrs. Glass: And at the end of it all.
Mrs. Glass: Look, if you want to live, honey, that's what I'm doing.
Mrs. Glass / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Look, if you think you're gonna get any, think again.
Mrs. Glass / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I'm not in the mood.
Mr. Glass / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Karev OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I'm not in the mood either.
Burke / Unknown (PVM): Good.
Burke / Dr. Karev (PVM): What do you want?
Cristina Yang / Dr. Karev (PVM): Nothing.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Karev (PVM): I just haven't seen you all day.
Burke / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): So I'm working.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Karev (PVM): I've never done a bovine replacement before.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Karev (PVM): I don't know what I'm doing.
Burke / Mr. Duff (PVM): Look it up, research it, and get someone to assist you.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Karev (PVM): It's not that easy.
Burke / Mr. Duff (PVM): This is a problem that has a solution, Burke.
Burke / Mr. Duff (PVM): There are a lot of problems that don't.
Meredith Gray / Cricket (PVM): Third thoracic laminae, nothing.
Meredith Gray / Cricket OR Mr. Duff (PVM): I think I see the dura pulsating here.
Derek Shepherd / Mr. Duff (PVM): No, it's not.
Derek Shepherd / Mr. Duff (PVM): Keep looking.
Meredith Gray / Mr. Duff (PVM): We've been at this for four hours.
Meredith Gray / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Jennings OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Maybe he just injured his spinal cord, and there's nothing to fix.
Dr. Derek Shepherd: Gray, when you read your books, make sure you reference them correctly.
Meredith Gray / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Progressive paralysis implies a pressure lesion.
Meredith Gray / Mr. Duff (PVM): My books got me here.
Nurse / Mr. Duff OR Mr. Duff (PVM): Pressure's up to 180 over 111.
Nurse / Mr. Duff (PVM): Pulse is in the 40s.
Derek Shepherd / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): What is it?
Meredith Gray / Mr. Duff (PVM): I'm pushing 70 milligrams of disoxide.
Unknown (likely a surgeon or doctor) / Dr. Jennings OR Mr. Duff (PVM): OK.
Unknown (likely a doctor or surgeon) / Mr. Duff (PVM): Autonomic dysreflexia.
Unknown (likely a doctor or intern) / Patient OR Mr. Duff OR Dr. Jennings (PVM): Damage to the sympathetic nervous system?
Unknown (likely a doctor) / Patient OR Mr. Duff OR Dr. Jennings (PVM): The CP in the heart rate are unstable.
Unknown (likely Dr. Meredith Gray) / Mr. Duff (PVM): We're in trouble, aren't we?
Unknown (likely Dr. Bailey or lead surgeon) / Dr. Jennings (PVM): We've got to find the clot.
Unknown (likely a surgeon) / Mr. Duff (PVM): Now, I can see the cord below the door.
Unknown (likely Dr. O'Malley) / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Jennings (PVM): Is he going to stroke out?
Unknown (likely Dr. Bailey) / Dr. Jennings (PVM): Just focus, Gray.
Unknown (likely Dr. Bailey) / Dr. Jennings (PVM): We're going to find the clot.
Unknown (likely Dr. Meredith Gray) / Dr. Jennings (PVM): It's there.
Unknown (likely Dr. Bailey) / Dr. Jennings (PVM): Peanut, please.
Unknown (likely scrub nurse or intern) / Mr. Duff (PVM): Okay.
Unknown (likely Dr. Meredith Gray or nurse) / Dr. Jennings (PVM): BP is still up.
Unknown (likely Dr. Meredith Gray or nurse) / Dr. Jennings (PVM): Heart rate's at 44.
Unknown (likely Dr. Bailey) / Dr. Jennings (PVM): Get on those bleeders.
Unknown (likely Dr. Bailey) / Dr. Jennings (PVM): Keep looking, Dr. Gray.
Unknown (likely nurse or Dr. Bailey) / Devo (PVM): Dr. O'Malley, our patient's pulse ox is dropping.
Unknown (likely Dr. O'Malley or nurse) / Devo (PVM): She's agonal.
Unknown (likely Dr. Bailey or Dr. O'Malley) / Devo (PVM): She needs to be intubated.
Unknown (likely Dr. O'Malley) / Mr. Duff (PVM): Isn't there anyone else who can do this?
Unknown (likely Dr. Bailey) / Devo (PVM): You're standing right here.
Unknown (likely Dr. O'Malley) / Devo (PVM): I could try and find someone.
Unknown (likely Dr. O'Malley) / Mr. Duff (PVM): No, that's... I got it.
Unknown (likely a surgeon or nurse) / Mr. Duff (PVM): Okay.
Unknown (likely someone monitoring vitals) / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Jennings (PVM): So that's down to 86%.
Unknown (likely lead surgeon) / Mr. Duff OR Mr. Duff OR Dr. Jennings (PVM): Crank pressure, please.
Unknown (team member) / Mr. Duff (PVM): Okay.
Unknown (likely intubating doctor) / Mr. Duff (PVM): I see cords.
Unknown (counting during procedure) / Mr. Duff (PVM): Two, three.
Unknown (likely monitoring lungs) / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Karev (PVM): Clear and equal.
Unknown (likely anesthesiologist) / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Karev (PVM): CO2 detector mellow yellow.
Unknown (teasing colleague) / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Karev (PVM): Smooth moves, doctor.
Unknown (affirming compliment) / Patient (PVM): Kicked ass.
Unknown (addressing Dr. Karev) / Dr. Karev (PVM): Ah, Dr. Karev.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Karev OR Patient (PVM): How long did it take to get a car valve?
Dr. Karev / Devo OR Patient (PVM): Oh, about 60 minutes by messenger.
Dr. Shepherd / Devo (PVM): You're scrubbing in.
Dr. Karev: Thank you very much, sir.
Dr. Shepherd / Dr. Karev (PVM): This doesn't get you any points, Karev.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Karev (PVM): I'm the only one with points around here, OK?
Unknown (informing about patient request) / Dr. Karev (PVM): Oh, by the way, Devo wants a rabbi to bless her before surgery.
Unknown (reacting to request) / Dr. Karev (PVM): Seriously?
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Karev (PVM): You came up with the call.
Dr. Bailey / Dr. Karev (PVM): You can find that girl a rabbi.
Unknown (giving surgical instruction) / Dr. Karev OR Mr. Duff OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): For the irrigation and suction, have it ready.
Unknown (acknowledging instruction) / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Right away.
Unknown (asking about something noticed) / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): What is it?
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Patient (PVM): See for yourself.
Dr. Preston Burke / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Patient OR Mr. Duff OR Cricket (PVM): Second thoracic vertebrae.
Dr. Izzie Stevens / Cricket OR Mr. Duff (PVM): Oh, my God.
Dr. Meredith Grey / Cricket (PVM): I see it.
Dr. Cristina Yang / Cricket (PVM): It really is there.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Jennings OR Cricket (PVM): Of course it is.
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Jennings OR Hospital Intercom OR Mr. Duff (PVM): Let's suction and pack this baby, shall we?
Dr. Miranda Bailey / Dr. Jennings OR Hospital Intercom OR Cricket (PVM): Here you go.
Hospital Intercom: Dr. Burke to oncology.
Dr. Meredith Grey / Hospital Intercom OR Mr. Duff (PVM): You were right.
Dr. Izzie Stevens / Mr. Duff (PVM): Is he gonna be okay?
Dr. Preston Burke / Mr. Duff (PVM): I think so.
Dr. Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff (PVM): But you don't know that.
Dr. Preston Burke / Mr. Duff (PVM): I know we stopped the paralysis from advancing.
Dr. Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff (PVM): But you don't know if the paralysis he already has will be permanent?
Dr. Preston Burke / Unknown (PVM): No.
Dr. Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff (PVM): You know, you keep taking everything on faith.
Dr. Cristina Yang / Mr. Duff (PVM): How do you know what's real and what's not?
Dr. Meredith Grey / Patient (PVM): We just do.
Dr. Izzie Stevens / Patient (PVM): You know, some people would call this a relationship.
Dr. Izzie Stevens / Patient (PVM): The kind where you exchange keys, leave your toothbrush over.
Dr. Meredith Grey / Mrs. Glass (PVM): Who?
Dr. Meredith Grey / Mr. Duff OR Mrs. Glass OR Cricket (PVM): Who would call it that?
Mr. Walker / Mr. Duff (PVM): Me.
Mr. Walker / Dr. Jennings OR Patient OR Dr. Jennings (PVM): I would.
Doctor / Mr. Duff (PVM): And I'm supposed to believe you.
Mr. Walker / Dr. Jennings OR Mr. Duff (PVM): Uh-huh.
Doctor / Mr. Duff (PVM): Show me something.
Doctor / Mr. Duff (PVM): Give me a reason to believe.
Doctor / Mr. Duff OR Mr. Duff OR Mr. Duff (PVM): I have your discharge papers.
Mr. Walker / Mr. Duff (PVM): Oh, you're not happy with me, are you?
Dr. Jennings: I'm your doctor.
Doctor / Mrs. Glass (PVM): It's not my place to be happy.
Patient (likely a female patient, not Mr. Walker) / Mrs. Glass (PVM): My husband and child are going to be together long after I'm gone.
Patient (likely same as 707) / Mrs. Glass (PVM): We've talked about it.
Patient (likely same as 707) / Mrs. Glass (PVM): It's our decision, and that's OK.
Doctor / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): So why do you need my approval?
Patient (likely same as 707) / Mrs. Glass OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I just want you to understand.
Doctor / Mrs. Glass OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Well, I don't.
Doctor / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I brought the consent forms again.
Doctor / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): You really need to sign them.
Doctor / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Your surgeon scheduled the OR.
Dr. Jennings: Mr. Duff, are you all right?
Dr. Jennings: Are you having another seizure?
Mr. Duff / Devo (PVM): Yeah.
Mr. Duff / Mr. Duff (PVM): I think maybe I am.
Unknown (likely a doctor or nurse) / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): What is it?
Mr. Duff / Mr. Duff OR Patient (PVM): It's me.
Mr. Duff / Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Patient (PVM): I think it's about to be over.
Doctor (possibly lead surgeon) / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): We know what we're doing, Mr. Duff.
Doctor / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): You saw the angio results.
Doctor / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): We're catching the AVM just in time.
Doctor / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): You don't need to be nervous.
Doctor / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): You're not gonna die.
Mr. Duff / Esther (PVM): I'm not talking about dying.
Mr. Duff / Esther (PVM): My whole life has been about what I see.
Mr. Duff / Esther (PVM): and about believing in myself, whatever people think.
Mr. Duff / Esther (PVM): And you're telling me there's a very good chance that will go away?
Doctor / Mr. Duff (PVM): Look, you're a healthy guy.
Doctor / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): You're going to live a long, full life.
Doctor / Mr. Duff (PVM): And if your psychic visions are real, you've got to believe you'll have them when you come out.
Unknown (possibly a rabbi, chaplain, or praying character) / Dr. Meredith Gray OR Cricket OR Mr. Duff (PVM): Meesha, Beirach, Avotenu, Avraham, Yitzchak, V'Yakob, V'imotenu, Sarah, Rivka, Rachel, B'Leah, Hu Yivarech, V'Yirapet, Acholah,
Dr. Chesney: This is Dr. Chesney from the Cleveland Clinic.
Unknown (likely another doctor or narrator) / Dr. Karev (PVM): He's an expert on bovine valve replacement surgery.
Unknown (likely another doctor or narrator) / Dr. Karev (PVM): He will be assisting via satellite.
Dr. Chesney / Dr. Karev OR Mr. Duff (PVM): Thank you, doctor.
Lead surgeon / Mr. Duff OR Devo OR Mr. Duff OR Dr. Karev OR Mr. Duff (PVM): After the sternotomy and connection to bypass, we're going to do a transverse left atrial to expose the valve.
Unknown (possibly another doctor) / Unknown (PVM): Good.
Unknown (possibly another doctor) / Cricket OR Mr. Duff (PVM): I tried to talk Shepard out of that clot surgery.
Unknown (possibly Mr. Duff or another doctor) / Mr. Duff (PVM): What is wrong with me?
Cristina Yang / Devo OR Mr. Duff OR Patient (PVM): Basically, you tried to kill the guy.
Meredith Grey / Devo OR Mr. Duff (PVM): Basically, you're an ass.
Cristina Yang / Devo OR Mr. Duff (PVM): Oh, you know you want it.
Poppy / Devo (PVM): Come to Poppy, baby.
Alex Karev / Patient (PVM): This is George.
Alex Karev / Patient OR Cricket (PVM): George has a hot date.
Izzie Stevens / Cricket (PVM): Oh, that's great, George.
George O'Malley / Devo (PVM): Yeah.
Alex Karev / Devo (PVM): Well, left pocket of my lab coat, Georgie.
Cristina Yang / Devo (PVM): No glove, no love.
Izzie Stevens / Esther OR Dr. Izzie Stevens OR Mr. Duff (PVM): My psychic had a surgery.
Meredith Grey / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Yeah?
Izzie Stevens / Cricket OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I wonder what happened with his gift.
Cristina Yang / Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): Come on, we all know he's crazy.
Meredith Grey / Cricket OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): I thought you said you didn't believe in that stuff.
Dr. Izzie Stevens: I grew up in a trailer park, no way to tables, which was supposed to put me through college, but...
Dr. Izzie Stevens: My mother was always calling these psychics all the time.
Dr. Izzie Stevens: And the bills started piling up, so I had to use my money to pay them.
Dr. Izzie Stevens: When I turned 18, I left and never went back.
Dr. Izzie Stevens: But this guy has been saying things to me, things he couldn't possibly know anything about.
Dr. Izzie Stevens: So I just wonder.
Doctor (possibly Derek Shepherd or Miranda Bailey) / Cricket (PVM): Do you have sensation anywhere else?
Patient / Cricket (PVM): Some feeling in my stomach and feet, I guess.
Doctor (possibly Derek Shepherd or Miranda Bailey) / Mr. Duff (PVM): Bladder and bowels?
Cricket / Cricket (PVM): Not so good still.
Cricket's Mother / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Jennings (PVM): They said the pressure stockings help relieve clots and bed sores.
Cricket / Dr. Jennings (PVM): They do.
Cricket: I want to thank you for everything, believing in me that I wasn't making it up.
Cricket's Mother / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Well, I'll come back tomorrow then.
Cricket / Cricket (PVM): Hey, I wanted to show you something.
Cricket: I wasn't sure it would last, but now, look.
Cricket / Cricket OR Cricket OR Patient (PVM): I know it's hardly anything, but... No, it's something.
Cricket: It's something really big.
Cricket: At the end of the day, faith is a funny thing.
Cricket: It turns up when you don't really expect it.
Cricket / Mr. Duff (PVM): Mr. Duff, you're still with us.
Cricket / Esther (PVM): For your recipe.
Cricket / Esther (PVM): One tablespoon coconut extract.
Cricket: It's like one day you realize that the fairy tale may be slightly different than you dreamed.
Cricket's Mother / Mr. Duff OR Cricket OR Patient OR Devo OR Esther (PVM): Where are we going?
Cricket: Trust me.
Cricket: The castle, well, it may not be a castle.
Cricket's Mother / Mr. Duff OR Cricket OR Esther (PVM): Does it beat?
Cricket's Mother / Mr. Duff OR Esther (PVM): Or move.
Cricket: And it's not so important that it's happy ever after.
Cricket: Just that it's happy right now.
Cricket: This love is all I have to give.
Cricket: Mom, it's me.
Unknown / Mr. Duff (PVM): Cricket.
Narrator / Mr. Duff OR Dr. Izzie Stevens (PVM): See, once in a while, once in a blue moon, people will surprise you.
Unknown / Mr. Duff (PVM): I've been thinking about you a lot, too.
Unknown / Patient OR Mr. Duff (PVM): Where are we?
Unknown / Patient OR Mr. Duff (PVM): Shh, shh, shh.
Unknown / Mr. Duff (PVM): I'm gonna tell you.
Main Character / Patient (PVM): All right, my mother's maiden name, Maloney.
Main Character / Patient (PVM): I have four sisters.
Main Character / Patient OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I have nine nieces, five nephews.
Main Character / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I like coffee ice cream, single malt scotch, occasionally good cigar, like the fly fish.
Main Character / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): And I cheat when I do the crossword puzzle on Sunday.
Main Character / Patient OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): And I never dance in public.
Main Character / Patient (PVM): Favorite novel, Sun Also Rises.
Main Character / Patient (PVM): Favorite band, The Clash.
Main Character / Patient OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): Favorite color is blue.
Main Character / Patient OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I don't like light, indigo.
Main Character / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): The scar right here on my forehead, that's why I don't ride motorcycles anymore.
Main Character / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): And I live in that trailer.
Main Character / Cricket OR Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): All this land is mine.
Main Character / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): I have no idea what I'm gonna do with it.
Main Character / Dr. Meredith Gray (PVM): So that's it.
Main Character / Dr. Jennings (PVM): That's all you've earned for now.
Main Character / Dr. Jennings (PVM): The rest you're just... just gonna have to take on fate.
Narrator / Mr. Duff OR Mr. Duff OR Dr. Meredith Gray OR Mr. Duff (PVM): And once in a while, people may even take your breath away.