It's a look
patients get in their eyes.
There's a scent. The smell of death.
Some kind of sixth sense.
When the great beyond is headed for you,
you feel it coming.
What's the one thing you've
always dreamed of doing before you die?
OK, hello? Clearly not my dream.
George.
You're the strongest,
most masculine man I have ever known.
You're smarter than me.
And you've got really great hair.
I'm in love with you, George.
I always have been
and I always will be.
See? I told you. Not my dream.
Oh. OK, this is the last time
I'm going to tell you this.
If you're gonna clog up the toilet,
you've gotta use a plunger.
Or we'll make you crap in the backyard.
What are you doing on the floor?
Get up. Something's wrong with Meredith.
I'm just not going.
You have to go to work. You're
an intern. Saving lives is not optional.
Yes, it is. I'm staying home.
You're supposed to be helping.
Uh... Mer?
Maybe there'll be a horrible accident
nearby the hospital.
Cut a bunch of people open.
Sternotomies, craniotomies.
- That'd be fun, right?
- I don't care about surgeries.
You have a feeling?
- Yes.
- OK. What kind of feeling?
Like I might die.
Today? Tomorrow? In 50 years?
We're all going to die eventually.
- But now, we're late. Let's go.
- Cristina... come on.
OK. This is me being supportive.
- Really?
- Yeah, hey, fine.
I'm totally supportive. Go.
OK. The man I love has a wife.
And then he chooses her over me.
And that wife takes my dog.
OK, I gave it to her. But I didn't
mean to, I meant to give it to him.
But that does not change the fact
that she's got my McDreamy...
and my McDog.
She's got my McLife.
And what have I got?
Do you know I can't remember
the last time we kissed?
You never think the last time is the
last time. You think there'll be more.
You think you have forever,
but you don't.
Plus my conditioner stopped working
and I think I have brittle bones.
I just...
I just need something to happen.
A sign that things are gonna change.
I need a reason to go on.
I need some hope.
And in the absence of hope,
I need to stay in bed
and feel like I might die today.
Whatever. Everybody has problems.
Now get your ass out of bed
and get to work! Now! Move, move, move!
What were you saying?
We're good to go.
- Quiet board.
- I know.
- That's a bad sign.
- Don't you think I know that?
That's a quiet board.
- Is he in a bad mood?
- Quiet board.
- He hates a quiet board.
- I can hear you talk about me.
- We're saying...
- A quiet board means trouble.
A quiet board is death.
A quiet board bodes bad news.
And stop looking at me like that.
- Dr. Shepherd.
- Dr. Burke...
You and I, we've known
each other for a while now, right?
- Yes.
- Done successful surgeries together?
- Your girlfriend is my ex's friend.
- Yes.
- Can't we use each other's first name?
I don't think so.
- Seriously?
- Seriously.
- Dr. Shepherd.
- Dr. Burke.
I haven't been in the OR in two days.
I'm getting some OR time.
- We haven't had a decent resident.
- The last two weren't that bad.
Doesn't matter which one we get.
They suck.
They all sucked. I miss Dr. Bailey.
You all right?
I have a feeling.
I get those.
Yeah?
- Yeah.
- And?
If you wait long enough, it passes.
Promise?
I promise.
Hey. What are you doing?
- Waiting for it to pass.
- For what to pass?
- Do you want to do charts later?
- Never gonna happen.
What?
I gave you your chance
and you slept with someone else.
I forgave you in the spirit of being
a bigger person, of rising above.
But these legs are closed to you now.
The panties are staying on.
- So you and me? Never gonna happen.
- So you don't want to do charts later?
- Stand over there.
- Let's get back to the point.
- You had a point?
- Yeah.
Which surgeon are we
having to suck up to today?
- That would be me.
- Dr. Bailey?
I've been gone two weeks, two weeks,
and you ran off two residents?
I've got people phoning me, telling me
my interns are Rosemary's Babies.
Nobody wants you.
Do you think I have time for this?
I am pregnant.
I'm supposed to be on bed rest.
I'm growing a human being.
I'm supposed to be calm.
Do I look calm to you?
Did I raise you fools to be pariahs?
- You're back.
- I'm not back.
- You're not?
- Get off me.
Yang, Karev, Grey, stay here
and wait for the incoming case.
O'Malley, page Addison Shepherd.
Stevens, get a wheelchair.
- A wheelchair?
- A wheelchair.
- What should I tell Dr. Shepherd?
- What did I say?
Dr. Bailey? What should I tell
Dr. Montgomery-Shepherd?
Tell her my contractions
are ten minutes apart
and my water just broke over your shoes.
Just... Boy, get off me!
Take her!
- Dude.
- Yeah.
James Carlson, age 46.
Paramedics found him unconscious.
Mechanisms of injury are unknown,
but he has a large sucking chest wound.
- And a wife with very healthy lungs.
- Vitals?
Tachycardic in the 140's,
BP holding in the 90's.
You were gone when I woke up.
- Oh, I had to do a thing.
- You didn't leave a note.
Yeah, well, I had this thing to do.
I did this thing.
- And once again...
- What?
We go to sleep,
I think everything is fine
and by the time I wake up,
you're just a little bit crazy.
- I get... I'm not crazy. I had a thing.
- OK.
- How's his respiratory effort?
- Absent breath sounds on the right.
Air bubbling at the wound.
He's shocky and a little cyanotic.
My wife was...
Let's get him intubated and place
an occlusive dressing over the wound.
- Now, you...
- Hannah. Hannah Davies.
Hannah. Why do you have your hand
inside my patient?
For the record, I told her not to.
I tried to tamponade the wound
with gauze and pressure,
but only my hand
would stop the bleeding.
Every time I move it
he starts bleeding out.
Can I take my hand out now?
You don't stick your hand in a patient
when you don't know how he was injured.
- Yeah, I know that now!
- Out of my room.
- She gets to stay?
- She has her hand inside my patient.
- Nice. Thanks.
- Well, don't get happy.
You have your finger on a bleeder
and Mr. Carlson is running out of time.
The only thing that you have won
is an all expense paid trip to the OR.
Dr. Grey,
prepare to transport her to the OR.
- Let's do this quickly.
- What do you want me to do?
I want you to make that woman stop
screaming and tell us what happened.
- I can't go to the OR?
- No, you have a thing to do.
- What was that about?
- If I'd known you'd get the good case,
I'd have let you stay in bed.
She's been going 20 minutes.
This must be some kind of record.
Look at her. She's not even turning red.
Good for her. Burke says shut her up.
We've got an incoming trauma.
MVC with a 30-minute extrication time.
Severe intrusion damage to the car.
Definite head injury. Stable vitals.
- Five minutes.
- I got it.
- I called first.
You said Burke told you to shut her up.
No, he told me
to tell you to shut her up.
Ma'am. Ma'am.
Mrs. Carlson... Are you injured?
I need you to try and calm down.
Mrs. Carlson? Can you hear me?
Can you hear me?
Good. OK. Now, can you tell me
exactly what happened to your husband?
- What are you doing?
- Chief. Bailey's in there.
Bailey's back?
- O'Malley!
- She's in labor.
Dr. Montgomery-Shepherd
is examining her cervix.
I can see that quite clearly.
O'Malley, stop looking!
Pretty amazing, right?
The miracle of life.
Our Bailey. Becoming a mother.
It feels good...
having Bailey back at the hospital.
Balance is being restored.
- That's all I'm saying, sir.
- Hey, guys.
Would you give this to Dr. Shepherd?
Thanks. What's going on?
- Bailey's in there.
- Oh, Bailey's back? That's excellent.
And her cervix
is being examined by my wife
which is a visual
I'll never get out of my head.
Thanks for the warning.
Well...
A gathering of men outside the delivery
room. How mid-century of you.
- Say hi to Bailey for me.
- Hm.
- How she doing?
- Taking it like a woman.
Six centimeters dilated,
50 per cent effaced,
and refusing pain meds, which I think
is stupid but I'm not in labor, so...
- What are you doing out here?
- Can I get you anything?
A boy the size of a ten-pound bowling
ball is working his way out of my body.
Can you get me a new vagina?
- Oh. Well...
- I didn't think so.
Look, I appreciate the concern,
but I'm fine. It's just childbirth.
All I need is my husband
who should have been here by now.
Write down his number.
I'll call him. I'll track him down.
All right. Then go away.
Give me some privacy.
I don't want to see any of you again
until after the baby is born,
which, if he does like I told him to
and stays on schedule,
should be in four-and-a-half hours.
I mean it.
- Bailey's back.
- She's back, sir.
- He's my patient. Get your own.
- I had one. Meredith took him.
- So now you're going to take mine?
- If I can.
- Is my wife here? Is she here?
- Was she in the accident with you?
- She's supposed to be...
- We'll find her, Mr. Jones.
- What have we got?
- Tucker Jones, 35. Flipped his car...
He's got a chest contusion and a head CT
shows a depressed skull fracture
and temporal epidural hematoma.
GCS 14 in the field, now down to 12.
His motor exams are intact.
- A gram of Dilantin and 70 of mannitol.
- I'm on it.
Mr. Jones,
I need to do an examination on you.
My phone.
It's my wife.
You need to answer. She needs me.
OK, we'll answer your phone.
Dr. Stevens, answer his phone.
- I've got it.
- Mr. Jones, squeeze my fingers.
Mr. Jones? Hey, I need you
to squeeze my finger, OK?
He's in a seizure.
Get him on his side. Watch his arm.
Hello? George? What are...
- It's me. Izzie.
- Let's get him to the OR.
No... I think I'd know if I had
Bailey's husband's phone, George!
Watch his arm, watch his arm.
- What's Bailey's husband's name?
- Watch the wall.
- How are you doing over there?
- My hand's getting numb.
And this whole
"insides are bloody and squishy" thing
is so not good for my gag reflex.
But I'm good.
Is this OK? Me being in here like this?
Once Dr. Burke scrubs in,
he'll have you remove your hand
and then you can go
and we'll fix Mr. Carlson.
Good. I know how much medicine I know
and it's just enough
to never be allowed in an OR.
It's my second week as a paramedic.
I got out of school about a month ago.
I haven't been doing this
that long either.
Talk about on-the-job training, huh?
- Dr. Burke.
- Dr. Shepherd.
You got Dr. Bailey's husband
on the table?
Bailey's husband is going into surgery?
Got into a car accident
trying to get to the hospital.
- What do we tell her?
- Nothing.
Wait until I see how bad the damage is.
Have something concrete to say.
Yeah, no use upsetting her
until we know.
- OK, keep me posted.
- OK.
- Hey, Preston.
- Good seeing you, Addison.
What?
She gets to call you by your first name?
- I like her.
- And you don't like me?
No.
- How are we doing?
- He's stabilized.
- I'm just about to put him under.
- Doctor?
You're... Shepherd, right?
- Yes. I am.
- I thought so.
Miranda... she really likes you.
I like her too.
We're having a baby.
I know. I'm gonna take care of you.
I'm going to get you back to Bailey,
safe and sound.
All this blood and none of it's hers?
No, she's fine. Acute anxiety reaction.
Give her two diazepam PO to calm her.
- She in shock?
- I'll say.
Can you tell us exactly what happened?
You mean the shock part?
It was shocking. I'm shocked.
You tell my husband when I get my hands
on him, he's a dead man.
- Do you hear me? Scaring me like this.
- Exactly how was your husband injured?
- Mindy? Mindy, you in here?
- I'm over here! You moron!
- How's James doing?
- Oh, he's bleeding all over the place.
The girl in the ambulance put her hand
inside him, that's how he's doing!
- What are you yelling at me for?
- Because!
You and James are idiots!
Playing like eight-year-olds.
We don't play. We reenact.
You play. You put on costumes, you build
your stupid toys and you play!
- We reenact.
- Nobody reenacts World War II!
- You moron!
- Exactly what happened?
What happened is my husband
and his moron best friend...
- Can you stop calling me a moron?
- Moron best friend
decided to build some kind of big gun.
Yeah, an exact replica of the finest
Allied antitank weapon of World War Il:
the M9A1 bazooka.
So they put on their stupid costumes
and they go out into the backyard
and they try to shoot the thing!
I'm the gunner. James is the loader.
We followed the specifications exactly.
It's a 60 millimeter,
1.5 pound rocket. It's a beauty.
It didn't work. So, like an idiot,
my husband has to go and stand in front
of his big gun to see what went wrong.
That's when the stupid toy
starts working.
- Stop calling it a toy.
- I'll call it whatever I want!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
He shot himself with a bazooka?
- Yeah.
- He shot himself with the bazooka?
- Like I said, morons, the pair of them!
- Was there an explosion?
- Huh?
No. Why?
Oh, crap.
What?
What is it?
Hey! Slow down.
If Bailey asks,
I'm not the one who did this.
OK. I'm going to do a thoracotomy and
Hannah is going to pull her hand out.
Dr. Grey is going to clamp the bleeder
when we have more exposure.
- Ready?
- More than ready.
Scalpel.
Tucker Jones...
you'd better be lying
in the street somewhere dead, mister,
because when I get my hands on you...
I am having your baby here, mister!
OK. On the count of three. One...
Two...
Dr. Burke?
I need to speak with you.
- I am in surgery, Karev.
- You want to talk to me, sir.
Unhook me.
If you interrupt me,
it better be for a...
- Was it through and through?
- What?
The wound. Was it through and through?
No. There's just an entry, no exit. Why?
He's cute. He single?
- Hannah.
- Yes, Dr. Burke?
What do you feel inside of Mr. Carlson?
What is your hand touching?
What do you mean?
Is your hand touching anything hard?
- Hard?
- Like metal.
Um... I don't know.
Don't move your hand.
Just tell me what you feel.
Dr. Burke, what's going on?
Hannah?
Um, my fingertips are touching
something... kinda hard.
Yeah, definitely.
- Oh, my God.
- Dr. Milton.
What? What's wrong?
Hannah, I don't want you to move.
Not your hand.
Not your body. Not an inch.
OK. You should know
you're starting to scare me.
Don't be scared.
Everything's going to be fine.
Dr. Grey, can you...
I want you to walk out of this room.
Walk, do not run.
Go and tell the charge nurse
that we have a Code Black.
I'm sorry. Code Black?
Code Black. Tell him that I am sure.
And then tell him
to call the bomb squad.
What did she stick
her hand in there for anyway?
- She was trying to save his life.
- And now she might die because of it.
What do we do now?
I go back in and wait for the bomb
squad. You leave. You all leave.
Mer, you coming?
It's your funeral.
You need a surgical team.
All I need is Dr. Milton to keep him
under. I can do the rest myself.
Fine. But you wait by the elevator.
I don't want anyone in here
that doesn't need to be in this OR.
When the bomb squad arrives,
we'll take it from there.
Until then, Milton and I
are doing this alone. Now, go.
OK, OK, OK.
Ah!
Eight minutes apart.
There is no shame in an epidural,
Miranda.
Epidural increases
the possibility of a C-section.
It also decreases pain.
Miranda, this is a big baby,
it is your first baby
and it is not going to be
a short or an easy labor.
I can handle a little pain. No problem.
Women all over the world do this at home
with nothing more than a pair
of scissors and a bucket of hot water.
Women all over the world also die
giving birth at home every day.
I did not just say that.
You're supposed
to be finding my husband.
- Well, I...
- He's not here.
He should be here by now.
OK, we're gonna go find him.
Right, Dr. O'Malley?
Right. I'm...
What?
Oh, nothing. I'll be right back.
Yang, could you check that?
- How's he doing?
- Oh, it's touch and go.
I'm just trying
to find the source of the bleeding.
Go and find Addison. Tell her
he's in worse shape than I thought.
- What'd they want?
- They want us to evacuate.
- Evacuate? Did they say why?
- Your pager said, "Code Black".
- You're sure they said that?
- Yes.
It could be a drill.
I can't evacuate.
I've got an open brain on the table.
I'm not leaving Bailey's husband
with his skull flap open
so if anybody wants to go,
they should go.
Anybody want to evacuate?
Going once, going twice, three times.
- You're sure they said, "Code Black"?
- Yes.
I don't like
having to lie to Dr. Bailey.
- Now is not the time, Dr. O'Malley.
- She'd want to know...
She'd want to know about her husband.
- Code Black? What's a Code Black?
- Wait, hold it! Whoa!
Dr. Shepherd wanted me to tell you
that Tucker's bleed is more extensive
than he thought.
It will be a few hours
before he has anything concrete.
Thanks, Stevens.
- What's a Code Black?
- A what?
Code Black?
Code Red, Blue, White...
I've never had a Black.
Dr. Shepherd?
Just go to your locker room and wait for
your resident to give you instructions.
- We have no resident.
- What's goin' on?
Is it something bad?
Yeah. It's something bad.
So...
So I'm touching
live unexploded ammunition?
I'm afraid so.
Not the greatest feeling in the world.
No. I guess not.
- And... he's still out?
- Yeah.
But he's not hooked up to the machine.
I had Dr. Milton
take him off the ventilator.
The flow of oxygen posed a danger.
The Ambu bag is breathing for him now.
But he can't hear me?
No.
Hannah?
What if I just take my hand out
really quickly?
We'd have to ask the bomb squad that
when they arrive.
But I'm guessing that would
cause the ammo to shift and explode.
Oh.
- Hannah?
- Yeah?
Your hand is keeping Mr. Carlson
from bleeding out.
You are keeping him alive.
Right. And the bomb squad is coming?
The bomb squad is coming.
OK.
We're moving
pre-op patients to Mercy West,
all trauma rerouted
to Seattle Presbyterian.
There is no danger
to the north, south and west wings.
Just the east surgical wing.
That said, anyone
who wants to leave can leave.
No one stays unless
they volunteer to stay. Understood?
OK.
- Richard. Is it Code Black? Really?
- Yes. I shut down the ORs.
- What? To trauma?
- To everything.
To "everything" everything?
Ten minutes ago, all operating rooms
at Seattle Grace were evacuated,
with the exception of Dr. Burke's team.
And Dr. Shepherd's team.
What?
What do you mean Dr. Shepherd's team?
They're still in OR Two.
- Bomb squad just arrived.
- Excuse me.
- You're the surgical team?
- Yes.
Dylan Young, bomb squad. Check
the area, then we'll secure the patient.
- Where are they?
- In there.
- This floor's been evacuated?
- Yes.
You stay here.
Nobody moves unless I say so.
We got people over here!
- You said the floor had been evacuated.
- I thought it had.
Cristina! No, she will hurt him.
- What's going on?
- A bomb in a body cavity.
Man. All I got
is Bailey's husband's open brain.
- What procedure?
- Craniotomy.
Shepherd's got Bailey's husband
on the table?
Excuse me? Excuse me! Stop talking!
Got to eat something.
You knew Meredith and Cristina
would be on the floor with the bomb.
- Yeah.
- Is it wrong that we're jealous?
The fact that we're jealous
that they might die
is not a reflection on our character.
- It's about feeling useless.
- Ineffectual.
We couldn't even
get Meredith out of bed.
We had to call in Cristina.
How embarrassing is that?
You know what I think, George?
I think Meredith and Cristina are doers.
They do. They're doers.
They do. And we...
We watch.
We're watchers.
Check on Mrs. Carlson's levels.
If they're stable she can come up here.
All right. Excuse me.
We have to become more proactive,
George. We have to become doers.
Fight for what we want.
- We have to do.
- Yeah.
Oh. You mean...
We are starting right now! OK.
Alex.
How crazy is this?
Dude, it's like the apocalypse.
- Alex...
- It's true. Look around you.
Half the people supposed
to be saving lives have fled.
Bailey's husband almost died
coming to see his kid get born.
The annoying twins are with a guy
who might explode in their faces.
It's a morgue. People should
get while the getting's good.
- There might be no tomorrow...
- Alex!
What?
- Take off your pants.
- What are you doing?
Being a doer. Getting while the
getting's good. Take off your pants.
I meant apocalypse metaphorically,
not literally.
Alex...
I haven't had sex
in eight months and twelve days.
I'm horny, half-naked and saying yes.
You wanna talk metaphors
or do you wanna take off your pants?
Sponge.
Dr. Shepherd,
there's an explosive device next door.
- I need you to evacuate now.
- I've got a guy whose brain is exposed.
I'm not going to leave him to die.
The rest of you can go.
You should go. Suction.
You close him up.
You do whatever you have to do.
The chief of surgery has authorized
me to tell you you cannot stay.
The chief of surgery doesn't scare me.
Dr. Bailey scares me.
I'm not going to be the one
to let her husband die.
And that's what would happen if I
put his skull flap on in this condition.
Bomb or no bomb. Now, get out of my OR.
Suction.
Trying to get gravity to do me a favor.
I'm nine centimeters dilated.
I need that last centimeter.
Good. That's uh... That's good.
Dr. Shepherd?
Where... exactly... is my husband?
He's with my husband.
Oh.
There is no telling how dangerous it is.
We need more info.
The longer we wait, the greater
the chance he'll bleed out and die.
Pink mist.
Excuse me?
That's what the bomb squad calls you
when you blow up.
Pink mist. I read that somewhere.
Bomb goes off and... anyone in range
explodes into a billion pieces.
You're liquid. There's nothing left.
Just flecks of human flesh and blood.
Pink mist.
Sometimes they don't even find a finger.
One minute, you're a person...
the next, you're... bloody rain.
Here. Take this.
- What?
- Go ahead.
Now I want you to squeeze it
in even beats.
OK, no, not too fast. Not too fast.
There you go.
Dr. Milton?
I've got kids.
Even beats.
OK?
That's it.
What about my husband?
How long can he stay like that?
With live ammo inside him?
- I honestly don't know.
- But you're gonna try to save him?
We're gonna try. The bomb squad has
to determine how to retrieve the device.
I'm sorry, Mindy. I'm so sorry.
Shut up! We've got three kids
and you've got him building bazookas?
Oh, God...
He's gonna die.
Paul, why don't you go
with the officer there
and answer his questions
about the device?
- Anything to help.
- Oh, Karev...
Why don't we get Mrs. Carlson
a cup of coffee?
I guess I should look
on the bright side.
It's not like this can get any worse.
I mean, this is it.
This is as bad as it gets. Right?
Dr. Bailey? Uh, I was...
Someone find me my suitcase.
I need my suitcase. I'm going home.
Dr. Bailey, you're having a baby.
There's not going to be any baby born
today! You hear me? I'm holding it in!
I'll have him tomorrow.
Just not now. Not like this. No!
Just... no.
I'm going home.
I'm going home right now!
I can't...
I can't do this without my husband.
I can't do this alone.
OK, OK, OK.
So how are they going to remove that
ammo without killing Hannah and James?
Cristina! The bomb squad guys said you
were supposed to stay away from there.
Is it me or is Hannah shaking?
- Is she squeezing that Ambu bag?
- Where is Dr. Milton?
Hannah?
- Where's the anesthesiologist?
- He, um...
He left.
He didn't want to die.
Hannah?
I think I'm gonna take my hand out now.
When the hell are people gonna learn?
- It may not be as bad as it seems.
- Her hand is holding the device steady.
Or maybe her hand is simply in there
with the ammo. We can't know.
My guys talked to the friend.
That device is homemade which means
it's unstable and unreliable.
It could be a dud
but we have no way of knowing.
Add that you've got a surgeon
next door refusing to leave
and a nervous paramedic's hand
inside the body cavity.
It's... definitely as bad as it seems.
That's what I'm saying.
Hey, somebody help!
Help here!
- I'm just going to take it out now. OK?
- You can do this.
No, no. No, I just want to take it out
and be done with it.
Hannah. It won't be much longer.
- You're keeping him from bleeding out.
- No.
I am 22 years old. I should not even be
in here. This is some kind of mistake.
- We need to clear the room.
- I'm not leaving.
- Grey.
- I'm not leaving her.
- Get everyone out now.
- She's my intern.
- I am responsible for her.
- No, it has to come out.
- Yang, go with Dylan.
- You go with Dylan.
- Hannah, look at me.
- No, it's got to come out. No, no.
Hannah, look at me. You can do this.
Hannah, calm down. You need
to relax and everything's gonna be fine.
- No!
- Hannah.
- You can do this, Hannah.
- It has to come out!
No, will you keep it there
just a little while longer? Hanna...
I have to!
Meredith.
What did I do? Oh, God.
Just stay where you are.
Nobody move. Stay exactly where you are.
Meredith?
What did I do? What did I do? What
did I do? What did I do? What did I do?
What did I do?
What did I do? What did I do?
www.tvsubtitles.net